- Coiling Dragon -
(Previously on)
That's a Velocidrake's tail.
Will Beibei be okay?
Beibei!
Linley!
You must have angered them
by taking the Blueheart Grass.
So when would be
the right time to come back for it?
Wait until you become a rank-seven mage.
It won't be too late
to come back for it then.
Episode 11
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
I wonder how Father will react when he
sees all these magic crystal cores.
You're giving them all to the family?
Mm.
Father has to manage
the family and Wushan Town.
He also has to pay
for Wharton's schooling.
Money is needed everywhere.
Then what about my big pork leg?
Don't worry.
You'll still have plenty of pork legs.
These are worth at least seventy
or eighty thousand gold coins.
He'll be overjoyed.
(This area should only
have low-level magical beasts.)
(Why is the fighting so intense?)
Are you alright?
My friend, please wait a moment.
My name is Kalan.
The Debs family's eldest son.
Thank you for what you did just now.
May I ask your name?
Linley.
Since you're heading back as well,
could you take us out of here with you?
Alice!
Please wait.
Mr. Mage,
please.
Help us.
Mm.
Follow me.
Linley,
I'll keep practicing
the Earth Spike techniques
you taught me.
Keep it up.
You're amazing.
Everyone says you're the top genius
at Welling Magic Academy.
It seems Welling
really is far behind Ernst.
We're the same age,
and I only just reached rank-four.
You're already a rank-five mage.
Don't you think those two
make quite a good match?
Don't be ridiculous.
That smells wonderful.
Linley,
come take a look.
What kind of flower is this?
It has the same name as me.
It's called Alice too.
I can't believe
I didn't notice it on the way here.
There's such a vast sea of flowers.
When you're with different people,
you notice different things.
Second Grandpa,
why did you come out in person?
Young man,
thank you for helping us this time.
These one hundred gold coins
may not be much,
but they're a small token
of appreciation from the Debs family.
I hope you'll accept them.
The Debs family certainly is generous.
Make way!
Isn't that Alice's father?
No wonder they're one of the most
prominent families in Fenlai City.
Just handing out
a hundred gold coins like that.
It was nothing.
Please don't think anything of it.
I'll take my leave.
That's a fine carriage.
If Alice could marry into that family,
she'd be truly fortunate.
Father,
let's go home.
Kalan, we're leaving now.
Alright.
Then I'll have my steward see you home.
That's wonderful.
Kalan,
come inside with me.
Yes,
Second Grandpa.
I'm telling you,
stay away from people like that.
You're the future mistress
of the Debs family.
You and him are destined
for completely different worlds.
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.com)
Grandpa Delin,
I feel this world
is a little complicated.
I used to think that
in the Magical Beast Mountain Range,
natural selection
and survival
of the strong are too cruel.
But after this trial,
I've come to realize
that although Fenlai City
appears peaceful and prosperous,
it cannot hide the hypocrisy
and indifference behind status and rank.
The divisions between people,
the hierarchy of society
- Come on, let's go home.
- make the Magical Beast Mountain Range
- Mm.
- seem far less cruel.
Watch your step.
If you don't work hard,
you'll be left behind.
Are you afraid of competition?
I'm not afraid of anything.
My goal is to restore
the Baruch family to its former glory
and become strong.
No challenge is too great for me.
Delia.
Linley?
It really is you.
You're finally back.
How did the trial go?
Mm.
It went fairly well.
Congratulations.
On completing the trial.
I'm leaving now.
This is a letter
from the Proulx Gallery.
Linley,
you're getting your own gallery!
Come on.
Here's to none of us failing our finals.
Cheers!
Time to head home for the break!
Linley!
Aren't you at the Ernst Institute?
What brings you to Fenlai City?
The break just started,
so I came to deliver some new sculptures
to the Proulx Gallery.
You make sculptures too?
Mm.
I should get going.
My family is waiting for me.
Linley,
you...
Will you
come back again?
Mm.
Alice.
Alice!
Linley,
with you around,
I feel especially safe.
Alice!
Father, I'm here.
Lord Hogg!
Look who's back!
Father,
I'm back.
Linley?
My boy,
you're as tall as I am now.
Father,
look.
This is
magic crystal core?
Mm.
It should sell
for eighty thousand gold coins.
You went to
the Magical Beast Mountain Range?
Were you hurt?
Take off your shirt.
Father...
Take it off.
Linley...
What have you been through?
You...
Go get some rest.
Lord Hogg,
you've been investigating this
for thirteen years.
Are you still going to continue?
Back then,
Wharton had only just been born.
Run!
Lina!
My Lord.
That was all in the past.
Young Master Linley and Young Master Wharton
are both doing so well now.
They are the future
of the Baruch family.
You should look ahead.
Look ahead?
Can I really look ahead?
♪Dragon scales freeze
beneath the moonlight♪
♪Melting into falling rain♪
♪After you turn away,
the night wind falls still♪
♪Our fate♪
♪Those sealed vows♪
♪Shatter at this very moment♪
♪Through countless freezing seasons,
through endless nights♪
♪Push aside the clouds,
and the light appears♪
♪Only through destruction
do I understand♪
♪This well-meant lie♪
♪I think I can♪
♪Throw everything aside♪
♪Until the day♪
♪I can appear in your world♪
(Next Episode Preview)
This is your first time seeing
Lord Hogg in action, isn't it?
In fact, he's a rank-six warrior
just like me.
Is this all you've learned at Ernst?
Our ancestor Baruch
wielded a battleblade.
The battleblade, Slaughter.
Could this be...
This is only a replica forged
by later generations.
Then where is the real Slaughter?
Today is the Yulan Festival.
It's also our first official date.
Of course I have to make it special.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™