- Ascendants of the Nine Suns -
[Animation adapted from "Ascendants of the Nine Suns"]
[Wo Chi Mianbao/Seven-Cat Novel]
Episode 1
[The Heavenly Emperor Rebirth]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Ye Yunfei, Heavenly Emperor Realm]
I've practised martial arts
for 1,000 years
and experienced many changes
that occurred in the world.
I'm finally
Hongmeng Realm's sole Heavenly Emperor
to face the Godhood Tribulation.
Once I transcend the tribulation
and attain godhood,
none in the Three Thousand Great Realms
shall stand against me.
Break!
Is this the so-called Godhood Tribulation?
Bring it on!
The key doctrines
of the Nine Suns Scripture:
chaos reincarnation,
the reversal of Yin and Yang!
Now is the time!
How dare you!
Kill you
when you're weak.
Kill!
[You Yue, Tian Luo, and Jin Wu,
Heavenly Emperor Realm]
Heavenly Emperor Ye.
You didn't see that coming, did you?
This is how it ends for you.
Tian Luo.
Jin Wu.
You Yue.
It's you guys.
The world's spiritual energy
has its limit;
the divine seats of the Great Dao
are numbered.
If you successfully transcend
the tribulation,
the odds of the 3 of us
attaining godhood will be slim.
So,
you must die.
Even if I fail,
you think you can kill me?
Ridiculous.
Don't forget
that I'm the Nine Suns Martial God,
Ye Yunfei!
This is bad!
He's going to take us down with him!
Yunfei!
Ye Yunfei.
Young Master Yunfei...
Yunfei.
Yunfei!
Turns out my life
is full of regrets.
What happened?
Ye Yunfei.
-Didn't I die?
-You know your place.
-Why did I get kicked?
-Just crawl under me,
and I promise
I'll only break one of your legs.
[Qin Feng, Level 3 of Body Refinement]
Has Ye Yunfei, the loser,
gotten scared to death?
Maybe.
Qin Feng?
Didn't you die long ago?
You loser!
How dare you curse me to die early!
Let Yunfei go!
Zhou Mu is still alive.
Could it be...
This is...
My martial meridian is still intact.
I've returned
from the dead!
Looks like heaven is still on my side.
I've got a chance to start my life over.
In that case,
nine meridians,
open up!
No.
I won't allow you
[Zhou Mu, Level 1 of Body Refinement]
to hurt Yunfei.
Since you want to die for that loser,
I'll grant your wish then!
What's going on?
How is that possible?
You...
[Ye Yunfei, Level 3 of Body Refinement]
How dare you hurt my people?
That's right.
I, the Heavenly Emperor,
have been reborn.
If you ask how it feels to be reborn,
of course...
It's awesome!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
I'm late.
Zhou Mu,
no one dares to bully you
in the Yuanyue Academy anymore.
Yunfei.
Could it be
that you've got
your martial meridian back?
How is that possible?
The loser hit Qin Feng?
How did this even happen?
Ye Yunfei!
How dare you hurt one of the Qin Clan?
You're dead!
You're a loser who has completely lost
your martial meridian.
You're simply
not worthy of me now.
[Shi Xiaodie, Level 6 of Body Refinement]
Shi Xiaodie.
Usually, for this type of
rebirth-counterattack-slap scripts,
after the slap in the face,
the next plot is...
Fine.
As I expected,
it really moves to
the engagement break-off part.
Shi Xiaodie.
You want to break off the engagement?
Yes.
I thought you were a genius,
so I agreed to marry into the Ye Clan.
But who would've known
you'd become a loser
without your martial meridian overnight?
Look how pathetic you've become.
Do you think you deserve me?
So?
So I'll give you a chance
to admit that you're too good-for-nothing
to be worthy of me
and agree to break off the engagement.
Otherwise—
Otherwise,
you'll have your adulterer Qin An
to break my leg,
right?
Ye Yunfei,
how dare you speak to me like that?
Do it!
Impossible!
With your martial meridian lost,
your cultivation should've been ruined!
Sorry to disappoint you.
My dear Qin An,
I love you the most.
Shameless.
Shut up!
You...
Shut up, all of you!
Ye Yunfei!
You...
You loser!
How dare you
humiliate me like this?
Shi Xiaodie,
you've behaved immorally,
committed adultery with Qin An,
and disgraced your clan.
You're a disgrace to the Ye Clan.
I'll cancel our engagement in writing.
From now on,
we have nothing to do with each other.
[Engagement Termination Letter]
[Terminated]
You...
How dare you repudiate me!
What gives you the right to do that?
Ye Yunfei,
who do you think you are?
How dare you repudiate me in public!
I'll kill you!
Oh no.
My soul power has suddenly disappeared.
I'll have to resort to other means.
A loser is useless indeed!
Die!
You loser, stop!
Qingluo.
Su Qingluo!
If you dare to hurt me,
my father won't let you go!
Fine.
I'll wait for you.
Don't let me hear you
criticize Yunfei again.
[Su Qingluo, Level 6 of Body Refinement]
Otherwise, I will surely
kill you myself.
Let's go.
Wait and see!
The Qin and Shi Clans
won't let you get away!
What happened?
Does he wish to die?
He's dead for sure.
If anyone in the Yuanyue Academy
dares to bully Zhou Mu again,
you'll end up
just like Qin Feng.
Qingluo.
Are you
okay?
Yunfei.
Are you willing to stay
for me?
You're a daughter of the Su Clan.
I don't deserve you.
Besides, my martial meridian
has been ruined,
and I haven't avenged my clan.
I'm sorry,
Qingluo.
It's so great
to see you again.
I'll never miss you again in this life.
Yunfei,
why did you suddenly say that?
I was so foolish before.
I never noticed
how deeply you feel for me.
Don't talk nonsense.
I...
Yunfei, Yunfei.
Are you alright?
I...
You've been acting
like some old man all along.
Has the hit made you lose your mind?
Yunfei.
This is the White Jade Pure Lotus Elixir
made by my clan.
Find a place to heal.
I'll find some wound-healing elixirs
for you.
It's all over. It's all over.
The Shi and Qin Clans won't let it go.
Yunfei,
hurry.
You've just got
your martial meridian back.
You're still too weak.
You'd better go out and hide.
I'll stall them for you.
At worst,
they'll break my arms and legs.
I can recover soon
with my strong constitution.
The Qin Clan and the Shi Clan.
If they hadn't slaughtered my Ye Clan,
I wouldn't have harbored hatred for them.
But you're right.
I'm still too weak.
To deal with the next crisis,
I have to confirm my strength first.
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
It's never too late
to seek revenge.
Now that the Heavenly Emperor
has been reborn,
he will surely rub their noses in it.
The Ye Clan's enemies
and Jin Wu, Tian Luo, and You Yue.
Die...
Yunfei!
I forgot I can't fly!
[Shi's Mansion]
Father!
You must stick up for me!
How dare Ye Yunfei, such a loser,
write an engagement termination letter
in public?
He is clearly provoking our Shi Clan!
Father,
I've been humiliated completely!
I want him dead!
Xiaodie,
don't worry.
Even though he's regained his strength,
he's still a loser
at Level 3 of Body Refinement.
Besides,
our Shi Clan isn't the only one
who wants Ye Yunfei dead.
Father.
You mean...
The Qin Clan?
[Shi Tianyuan, Mid-Stage Earth Realm]
No.
The one who wants Ye Yunfei dead the most
is the Ye Clan.
♪ Who in life has never had to poop ♪
♪ No one poops without toilet paper ♪
♪ If you go without it ♪
Luckily, only Zhou Mu saw it.
Otherwise, I would be so embarrassed
that it'd haunt me into my next life.
I never thought I'd actually be reborn.
Could it be
because of the Nine Suns Scripture?
As expected, the Nine Suns Scripture
and Heavenly Emperor's soul power remain.
It's just that I'm only
at Level 3 of Body Refinement.
Seems that for my rebirth,
I'm playing an anti-cliché script.
The Heavenly Emperor's full soul power
actually remains.
But this physical body is too weak.
It's hard to control and use the power.
Looks like I have to go to other realms
to find a way to control my soul power.
If I force it,
I don't know...
Nine suns illuminate the heavens.
Perfect rotation follows desire!
Why do I feel
a chilly tingle on my butt?
Someone blew up the poop!
Senior Young Master is back!
[Next Episode Preview]
I never thought
I could come back home.
As long as I ruin you,
the heir of the Ye Clan
will be my brother!
This little beast has not only
regained his cultivation
but also obtained
such a strange technique.
I must get rid of him today!
In 3 days, my elder will surely
get rid of Ye Tianpeng
and become the master of the clan.
Beauty's Blade?
Does that mean
she's good at blade technique?
It's not like what you think—
lust
is a dangerous blade.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™