- Ascendants of the Nine Suns -
[Animation adapted from "Ascendants of the Nine Suns"]
Episode 2
[Chuchu's Charm]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Ye's Mansion]
[Shi Clan's Master, Shi Tianyuan]
I never thought
Where do you think you're running?
I'd be able to return home.
I'll stop them.
Go!
Father!
I'm not leaving.
I will never let the regrets
of my previous life
happen again.
Senior Young Master has returned!
Ye Qiang?
Ye Yunfei,
[Ye Qiang-Level 5 of Body Refinement]
your crimes are unforgivable!
Surrender now!
What crime have I committed,
that I should surrender to you?
How dare you abolish Qin Feng
and divorce Shi Xiaodie!
I'll teach you a lesson
on behalf of the Ye Clan!
Teach me?
Every strike of yours is lethal,
and you call that a lesson?
You idiot!
Aren't you only at Level 3 of Body Refinement?
[Level 3 of Body Refinement]
An illusion…
It must be an illusion.
As long as I cripple you,
the position of the Ye Clan's heir
will belong to my elder brother!
Ultimate move!
Buddha Kick!
Go to die!
Your ultimate move sure stinks,
but your aim is absolutely terrible.
Who is making trouble here?
[Ye Zhongnian, Early-Stage Earth Realm]
Father.
You loser!
How dare you hurt your people!
It's you!
Go!
You old thief!
What did you say?
Showing no respect to your elders
only adds to your mistakes.
The gap between
the early Earth Realm stages is too vast.
However...
it seems you really have recovered.
All the more reason I can't let you live.
Cloud-line Palm.
I can't overpower him head-on,
so I'll have to rely on speed to win.
This is it—
Windstride Divine Steps!
Old thief,
let me collect a little payback first.
Where did you learn this skill?
Ye Yunfei!
Don't look at me.
It's clearly your own backside
that lacks eyes—
you insisted on taking a seat
that wasn't meant for you.
This little brat not only
recovered his cultivation,
he even obtained
such a bizarre movement skill.
I must get rid of him today!
I can't escape.
Kneel down!
Old thief,
I will take back
what you owe me.
I'll fight you to the death!
Who dares to bully my son?
Ye Zhongnian,
you've got some nerve—
raising your hand against my boy.
[Ye Tianpeng, Mid-Stage Earth Realm]
Do you take me, the master of this family,
for nothing?
[Ye Tianpeng, Mid-Stage Earth Realm]
Father.
Ye Tianpeng,
even if you're the master of the family,
you can't be biased
for your own selfishness
and harm the whole Ye Clan!
Then what do you suggest
my son should do?
He should naturally cripple himself,
sever his hands and feet,
and apologize to Qin...
How despicable!
Ye Tianpeng,
let's see how long
you can protect your useless son.
Get lost!
Go!
Are you alright, Yunfei?
Are you hurt?
Father.
Father!
It's great
to see you again.
Well...
Yunfei,
men shouldn't have that kind of contact.
Father.
Father!
Young Master!
Young Master, you're back!
You came home so early today!
Yue, let go!
[Yue]
Let go!
Young Master!
[Yue]
Let go!
-Men and women shouldn't
have that kind of contact either.
-That's great.
How inappropriate!
All right.
Yue is still so energetic.
Yunfei,
[Second Elder of the Ye Clan]
is it true what Zhou Mu said
that your martial meridian has recovered?
[Second Elder of the Ye Clan]
What?
Yunfei,
your martial meridian…
Yes,
Second Grandpa,
Father,
my martial meridian has fully recovered.
No one dares to call me useless again.
You're indeed my good son.
Great!
[Ye Fan, Ye Xue]
Brother Yunfei,
you can teach me cultivation again.
[Ye Fan, Ye Xue]
Congratulations.
I'm back.
[Ye Clan's Council Hall]
What?
You mean
Ye Zhongnian colluded with
the Qin Clan and Shi Clan?
Yes, Father.
I've collected some evidence.
Ever since your martial meridian
was completely destroyed,
I knew
he had been eyeing
the position of family master.
But to actually collude with
the Qin Clan and Shi Clan…
he's practically playing with fire!
In Yuanyue City, the four great clans
—the Qin, Shi, Ye, and Lyu—
have been at odds for years.
Each wants to swallow the others.
For Ye Zhongnian to
openly move against me,
there must be elders in the family
backing him.
Father, you must be extremely careful
at the clan meeting three days from now.
I've been master of the clan
for so many years,
and it's not as if I've done nothing.
Yunfei,
how did your martial meridian
suddenly recover?
Well...
If it's something you don't wish to say,
then don't.
It's good that you can recover.
Father.
At the Clan Competition
three days from now,
Ye Zhongnian will definitely have his son,
Ye Lei, make a move against you.
Ye Lei
must have already broken through to
the Level 8 of Body Refinement.
Yunfei.
You...
Father,
don't worry.
I will win the Clan Competition
three days from now.
Father,
your cultivation has been stuck
at Mid-Stage Earth Realm
for almost seven years now, right?
With the aid of
a Grade 3 Profound Essence Pill,
you could break through to
the Late-Stage Earth Realm.
That may be true,
but a Grade 3 Profound Essence Pill costs
tens of thousands of gold.
Our clan is now…
Forget it.
Don't worry
about me.
Isn't it just a
Grade 3 Profound Essence Pill?
Father,
which is the biggest herbal medicine
merchant in Yuanyue City?
Herbal merchant?
That would naturally be Lingzhen Workshop.
But although they have many
rare treasures,
they're extremely shrewd in business.
The chief of the workshop
has a mysterious background
and is rumored to be
the "Beauty's Blade"—
very difficult to deal with.
Beauty's Blade?
Does it mean she's good at
blade technique?
Not exactly.
This isn't just any blade—
[Lingzhen Workshop]
but
the "Beauty" blade, if you catch my meaning.
[Lingzhen Workshop]
Sir,
what would you like to buy?
I want to sell a pill recipe.
A pill recipe?
Please
have it evaluated by Alchemist Lyu
at the counter first.
This way, please.
I want to sell a pill recipe.
You evaluate it
and give me a price.
[Alchemist Lyu]
This is...
How is that possible?
Nonsense.
Aren't you that useless brat
from the Ye Clan?
This isn't a pill recipe—
this is poison!
Guards!
Take him down!
Since when did the Lyu family
take charge of Lingzhen Workshop?
That's right.
I'm in charge here.
I'm targeting you.
What can you do?
You're doomed.
Ye Yunfei,
you've completely offended
Lingzhen Workshop this time!
You, an esteemed alchemist
of Lingzhen Workshop,
can't even recognize
a low‑grade pill recipe?
It looks like Lingzhen Workshop is nothing
but an empty name.
Stop!
What's going on?
Why are they fighting?
Isn't this the useless from the Ye Clan?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
How dare someone question the reputation
of Lingzhen Workshop!
So beautiful.
[Xiao Chuchu, Chief of Lingzhen Workshop]
Chief,
he…
Since when did it
become your turn
to give orders at Lingzhen Workshop?
This Beauty's Blade
looks difficult to deal with.
She has internal injuries.
That's easy to deal with.
I'm really sorry.
I have some trouble to deal with.
Everyone,
please go back.
Why is she suddenly kicking us out?
Yes, how can she do business like this?
You must be the chief
of Lingzhen Workshop, right?
Sure enough, a venomous beauty
with a "Bone-Cutting Blade"—
every strike could take a life!
You sure have a sweet tongue.
But don't flatter me just yet.
The total damage
comes to 3,321 taels, 5 mace, 9 fen.
Cash or on credit?
I don't have money.
So you're here to make trouble?
You're so naughty.
Then I need to
teach you a lesson.
Where are you going?
Don't be shy.
Qihai acupoint is swollen,
the Danzhong acupoint icy cold,
and the limbs weak and powerless…
Naughty.
My apologies.
[Master Huang, Early-Stage Celestial Realm]
Miss!
Stop!
My energy and blood are much smoother.
Who are you?
I am someone who can cure your ailments
and even help you break through to
the Late-Stage Earth Realm.
[Forced to Abdicate]
Whether you believe me or not,
it's up to you.
[Forced to Abdicate]
Mr. Ye,
please come to the tea room for a chat.
Ye Mansion
should be this way.
I think I've been here before.
It must be this way.
Ye Yunfei and his son
won't be arrogant for long.
Please report to the master
of the Qin Clan:
three days from now, our elder
will eliminate Ye Tianpeng
[Ye Fu]
and take the position of family master.
[Lingzhen Workshop-Tea Room]
This is Snow Peak Green Tip—
truly excellent tea.
This tea is a specialty of the Qin Empire.
I never expected a young man like you
to recognize it.
Alright, Young Master Ye.
Let's talk about our cooperation.
Can you really cure my illness?
Of course.
But you must think clearly—
the consequences of
deceiving Lingzhen Workshop
are not something a mere
Ye Clan from Yuanyue City
can bear.
Senior,
I have here a pill recipe.
Take a look.
Wonderful.
Wonderful!
The combination of primary
and secondary ingredients
is unconventional,
yet their effects harmonize perfectly.
This kind of spiritual pill
can solidify a warrior's foundation.
It's absolutely a rare treasure.
Moreover,
this Minor Liuyi Pill
can cleanse all residual pill
toxins from a warrior's body,
allowing them to use pills
to aid their cultivation without worry.
What?
A peerless pill.
Truly a peerless pill.
This will undoubtedly
expand the market reach of
Lingzhen Workshop even further.
What are your conditions?
Chief Xiao, you are
indeed straightforward.
It's simple.
I wish to collaborate with
your Lingzhen Workshop
to develop this pill recipe,
with a fifty-fifty split of the profits.
You're willing to do that?
The pill recipe is yours.
This arrangement
would be a great benefit
to our Lingzhen Workshop!
Young Master Ye,
from now on, you can
collect your Minor Liuyi Pill
profit share monthly at Lingzhen Workshop,
or I can deliver the funds
to you each month.
Okay.
Please send it to the Ye Clan
and leave it to my father.
But
I want to request an advance on a portion
of the funds now.
This contains 10,000 spirit crystals
and the Lingzhen Workshop
Supreme VIP token.
As for this spatial ring,
it is my personal gift to you.
Spatial ring?
Chief Xiao, you are truly generous.
Since our collaboration is settled,
I won't bother you.
Wait.
Young Master Ye,
did you forget something?
Sixteen Yin Spirit Fruits,
thirty Heavenly River Grasses,
and two Three Demon Divine Woods—
please deliver these along with the other
ingredients listed in the pill recipe.
I will treat you
in three days.
What's the condition?
It's a gift.
Three days later?
This young master of the Ye Clan
is quite intriguing.
Qingluo.
Qingluo,
why are you here?
I...
By the way, Yunfei,
I heard someone plotted to harm you.
It seems certain elders of the Ye Clan
are colluding with the Qin Clan.
Don't worry.
I've already made some preparations.
Yunfei,
I can help you.
I don't want you to get involved.
I can handle them.
I almost forgot
I actually
came to deliver the
Purple Gold Ginseng Pill.
It will benefit you
now that your martial meridian
has just recovered.
She always cares about me,
yet in my past life, I let her slip away.
Yunfei.
Let go!
Madam Rong!
Miss Qing,
[Madam Rong]
he...
I'm telling you one last time—
stop right now.
The old lady beside Qingluo
is actually this powerful.
Yunfei,
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
Qingluo,
I need to prepare
for the Clan Competition.
I can't see you for a few days.
Wait for me.
Okay.
I...
I'll wait for you.
The Clan Competition is about to begin.
I want to show my real skills
to replenish Young Master.
Carp,
turtle,
pig brain,
ox penis—
they all look delicious.
I also need earth dragon
to stimulate lactation...
Wait, isn't earth dragon
just earthworms?
I'll dig some in the yard.
Today's arena battle will determine
the new heir of the Ye Clan.
The one who wins the arena battle
shall become the
Senior Young Master of the Ye Clan.
Senior Young Master!
Yue has been taken to the Execution Hall
by Steward Ye!
Do you want to break
the ancestral rules of the Ye Clan?
The Ye Clan
will soon belong to the Second Master!
Ye Yunfei,
come out!
I'll wait here.
Here's the sword!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™