- Ascendants of the Nine Suns -
[Animation adapted from "Ascendants of the Nine Suns"]
[Wo Chi Mianbao/Seven-Cat Novel]
Episode 3
[Clan Competition]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
This time, I'll show what I'm capable of!
Go for it!
It's a feast for our eyes!
[Ye Tianpeng, Master of the Ye Clan]
In last time's competition,
[Grand Elder, Third Elder, and Fifth Elder of the Ye Clan]
Ye Yunfei shone the most.
[Grand Elder of the Ye Clan]
For this year, I wonder...
[Second Elder of the Ye Clan]
This year, it's only natural that all young talents show their stuff
and emerge in succession.
[Second Elder of the Ye Clan]
[Ye Zhongnian]
[Fourth Elder of the Ye Clan]
Of course. Of course.
[Ye Zhongnian]
[Fourth Elder of the Ye Clan]
The Ye Clan holds its meeting once a year.
Agenda one
is an arena contest for youngsters.
Whoever wins
will become the core disciple
of the Ye Clan
and obtain the key cultivation
of our clan.
Remember,
pull your punches,
without any lethal strikes.
Alright.
Let's begin.
Brothers and sisters,
I may not be talented.
But I'm willing to kick off
the first arena duel.
Anyone who wants to combat first,
please come to the stage!
It's Ye Qiang.
Ye Qiang is getting
more and more arrogant lately.
Why isn't Yunfei here yet?
It's just Ye Qiang.
I'll challenge you!
[Ye Fan, Level 5 of Body Refinement]
Are you okay?
Level 6 of Body Refinement!
[Ye Qiang, Level 6 of Body Refinement]
He's at Level 6 of Body Refinement!
Next one!
Qiang has advanced to the next level
so quickly.
Great job.
Looks like he should be granted
additional cultivation resources
in the future.
Yes.
I hope he didn't make a fool of himself
in front of you.
Although Qiang is not gifted,
he's better than that loser,
Ye Yunfei.
Ye Zhongnian.
Yunfei has got his martial meridian back.
With his previous talent,
in time,
he'll surely achieve great things.
In time?
Master.
With Ye Clan's current situation,
should we waste the cultivation resources
on a useless person?
You...
That's right.
Tianpeng,
Yunfei has been a lost cause
in martial arts for 3 years.
He was long deemed unfit
to inherit the Ye Clan.
So,
I've discussed it with the elders.
We've decided
to reselect an heir based on the outcome
of today's arena duel
in the training ground.
You are clearly
bullying Tianpeng and his son!
I don't agree!
Second Elder,
we're doing this
for the future of the Ye Clan.
That's right.
This matter
is settled.
After the Elders' Union's decision,
today,
we'll reselect the heir of the Ye Clan
through this arena duel.
The winner
will become
the Senior Young Master of the Ye Clan!
Grand Elder.
Don't forget,
the Senior Young Master of the Ye Clan
is still Yunfei!
Of course.
For the sake of fairness,
if Yunfei wants to keep his position,
he just needs
to accept everyone's challenge.
You...
Second Elder.
No wonder you came after Yunfei.
Turns out you've long since
curried favor with the other elders.
The elders
are also acting in the long-term interest
of the Ye Clan.
Even though you're the master of our clan,
you can't go against
the decision of the Elders' Union.
You...
Why?
Tianpeng,
do you want to break the ancestral rules
of the Ye Clan?
I dare not.
[Ye Clan's Alchemy Room]
The Grade 3 Profound Essence Pills
are done!
To defeat Ye Lei
at Level 8 of Body Refinement
and guard against
Ye Zhongnian's backup plans,
with my current body refinement level,
I'm no match for them.
Looks like I have to think of a way
to make up for the gap
in body refinement levels.
All I can rely on now
is the Heavenly Emperor's soul power.
In that case,
I'll use this soul power technique
to form my soul power as a weapon—
which specializes in attacking
human souls—
Soul-devouring Needle.
The Clan Competition should have begun.
It's too late to rely on
ordinary cultivation techniques.
It seems
I can only consume the Power of Nine Suns.
Bad news! Bad news!
Senior Young Master!
[Chun Fang]
Yue has been taken by Steward Ye
to the Execution Hall!
[Chun Fang]
What?
I give up! I give up!
But I don't think I've won.
Get off this arena!
We're all from the same clan.
[Ye Tianfeng]
How could you be so ruthless?
In the arena,
[Ye Tianfeng]
weapons know no mercy.
I'm just stronger than all of you!
Enough talk!
Who's next?
If no one challenges me,
I'll be the Senior Young Master
of the Ye Clan!
You haven't defeated Yunfei yet!
That doesn't count!
Ye Yunfei, that loser.
Ye Yunfei!
Come out!
I'll wait here!
[Ye Clan's Execution Hall]
If you don't come,
the Ye Clan's heir position is mine for the taking!
[Ye Clan's Execution Hall]
Tell me.
[Ye Fu]
Did Ye Yunfei order you
to steal Young Master Ye Qiang's pills?
[Ye Fu]
No.
Even if you beat me to death,
I won't frame him.
Such a stubborn girl.
The Ye Clan
will soon be in Second Master's hands.
Guys!
Bring out a finger crusher.
Yue!
You losers!
Come on!
Come up!
Master,
if Yunfei doesn't accept the challenge,
he'll automatically forfeit.
Are there no more outstanding disciples
of the Ye Clan
willing to step up and challenge him?
Ye Qiang has shown off big time.
You go. You go.
Looks like only Ye Yunfei can do it.
Is there no one
in the Ye Clan
willing to stand up for Yunfei?
Ye Yunfei is indeed a loser.
You too.
A bunch of losers!
Shut up!
[Ye Xue, Level 5 of Body Refinement]
We're all from the same clan.
We should support each other.
Stop calling others losers.
You're only at Level 5.
Do you really think
you can defeat me by jumping ranks?
Xue!
Don't force yourself!
You don't know
till we fight.
Fine.
I'll fight until you surrender!
You've mastered
the rudimentary sword intent?
How is that possible?
Well, thanks to that useless Ye Yunfei.
A single sword's frost
chills 14 realms!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
You annoying woman,
go to hell!
Thank you.
Leave the rest to me.
Yunfei.
That loser.
Ye Yunfei.
This time, I'll publicly prove
you're merely a pathetic loser!
Who said
lower levels
can't beat
higher ones?
You keep calling me a loser.
What are you now?
You're worse than a loser.
Don't come near me!
You crazy man!
No!
Ye Yunfei!
Your cultivation was...
My cultivation was forcibly interrupted,
and I suffered internal injuries, right?
You...
You despicable man
only know how to play dirty.
But you don't know
there is
always
someone
better.
He's broken through 3 levels in 3 days?
Miracle!
An absolute miracle!
I,
[Level 6 of Body Refinement]
Ye Yunfei,
accept everyone's challenge!
[Level 6 of Body Refinement]
Who dares?
How arrogant you are!
Watch your...
Elders,
didn't you say the Senior Young Master
of the Ye Clan
would be determined
based on today's arena outcome?
Since the rules are set,
if anyone gets involved again,
don't blame me for being merciless.
Of course. Of course.
Since no one challenges me,
the Senior Young Master of the Ye Clan
is still—
You're counting your chickens
before they hatch!
[Ye Lei, Level 8 of Body Refinement]
Level 8?
So Ye Lei is the trump card
you've been hiding all along.
How dare you hurt my brother?
I'm going to beat you
into permanent disability!
Try it then.
[Level 9 of Body Refinement]
Level 9?
Level 9, actually?
Die!
Wild Lion Fist Consummate Realm,
Wild Lion Roar!
After being hit by my Grade 3
martial arts technique, Wild Lion Fist,
he will never survive!
Yunfei!
Get lost!
You've reached the Mid-Stage Earth Realm.
That's right.
Ye Tianpeng, your cultivation
has made no progress at all.
You've even raised a useless child.
So incompetent,
you'd better step down
and hand over the position of master!
No way!
Master Ye!
How dare you!
Changing the master
is not for you to decide!
Chaoxian,
I think Zhongnian is right.
Yes.
Now that his son,
Ye Lei, is such an excellent child,
the Ye Clan should be handed over to them.
That makes sense.
Only the strongest shall hold
the master position of the Ye Clan.
Although I'm not talented,
I'm willing to take this responsibility.
From now on,
the Ye Clan will be mine!
What a dramatic show.
Ye Yunfei.
How is that possible?
If it weren't for making the old cur
Ye Zhongnian show his true form,
I wouldn't have been entangled with you
until now.
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible!
Windstride Divine Steps.
Ye Yunfei,
are you a coward?
Do you dare to fight me head-on?
As you wish then.
Come, the sword.
Sword intent.
Yunfei has mastered the true sword intent.
Why?
You loser.
Go to hell!
I'll be the final winner!
How is that possible?
I originally spared you
out of consideration
for you being a Ye Clan disciple
and the hardships of cultivation.
I didn't expect you to be so sinister.
I can't keep you alive.
Soul-devouring Needle.
Ye Yunfei!
You...
Old cur,
it's time to settle the score
with you for Yue.
Whoever dares lay a finger on my people
shall die!
[Next Episode Preview]
Ye Yunfei,
I have a clear conscience.
A junior like you has no right to meddle!
What is done in the dark
will come to light.
That depends on what you've got!
So Ye Zhongnian
has long been colluding with you
to covet the Ye Clan.
Master Ye, are you
going to deny it?
Greetings, everyone. I'm Xiao Chuchu,
Chief of the Lingzhen Workshop.
No one else is needed
for what happened today.
Senior Young Master, congrats
on awakening the Heavenly Spirit Body!
Ye Yunfei is nothing at all.
My gaze spans
the whole Qin Empire.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™