[For underage viewers,
please watch with parental permission.]
[The following content was entirely produced
through virtual production.]
[Do not imitate in real life.]
♪Let the wind♪
♪Blow the road ahead♪
♪Fate is waiting for me♪
♪Through the long journey of experience♪
♪Who doesn't have♪
♪Passion♪
♪But hide the talents♪
♪In dimly lit places♪
♪How can life♪
♪Be invulnerable♪
♪Disdain for the night♪
♪Why show your edge♪
♪Occasionally taking some detours♪
♪Is to take exercises♪
♪A crisis is a close call♪
♪I also stand up♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪I play to the score♪
♪Don't have to risk life
being smart and brave♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪No fear of abyss♪
♪Still clench fists
without showing any signs♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪Keep calm and thoughtful♪
♪Walk in the courtyard
and fearlessly cross the natural moat♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪If the viral is inevitable♪
♪Counter measure for measure♪
[Previously]
I'm Li Changshou, a Blue Star native.
With my master Qi Yuan's death,
I chose to fight the Tao of Heaven
to the end.
[Peng]It was actually Demon Master,
Peng, who showed up.
I joined forces with Yunxiao, Roc,
and Mr. Bai, to besiege him.
Peng used all his might to escape,
but I blocked him with a trap.
Cornered, Peng began
to belittle the Tao of Heaven.
Roc rebuked him
and struck him down.
In the cave,
I found Senior Bold's belongings.
At the same time, I inferred
that Peng's death seemed suspicious
in many ways.
Episode 116
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Of course,
this should only be the first step
of the plan on the surface.
The second step should be related
to the notebook.
Turns out Peng is quite the schemer.
Wait.
Did he show up for you, Master?
That's right.
He claimed he had waited here
for you for a long time
and said something strange.
Lord Taibai,
judging from your reaction back then,
you seemed to know something.
Oh my!
Good heavens!
Please save me.
I was only pretending to slip up
on purpose for Peng,
hoping to coax some useful information
out of him.
Didn't expect it was all nonsense.
How did you get fooled too?
I'm really too dull.
I must study more from you, Master.
I see.
So I misunderstood his words as well.
I managed...
to convince them,
right?
What's wrong?
Did Peng's words unsettle you?
I'm good.
Master is really awesome.
Lord Taibai and Immortal Yunxiao
are truly fond of each other.
It's not something you can follow.
I'm not interested in women.
Oh, right.
When you return to the primordial world,
report this to Martial Uncle Tongtian.
I was planning to do that.
Oh no.
Will they blame me for meddling?
Hey, I'll go find Zhong.
If Yunxiao arrives, please receive her.
[One day later]
Lord Taibai, the Saintess is gone.
When did this happen?
She was already missing
when I returned to Lintian Hall.
We just got back from the Chaotic Sea,
and she suddenly disappeared.
Could it be another scheme of Peng?
Mr. Bai, don't worry.
I'll use papermen to search at once.
I've found Martial Aunt Jiu Jiu.
I've been away so long.
It's time I came back to take a look.
Is everything still alright?
For now, Elder Qiling
is acting Sect Master.
Other than that,
nothing much has changed.
Come on,
I'll show you around Xiaoqiong Peak.
Wasn't it already moved
to the Heavenly Court?
The place beside the Tushita Palace
belongs to Sage Taiqing's disciple,
Taibai Jinxing, also Li Changgeng.
And this place
is the residence of Li Changshou,
Xiaoqiong Peak's disciple.
Changshou,
your master is gone.
[Master Qi Yuan's Tomb]
Alright.
If we don't return to Lintian Hall,
Mr. Bai will start worrying.
I'll take my leave, then.
The primordial world
is no longer as stable as before.
I'll escort you back.
Martial Aunt, how have things been
at Lintian Hall lately?
Everything's fine, just boring.
Someone keeps telling us to lie low.
Who knows how long
we're supposed to lie low.
Martial Uncle, that means
waiting for the right moment.
Another right moment?
I've heard of that countless times.
Let's drop this topic.
I heard you recently
found a good partner.
You're well-informed.
Taibai Jinxing and Yunxiao's love story
has spread across the primordial world.
It'd be hard not to know.
She and I have made an oath.
She's the one and only in my life.
Great.
Then I wish you and Immortal Yunxiao
be on the same page
and live happily together.
Thank you, Martial Aunt Jiu Jiu.
Changshou,
didn't you once say
your heart would twitch
whenever a woman touched you?
Then with Yunxiao...
Did I say that?
Why don't I remember?
Li Changshou, you dared lie to me?
Martial Aunt, that was a white lie.
How could you still remember that?
[Ahhhh]
We're almost there.
I'm at least
at the Celestial Immortal Realm.
Go back.
Martial Aunt,
take care.
Take care.
[Big Brother]
The notebook includes
the primordial world's taboos.
It's safer to read it
deep in the Chaotic Sea,
where the power
of the Tao of Heaven cannot probe.
Now I review Peng's
every word and action.
It's not hard to see
that the secret code was meant
to confirm that I'm a Blue Star native.
His rambling before death,
"Hong Jun would never allow
another one like him to exist"
was meant to hint
that Hongjun has a problem.
Was Peng trying to tell me this,
or was it Senior Bold?
This notebook
may be the key to answering everything.
Entry 1:
[001]
Since the beginning of the world,
I took a nap and woke up here.
This body's cultivation
is ridiculously high.
Pretty good.
The second primordial spirit I cultivated
is finally complete.
Entry 2:
The Tao of Heaven
is getting more and more refined.
I can feel the laws and order here
becoming much clearer.
That's good.
Pangu's final wish
might be fulfilled sooner.
Entry 3:
The biodiversity has painstakingly
developed since ancient times,
yet the Witch
are almost eating all beings up.
Hongjun wants
to unite all beings into the Saint
to restrain the Witch.
Calling the Demon
the Saint?
Come on.
Entry 4:
Hongjun's preaching is just the level?
Back in Blue Star,
I could hear all it free of charge.
This philosophy is all garbage.
Entry Five:
The Human are born.
Nyuwa finally became a sage.
She has a bit of my old flair.
But it feels strange
to watching my ancestor
pinch clay to make people.
Entry 6:
Among the three of the Taoism sects,
Taiqing really has some skill.
He actually deduced the evolution
of the Tao beyond the Tao of Heaven.
Tongtian really needs to be less fiery,
or he will suffer for it later.
The Demon even refines Human spirit souls
into weapons to use against the Witch.
I'll secretly protect a group of Humans
and send them to settle somewhere
in the Three Thousand Worlds.
Entry 373: Took in a good disciple.
She should become
the future Immortal Heng'e.
Anyone who dares
set their sights on my disciple
will get broken legs. Absolutely!
Entry 379:
Got nothing to do. Played cards.
Entry 380:
Entry 381: Play Cards.
Entry 382...
[Notebook]
Why?
No.
[Notebook]
Something's off.
This is wrong.
It's all wrong.
It shouldn't be like this.
It's you.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[It's wrong!]
The information
in the Bold Notebook is overwhelming.
Senior Bold said "wrong"...
Could he be referring
to the fact
that between the two stories,
one must be a lie?
According to the Taoist Ancestor's
previous account...
He went mad.
He wanted to prove the Tao by force
and destroy the primordial world.
So I had no choice but to kill him.
But Senior Bold said...
Hongjun.
It's you.
It's all your fault.
The Taoist Ancestor's story
seems logically airtight on the surface,
but if Senior Bold spoke the truth,
then he must have discovered
the Taoist Ancestor's secret.
Thus, the Taoist Ancestor
joined forces with the Tao of Heaven...
Wait.
The Taoist Ancestor claims
he's bound by the Tao of Heaven.
But the Tao of Heaven is impartial.
How would it kill anyone
for Taoist Ancestor's personal motives?
Unless
the Taoist Ancestor
isn't constrained by the Tao of Heaven,
but the Tao of Heaven
is constrained by the Taoist Ancestor.
There's too little information.
I should return to the primordial world,
then figure out the next step.
Do you still remember our slogan?
Of course.
Target locked, instantly erased.
Encrypted data, zero footprint.
Pro service on demand,
high-speed results on delivery.
I'm Mr. Readman.
I'm Miss Noculture.
We're at your service.
How could an outer-world demon
appear in the primordial world?
I really meet you here,
Taibai Jinxing, Li Changgeng.
My master's been waiting for you
in the Chaotic Sea for a long time.
Why would the outer-world demon
lure me to the Chaotic Sea?
Wait,
could it be related
to the Bold Notebook?
What is your master's connection
to Peng?
Just come with us to the Chaotic Sea,
and you'll know everything.
Did you really think
I had no way to make you talk?
Taste my self-developed array,
Matcha Shatter Ice!
And here's a little extra topping.
[Sago]
[Boba]
[Coconut jelly]
Hey,
now,
let me take a look at your memories.
[Senior Bold's notebook recorded
some of his random thoughts,]
[like when he woke up,]
[Pangu's wish, the Tao of Heaven...]
[Li Changshou seemed
to notice something new from it.]
[It's like primordial world's
role-playing game.]
[BTY, Senior Bold's self-portrait
is pretty cool.]
Life is so long.
I will finally find the right person.
Scan the QR code.
Let's wait together
for the day to reunite.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Who is stirring up the ripples♪
♪Face that turns red day by day♪
♪My heart is rippling in circles♪
♪The spring breeze is lingering♪
♪Who's figure appears in my heart♪
♪Only I know it's extraordinary♪
♪Draw my thoughts
in front of the bronze mirror♪
♪Hide my covet♪
♪First meet in the clan♪
♪Heroic eyebrows♪
♪The days and nights spent together♪
♪Who is by whose side♪
♪Favorite plots♪
♪Occasionally forget to cover up♪
♪The stars lingering on Xiaoqiong Peak♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪Especially hope you're safe♪
♪Much insurance for everything♪
♪Suddenly disappear♪
♪It turns out to be in my heart♪
♪A fleeting glimpse is caught♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪Like a difficult trial♪
♪Junior's wish♪
♪Can you hear it♪
♪Merry matrimony♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪Especially hope you're safe♪
♪Much insurance for everything♪
♪Suddenly disappear♪
♪It turns out to be in my heart♪
♪A fleeting glimpse is caught♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪Like a difficult trial♪
♪Junior's wish♪
♪Can you hear it♪
♪Merry matrimony♪
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[Next episode]
You...
know your place, at least.
Outsider...
That outsider...
Go to Duxian Sect
of Dongshengshen Continent.
Ask Taibai Jinxing
whether he wants to see the rest.
Trash.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™