[For underage viewers,
please watch with parental permission.]
[The following content was entirely produced
through virtual production.]
[Do not imitate in real life.]
♪Let the wind♪
♪Blow the road ahead♪
♪Fate is waiting for me♪
♪Through the long journey of experience♪
♪Who doesn't have♪
♪Passion♪
♪But hide the talents♪
♪In dimly lit places♪
♪How can life♪
♪Be invulnerable♪
♪Disdain for the night♪
♪Why show your edge♪
♪Occasionally taking some detours♪
♪Is to take exercises♪
♪A crisis is a close call♪
♪I also stand up♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪I play to the score♪
♪Don't have to risk life
being smart and brave♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪No fear of abyss♪
♪Still clench fists
without showing any signs♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪Keep calm and thoughtful♪
♪Walk in the courtyard
and fearlessly cross the natural moat♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪If the viral is inevitable♪
♪Counter measure for measure♪
[Previously]
I'm Li Changshou, a Blue Star native.
With my master Qi Yuan's death,
I chose to fight the Tao of Heaven
to the end.
Yang Jian was granted the title
True Lord of the Mystic Way,
yet he declared he'd follow
only the military commands, not decrees.
It'll take quite some time
to ease the resentment
in that rebellious guy's heart.
Yunxiao invited me to the Chaotic Sea to seek the opportunity that Martial Uncle Tongtian discovered.
In a mysterious cave,
we poured our hearts out to each other.
Only then did I realize
that the opportunity wasn't a treasure,
but...
Episode 115
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Lord Taibai, watch out.
It's Demon Master, Peng.
So... he really appeared!
Every time we're about to kiss,
we'll be interrupted.
But today, no matter what, I must kiss Yunxiao.
Demon Master Peng?
How could he be here?
This is the opportunity I arranged.
What treasure could compare to the memories they make by facing hardships together?
[Pass]
After this journey, their bond will surely grow deeper.
As Junior Changgeng would say,
Master's plan is below zero level.
[Peng]
Who?
Who dares make out outside my cave?
Marvelous Tower.
Taiji Diagram.
Heaven and Earth Ruler.
God-slaying Spear.
Who exactly is he?
And just how many treasures
does he have?
Peng,
you're surrounded.
Surrender now.
Stupid goat,
back in the Demon Court,
you opposed me at every turn.
Too bad your skills are lame.
You even dragged my foolish brother here
to help you.
You forged the Witch-slaying Sword with the Human spirit souls and plotted a plan to wipe out the Human.
You've always rubbed me the wrong way.
Peng,
you stole Mother's origin power, leaving her trapped within Undying Volcano.
Today, one of us must die here.
You're no match for me.
Spirit Enshrouding Technique!
Didn't expect Peng to actually develop such a technique just to flee more easily.
I underestimated him.
[Before the First Great War
of Witches and Demons]
Roc,
I've bestowed upon you
the Phoenix Essence Blood.
[Primordial Phoenix]
From this day forth,
you are one of the Phoenix.
Mother.
After the Dragon-Phoenix Catastrophe, the Phoenix declined.
Peng, as the eldest,
you must bear the duty
of reviving the Phoenix.
Peng! Peng!
Just as the Demon Court was rising, Peng betrayed the Phoenix and joined the Demon Court instead.
Now that the Demon Court has fallen, he returned to Undying Volcano.
Mother,
he's such an opportunist.
He doesn't deserve to be taken back.
That's right, Mother.
He must have another agenda this time.
Even so, he was once my child.
Mother...
Mother!
Peng,
you dared to steal
Mother's origin power.
You must pay the price for what you did!
Can't catch me, can you?
Time to put it to an end.
Master.
Spirit Enshrouding Technique.
You can't hurt me.
I said you couldn't hurt me.
Wait...
What's happening?
God-slaying Spear can wound both
physical form and primordial spirit.
Peng may protect his physical form, but not his primordial spirit.
What's on earth is this?
Go to heck!
[Big Brother]
Happy Henry Likes Beer.
But Could Not Obtain Four Nuts.
Happy Henry Likes Beer...?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Master,
why did you stop?
Happy Henry Likes Beer.
But Could Not Obtain Four Nuts.
That's a line
everyone on Blue Star knows.
How could Peng know it?
Could he also be from Blue Star...
or has he met someone from there?
Like Senior Bold?
So it's you.
You couldn't hide the hesitation at that very moment.
All so many years, I finally got you.
Martial Uncle Tongtian.
You set me up?
We set each other up.
When Changgeng called out
Martial Uncle Tongtian just now,
I almost teleported over myself.
If Yunxiao gains Changgeng's help, who could possibly stop her?
I might as well yield my title
as the senior to her.
Peng, your crimes are countless.
You can't get away today.
Do you really think every evil
in the primordial world was my doing?
The rise of the Demon
was secretly driven by Hong Jun,
wasn't it?
You think the Tao of Heaven granted you
that fate-sensing power for free?
What Taoism do you think Hong Jun spread
in the primordial world?
Let me tell you,
it's the Primordial Spirit Taoism,
one that the Tao of Heaven can sway.
Exactly.
The Tao of Heaven
can control people's hearts.
He badly wanted
to dominate living beings,
and I helped him
accomplish everything he desired.
But in the end,
you know what,
when the Demon Court declined, all I received was a single glance from him.
And that glance
left me in this miserable state.
Hong Jun would never allow another one like him to exist.
How dare you disrespect
the Tao of Heaven!
Roc.
Peng, you betrayed the Phoenix and stole our mother's origin power.
Today, I'll settle the score with you
with the very technique
our mother taught me.
Sun-piercing Skill.
Mother...
This place lies right on the border
of the Tao of Heaven's influence.
If we let him finish speaking, we might get dragged into it as well.
Search this area.
See if there's any treasure we can use.
Yunxiao, please refine
Primordial Phoenix's origin power.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
If what Peng said is true,
why would the Tao of Heaven secretly
support the rise of the Demon Court?
What is the connection between Peng,
Hong Jun, and Senior Bold?
Why did Hong Jun spread
the Primordial Spirit Taoism?
The more you know, the more danger you'll face.
I can't let you be dragged
into the huge mess.
Could this be Senior Bold's relic?
So weird.
Peng is from the Demon Court.
No matter how down-and-out he is, he shouldn't have so few treasures.
No Primordial Phoenix's origin power
was refined from his corpse either.
Peng's death raises too many questions.
Do you remember when he appeared?
Yes.
Master, after you and Immortal Yunxiao entered here, you triggered the outer warning seal.
Peng was alerted and rushed over.
As a fugitive hunted
by the Heavenly Court for years,
he didn't flee
when his cave's alarm went off.
Instead,
he chose to show himself.
You mean
he deliberately showed up?
What was his intention?
As a fugitive, what scares him most?
Being caught, of course.
You mean...
Only when the fake Peng is dead,
the real one could slip away.
Turns out Peng is quite the schemer.
Of course, that's likely only the first step of his plan.
The second step is probably
tied to the notebook.
[Bold Notebook]
[A notebook left]
[in the Chaotic Sea by Senior Bold.]
[With many secrets recorded on it,]
[even the trigger for Great War
of Witches and Demons can be traced.]
[After reading, Changshou can't help
but marvel at Senior Bold's Boldness!]
Life is so long.
I will finally find the right person.
Scan the QR code.
Let's wait together for the day to reunite.
♪Who is stirring up the ripples♪
♪Face that turns red day by day♪
♪My heart is rippling in circles♪
♪The spring breeze is lingering♪
♪Who's figure appears in my heart♪
♪Only I know it's extraordinary♪
♪Draw my thoughts
in front of the bronze mirror♪
♪Hide my covet♪
♪First meet in the clan♪
♪Heroic eyebrows♪
♪The days and nights spent together♪
♪Who is by whose side♪
♪Favorite plots♪
♪Occasionally forget to cover up♪
♪The stars lingering on Xiaoqiong Peak♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪Especially hope you're safe♪
♪Much insurance for everything♪
♪Suddenly disappear♪
♪It turns out to be in my heart♪
♪A fleeting glimpse is caught♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪Like a difficult trial♪
♪Junior's wish♪
♪Can you hear it♪
♪Merry matrimony♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪Especially hope you're safe♪
♪Much insurance for everything♪
♪Suddenly disappear♪
♪It turns out to be in my heart♪
♪A fleeting glimpse is caught♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪Like a difficult trial♪
♪Junior's wish♪
♪Can you hear it♪
♪Merry matrimony♪
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[Next Episode]
Lord Taibai is missing.
It's another plot by Peng.
The secrets of the Taoist Ancestor...
There must be lies
between them.
Could it be it refers to...
Something feels off.
Hong Jun would never allow
another one like him to exist.
My master has been waiting
for you for a long time.
deep in the Chaotic Sea.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™