[For underage viewers,
please watch with parental permission.]
[The following content was entirely produced
through virtual production.]
[Do not imitate in real life.]
♪Let the wind♪
♪Blow the road ahead♪
♪Fate is waiting for me♪
♪Through the long journey of experience♪
♪Who doesn't have♪
♪Passion♪
♪But hide the talents♪
♪In dimly lit places♪
♪How can life♪
♪Be invulnerable♪
♪Disdain for the night♪
♪Why show your edge♪
♪Occasionally taking some detours♪
♪Is to take exercises♪
♪A crisis is a close call♪
♪I also stand up♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪I play to the score♪
♪Don't have to risk life
being smart and brave♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪No fear of abyss♪
♪Still clench fists
without showing any signs♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪Keep calm and thoughtful♪
♪Walk in the courtyard
and fearlessly cross the natural moat♪
♪Keep courage in heart♪
♪If the viral is inevitable♪
♪Counter measure for measure♪
[Previously]
I'm Li Changshou,
a Blue Star native.
With my master Qi Yuan's death,
I chose to fight the Tao of Heaven
to the end.
The trip to the Chaotic Sea
was truly full of twists and turns.
My conversation with Peng
ultimately raised everyone's suspicions
about me.
Luckily, I managed to
bluff my way through with nonsense.
Martial Aunt Jiu Jiu happened to return
to mourn for the Sect Master.
I caught up with her for a while.
After seeing her off,
I learned much about ancient history
from the Bold Notebook.
Later, I was attacked
by two outer-world demons.
Episode 117
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Now...
let me take a look at your memories.
Go to the Duxian Sect
on the Dongshengshen Continent.
Ask Taibai Jinxing
if he wants to see what comes next.
I understand.
Now I understand everything.
The reason why the outer-world demons
were able to enter the Primordial World,
or rather,
why the Tao of Heaven
and the Taoist Ancestor let them in,
allowing them to deliver a message
for Peng.
Shouldn't anything related
to Senior Bold
be a taboo for the Tao of Heaven?
Shouldn't it be erased?
There's
only one explanation for everything...
It's that Bold Notebook.
So, from that moment on,
the Tao of Heaven and Taoist Ancestor
already knew everything.
They've been
testing me all along.
First, tell me what you want to ask.
Let me give you a quote.
The relationship between Peng
and Senior Bold,
and whether Senior Bold truly
went mad in the end...
I won't charge you consulting fees
for these two answers.
Peng and he used each other,
but most of the time,
Peng was under his control.
As for the second question,
I cannot give you
a definitive answer either.
I know he had a plan to become a Sage,
but back then,
he suddenly moved the plan forward,
seeming impatient to obtain power
comparable to Sage Pangu's.
Sage Pangu used a Heaven-Splitting Axe
to cleave heaven and earth apart,
slaying countless Innate Divine Demons
in the process.
To achieve that,
he did not hesitate
to wield Universe-origin power.
Had it not been for the Master
and the Tao of Heaven
suppressing him to death,
the Universe
would have ended long ago.
I always thought Senior Bold
was a good person, like me.
I never imagined he would
commit such atrocities.
No wonder the Taoist Ancestor
took action.
You'd better
be more careful in your actions
from now on.
Do not entertain
any treacherous thoughts.
Ah, Martial Aunt,
I've recently got something new...
I believe it might please you.
You've created a new comic?
What do you mean?
To be frank,
I accidentally obtained this
during my trip to the Chaotic Sea.
Because this notebook touches
on a taboo of the Tao of Heaven,
I wished to keep it from others,
but my curiosity got the better of me,
so I delved deep
into the Chaotic Sea to read it.
Unexpectedly, the notebook was filled
with utter nonsense.
I couldn't make head or tail of it.
I thought it was of little consequence,
but after your reminder,
I decided to hand it over.
After all, inviting trouble
over a madman's notebook
would be far too unworthy.
You are quite sensible.
Thank you for the praise.
Stop a single thought,
and all things revert to their origin.
Martial Aunt,
you mentioned that he suddenly
moved up his plan to become a Sage.
Was his rush
to compete with the Taoist Ancestor?
That question carries a separate price.
Are you truly sure you wish to know?
I've overstepped.
Your greatest virtue
is knowing exactly when to advance
and when to withdraw.
Keep drawing.
Make it more exciting.
I'm afraid that both the Taoist Ancestor
and Senior Bold back in the day...
weren't exactly clean.
The Taoist Ancestor and Tao of Heaven
may not share the same stance either.
And you...?
You've already stepped
into the Perfected Great Dao Realm
and mastered the Path of Balance.
You care so much about him...
Do you also wish to transcend
and become a Sage?
Transcendence has always been
on my mind,
but becoming a Sage...
let's forget that.
The current Universe
can no longer withstand
the impact
of a living being achieving Sagehood.
The more resources one occupies,
the greater the risks one must bear.
Excessive intervention in the Universe
brings inevitable backlash.
So imprudent
and doomed to fail.
If you don't become a Sage,
how can you transcend?
Becoming a Sage is transcendence?
What exactly is your hometown like?
How is it that everyone from there
is more inscrutable than the last?
My hometown has plenty of excellent,
upstanding youths like me.
Of course,
few can remain as steadfast
as a great mountain,
the way I can.
I will find a way to deal with this.
But,
you obtained it from Peng, didn't you?
He kept sending outer-world demons lately
to lure me deep into the Chaotic Sea.
Do you plan to go?
Peng's speed pushes
the very limits
of the Primordial World's rules.
Why would I deliver myself
to his doorstep?
As for these outer-world demons,
they are the enemies of all
in the Primordial World.
I will kill every one I see.
I've made a two-step plan:
First, submit a memorial to His Majesty,
branding him a most-wanted criminal
across the Primordial World,
[Demon Master Peng]
shattering Peng's strategy
of feigning death.
Second, since Peng has always controlled
the outer-world demons.
I will launch a campaign
across the Three Thousand Worlds
and surrounding regions
to cleanse the outer-world demons,
and create a beautiful,
new Primordial World.
As for the outer-world demons' tendency
to possess human bodies,
Reincarnation Tower has a Divine Beast
just recovered from its injuries.
It might be time to take it for a walk,
world by world.
[Demon Lord]
Master, you're awake!
Thirty-five years...
A full thirty-five years!
Why hasn't he come to the Chaotic Sea?
You!
Attack Xuandu City!
You must draw him out!
Yes, Master.
Wait.
Take this.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[Big Brother]
Kill Taibai Jinxing!
He has killed so many
of our brothers and sisters!
He must pay the price!
If you destroy my heaven,
I will tear your world apart!
Kill Taibai Jinxing!
Changgeng, what have you done?
As expected of Junior Changgeng,
you've even managed to cozy up
to the outer-world demons.
Although Senior Taiyi's words are crude,
they are not entirely unreasonable.
Do you regret inviting Senior Taiyi
to guard Xuandu City now?
A top-tier team must have
a stable initiator to cover
for the main damage dealer
while they unleash their full power.
You're always saying things
no one can understand.
It's the Demon Lord!
You outsider!
I come by my master's command,
to deliver a small gift.
Primordial chaos birth radiant splendor;
the sea of clouds weaves heaven's net.
Mission accomplished.
Kids,
withdraw!
No, Mother!
He killed so many of our brothers
and sisters!
Kill him! Kill him!
I'll say it again: withdraw!
You came to Xuandu City
and think you can just leave?
Senior, catch!
You all, repair the formation here.
Leave the Demon Lord to me.
These past few days,
you've had quite the fun
assaulting Xuandu City.
Scum.
Demonic Annihilation.
First strike: Settle the Universe.
Second strike: Shatter all laws!
Envoys are not to be harmed
during the war!
Universe, return to one.
Third strike:
Suppress the chaotic!
Explode!
The same ruler, in different hands...
makes such a vast difference!
Is this truly the Creation Jade Disc?
To be precise,
it's a fragment of it.
When Sage Pangu cleaved heaven
and earth apart,
the Creation Jade Disc was struck by it,
and a corner of it shattered
and broke away.
That fragment vanished
without a trace ever since.
The remaining was then
comprehended by the Taoist Ancestor,
thus becoming part of the Tao of Heaven.
[Demon Lord]
[Ruler of the outer-world demons.]
[Due to the unique reproductive methods
of this race,]
[Demon Lord is the "Mother"
of all outer-world demons.]
[With horns on and a tail behind,
a rather distinctive appearance,]
[it proves that the darker the place,
the more bizarre its life forms.]
Life is so long.
I will finally find the right person.
Scan the QR code.
Let's wait together
for the day to reunite.
♪Who is stirring up the ripples♪
♪Face that turns red day by day♪
♪My heart is rippling in circles♪
♪The spring breeze is lingering♪
♪Who's figure appears in my heart♪
♪Only I know it's extraordinary♪
♪Draw my thoughts
in front of the bronze mirror♪
♪Hide my covet♪
♪First meet in the clan♪
♪Heroic eyebrows♪
♪The days and nights spent together♪
♪Who is by whose side♪
♪Favorite plots♪
♪Occasionally forget to cover up♪
♪The stars lingering on Xiaoqiong Peak♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪Especially hope you're safe♪
♪Much insurance for everything♪
♪Suddenly disappear♪
♪It turns out to be in my heart♪
♪A fleeting glimpse is caught♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪Like a difficult trial♪
♪Junior's wish♪
♪Can you hear it♪
♪Merry matrimony♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪Especially hope you're safe♪
♪Much insurance for everything♪
♪Suddenly disappear♪
♪It turns out to be in my heart♪
♪A fleeting glimpse is caught♪
♪Senior is so special♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪Like a difficult trial♪
♪Junior's wish♪
♪Can you hear it♪
♪Merry matrimony♪
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[Next Episode]
Who is this person?
All related matters leave no trace
for investigation.
Then it's the greatest variable
in the Primordial World.
Don't tell me... you know something?
There's no revolution without bloodshed.
If we allow him to continue
acting so recklessly,
sooner or later he'll tear a gaping hole
in the Primordial World.
The Chaotic Sea, too,
will return to a dead silence.
If all this is true...
Unless...
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™