Hun Mie Sheng unleashes his hidden
five-star Dou Saint power.
He’s determined to seize the
Demonic Flame’s origin from Xiao Yan.
Luckily, Xiao Chen intervenes in time.
And defeats him.
Refusing to accept defeat, Hun Mie Sheng
summons the five-star Dou Saint, Soul Demon Elder.
At the same time, the six-star Dou Saint
and Pill Tower Ancestor also appears.
The Pill Tower Ancestor reveals the truth—
the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame was sealed on purpose.
Forcing the flame to reveal itself.
Enraged, the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame
summons the Ancient Refining Heaven Array.
Intending to refine everyone present.
At the critical moment...
The Pure Lotus Demon Saint
possesses Xiao Yan’s body.
And saves everyone.
Pure Lotus Demon Saint...
The legendary peak expert from back then,
said to be closest to becoming a Dou Di.
How did Xiao Yan...
manage to summon the Pure Lotus Demon Saint?
This Demon Saint isn’t in soul form.
It looks more like a residual image.
What’s going on?
Could it be because of that remnant map?
When Xiao Yan collected all the
remnant map pieces...
A ray of light shot into his body.
What do we do now?
The Pure Lotus Demon Saint has taken over
Brother Xiao Yan’s body.
If anything goes wrong...
Brother Xiao Yan will be the one
who suffers the most.
Don’t panic.
He will save us.
I don’t think he means any harm.
His target...
should be the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame.
You old bastard...
How is this possible?
How can you still be alive?
After thousands of years of sealing...
It seems it still couldn’t erase
the madness in your heart.
Damn you!
Pure Lotus Demon Saint...
You ungrateful bastard!
I helped you so much...
Yet you repaid my kindness by sealing me away!
Serves you right to have been devoured
and killed in the end!
This grand array was created by you personally.
Today...
You shall taste its power as well!
Die!
You old fool!
Refine!
Stabilize!
That you turned out so violent...
I bear some responsibility as well.
But if I had let you leave freely...
This world...
would have faced a great catastrophe.
I created the Ancient Refining Heaven Array.
When it comes to understanding it...
You are still far beneath me.
Old bastard!
I’ll fight you to the death!
Demonic Flame—World Annihilation!
Hurry and leave this place.
If the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame
fully erupts...
None of you will survive.
Go, quickly!
Miss...
We should leave at once too.
But Brother Xiao Yan’s mind
has been taken over by the Demon Saint.
If we just leave like this...
I won’t feel at ease.
Stop worrying about that!
Hurry and go!
Staying here won’t help anything.
Since the Demon Saint Senior has borrowed
Xiao Yan’s body...
He won’t harm him.
Let’s go too.
Miss...
You...
I’m going back to stay with Brother Xiao Yan.
Miss, please don’t be reckless!
Going back now is no different from suicide!
Besides, Miss should understand even better...
What you mean to the Ancient Clan.
Enough!
All these years...
I’ve always followed the clan’s arrangements.
Whenever Brother Xiao Yan needed help most...
I was never there.
Now that Brother Xiao Yan is right in front
of me facing mortal danger...
You still want me to follow the rules?
I refuse!
Miss...
When you return, please tell Father...
This time...
Allow Xun’er to be willful once.
When I first met you all those years ago...
You were as pure as an infant.
I granted you spiritual awareness
so you could possess human thoughts.
But the path you chose to walk
is completely different from what I envisioned.
Diametrically opposed.
How I grow...
is my own affair.
Old thing!
You interfere too much.
I simply do not wish for you
to sink into self-destruction.
I was the one who made you this way.
So let me be the one to end this.
Pure Lotus Demon Saint!
You heartless bastard!
I will never let you have your way.
When my end was near,
I did consider erasing your memories.
But I could not bring myself to do it.
Hence, I sealed you,
hoping to dissolve the tyranny
and killing intent in your heart.
But now it seems,
that thousands of years of sealing
have only intensified your hatred.
Since that is the case,
Ancient Refining Heaven Formation—
Strip!
Stop!
You old bastard!
Stop right now!
Without memories,
without spiritual intellect,
what difference is there from killing me?
Hypocrite!
Your temperament
is utterly brutal.
Now, having received my inheritance,
if I let you break the seal,
it will surely spell disaster.
The calamity was drawn by me,
so naturally, it must end with me.
No...
Return my true body!
Give me back my body!
Master...
Little Demon, I know I was wrong.
Spare me this once.
I will definitely change!
Master...
For the sake of our many years together,
please let me go.
Xun'er...
Why are you still here?
Brother Xiao Yan.
This time,
I must stay with you.
You...
Stand behind me.
I have lived my life without disciples or sons,
alone in solitude.
From beginning to end,
you have been the one closest to me.
Even if you eventually backslash me,
I do not hate you.
But I hate you!
Die!
Old thing!
You've been fooled again!
You've been tricked once more!
This appearance...
is just like that day.
Little Demon,
follow me.
Together,
we will dissipate forever
between heaven and earth.
No!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Demon Saint Senior...
Go well.
Brother Xiao Yan,
look.
This is...
The source of the Demon Flame.
This Pure Lotus Demon Fire...
seems different from before.
The Demon Saint Senior erased its memories
and even its spiritual intellect.
The Demon Flame now
is as pure as a newborn.
What now?
Now that the space channel has dispersed,
with our current abilities,
we likely cannot tear apart
this space.
Since we can't get out,
then I shall refine the Demon Flame
right here.
Does Brother Xiao Yan have confidence?
Less than fifty percent.
It can't be helped.
If we took the source of the Demon Flame out,
it would surely invite the covetousness
of countless people.
Even if we fled to the Gu Clan for refuge,
it would bring great trouble.
And this space was hand-crafted
by the Demon Saint himself;
almost no one can break in.
It is the perfect location
to refine the Demon Flame.
Besides, we can't leave for a long while.
Perhaps some will assume we met with misfortune.
That would save us quite a bit of trouble.
Miss...
We're finished.
We actually left the Miss behind.
If we return to the Gu Clan like this,
I dread to think what kind of scolding we'll face.
Elder,
do not blame yourself.
Xun'er insisted on staying with Xiao Yan.
Even if we reacted in time, it would have been useless.
The Gu Clan has suffered a great loss this time.
Just two youngsters...
Is it worth such a fuss?
Having missed the Pure Lotus Demon Flame this time,
I hope the Palace Master will carefully consider
how to report back to the Clan Leader.
In the meantime,
don't let the Tianfu Alliance live too comfortably.
Well?
Any news?
Negative.
That place has the seals of the Pure Lotus Demon Saint.
I cannot sense their location.
However,
Elder Gu need not worry.
With Sister Xun'er and Xiao Yan together,
nothing untoward will happen.
Otherwise,
Xiao Yan would go utterly mad.
The Dragon Seal
would not remain so calm either.
Then I must trouble Lady Ziyan to keep watching for us.
Now that this has happened,
I must return to the Gu Clan immediately
to report this matter.
Rest assured.
I have people monitoring this area.
At the first sign of trouble,
we will notify the Gu Clan.
Many thanks.
Brother Xiao Yan,
are you ready?
This formation is the Blazing Cold Grand Array.
It can suppress the Demon Flame to some extent.
Xun'er,
I am about to begin refining the Demon Flame.
It's working.
Brother Xiao Yan...
For this day,
I have strived for so many years.
This little pain
cannot stop me.
Burn!
Refine for me!
If this continues,
Brother Xiao Yan is certain to die.
Xun'er...
You...
Brother Xiao Yan,
this time,
Xun'er will help you.
Together, we will refine it.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™