Under the combined eruption of the seven Dou Saints,
the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame was finally sealed.
And with it, the fragile agreement between Xiao Yan and the various factions vanished.
The scramble for the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame officially began.
In the chaos,
Xiao Yan defeated Hun Feng and successfully seized the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame.
But then...
the Hall Chief of the Soul Hall, Hun Mie Sheng, suddenly struck.
Yet that was exactly what Xiao Yan had been waiting for.
A destructive fire lotus
had been ready for a long time.
Xiao Yan!
Brother Xiao Yan!
This brat actually wants to take me down with him!
he fused Heavenly Flame is indeed powerful.
but with Xiao Yan’s own strength...
there’s no way he can kill the Hall Chief.
Brother Xiao Yan!
Are you hurt?
I’m fine.
Sorry for worrying everyone.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?!
If you’d been caught in that blast,
the fire lotus would’ve destroyed you too!
Thank you.
Unfortunately...
that still wasn’t enough to finish him.
As expected of the one who’s repeatedly foiled my Soul Hall.
You want a fight?
I’ll gladly oblige.
You all thought you’d figured out my true strength when we teamed up earlier.
If that were really the case...
then right now,
it’s time to give you all a little surprise.
Five-star Dou Saint...
That old ghost actually tricked us all!
He’s been hiding his real strength this whole time!
Hun Mie Sheng...
You’ve reached five-star Dou Saint and still dare to act?
Do you intend to trample the ancient clans’ agreement underfoot?
I’ve merely taken half a step into that realm.
It can hardly be considered breaking the agreement.
Hand over the origin of the demonic flame.
In your dreams!
The Taixu Ancient Dragon may be powerful,
but challenging this Hall Chief...
is still far too naive.
Sealing the demonic flame consumed too much energy.
Even if we join forces now,
I’m afraid we still can’t deal with him.
Today,
this Hall Chief will not let you escape.
Be careful!
Stay out of my way!
Brat...
Prepare to die!
My descendant...
is not someone you can kill on a whim.
Ancestor Xiao Chen!
You’ve broken the fire slave imprint?
While the demonic flame was sealed,
I took the time to erase it.
Ancestor...
You’re from the Xiao Clan?
Soul Clan vermin,
cease your barking.
Mid five-star...
Ancestor... he actually...
Who exactly are you?
If you truly belong to the Xiao Clan,
the Soul Clan should have some information on you.
Enough of your nonsense!
Not good...
Heaven-Splitting Three Axes!
Soul Burial Shield!
Ancestor Xiao Chen’s strength is actually this terrifying...
No wonder he could last so long in the illusion realm.
You’re quite tough.
Old Demon,
you’ve been watching the show long enough.
Time to make your move, no?
And the Soul Clan as well...
Hun Mie Sheng,
you’ve truly disappointed this old man.
Soul Demon Elder...
The Soul Clan actually sent you out here.
Are you truly intent on tearing all ties with the ancient clans?
Ridiculous.
In front of the origin of the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame, what are you all worth?
I knew it.
Your Soul Clan would never play by the rules.
This aura...
Ox...
Disciple greets the Old Ancestor.
You’re Little Mo, right?
It’s been many years.
You’ve become a Dou Saint now.
It’s all thanks to the guidance you gave me back then, Old Ancestor.
Only then was I able to break through.
Old monster from the Little Pill Tower...
You still love putting on this mysterious act.
If the Soul Clan had followed the rules,
I wouldn’t have needed to show myself.
The origin of the demonic flame...
belongs to my Soul Clan now.
You’d best stay out of it.
Otherwise, our Clan Chief
won’t mind claiming that peak nine-grade Mystic Pill of yours.
He’s had his eye on me for more than a day or two.
But if I deliver myself to his mouth,
would he even dare to take a bite?
The Xiao Clan really is like a centipede—
still wriggling even after it’s dead.
Blood Axe Xiao Chen actually managed to survive until now.
That’s quite something to celebrate.
Blood Axe Xiao Chen...
It’s actually him.
Truly...
it’s been a long time.
Alright.
Now is not the time for catching up.
Xiao Yan,
hand over the origin of the demonic flame.
This aura...
It’s the senior who saved me from Hun Mie Sheng earlier.
Old Ancestor,
catch!
I’ll hold onto it for you.
Spatial Shift!
Six-star Dou Saint...
The Little Pill Tower actually has a six-star Dou Saint!
No wonder my Soul Hall’s repeated attempts to move against the Pill Tower
were always stopped by the clan.
An expert of this level
is extremely rare even within our own clan.
Pure Lotus Demonic Flame,
you allowed yourself to be sealed on purpose,
just to watch us fight among ourselves
so you could reap the benefits in the end, right?
You hid yourself well,
but you can’t hide from me.
Come out!
If you refuse to show yourself willingly,
then I’ll have to force you out.
Old monster,
you’ve ruined my plans again.
Are you looking to die?
This guy...
really did let himself get sealed on purpose.
Pure Lotus Demonic Flame,
your nature is violent and cruel.
If we let you enter the Central Plains,
you would bring endless slaughter.
That’s why
the Pure Lotus Demonic Saint chose to seal you back then.
You
cannot leave this place.
Don’t mention that old bastard!
I accompanied him for over a thousand years.
Even if I had no merits, I still suffered hardships.
And yet he still wanted to seal me!
Serves him right that he got devoured in return!
As for whether I can leave today...
that’s not for you to decide.
Demonic Flame Divine Statue!
Die!
Everyone, be careful!
What’s happening?
All of you, go to hell!
Pill Melting Heaven!
It can actually melt demonic flame...
Today, anyone who dares to stop me from escaping
will be refined alive by me!
And you—
this old ghost whose true form is a pill...
I’d like to see what you turn into after I refine you.
Refining Heaven Ancient Array!
Appear!
This grand sealing array personally set up by the Pure Lotus Demonic Saint
has ultimately been deciphered by me.
Now it serves me.
Inside this demonic flame space,
who can possibly stand against me?
Not good...
His aura is surging wildly!
Retreat, quickly!
The passage won’t open!
This demonic flame space was created by the Pure Lotus Demonic Saint,
the one said to be closest to Dou Di.
A space built by such a supreme expert
is not something anyone can open a passage through at will.
I will refine every last one of you into my fire slaves!
What do we do?
How about we join forces?
The Heaven-Refining Grand Array is divided into two sides—heaven and earth.
We’ll handle the Heaven Array.
You all take the Earth Array.
Follow me!
Everyone,
attack with me!
Let’s go too!
Youngster,
lend me your body for a moment.
Otherwise today,
none of you will escape death.
How dare an ant try to stop a chariot!
Refining Heaven Ancient Array!
Refine the heavens into slaves!
Attack together!
Kid,
hand over your body to me now!
Once the Refining Heaven Ancient Array is fully activated,
you will have no path to survival.
Even if it’s for the lives of the people beside you,
trust this old man just this once.
Struggling in vain.
Although I hate that guy with every fiber of my being,
if even the grand array he set up could be casually broken by you third-rate amateurs,
would I have been trapped here for thousands of years?
A thousand years...
It’s finally coming to an end.
Pure Lotus Demonic Saint...
Do you really think this can destroy me?
I am a divine entity of heaven and earth.
Heaven and earth themselves protect me.
He’s still alive?
How is that possible?
Xiao Yan!
Brother Xiao Yan!
Pure Lotus Demonic Flame...
It’s not the Pure Lotus Demonic Flame.
He is...
the Pure Lotus Demonic Saint!
Little demon...
Long time no see.