After Xiao Yan subdued the Pure Lotus Demon Flame,
he left the Demon Flame Space with Xun Er.
Concerned for his companions, he rushed back to the Tianfu Alliance.
Meanwhile, the Alliance received a challenge letter for a final battle from the Soul Hall.
Yao Lao worried their strength was insufficient to withstand the assault.
But Xiao Yan's return...
not only filled the void in their battle power...
but also ignited everyone's fighting spirit to protect Central Plains.
News of the decisive battle spread throughout Central Plains.
All major powers focused their gaze on the Dipping Fallen Peak.
In this showdown between the Tianfu Alliance and the Soul Hall...
who will become the overlord of Central Plains?
Pray that the Tianfu Alliance wins.
So Central Plains no longer has to live under the shadow of the Soul Hall.
You really are alive.
Much obliged for the Hall Master's concern.
Not only did I not die...
but I conveniently refined the Pure Lotus Demon Flame.
Never expected that the Xiao Clan could still produce someone comparable to Xiao Xuan.
But the Soul Clan made Xiao Xuan fall...
and as for you...
the result will be the same.
This battle today...
if your Tianfu Alliance loses...
it will be utter doom.
Xiao Yan, do you dare to accept?
Bring it on!
It is time to settle the grudges of these years.
What are the rules of this challenge?
Best of three.
Three fighters each.
A fight to the death.
Of course...
if you wish for a full-scale war, this Hall Master won't object.
The Soul Hall has stood in Central Plains for so many years...
it is not something you can resist just by cobbling together some alliances.
If we truly engage in an all-out war...
even if the Tianfu Alliance is annihilated...
your Soul Hall will be crippled by eighty or ninety percent.
Seems the Soul Clan is reluctant to bear such losses.
Choose between the two options.
Best of three...
accommodating your wish is a fine virtue.
Send forth your combatants.
These years...
the greatest challenge my Soul Clan has faced is this.
Xiao Clan whelp...
count me as one of your three.
Xiao Chen.
The Soul Clan's dogs are still skulking in the shadows.
Worthy of the Bloody Axe Xiao Chen.
Even after all these years, you remain this barbaric.
Hun Qian Mo...
you trash who begged for mercy before our Clan Chief...
still have the face to show yourself?
No matter how formidable he was, he ultimately fell.
The victor is king.
The current Soul Clan...
still stands atop this continent.
And what of Xiao Xuan?
The name of the Clan Chief...
is not for ants like you to utter.
Xiao Chen...
even if you survived luckily until now...
the current you...
is no match for the Bloody Axe Xiao Chen of old.
The current you is no match for this old man.
The aura of Xiao Xuan...
let this old man serve as the vanguard.
Xiao Yan.
My three warriors are ready.
It is your turn.
Hun Qian Mo's strength is around 6-star...
none of us can contend with him.
Six-star Dou Sheng...
Such a lively gathering...
how could this old ancestor be missing?
What is that?
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
So many people...
Old Ancestor...
Greetings, Senior.
Enough.
Old ghost of the Dan Tower...
leave this old immortal to me.
Old ghost...
in the past, for your sake...
my Soul Clan did not move against the Dan Tower.
For you to do this now...
is unwise.
Now, the Dan Tower is a member of the Tianfu Alliance.
Shared glory...
shared loss.
As a Guardian of the Dan Tower...
this old ancestor naturally cannot stay out of it.
It seems you are determined...
to oppose my Soul Clan to the bitter end.
Less talk, more action.
Take this!
Old ghost...
the space outside is too cramped.
Dare to enter?
Why would I fear you?
Worthy of an old ghost who survived in the Soul Clan for so long.
You still have some guts.
Old thing...
you have sabotaged my Soul Clan's plans time and again.
Today, I will finish you off!
Explode!
Old Ancestor...
to think you could fight Elder Qian Mo to a standstill.
With this old ghost interfering...
Hall Master, this might end in a loss for us.
Mo'er, just watch the others for me.
Leave Xiao Yan to me.
I know what I am doing.
Hungry for so long...
it is time to come out and eat.
Retreat quickly!
Senior...
Old ghost...
save your breath and prepare your final words.
In these thousand years, your strength hasn't grown...
but your lip service has improved greatly.
Can't even stand steadily...
still daring to talk tough?
Senior, leave the rest to us.
Please, go rest.
Very well, I leave it to you.
Old Ancestor...
How should we judge this round?
Don't be ungrateful.
With this old thing interfering...
achieving a draw is already quite good.
Consider yourselves lucky.
We'll call it a draw.
Hun Mo Old Ghost...
get out here!
Bloody Axe Xiao Chen...
I will deal with you, this outdated fellow.
Outdated or not...
we'll know after exchanging blows.
Earth-Splitting Slash!
Is this all you've got?
You've completely disgraced the prestige Xiao Xuan earned.
Shatter!
Sky Demon Blood Gu!
Soul Gu Toad!
This Hun Mo Old Man's methods are truly vicious.
Go!
Die!
Has it all ended?
Xiao Chen, you can go rest...
I will handle the Xiao Clan's affairs.
Big brother...
didn't you say that possessing strength allows one to protect everything?
I have been chasing after you...
wanting to stand tall and upright just like you.
Who knew fate would play tricks...
leaving me stubborn and alone.
Ancestor...
if this is Heaven's trial...
given to the Xiao Clan...
then let me pay any price...
to guard the Xiao Clan.
Late Five-star Dou Sheng.
Heaven-Cleaving Slash!
Slash the Heavens!
Ancestor...
are you alright?
I am fine.
Another draw.
Next...
we can only rely on you.
Another draw...
Elder Hun Mo really overestimated himself this time.
This old man said long ago...
that a direct full-scale war would be simpler.
Now, you are stuck in a dilemma.
If you truly lose...
let's see how you explain it to the Clan.
The Soul Hall is a crucial part of the Clan's plan...
it should not be used to clash head-on like this.
Hurry and prepare.
That brat is very cunning...
and now he possesses the Pure Lotus Demon Flame.
Do not capsize in the gutter.
Pure Lotus Demon Flame...
this Hall Master is quite curious to see it.
In his hands...
how much power can it display?
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™