(Adapted from the Qidian novel "Dou Po Cang Qiong"
by Tian Can Tu Dou)
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors should watch only with
guardian permission)
(All content in this film is
computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
- BATTLE THROUGH THE HEAVENS -
- REINCARNATION OF A HUNDRED LIVES -
♪Karma is unraveled♪
♪Bodhi dispels confusion♪
♪Love and hate fade away♪
♪Heaven and earth are mine♪
♪Joy and sorrow intertwine♪
♪Reincarnation surges on♪
♪Reason for immortality♪
♪Remold the veins♪
♪No longer a trapped beast of fate♪
♪Seeking alone♪
♪Holding destiny's end♪
♪Who guards his spark, dares to shake the sky♪
♪Battle stirs the clouds♪
♪Thunder crowns me in the nine heavens♪
♪Right or wrong, I command victory or defeat♪
♪In a thought, the world shifts♪
♪I have reached the highest peak♪
♪My palm transforms the land♪
♪In a snap, in a wave♪
EPISODE 174
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Xiao Yan faces Ancestor Huo Yun,
who suffers from an old illness)
(He promises to help,
whether they form an alliance or not)
(He will lend a hand regardless)
(His righteous act moves Ancestor Huo Yun)
(Ancestor Huo Yun agrees to the alliance)
(But Immortal Qing of the Flower Sect,
due to old matters with Medicine Elder)
(Holds a prejudice)
(So Flower Sect's alliance remains uncertain)
(It is still unknown)
(Now, winning over Alchemist Tower
is crucial)
(It is of utmost importance)
(But most elders of Alchemist Tower
are stubborn)
(Xiao Yan must defeat Old Eccentric Hou
in the elder election)
(To secure the key vote)
(And persuade Alchemist Tower to ally)
He really dares to compete
with Old Eccentric Hou
Xiao Yan is Medicine Elder's disciple
Champion of this Pill Gathering
He must have some skill
So young
Even as Pill Gathering champion
He may not beat Old Eccentric Hou
Medicine Elder
Today I'll make an example
of your fine disciple
Watch closely
Alchemy is no place for your
tricks and shortcuts
(The elder seat in Inner Dan Ta)
(Is essential for the alliance)
(Xiao Yan)
(You must win)
Competition rules
I won't repeat them
Inner Dan Ta's mountains of herbs
Both of you may take as you wish
(Such a vast store of herbs)
(Inner Dan Ta is like another pill world)
Youngsters who've never seen the world
Are you both ready
Then let's begin
After all these years, you're still
the reliable old guy
Ignite the fire
Youngster
Watch and learn
This is...
There are actually four Heavenly Flames
He can even fuse them
(This is all show, no substance)
Forming cauldron with Heavenly Flame
Xiao Yan's fire control is impressive
He learned all that flashy nonsense
from Medicine Elder
Not following the rules
He'll get burned playing with fire
It's been nearly twenty years since
Old Eccentric Hou went all out
He once summoned Eight-Colored Pill Lightning
He might summon Nine-Colored Pill Lightning now
Nine-Colored Pill Lightning
At this level of competition
The pill formula is crucial
Old Eccentric Hou even collected rare
Ninth-Grade Pill Formulas
He has several scrolls
So many Ninth-Grade Pill Formulas
(I couldn't refine Ninth Grade Pills before)
(I only left Xiao Yan two Ninth-Grade Formulas)
(Both are the lowest grade)
(They probably won't help much)
The heat is just right
Bodhi Seed
Xiao Yan plans to refine a Bodhi Pill
Even if he perfects the Bodhi Pill
It'll be hard to win
What is Xiao Yan doing
So many herbs
What's going on
The quality of these herbs
Is as good as Inner Dan Ta's
He's using more herbs than needed
for a Bodhi Pill
Is he not making a Bodhi Pill
But most of these herbs
Have similar effects to the Bodhi Pill
He must have a plan
The herbs Xiao Yan uses
Aren't from either of my two formulas
Hope he found another formula
Hope he's not just messing around
(For decades)
(I've stayed in Inner Dan Ta)
(Never left)
(Studying pill formulas day and night)
(With only one thought in mind)
(Medicine Elder)
(Luckily, you're still alive)
(So I have a chance to defeat you)
Medicine Elder
Today I will defeat your fine disciple
And show you the true path of alchemy
Details are the key to alchemical success
Forming cauldron with Heavenly Flame
All show, no substance
Double the herbs
Too ambitious
Top-heavy, unstable
A complete and utter failure
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Old Eccentric Hou should achieve Core Formation
within three days.
If I'm not mistaken,
he's refining the Flame Demon Clear Mysterious Pill
this time.
Once he succeeds,
it will surely attract Nine-Colored Pill Lightning.
His alchemy skills over the years
have improved a lot.
Xiao Yan, on the other hand, is calm and composed.
Using twice the amount of ingredients to refine pills
is no easy feat.
He failed several times these days,
probably just now grasping how to balance the medicinal power.
But no matter how many ingredients he uses,
the Bodhi Pill can't reach Ninth Grade.
What is he...
What exactly is Xiao Yan doing?
Why can't I sense any pill fluctuations?
The youngster is just putting on a show.
Maybe he just doesn't want to lose too badly.
Looks like Hou Qing has a high chance of winning.
(All these years,)
(very few people have ever puzzled me.)
(But this Xiao Yan...)
(Right now...)
(Excuses like "the formula is obscure")
(or "not enough soul power")
(are all just excuses.)
(As long as I act,)
(there's no pill I can't refine.)
(I remember back then...)
(when Yao Chen forcibly boosted pill quality)
(and took the championship at the Pill Gathering,)
(members of the Alchemist Tower all started imitating him,)
(trying to take shortcuts.)
(The depth of alchemy)
(can't be overturned by shortcuts.)
(The formula is the foundation of alchemy.)
(The precise timing and ingredients)
(once set,)
(must not be changed.)
(The more you stick to the formula,)
(the more you appreciate its wonders.)
(Pills made step by step like this)
(are true quality pills.)
Look, Nine-Colored Pill Lightning!
The winner this time
is surely Old Eccentric Hou.
Yao Chen.
This time, I have won.
Not necessarily.
Boasting with words
won't do you any good.
Each ingredient has its own traits.
Only by categorizing them
and refining carefully
can you extract the strongest medicinal power.
And produce the highest quality pills.
(This kid really is something different.)
Just playing tricks.
What's that?
Not good!
My Flame Demon Clear Mysterious Pill!
What are you doing?
Can't delay any longer.
Core Formation!
Fire Dragon Pill Condensation!
Material Formation with Fire!
Pill Hidden in Material!
It's the Object-Forming Pill-Concealing Method!
Medicine Elder,
did you teach him this too?
Object-Forming Pill-Concealing Method
is extremely demanding on fire control and soul power.
Even I,
wouldn't dare use this method when refining pills.
Xiao Yan...
He mastered it on his own.
Someone with such pill refining skill
is one of less than five in Inner Dan Ta.
Yao Chen's disciple
is truly remarkable.
It's actually Black Demon Lightning!
Haven't seen that in years.
Go!
Dread Golem!
Hold on!
Break!
Black Demon Lightning!
Xiao Yan actually dares to face Black Demon Lightning head-on.
Xiao Yan has early One-Star Saint of Battle Qi strength.
Handling one Black Demon Lightning shouldn't be too hard.
Xiao Yan is about to win.
Doesn't that mean...
So what if he wins?
Our Alchemist Tower has always kept neutral rules.
That's right.
Neutrality is the foundation of the Alchemist Tower.
Tower rules, tower rules...
No tower, no rules.
If the tower is gone,
what rules are left to talk about?
The Alchemical Thunder drawn by Ninth Grade Pills
is truly formidable.
Such a terrifying energy storm didn't harm him at all.
No wonder he's a Saint of Battle Qi.
What's that?
Humanoid.
Interesting.
Is this the Nine-Grade Treasure Pill?
It even mimics my appearance.
You think I'll let you go because of that?
This kid...
actually succeeded in refining it.
But I don't know what pill he made.
I can't recognize it either.
It just has a hint of Bodhi Pill's aura.
But its power is several times stronger than the Bodhi Pill.
You two,
please announce the pills you refined.
Flame Demon Clear Mysterious Pill.
Eight-Grade Pill with Nine-Colored Pill Lightning.
If someone with fire attribute Fight Qi takes it,
it will cause their Fight Qi to mutate,
thus boosting their combat power.
Great Bodhi Restoration Pill.
Nine-Grade Treasure Pill.
It doubles the success rate
of breaking through to Half-Saint.
Double?
How is that possible?
I've never heard of such a formula.
The energy in this pill is truly terrifying.
Just as Xiao Yan said,
the effect of this Great Bodhi Restoration Pill
far surpasses the Flame Demon Clear Mysterious Pill.
I announce
the winner of this selection is
Xiao Yan.
Thank you, Great Elder Lin.
From today on,
you are an elder of Inner Dan Ta.
Reckless fellow.
Just refining a pill,
yet you risked your life against Black Demon Lightning.
Even more daring than me.
Forget it, forget it.
Teacher
What did you say to Old Eccentric Hou?
Yao Chen
Let me find a worthy disciple first
Then I'll come back to challenge you again
Want to uncover the ultimate secret
of reaching the Fight God realm?
Scan the code to follow the Dou Po Cang Qiong account
Get the latest updates and exclusive news
about the animation
The legend ahead awaits your passion
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Borrow tonight's moonlight, look back
on the road at dawn♪
♪Forgetting the moon waxes and wanes♪
♪And the sun I can't let go of♪
♪Shadows stretch out unreasonably♪
♪The cheapest luxury is hope♪
♪Nothing beats everlasting time♪
♪Watching myself like a child♪
♪Running, laughing, playing around♪
♪Borrow a few nights to finish my dreams♪
♪Borrow a few candles to light up day and night♪
♪Under flickering light and shadow♪
♪I keep tangling with my past♪
♪Making the present so awkward♪
♪Backwards, forwards, not knowing where to go♪
♪The present and the past keep washing over♪
♪I'm the most stubborn one♪
♪And also the most naive♪
♪Let this light guide the long road ahead♪
♪The past can't be chased, twists and turns abound♪
♪In the end, watchful eyes fall on me♪
♪Let my heart sprout and grow in hope♪
♪A hundred lifetimes can't match this moment♪
♪Familiar scenes♪
(Next episode preview)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™