(Adapted from the Qidian novel "Battle Through the Heavens" by Heavenly Silkworm Potato)
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, please watch only with guardian's permission)
(Adapted from the Qidian novel "Battle Through the Heavens" by Heavenly Silkworm Potato)
Episode 172
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(During Xiao Yan's seclusion)
(Tianming Laoyao leads the Nether River Alliance to besiege the city)
(Yao Chen leads the group to confront the enemy)
(Nether River Alliance boasts with Soul Hall's Heavenly Venerable's support)
(Vows to destroy Starfall Pavilion)
(And capture Xiao Yan alive)
(Outnumbered and outmatched)
(Yao Chen forcibly opens the soul space)
(Trying to block the powerful foes)
(But is ultimately defeated)
(Facing the fierce assault of Nether River Alliance)
(Starfall Pavilion retreats step by step)
(Many disciples are killed or wounded)
(At a critical moment)
(Xiao Yan ascends to Saint of Battle Qi and emerges in time)
(The tide of battle turns instantly)
The scenery in the astral realm is nice
Being buried here
Isn't a bad resting place
Two years ago, this kid was just at the peak of Nine-turn Dou Zun
Now he's broken through to Saint of Battle Qi
We must eliminate him quickly
Do it
Ten Thousand Souls Heavenly Lock
Go die
Xiao Yan
Tianming Laoyao
Why are you still standing there
Little demons
Come out, all of you
Today you'll feast well
What Fight Technique is this
My hand
This move
Is called Buddha's Wrathful Samsara
Help me, quick
Tianming Laoyao
Don't worry
Soul Hall will avenge you
Jerk
Xiao Yan
Spare me
From now on, Tianming Sect will submit to you
Too late
Since you want to wipe us out
Then let's perish together
Half-Saint Self-Detonation
Everyone, form a defensive array
This lunatic
Young Pavilion Master
The Young Pavilion Master protected Starfall Pavilion
Xiao Yan
Starfall Pavilion is safe
We're saved
I've finally been saved
We survived
Old monster
Get out here
Soul attack
My spirit
Just now
That was possession
Thank you, Young Pavilion Master, for saving us
Defeated a Half-Saint in one move
Even the soul couldn't escape
Retreat, quickly
Did I say you could leave
What are you going to do
Gu You
You
It's your turn
You finally made a move
Useless fool
So many lost to a mere Xiao clan junior
Saint of Battle Qi from the Soul Clan
Thank you for saving me
Xiao Yan
So what if you sealed this space
My Soul Clan has countless Saints of Battle Qi
You can't keep me here
Go, quickly
Hurry, go
Stay here forever
Xiao clan junior, don't be arrogant
So what if you're a mere one-star Saint of Battle Qi
You'll end up a prisoner of my Soul Clan
Did you forget your father is still in our hands
If you dare, don't leave
If you want to save your father
Come to the Soul Realm
I'll be waiting for you
That place
I'll go there sooner or later
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Everyone, hold on
Even if we die
We must defend Starfall Pavilion
Yes
I came too late
If they hadn't fought to protect the array
And resisted the Nether River Alliance
We wouldn't have lasted until you emerged
Tianming Sect, Ice River Valley, Wind Thunder Pavilion
Killed so many of us
I will make them pay
(Han Family, Tianbei City)
Father
Han Fei
Come back with me quietly
Even if the Han family dies in battle
We won't just let others slaughter us
Or be used as bargaining chips
- Great-grandfather
This is outrageous
Move quickly
Seize the hostages now
To restrain that Xiao Yan kid
Yes
Will you come yourselves
Or should I do it
Sister
Wishful thinking
(North Wind Thunder Pavilion)
Keep a close watch on the Han family
Starfall Pavilion could come cause trouble
at any moment.
Yes.
Where are they?
Who do you mean?
Come out right now!
Wind and Thunder Pavilion.
Are you trying to get your Pavilion
destroyed even faster?
Saint of Battle Qi.
Darn it.
Xiao Yan.
Don't act rashly.
The Han family is in my hands.
Aren't you afraid for their lives?
Are you threatening me?
The Nether River Alliance is led
by Tianming Sect.
Wind and Thunder Pavilion
was barely involved.
If you let us go,
from now on,
Wind and Thunder Pavilion will
cut all ties with Starfall Pavilion.
We’ll stay out of each other's way.
Tianming Sect’s affairs
are none of your concern.
These past two years,
Wind and Thunder Pavilion abused
its power.
You harassed Starfall Pavilion
again and again.
You falsely accused me of stealing
Three Thousand Thunder Motion.
You used your sect’s grand array
against a junior like me.
I could tolerate all that.
But you killed my companions
and took my friends hostage.
That I cannot forgive.
Fei Tian.
Twenty-eight brothers of Starfall Pavilion
died by your hands.
Today,
you will pay for your blood debts.
Xiao Yan.
Wind and Thunder Pavilion is allied
with the Celestial Demon Phoenix Clan.
If you destroy Wind and Thunder Pavilion,
the Celestial Demon Phoenix Clan
won’t spare you.
Celestial Demon Phoenix Clan?
Are they really that powerful?
Xiao Yan.
I’ve planted Thunder Marks
inside the Han family.
With just a squeeze of my hand,
the Han family will die
from self-detonation.
Let’s see if you can save them
faster than
my hand can kill them.
Senior Sister.
I’ve dragged you all into this.
Sorry.
Even without you,
Wind and Thunder Pavilion
would still torment the Han family.
Don’t blame yourself.
How are the others?
Great-grandfather is very old.
And his injuries are severe.
He needs more time to recover.
Take these pills to help
Elder Han heal.
Thank you.
Thank you, Xiao Yan, for saving us.
I was in seclusion for two years.
I never thought my past actions
would implicate you all.
I didn’t think it through.
After today,
there will be no Wind and Thunder Pavilion
in the Northern Region.
If the Han family is interested,
you can take their place.
Starfall Pavilion will fully support you.
The Han family doesn’t seek domination.
We just want to live peacefully
in the Northern Region.
Since Xiao Yan wishes to help,
we’ll follow your arrangements.
Xiao Yan.
Thank you.
Now we owe you a huge favor.
No need to be so polite, Senior Sister.
Tianming Sect, Ice River Valley—
You’re next.
Want to uncover the ultimate secret
to reaching Fight God?
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™