Episode 196
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
The Stone Clan's mysterious disappearance
has thrown the ancient clans into a panic.
The Thunder, Flame, and Medicine Clans allied for survival
and targeted the Ancient Clan and Hun Zu.
At this moment,
Hun Zu's Six-Star Dou Sheng Hun Qian Mo arrived at Soul Hall,
to help Hun Mie Sheng destroy the Celestial Alliance.
Hun Zu's declaration of war has arrived.
The Celestial Alliance is in grave danger.
Three days hence, atop Fallen Mountain,
shall be the final battlefield for survival.
Within the Demon Flame Space,
Though Xiao Yan mastered the Pure Lotus Demon Flame
and condensed the Fire Spirit Xiao Yi,
but whether this unprecedented power
can truly help the Alliance turn the tide remains to be seen.
At this pace, we will reach the Alliance in half a day.
Then let us make haste.
This way, this way.
Coming.
Put this one here.
Hold it steady.
Everyone, move faster.
Do not slack off.
Once we deliver these Demon Flame Stones tomorrow,
we can be promoted to the Inner Alliance.
Yes!
Hey, slow down, slow down.
Give me a hand.
Go, go.
Careful!
My foot is pinned under here.
Over here.
Where are you rushing those Demon Flame Stones?
Soul Hall.
You fools of the Celestial Alliance,
mining Demon Flame Stones on Soul Hall territory...
You seek your own demise.
Today,
your heads and the stones shall remain here.
In your dreams!
We are dead either way.
Fight them to the death!
Right!
Attack!
Yes!
Quickly!
Form a defensive array!
Kill!
Retreat!
Kill them all!
Hang up their heads.
Send them to the Celestial Alliance.
Hang the heads.
Soul Hall has quite the audacity now.
Retreat!
Has Soul Hall's reach extended this far?
Who... who are you?
You killed so many people,
and think you can just leave?
The Alliance's people are not easily slain.
(Such terrifying power...)
Are you all right?
Thank you, Senior, for saving us.
We are Xuan Squad, Outer Third Division of the Celestial Alliance.
We were tasked with mining Demon Flame Stones.
We shall never forget your saving grace.
- Thank you, Senior.
Thank you.
Outer Alliance...
The Celestial Alliance has grown significantly.
Tend to the wounded first.
Please distribute these elixirs among them.
Yes, Senior.
Thank you, Senior.
(Extraordinary strength.)
(And so generous.)
(Who exactly is this Senior?)
Is it not enough?
I have more.
No, no, no.
These elixirs are more than enough.
Thank you for bestowing these elixirs.
Our brothers are out of danger now.
Soul Hall has a branch nearby.
It is guarded by a One-Star Dou Sheng.
They will sense the Guardian's death.
We had best depart at once.
Dou Sheng...
One-Star, you say?
You know the way, do you not?
Lead me there, if you would.
Lead the way...
What does he mean?
Where is he?
Where is the Captain?
Captain!
Where have you been?
What happened?
He... with but a single move,
a mere flick of his finger,
wiped out the entire branch hall.
Who... who in the heavens is this Senior?
Return and find your regional commander.
From this day forth,
you shall be Earth-Rank members of the Inner Alliance.
Tell him
that Xiao Yan sent you.
Xiao... Xiao Yan?
Young Alliance Master Xiao!
Xiao Yan...
Is it truly him?
Young Alliance Master!
You are the Young Alliance Master!
Tell me
what occurred in Central Province since the Demon Flame Space closed.
Yes, Senior.
After the Demon Flame Space closed,
the powers of Central Province were reshuffled.
The Stone Clan and Spirit Clan vanished suddenly.
(The Stone Clan disappeared inexplicably.)
(Who is the hidden hand behind this?)
(And what is their purpose?)
Brother Xiao Yan.
With the Stone Clan and Spirit Clan gone,
and the three clans suddenly forming an alliance,
the Ancient Clan must have felt the impact too.
So I must return and see for myself.
Indeed.
Go see what troubles the Ancient Clan faces.
Take care on the road.
If you need anything, send word at once.
Brother Xiao Yan, you must take care as well.
Once my affairs are settled, I shall come find you.
(Two years have passed.)
(The Celestial Alliance has risen to prominence.)
(I wonder if Master and the others are well.)
In this coming battle at Fallen Peak,
Hun Zu dispatched many warriors to aid Soul Hall.
The one we must be most wary of
is an elder of Hun Zu.
This man is known as
Hun Qian Mo.
A Six-Star Dou Sheng warrior.
It is said he once took part in the siege against Xiao Xuan.
Hun Qian Mo.
The ancient clans decreed that anyone above Four-Star Dou Sheng
is forbidden from intervening.
Will the Ancient Clan and the three-clan alliance just stand idle?
The ancient clans now fear for their survival,
dreading a repeat of the clans' disappearance.
In matters of the outside world,
they have no intention of getting involved.
Hun Zu sending out Hun Qian Mo this time
is likely meant to test their limits.
Indeed.
If this man truly intends to act,
we may have to ask the Ancestor to step in and hold him off.
But Soul Hall still has its Hall Master and Soul Demon Elder.
If even one of them breaks away,
they could temporarily pin down Senior Xiao Chen,
splitting the Alliance's strongest forces.
The other
could easily lead Soul Hall
in an attack on the Alliance's main base.
If Lady Zi Yan could come to our aid,
there might yet be a turning point.
Zi Yan would be an immense reinforcement,
but the Three Islands' forces are not fully uprooted.
She must guard East Dragon Island and cannot come to help us.
I can handle Soul Demon Elder,
but as for the Soul Hall Master...
Leave the Soul Hall Master to me.
Xiao Yan!
It is Young Alliance Master Xiao Yan!
He has returned!
He has finally returned!
You have all worked hard.
- The Young Alliance Master is back!
- Welcome home!
- Young Alliance Master!
I told you long ago this lad would not die so easily.
This time,
you ought to believe it, yes?
You truly succeeded.
You refined the Pure Lotus Demon Fire.
Mere good fortune.
What was once thought impossible for any man,
you have accomplished.
I never imagined you would truly succeed.
Together, we should be able to hold off the Soul Hall Master.
With his current strength,
facing the Soul Hall Master alone poses no problem.
Then we need not worry about the decisive battle.
By the way,
Cai Lin has not emerged since entering the Nine Nether Yellow Springs.
Qing Lin and I go to check on her from time to time.
She must have encountered some fortune in the depths of the Springs.
We can sense her presence,
but we cannot enter the depths of the Springs.
I never expected Cai Lin's seclusion would last this long.
It seems that once matters here at the Alliance are settled,
I must visit the Nine Nether Deep Ground Python Clan.
Over the years, against Soul Hall's relentless encroachment,
the Celestial Alliance retreated, defended, and fought with all its might.
From the very first battle,
every drop of sweat we have shed,
every drop of blood spilled has been for tomorrow,
so we might stand proudly atop Fallen Mountain
and tell Soul Hall:
If it is war you want,
then war you shall have!
War!
Soul Hall destroyed my home and tormented my father.
This hatred is carved into my very bones.
Not for a single day have I dared forget.
But I know well
that their cruelty against the Xiao family is but a microcosm.
What they seek is not the ruin of one house or one clan,
but to bring all of Central Province to its knees.
Today I come not as an avenger to call upon you,
but as your comrade, to implore you to fight by my side.
Drive out Soul Hall!
Defend Central Province! Drive out Soul Hall!
The decisive clash between Soul Hall and the Celestial Alliance,
along with Xiao Yan's return,
has reached all major powers at once.
It has drawn the gaze of all Central Province.
All wonder who shall have the last laugh,
becoming the sole overlord of Central Province.
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
I hear the Fallen Mountains once housed many clans of Magical Beasts.
Today, they have all cleared out completely.
With Soul Hall and the Celestial Alliance at war,
even the slightest collateral impact
would spell extinction for their clans.
Soul Hall is the overlord of Central Province.
Look!
The Soul Hall's forces have arrived.
Seven Dou Sheng masters deployed at once.
Xiao Yan and his allies are in grave trouble.
Why has the Celestial Alliance not yet arrived?
Could it be they have grown afraid?
Afraid?
The Celestial Alliance has never feared anyone.
Our Celestial Alliance has deployed ten Dou Sheng.
Wish to uncover the ultimate secret to reaching the realm of Fight God?
Scan to follow the Battle Through the Heavens account.
Get the latest animation updates and exclusive insider news.
The legend ahead shall be forged by your passion.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™