(Adapted from the Qidian novel "Dou Po Cang Qiong"
by Tian Can Tu Dou)
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, please watch with guardian's permission)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
- BATTLE THROUGH THE HEAVENS -
- HUNDRED LIFETIMES OF SAMSARA -
♪See Through Cause and Effect♪
♪Bodhi dispels confusion♪
♪Love and hate fade away♪
♪Heaven and earth are mine♪
♪Joy and sorrow intertwine♪
♪Samsara surges on♪
♪Reason for immortality♪
♪Recast meridians♪
♪No longer a trapped beast in samsara♪
♪Seeking alone♪
♪Holding fate's end in my hand♪
♪Who shields his spark, dares to shake the sky♪
♪Dou Po stirs the clouds♪
♪Thunder crowns me in the nine heavens♪
♪Don't ask right or wrong, I command victory♪
♪In a thought, the winds shift♪
♪I have reached the highest peak♪
♪My palm transforms the world♪
♪In a snap, in a wave♪
EPISODE 173
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(A One-Star Saint of Battle Qi, Xiao Yan, emerges)
(With his own Buddha's Wrathful Samsara)
(He incinerates all Half-Saint foes at once)
(Nether River Alliance's defeat)
(Spreads quickly across Central Plains)
(Xiao Yan leads troops to pursue the victory)
(He wipes out the Nether River Alliance)
(The fall of Nether River Alliance)
(Starfall Pavilion rises among
Wind and Thunder Pavilion, Sky Nether Sect, Ice River Hall)
(Wind and Thunder Pavilion, Sky Nether Sect)
(The Central Plains are in turmoil again)
(Ice River Hall)
(Meanwhile)
(Three alliance letters from Starfall Pavilion)
(Are quietly sent to three top powers)
(Xiao Yan knows only alliance)
(Alchemist Tower, Burning Flame Valley, Starfall Pavilion)
(Only together can they face Soul Hall)
(These three powers' choices)
(Flower Sect)
(Will decide if the alliance succeeds)
Starfall Pavilion, in just two years
Produced a Saint of Battle Qi
Is this your so-called countermeasure?
Hall Master
Things have come to this
Why get angry over a discarded pawn?
You have an idea
Xiao Yan must have obtained the Bodhi Core
That's how he became a Saint of Battle Qi
But his foundation is unstable
We can make him stop here
(Soul Hall Vice Hall Master, Three-Star Saint)
Make an example
It's not just Starfall Pavilion that can do this
Alliance
Still has to fight Soul Hall
Those freaks from Soul Hall are disgusting
But who wants to mess with them?
(Ancestor Huo Yun, One-Star Saint)
Let Starfall Pavilion's people leave
Ancestor
Soul Hall is watching us closely
I'm afraid one day
Father, please stop for now
Ancestor, calm down
Take care of your health
Be careful your hidden ailment worsens
Huo'er is the sensible one
Xiao Yan from Starfall Pavilion
Is a One-Star Saint of Battle Qi
Yes
And has ties with us
So young
How does he look?
If he's decent-looking
And willing to marry Huo'er
I'll agree
Ancestor, you...
You're not acting your age
Huo'er, don't be rude
To reach One-Star Saint at his age
Shows how outstanding he is
And you both like him
This young man is extraordinary
Ancestor
They said
If we join the alliance
They can cure your hidden ailment
What if we refuse?
If we refuse
I will personally help
To cure your internal problem
Young friend Xiao Yan
You're here
Ancestor
This is Xiao Yan from Starfall Pavilion
I am Xiao Yan
Greetings, Ancestor Huo Yun
You're not bad, kid
Without this
The alliance
Is off the table
Ancestor
What do you mean?
Let's form the alliance
I've been away for years
I wonder if anyone
Still remembers the name Ancestor Huo Yun
On behalf of Starfall Pavilion
I welcome Burning Flame Valley to the alliance
Good
See you at Starfall Pavilion
Soul Hall may attack again anytime
We must quickly repair the Sect-Protecting Array
Yes, Sect Leader
Teacher, are you alright?
I'm fine
Go check on the other sisters
Senior Sister
The urgent task
Everyone, go heal your injuries quickly
Yes
Medicine Elder
Sect Leader Yun
What happened?
Flower Sect's Sect-Protecting Array failed
Flower Sect was ambushed by Soul Hall
Luckily, the Grand Elder emerged in time
And repelled them
Slightly injured
But nothing serious
You all should recover quickly too
Thank you, Medicine Elder
No need to thank me
If Starfall Pavilion hadn't pushed for alliance
Soul Hall wouldn't have targeted us
That voice is...
(Immortal Qing, Half-Saint)
Greetings, Grand Elder
Immortal Qing
Yao Chen
He actually survived
Made such a mess
Hurry and clean up, send the guests off
Don't let others laugh at us
- Yes
Medicine Elder, we still have aftermath to handle
Sorry for the poor hospitality
It's fine
After all these years,
your temper hasn't changed a bit.
Medicine Elder,
who is Starfall Pavilion allying with?
That's none of my business.
But if Flower Sect gets involved,
don't blame me for being harsh with you.
Sorry.
Flower Sect suffered because of Starfall Pavilion.
But that was never our intention.
What's done is done.
Please, you should leave now.
I don't want Flower Sect to be destroyed.
Soul Hall failed this time,
but they'll surely attack again.
The Spirit Clan vanished mysteriously.
There must be a bigger plot behind Soul Hall.
You know the forces backing Soul Hall.
If I agree to join forces with you,
and something happens to Flower Sect,
I can't bear that responsibility.
Soul Hall is ruthless and cruel.
Their actions are unpredictable.
If Flower Sect joins the alliance,
the alliance will do everything
to protect every member.
Three days from now,
if I come,
it means Flower Sect agrees to ally.
If I don't show up,
then all of this
never happened.
I hope you'll come.
Burning Flame Valley has agreed to ally.
Now we just await replies from Flower Sect and Alchemist Tower.
Don't expect too much from Flower Sect.
Soul Hall's attack this time
has left them disheartened.
So now,
Alchemist Tower
is our key focus.
That's right.
Alchemist Tower hates Soul Hall deeply,
but they've always stayed neutral.
It's not easy to deal with.
Should we send another letter to test them?
We can't be hasty with this.
To persuade them,
Xiao Yan and I must go in person.
We'll look after things at Starfall Pavilion.
Everything's been settled for now.
There shouldn't be any trouble.
Brother Chen,
when do you plan to leave?
No time to waste.
We'll leave today.
It's been years since I came here.
Alchemist Tower is still so vibrant.
But thinking of the Inner Dan Ta Elder Court,
those stubborn old men,
it's hard to describe.
Inner Dan Ta—
Most people only know Alchemist Tower,
but Inner Dan Ta is its true core.
Alchemist Tower is different from Flower Sect
and Burning Flame Valley.
Alliance decisions depend on elder votes.
Since its founding,
Alchemist Tower has never meddled in others' affairs.
Even if the three giants help us win votes,
we must be ready to fail.
Soul Hall dominates Central Plains.
Their power far surpasses ours.
Only by bringing Alchemist Tower into the alliance
can we unite everyone against them.
No matter how hard it is,
I must give it a try.
Well said.
Old Medicine Elder,
you've been recovered for a while now.
Why only now did you come back to visit?
You know as well as I do,
the Elder Council doesn't like me.
You seem to have recovered well.
You've even reached Half-Saint.
A blessing in disguise.
Long time no see.
I'm only here because I need something.
How's the alliance going?
After receiving your letter,
I proposed the alliance to the Elder Court.
But those stubborn elders are hard to convince.
After much effort, I got four votes.
Including your three, that's only four.
That's not enough.
We need a majority of the eight seats.
Only then will it pass.
The Alchemist Tower Ancestor is absent now.
It's really tough.
The Ancestor is wandering the world again.
He's been missing for years.
If not for his soul jade slip being intact,
we'd think something happened to him.
Three days from now,
the Elder Council will induct a new elder.
The new elder will have a vote then.
Elder Xuan,
who is the candidate for new elder?
Has the candidate been decided?
The strongest contender now
is Old Eccentric Hou.
But he's always been at odds with you.
If he gets elected,
he'll surely obstruct the alliance.
Old Eccentric Hou—
that old guy
has disliked Medicine Elder since the Dan Meeting.
He's never liked Medicine Elder.
You beat him at the Dan Meeting with the Soul Ascension Technique.
He's always doubted your methods.
He holds a grudge against you.
Elder Xuan,
can my teacher run for election?
Medicine Elder left Inner Dan Ta voluntarily.
He can't rejoin the Elder Court.
Old Medicine Elder isn't eligible.
But Xiao Yan is.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
After you left,
Xuan Yi kept worrying about you.
Xuan Kongzi,
No one thinks you're mute if you stay quiet.
Xiao Yan is the Dan Meeting champion,
and a candidate for Alchemist Tower leader.
He's eligible to run.
That's actually a good idea.
But Old Eccentric Hou can summon Nine-Colored Pill Lightning now.
Are you confident?
It's worth a try.
Remember to re-certify your alchemist badge.
So no one questions you.
No time to waste.
I'll go prepare with Xiao Yan first.
The three of us should return to Inner Dan Ta to prepare for the contest.
Sorry to trouble you, seniors.
Eighth-grade Alchemist
Not bad, almost as good as I was.
Senior Hou
Something feels off about this pill.
Could you take a look for me?
(Old Eccentric Hou, Eighth-grade Alchemy Master)
You clearly didn't follow the scroll.
Did you sneak in extra ingredients again?
I've told you before,
stop always trying to innovate.
Stick to the rules.
Senior, please check my pill.
Who's this brat?
You startled me.
This pill is quite good.
Fragrant and evenly colored.
Technique...
is off.
You mixed in other ingredients.
That's against the rules.
Teacher.
Yao Chen.
Why are you here?
So you're Yao Chen's disciple.
No wonder.
You old geezer, still alive after all.
You actually escaped Soul Hall.
Lucky to be alive.
How could I go before you?
Teacher, this is Senior Hou.
That's just how he is.
Just call him Old Hou.
You left the Inner Dan Ta on your own.
I thought you'd never return out of pride.
Alchemist Tower nurtured me.
It's only right to come back and visit.
I see.
You must be after the Inner Dan Ta elder seat.
That's why you shamelessly came back.
I wasn't interested in the elder seat.
But since you're competing,
I have to show you my skills.
Let you see my current strength.
See you in the arena.
(I'm the one competing.)
He doubted me back then,
but he's not a bad person.
Just got caught up in winning and losing.
His dedication to alchemy
is no less than mine.
Such a strong herbal scent.
Didn't expect this hidden place in Alchemist Tower.
That's because...
Inner Dan Ta is the elite force here.
Greetings, Elder.
Two intermediate eighth-grade alchemists.
One advanced eighth-grade alchemist.
This one's aura is unfathomable.
(Great Elder Lin, Two-star Saint of Battle Qi)
That's Great Elder Lin of Inner Dan Ta.
Except for the Ancestor,
he's the most senior in Inner Dan Ta.
Even I must show respect to him.
Elder selection.
We've all been through this before.
The rules
need no further explanation.
All herbs here are free for contestants.
Whoever refines the best pill
- Highest grade wins.
- Yao Chen.
- That person is the winner.
- I'll challenge you this time.
If there are no questions,
contestants, please enter.
Yao Chen, step down.
Teacher, wait for my good news.
Yao Chen's disciple.
Who is this young man?
So young,
yet already an eighth-grade alchemist.
Xiao Yan is Yao Chen's disciple.
He's also this year's pill competition champion.
He has eighth-grade alchemist skills.
By the rules,
he's qualified for the elder selection.
Brat.
This isn't an ordinary contest.
Let me show you my skills today.
See what true alchemy is.
(Such powerful soul waves.)
(Don't worry, Teacher.)
(Xiao Yan won't shame your name.)
Want to uncover the ultimate secret to reach Fight God?
Scan to follow the Dou Po Cang Qiong official account.
Get the latest animation news and exclusive secrets.
The legend ahead awaits your passion.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Borrow tonight's moonlight, look back at the road at dawn♪
♪Forgetting the moon waxes and wanes♪
♪And the sun I can't let go♪
♪Shadows stretch out unreasonably♪
♪The cheapest luxury wish♪
♪Is nothing but everlasting time♪
♪Watching my childlike self♪
♪Running, laughing, playing♪
♪Borrow a few nights to finish my dreams♪
♪Borrow some candles to light up day and night♪
♪Under flickering light and shadow♪
♪I keep tangling with my past♪
♪Making the present so awkward♪
♪Backwards, forwards, not knowing where to go♪
♪The present and past wash over each other♪
♪I'm the most stubborn one♪
♪And the most naive♪
♪Let this light guide the long road ahead♪
♪The past can't be chased, twists and turns♪
♪In the end, watchful eyes fall on me♪
♪Let my heart sprout and grow in hope♪
♪A hundred lifetimes can't match the present♪
♪Familiar scenes♪
(Next episode preview)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™