(Previously)
Our family's bloodline is unique.
You must use the Dragonblood manual.
But your current bloodline concentration
isn't strong enough.
It's alright.
Even if I can't become
a Dragonblood Warrior,
I'll still find a way to grow stronger.
Kid, your blood awakened this ring.
From now on, you're my magic apprentice.
Linley, you've tamed a magical beast.
On behalf of the Ernst Institute,
I sincerely invite you to join us.
Sir,
it is my honor
to become a member
of the Ernst Institute.
- Coiling Dragon -
Episode 4
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Delia, aren't you joining
the competition either?
Not interested.
Welcome, teachers and students,
to the first-year magic tournament.
Today, the top two first-year
students will be decided.
Please look forward to it.
First match, Reno Dunstan
(Reno Dunstan)
from the fire-element magic academy.
Reno!
Isn't that the little monster
from the fire-element magic academy?
Yeah, that's him.
He completed rank-one mage training
while on his way to the academy.
Amazing.
And his opponent,
Leto from the water-element magic academy.
Leto!
A rank-one mage,
although they possess
preliminary magical power,
it remains disordered and chaotic,
making spellcasting unstable.
A rank-two mage
gradually forms an orderly circulation
of magical power within the body,
allowing stable control of minor spells.
As for a rank-three mage,
they must use mental strength
to refine the magical power
within their body into a magic vortex.
From ranks four to six,
mental strength condenses into stars.
Above rank seven,
those stars form a star chart.
You are currently at the rank-two level.
Follow my instructions
and strive
to break through to rank three.
How is that possible?
Two minutes and thirty seconds.
Reno Dunstan wins.
Reno!
Thank you.
As expected of a genius battle mage.
The freshman championship
is definitely yours.
Obviously.
Too bad Linley isn't here
to see my shining moment.
Showing off again.
He's just some small fry.
(Promotion Round Day Two)
(Promotion Round Day Three)
(Top Eight of the Promotion Round)
(Top Four of the Promotion Round)
(Final Match)
(Reno Rank-One Flame Mage VS
Rand ?-Rank Flame Mage)
Linley,
if you want to master
rank-three magic power control,
being too impatient is a major taboo.
Grandpa Delin,
you're right.
The situation was extremely
dangerous then. His attacks kept coming.
I pretended to retreat,
and he pressed forward.
I turned around
and ended the fight
with a single Fireball.
From what I've observed,
Rand is already a rank-two mage.
Rand,
just looking at that arrogant face
of his annoys me.
Reno will be fine.
Of course.
Rand is in the same class as me.
His rank-two elemental affinity
really is better.
But I'm a genius mage.
My mental strength is exceptionally high,
and my control over magic is far superior to his.
I'm back.
Linley is back!
Seriously, you push yourself
too hard every day.
You need to relax.
Exactly. You need a balance
between work and rest.
I'm alright.
Go for it, Reno.
Linley's family lacks resources.
It wasn't easy for him
to become a rank-two mage.
From now on, we should help him more.
Look how exhausted he's been lately.
Reno,
you have to win
the championship tomorrow!
Win the championship...
Reno! The championship is ours!
Rand number one! Unstoppable!
The final match of the Ernst Institute
first-year magic tournament is about to begin.
The atmosphere here today
is incredibly lively.
- I'm sure everyone wants to know
- Reno!
- who will claim the grade competition championship.
- The championship is ours!
Next, please welcome both contestants
to give their pre-match declarations.
Today,
my flames will shine across Ernst.
In respect for my worthy opponent,
I will show mercy.
But definitely not to you,
Rand.
All bark and no bite.
Tell your friends to get ready.
In a moment,
they'll be carrying you out of here.
Such intense hostility
in their speeches.
Now I announce,
the final match of the Ernst Institute
first-year magic tournament
officially begins now!
Reno, go for it!
Such fierce flames.
Even the audience in the front rows
can feel intimidated.
The kid's got some skill.
But your luck ends here.
Heavenfire Meteor!
As expected of Reno,
born into a military family.
His reactions rival those of a warrior.
Having fun yet?
Now it's my turn.
Take this punch!
Naive!
No.
This guy's about to play dirty.
An opening.
You've fallen for it.
You arrogant brat,
taste my power!
Reno!
Reno ranked up!
Nicely done!
Reno broke free from the restraint!
What?
He actually broke through to become
a rank-two mage in the middle of battle!
My turn now.
Heavenfire Meteor!
(This kid just broke through,
and he's already this troublesome?)
Earthfire Bind!
This...
This is...
Now it seems Rand has run into trouble.
Awesome!
Rand, pull yourself together!
Rand, go!
I can't break free!
Brat, if you've got guts, let me go!
Weren't you enjoying yourself just now?
Wait, I surrender!
What a surprise.
So even you know how to surrender.
Then I'll let you off this time.
What just happened?
Reno actually released Rand.
Useless fool.
- Surrender? Dream on!
- Could Rand really be preparing to surrender?
So what if you're a rank-two mage?
I'm a rank-three mage!
Earthfire Spell!
No!
Reno!
The match is already decided. Stop now!
Now you know what I'm capable of, right?
Go on, keep talking.
Reno!
How are you?
You despicable coward!
What a touching display of brotherhood.
But right now,
shouldn't the most important thing
be announcing the champion?
Right, host?
You fool!
If you've got the nerve,
fight me instead.
Yale.
Now's not the time to act recklessly.
Let's get Reno to the infirmary first.
Let's go.
That incompetent host
actually ran off with the loser.
I hereby announce
that the champion
of this year's grade competition is
Rand!
Rand number one!
Earth Spike!
Spear Formation!
You've already gained a basic grasp
of this rank-three spell.
I didn't expect
your progress to be this fast.
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Sir,
do you have an appointment?
This is infuriating!
That shameless Rand!
Brothers, I'm here! Congratulations...
Reno, your favorite drink is here.
Calm down, Reno.
If it had been a fair match,
you definitely would've won.
Just treat this as a lesson.
That's right.
Cheers.
Mm, cheers.
Well said.
You're making it sound like
losing is better than winning.
You...
You're not welcome here.
Please leave.
No need to get worked up.
I just came to check on
my respected opponent's
injuries.
Someone like you thinks
you deserve to compete?
Enough.
And who are you supposed to be?
What gives you the right?
If you've got the nerve,
hit me.
You...
Let go of me!
- Do you know who I am?
- Rand!
Put Rand down!
You bumpkin!
Put me down!
Nicely done!
Keep the music going.
Everyone, continue eating.
Rand.
You...
You dare hit me?
Rand, fighting in private
is forbidden here.
Linley.
What kind of skill is it for a mage
to fight like a warrior?
Come on, let's settle this with magic.
Yeah, settle it with magic!
Fine then.
Linley,
ignore him.
That guy's already rank three.
Alright.
We'll meet in the arena later.
The loser must not only avoid
the winner whenever they meet,
but also hand over
one hundred gold coins.
What do you say?
Rand,
and you call one hundred
gold coins a wager?
How about this?
The loser hands over
ten thousand gold coins instead.
Ten thousand gold coins?
What, scared now?
Rand, the three of us can scrape together
ten thousand gold coins.
Besides, that guy clearly
isn't your match.
Fine. Ten thousand gold coins it is.
See you later.
I'll make you regret this.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™