Come forth!
I'm too weak to use my power now.
My power...
You're injured.
The intelligence is wrong.
The Nightraven could not be sealed.
Ms. Liu, I'll get you out of here.
Ding Xiao, see you outside.
Ding Xiao!
Monkey?
Ding Xiao, you're finally here.
Elder Lin,
the Nightraven broke the seal!
What?!
Miao Xun.
What exactly happened?
Director Ling.
For some reason, the Nightraven shattered the Heavenly Chains.
Facing the monarch-level evil spirit, we lost a lot of disciples.
Where's Ding Xiao?
He's still in the tower.
My power-recording talisman failed,
so he sent me out using his own talisman.
Monkey,
take care of Ling for me.
Without the power-recording talisman, you'll be trapped...
What did you say?
Form up!
Seal off the Spirit Suppression Tower!
Hold on!
One of my disciples is still in the tower.
You know exactly what's happening now.
Facing a monarch-level evil spirit,
a level-6 spirit disciple can never survive.
Elder Lin.
Please allow me to enter the tower.
Bai Xi!
Episode 6
[Nightraven]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Adapted from the original novel Divine Manifestation by Ming Gei Ni Xing Bu Xing.]
[Season One
Awakening of the Spirit Beast]
- Divine Manifestation -
[15 Years Ago]
[Duanmu Yan
Spirit Cultivator]
[Bai Xi]
Mother, I've mastered this swordsmanship.
When will you teach me the Flaming Sword?
Just wait until you can use your spirit power.
I want to be a great heroine like you, Mother.
When can I use my spirit power anyway?
Xi, you're a talented girl.
That day will come soon.
[Bai Shou
Spirit Cultivator]
So?
Any updates?
Luofeng City has fallen.
Master asked us to set off right away.
Mother.
You're leaving again?
Xi.
We'll be away for a few days.
You gotta practice more at home.
Mother.
My birthday's in two days.
Will you and Father celebrate with me?
Yan.
They're waiting for us.
We should go.
Xi.
You can definitely develop a better spirit beast.
Make sure you show it to me first when you succeed.
Got it.
Mother.
I'll be waiting for you at home.
What's that?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Why are you here?
Just leave.
The elders have started sealing the tower.
We're trapped.
You really shouldn't have come in.
Let's get out of here together.
This is a healing pill.
It can help restore some of your power.
Run!
Crap!
Dodge, now!
Ding Xiao!
Spirit-subduing Spell! Stage 1!
Thunder Armor!
We must find a way to restrict the Nightraven's movement first.
Okay.
Spirit-binding Formation! Initiate!
Bai Xi!
Ding.
As long as you can suppress the bird,
I'll be able to devour it.
We're talking about a monarch-level evil spirit.
So what?
I can still take it down.
This power...
Ding Xiao.
You have to make it.
Spirit Power, take shape
and protect me!
So this is your spirit power?
Good or evil,
it's all decided by the host's will.
Seven-colored Sacred Bird!
Come forth!
Flaming Sword!
Spirit-subduing Spell! Stage 2!
Invincible Rods!
Can't believe your power is so great.
Little ball,
it's your turn.
Hurry!
Ding.
I'm going to scarf down this bird.
What are you doing?
My pet is starving.
Your pet?
What are you saying?
Young man,
thanks for helping me get rid of the evil spirit,
or I can never see Xi again.
You're Bai Xi's mother?
So you are...
Xi.
You've grown up.
Mother?
You're really my mother!
It's been 15 years.
I've been looking for you all along.
Why would you end up here?
Xi.
You must have gone through a lot.
Mother...
What exactly happened?
Xi.
The evil power has eroded most of my memories.
Now I only know that I was asked to eliminate evil spirits in Luofeng City.
To save my teammate Xue Qing,
I had a fierce fight with the evil spirits.
That's all I can remember now.
Father refused to tell me anything.
He even forbade me from looking for you.
Even so, I still believed you were alive.
Young man,
when you helped me get rid of the evil spirit, I sensed an evil power in your Spirit Space.
Ma'am, do you know what it is?
I do.
15 years ago,
I saw the same power in Luofeng City.
So,
you and Ling are really the survivors of Luofeng City.
Your strange power comes from this evil power.
My sister suffers a lot from this strange power.
Ma'am, is there a way to get rid of it?
I've lost all my power, so there is nothing I can do.
However, Xue Qing might make a difference.
He's an expert in healing arts.
Maybe he can help you.
Ma'am?
Mother!
Within 15 minutes,
if a soul can't be guided to the afterlife,
it'll disappear for good.
Mother!
Xi.
I wasn't there when you grew up.
Do you hate me?
No, I only miss you day and night.
Xi.
I'm so happy to know that you've been missing me
all these years.
How I wish I could watch you grow up.
If there's a next life,
I hope I can make it up to you.
Mother.
Didn't you say you wanted to see my spirit beast?
Sure.
Good or evil,
it's all decided by the host's will.
Seven-colored Sacred Bird!
Come forth!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Ma'am,
it's time.
Wait.
Let me do this.
Miss Bai.
To guide a soul to the afterlife, disciples of the Guibu Division must recite the Soul-guiding Mantra.
I'll use my power to help you activate the soul-calming talisman.
The living are but travelers,
going to the same destination.
Heaven or hell,
we're all pathetic.
Mother!
[A few days later]
The Evil Spirits Termination Contest is really full of challenges.
Without you guys, I could never get the pill.
Thank you so much.
Xiao, you're too kind.
It's because of your help that we can be promoted to the Sect's branch in Longlin County.
Exactly!
Ling is your sister.
Helping her is actually no biggie.
The four of us will have to report to the branch in Longlin County tomorrow.
We're here to say goodbye to you.
Bottoms up!
From now on, we're like family.
Exactly!
We're family!
Bottoms up!
The Golden Spirit Pill may suppress the strange power in Ling's body for now,
but it can't wipe it out for good.
Ding Xiao.
There are many talents in the Ghost Market.
Yeah!
Ghost Market!
Perhaps, we can find something useful there.
I did hear about it before.
There are only a few people
who know where it is.
I know its location.
Bai Xi?
Xun, let's go check on Ling.
Yeah, yeah!
We'll go check on Ling.
Let's go.
I can walk by myself.
I just wanna see what happens next.
The Ghost Market is where all kinds of information flow.
It is said that there's a legendary doctor there.
His witchcraft is totally worth a try.
Maybe we can even get Xue Qing's whereabouts.
Let's go.
Okay.
[Preview] What exactly [Preview] happened in Luofeng City back then?
[Preview] I have a hunch that [Preview]
[Preview]
the truth is close.
[Preview] What I want is [Preview]
[Preview]
something you can't give.
[Preview] Even if you want my life, [Preview]
[Preview]
I'd still give it to you.
Ding Xiao.
[Preview]
My master ordered me to bring you back.
I don't care who you are.
[Preview]
None of you is getting out of here alive today.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™