[Adapted from the original novel Divine Manifestation by Ming Gei Ni Xing Bu Xing.]
[Season One /Awakening of the Spirit Beast]
- Divine Manifestation -
Episode 7
[Ghost Market]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
It's wet.
I got this.
Good or evil,
it's all decided by the host's will.
W...
Come forth!
Wait!
Did you do it on purpose?
You stared at me first.
I...
I didn't.
I really envy Ling
having a brother like you.
Just trying to do better.
And you?
I've never heard you mention your father.
My father...
Ever since my mother disappeared,
he's been trying to control me.
He forbade me from cultivation
or asking about my mother.
To get away from him,
I went to the capital.
What exactly
happened in Luofeng City back then?
I have a hunch that
the truth is close.
[Ghost Market]
Ghost Market started as a black market.
Debt dodgers,
fugitives,
and convicts all ended up hiding here.
Over time,
it became a den of outlaws.
Excuse me.
May I ask where Magical Doctor is?
Let's go.
We must bring him back.
Keep up!
Come on.
Let them have fun.
Thanks a lot, sir.
That's nothing.
I just sensed a strange power.
Sir,
may I ask you something?
What?
Do you know the Magical Doctor?
Sir,
do you...
Magical Doctor?
[Magical Doctor]
Magical Doctor
I like this nickname.
This way,
please.
[Magical Doctor]
[Clinic]
Sir,
are you really the Magical Doctor?
You gave me that name.
What can I do for you?
My sister has a strange illness.
Still no cure for her.
If you'd help her,
I'll repay you handsomely.
Handsomely?
How much could it be?
As much as you want.
What I want is
something you can't give.
Even if you want my life,
I'd still give it to you.
You serious?
Deadly serious.
Great!
I'd like to get it now!
Stop!
Who exactly are you?
Release me now!
Be quiet.
Your body
is extremely rare.
Great!
Sir, I have no grudge against you.
I just want you to help my sister.
Don't be scared.
I'm always a fair person.
After taking away your spirit power,
I'll start curing your sister.
Soul-transferring Talisman! Activate!
Get out!
There is no place for you.
Sadly, your spirit embryo is useless.
Those people at the ferry...
Did you take away their spirit power?
Exactly!
To find a cure for their family or friends,
they offered me their spirit power.
Let me crack open your spirit embryo
and see what's inside.
So weak.
That is...
Master's 81 Golden Seals?!
Eat this!
Is this fate?
Life is a game,
and everything is in play.
Watch and learn.
This move is called Sky-sundering Axe!
This dark mist here stifles your spirit embryo
and limits your potential.
This is how you deal with it.
Sky Net! Bind!
Sky-sundering Axe!
This old coot's so nice.
He helped you disperse the dark mist.
I'm coming out!
Did he just reach the Spirit Soldier Realm?
Thank you, sir.
That's no biggie.
Please release my friend, sir.
You freak!
How dare you imprison me!
Chill out!
Move aside.
He nearly took away your spirit power.
Flying Swords! Attack!
Withdraw!
Give me back the pendant!
Duanmu used to wear this.
Well, half of it.
So you're my mother's martial arts brother.
[Xue Qing /Magical Doctor]
Xue Qing [Xue Qing /Magical Doctor]
The elder also helped me
reach the Spirit Soldier Realm in the Spirit Space.
The elder?
I'm only 35 this year.
Over the years,
the evil power has turned me into a monster.
You had it coming.
This is the price you paid for
taking away other people's spirit power.
Bai Xi.
If cursing me can ease her hatred,
then so be it.
You're not as soft as Duanmu,
but you have her kindness.
Don't you dare mention her!
Do you think she would be happy
after knowing what you've done?
I've failed her terribly.
Sir.
What exactly happened in Luofeng City back then?
15 years ago,
Luofeng City was overrun by the evil spirits.
Master led us to reinforce the city.
Outside the city,
Duanmu and I were surrounded by the monarch-level evil spirits.
They almost got us.
Duanmu shoved me into a dry well
and sealed it with talismans.
When I climbed out,
she was already gone.
Duanmu,
I should be the dead one.
Days ago,
we came across an evil spirit born from Ms. Duanmu's soul.
What?!
Where is she now?
We've purified her soul.
She was imprisoned in the Spirit Suppression Tower for over a decade.
How cruel fate is!
Even after death, she suffered such torment.
It's all fated.
Besides, Mother never resented you.
Still,
would you please tell us more
about Luofeng City?
I only
heard about it from my master.
That day,
we were supposed to repel the evil power surrounding the 49 pairs of infants.
We didn't expect the formation to turn against us.
Only one pair of infants survived.
Our master was very kind.
He decided to adopt the babies.
May I ask your master's name?
Well,
his name is Ding Yuan.
Ding Yuan?
Grandpa?!
After adopting you and your sister,
he started investigating this accident in secret,
but his efforts were in vain.
Mr. Xue,
check this out.
This talisman...
seems to be the work of Xiao Yu, the lord of Luofeng City.
He was brought to justice years ago.
Where did you get this?
We've met many evil spirits so far.
This kind of talismans was found at every scene.
Besides,
my sister got tainted by evil power.
It has something to do with this talisman.
With my power severely impaired,
there is nothing I can do.
Is there really no other way?
Not exactly.
Master once told me...
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Mr. Xue!
Finally, I can see Duanmu again.
Take care of him.
The Great Wasteland...
There is
a purification formation
there...
Mr. Xue.
You may rest in peace.
The living are but travelers,
going to the same destination.
Heaven or hell,
we're all pathetic.
Soul-burning Icicle! Scorch!
Invisible Blade! Pierce!
Ding Xiao.
My master ordered me to bring you back.
I don't care who you are.
None of you is getting out of here alive today.
Spirit Shield! Block!
Shadowless Blade! Slash!
Heavenly Thunder! Strike!
Spirit Shield! Block!
Sky-sundering Axe!
Golden Armor!
Your moves tell me you're from the Lingbu Division.
Tell me.
Who sent you here?
Ding Xiao.
Our sect won't let this go.
Three puppet talismans wasted.
[The Next Day]
Ling! [The Next Day]
I'm back. [The Next Day]
I'm back.
That evil power again.
Yeah.
The same scent.
Smells so good.
Ding Xiao.
Look!
This talisman again.
Ling must be kidnapped by someone.
Where could she be?
Let me use the Fire Bird to track Ling's whereabouts.
All disciples, listen up!
This is rather urgent.
Come back to the Sect immediately.
Recently,
a plague has broken out around Baihe.
The evil spirits are running wild.
Our branch in Baihe suffered heavy casualties.
They need reinforcements badly.
The Sect exists to protect the people from the evil spirits.
Every disciple of the Guibu Division
is responsible for eliminating them.
I've located Ling's whereabouts.
She's in
Baihe.
What?!
Those willing to take this mission
may light your life lamp.
I, Ling Jiang,
as the head of the Guibu Division,
will lead the charge.
Li Zhennan, level-8 Coffin Guard of the Guibu Division,
requests to join you.
Deng Xiang, Coffin Bearer of the Guibu Division,
Zhao Kang, level-6 Spirit Officer of the Guibu Division,
requests to join you.
Zhou Zhengtai, Coffin Bearer...
Fang Jie, Coffin Guard...
Liu Baihu, Spirit Officer...
I'll head to Baihe to find Ling.
And I'll return home.
My father must know more details.
Okay.
I'll see you in Baihe.
Ding Xiao, level-9 Coffin Guard of the Guibu Division,
requests to join you.
I wonder how many disciples will fall in this expedition.
[Preview]
You're the evil spirits' leader? [Preview]
The source of the plague? [Preview]
[Preview]
There are many villages near Baihe. [Preview]
These evil spirits only spread plague. They don't kill. [Preview]
[Preview]
That's why their number is increasing. [Preview]
You really don't know where my mother is? [Preview]
[Preview]
She's turned into an evil spirit. [Preview]
Am I right? [Preview]
[Preview]
Brat. [Preview]
You're dead meat! [Preview]
[Preview]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™