At this pace...
we won't reach the outpost
before nightfall.
Yeah...
Why not try the talisman art
Brother taught me?
Heavy to Light as Feather...
Activate!
Bro, leave the carriage to me.
Cultivate in peace.
After Luofeng City,
my phase force surged.
Time to evolve
the Twelve Spirit Palaces.
If your Twelve Spirit Palaces
can handle that black mist...
I'll call you Grandpa!
Spirit converges in qi sea...
force shatters divine court.
Nine apertures open,
sun and moon eternal!
Heaven follows constant laws...
sun and moon alternate...
yin and yang in harmony...
inner cosmos born.
Body and spirit unite...
grand cycle complete.
Twelve Spirit Palaces manifest!
Old Ding's got some skills!
How do I truly summon
your true spirit form?
Told you already...
reach Spirit Emperor realm...
and I'll come out naturally.
If you don't...
how do I reach it?
And Ling'er's matter...
can't wait forever.
Whoa!
Slow down!
You little rascal...
learn tricks from monkeys?
Bro...
I just don't want you tired.
Ungrateful!
Hmph.
Got it...
just teasing.
Regret coming to the Great Wilderness
with me?
Anywhere with Bro is fine.
This Great Wilderness...
differs from elsewhere.
Vicious criminals exiled here...
fierce malign spirits roam...
they love feasting
on girls like you.
I'm so scared~
Drama queen!
Once in the Wilderness...
we'll find that grand array...
cure your anomalous phase.
When I'm healed...
I'll become a phase master too.
Then...
I'll protect you.
Giddyup!
Whoa!
This gate is like the Gates of Hell...
separating life and death.
Why isn't the gate opening?
Probably timed...
opens every few hours.
Enter alive, return dead!
Doomed fools, shut up!
Giddyup!
Bro...
No signs of life all the way...
we need to hurry...
reach the Spirit Suppression outpost...
rest up.
Bai Xi...
Nails...
This three-star malign king
is coming for you!
Perfect, I'm starving!
Giddyup!
Malign spirits everywhere here...
show up uninvited.
Bro, what's wrong?
Malign spirit incoming!
We've slain king-level before...
no need to panic.
You know nothing!
Wilderness maligns kill each other...
far stronger than peers.
Too late!
Stay inside!
I'll handle it.
Bro, I can help!
No!
Summoning your phase
worsens your condition.
Don't use it again!
Xiang...
Flying Flower Sword Shadows!
Break!
Golden Light Shield!
Defend!
Swift as Lightning!
Dodge!
Blazing Soul Flames!
Burn!
Phase Manifestation!
Scorching Breath!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
This...
mist...
Bro!
Give my brother back!
Get lost!
You brat...
I could tear this mongrel apart
with ease.
Hand over your body now!
Stop hesitating!
Never!
How will trash like you
avenge your brother?
Give me the body!
Shut up!
Ling'er, wake up!
Don't let it sway you!
Bro...
Ling'er...
Ling'er!
Bro...
I knew...
you wouldn't abandon me.
Ling'er...
No more using your phase!
If you lose control...
it'll possess you forever.
Promise me!
This mist is strange...
Bro will get you out.
This mist...
feeds malign qi to spirits.
Bro, something's coming!
Careful!
What are you waiting for?
Run!
This one's too tough for me!
Go!
People coming!
Follow me!
Seal Spirits, Halt Malign!
Bind!
Done.
Just wait for the malign mist
to disperse.
That was malign mist?
It coexists with the Great Wilderness...
origins unknown.
All malign spirits in it...
grow frenzied.
Especially that giant in the mist...
once it locks on...
nine deaths, one life.
Thanks for the aid, miss.
Your name?
Ding Xiao...
Ninth-rank protector
at Nanlin Town Spirit Bureau...
exiled here for breaking rules.
My sister, Ding Ling...
bears a malign phase...
anomalies since childhood.
Who are you?
How...
don't recognize your big sister
we grew up with?
Sister Feng!
Sister Yuanyuan!
Gone so many years...
thought I'd never see you again.
How could that be?
In the Wilderness these years...
I longed to return to Nanlin
and find you.
But malign mist surged...
spirits everywhere.
Master insisted on Spirit Martial breakthrough
before letting me go.
Sister Yuanyuan...
how did you find us?
Long story...
Two months ago...
I broke through to Spirit Martial.
Master finally allowed return
to Nanlin.
But who knew...
upon arriving...
spirits besieged the city.
After it ended...
Commander Ling told me...
you'd been sent here.
I rushed back at once.
Years apart...
yet we meet here.
That lantern festival incident...
Commander Ling told me too.
If I hadn't left then...
that phase wouldn't have...
harmed you like this.
These years...
must've been hard for you.
Sister Yuanyuan...
This has weighed
on my heart all these years.
Sister Feng...
don't blame yourself.
Ling'er and I are fine.
We came to the Great Wilderness...
to find the array
that purifies her anomalous phase.
But the Wilderness is vast...
no leads yet.
Such an array exists here?
Could it be...
You know something?
Rest assured...
with Haoxuan Sect's strength
in the Wilderness...
we'll find clues for you.
[Great Wilderness: The Great Wilderness lies far to the west of the Great Desolate region. It is a land of death and desolation. From ancient times to the present, countless powerful figures have fallen here—its soil soaked with blood, its air thick with resentment, like a vast burial ground of gods and heroes. The Great Wilderness is home to numerous fierce beasts and savage tribes. Ferocious creatures roam freely, and danger lurks at every step. For cultivators, this place is both a forbidden land and a crucible. Those who survive its trials often gain extraordinary strength, while the unprepared vanish without a trace.Over countless years, the Great Wilderness has been transformed by endless slaughter and struggle. Its violent aura grows ever stronger, its environment more hostile, resembling a flowing river of killing intent. Legends say that only those with supreme resolve and exceptional fortune can emerge alive—and those who do are forever changed by the experience. For this reason, the Great Wilderness is both feared and revered: a realm of chaos, death, and opportunity, where the weak are devoured and the strong are forged.]
Heartless beasts in human skin!
Planning to slaughter
all 178 souls...
in Hukou Village!
Phase born from mind,
spirit gathers form...
Nine-Tailed Spirit Fox manifests!
Phase takes shape—
Scorching Breath!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™