When I first met Sister Ling'er,
I already knew
she was destined for greatness.
Hindsight hero.
Could this be Ling'er's Spirit Phase?
No matter who you are,
today this lord will slay gods
if they stand in my way—
and Buddhas too.
Anyone who dares hinder the Holy Sect's plans
will be crushed to dust!
How am I flying?
Bro, I'm right here!
Ling'er!
First level of the Demon-Subduing Curse—
Thunder envelops me!
Brother Hu!
I'll leave this to you.
Don't worry, I can hold them off.
And me too!
Go beat the crap out of that perverted sect!
The All-Heavens Demon-Subduing Array has been broken.
The Great Wilderness is on the brink of destruction.
You're just a useless Phase-less person.
Why fight against heaven?
Ling'er!
Circulate your Phase power.
Feel your Spirit Phase.
Even if you save the Great Wilderness,
when the Heavenly Tribulation comes
and the evil god descends...
it will only turn more people to ash.
Heavenly Tribulation...
Evil god...
Neither is an excuse for you to kill!
Second Phase Technique!
Spirit Source Limit Break!
Foolish and stubborn.
Die!
Form without restraint.
Illusion born from the heart.
Transcending life and death.
Freedom without limit!
Soul-Devouring Annihilation!
Ling'er!
Stay back!
I'll handle this tentacle freak.
Secret Technique—
Ice Seals the Nine Provinces!
Mu Xue!
Are you alright?
You're too foolish.
You insignificant ants!
To sacrifice yourselves for the Holy Sect
is already a great honor.
Yet you dare resist!
Death is too merciful for you.
Three-Headed Flood Dragon...
Rest in peace.
Oh no!
It's absorbing the evil mist!
Merging with all that spirit evil...
Ding Xiao!
Everyone will die because of you!
This young master is going all out today!
Mere Ninth Star Spirit Adept Realm...
Nothing but a worthless nobody.
Brother can't hold on much longer!
Why struggle?
Death is inevitable either way.
Stop wasting your energy.
If I can isolate the evil qi...
and those spirit evils...
Phase Technique!
Phase Evil Returns to Origin!
How is this possible?!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
We need to repair the grand array first.
It won't hold much longer!
Little Broken Ball!
Little Broken Ball, are you still there?
The grand array has fallen.
Heaven itself wants me dead.
This is not a defeat by force...
This time, the Great Wilderness
is doomed.
AR
Xia dogs!
Invading our lands...
must be exterminated!
Mother...
Forgive your unfilial son.
I'll serve you again in the next life.
Dream Sister...
Don't wait for me.
Find a good family.
Father has broken his promise.
You must honor and care for Mother.
Help me look after our parents.
I can feel their pain...
as if trapped in the deepest hell,
unable to transcend.
At that time, the Heavenly Venerable
who saves from suffering
shall fill the ten directions of the world.
With your mighty divine power,
you rescue all sentient beings,
leading them away from delusion.
Yet sentient beings remain unaware,
like the blind beholding the sun and moon.
Grandpa...
Ah Xiao...
All these years, curing Ling'er
has been so hard on you.
You've suffered greatly.
Grandpa...
This is all my fault.
I shouldn't have rashly opened the grand array.
Everything is fated.
Do not let it disturb your Dao heart.
Grandpa...
What should I do?
Ten years ago,
I led over a thousand Spirit Phase masters
into the Great Wilderness to eradicate evil.
Nearly all perished.
Leaving behind hidden dangers.
This All-Heavens Demon-Subduing Array
may seem to protect the Great Wilderness,
but in truth, it also imprisons it.
Do you still remember your great vow?
To redeem all evil spirits,
and bring salvation to every living being.
Grandpa...
This unfinished path...
I will walk it in your stead.
Mm.
As a disciple of the Gui Division,
I will always remember:
salvation before slaughter.
I offer the power of our ancestors.
With this vow's strength,
I shall redeem these countless wronged souls!
If we live, we live together.
If we die, we die together.
Mm.
Phase Evil Returns to Origin!
The living are but passing travelers,
the dead are those returning home.
Heaven and earth are one fleeting inn,
sharing the same eternal sorrow of dust.
Grandpa...
Ling'er misses you so much.
Silly child.
Grandpa will become a star in the sky
and watch over you all.
Grandpa...
Don't go!
We won!
We won! We actually won!
Just as that saying foretold.
But Senior Brother Yuan...
With such fine juniors,
you can rest without regrets.
It feels like waking from a nightmare.
Finally awake.
The evil mist has vanished.
The people here no longer have to live in hiding.
Mm.
Ling'er...
Your abnormal Phase...
It's gone.
I'll never be tormented by that monster again.
I still need to train hard and protect everyone.
Good.
Come with me to the Wu Xuan Sect.
I'll personally oversee your rigorous training.
Mm.
Princess...
Using secret arts like that
could cost you your life and destroy your Dao.
Mu Xue...
Are you alright?
Don't worry.
With my master here,
I'll be back to full strength in a few days.
This Phantom Scale Jade of the South Sea.
will help you break through to the Spirit Martial Realm.
Keep it safe.
This...
I can't accept a reward without merit.
Take it.
That's an order.
These past days...
Thank you, Princess Mu Xue,
for all your invaluable help.
I'm truly grateful.
H-How did you know?
I just do.
Then...
Since you've met this princess,
why haven't you paid your respects?
You...
Your attitude changes faster than flipping a book.
Just kidding.
I've had enough training in the Great Wilderness.
Master, let's head back.
There will be plenty of time ahead.
Until we meet again.
You haven't fallen for that silly boy, have you?
Master!
What nonsense are you saying?
We're just friends.
Brother Ding Xiao.
What are your plans moving forward?
The Great Wilderness has been reborn.
Those laws of the jungle,
where the weak are prey to the strong,
should vanish along with the evil mist.
I want to work with the Wu Xuan Sect
to build a Great Wilderness City,
a safe haven for all the displaced villagers.
It sounds impossible.
But how will we know
if we don't try?
Well said.
Leave the sect matters to me and Master.
You can rest assured.
When I first met you, Brother Ding Xiao,
I already knew you were no ordinary person.
Good.
I'll rally the Thunder Leopard Village
to be the first to join Great Wilderness City.
The long night stretches on, without a guiding lamp...
A lone wild goose cries in sorrow, having lost its kin...
The spirit cultivator has passed.
His soul has returned to the heavens.
We inherit your final wish
and guard this cherished land.
Heroic soul...
Send Uncle Lei on his final journey.
Return...
The living are but passing travelers.
The dead are those returning home.
Heaven and earth are one fleeting inn,
sharing the same eternal sorrow of dust.
Heroic soul, return...
Bro, look!
Wait!
Clear the way!
Sister Ling'er.
Take care.
I was once a useless Phase-less person
who only wanted to carry coffins for a living
and cure my sister's strange illness.
I never expected
to be exiled to the Great Wilderness.
Having witnessed life under the evil mist,
where lives are worth less than ants,
I made a great vow:
to save the people of the Great Wilderness.
Now the evil mist has vanished,
and the people live in peace.
All my wishes have been fulfilled.
This journey was not in vain.
["The journey through the martial world is long, with towering mountains and endless rivers."]
[Great Wilderness City: “The Great Wilderness is vast and boundless, yet it first wins hearts.”Ding Xiaoming was exiled to the Great Wilderness. The people there lived like grass, yet he was willing to risk his life to save them. Under the oppression of the monstrous beasts, countless lives suffered; after driving the beasts away, destiny entrusted him with the mission of rebuilding the Great Wilderness.
Starting from Leipo Village, he joined forces with Wu Xuan Sect, the foremost sect of the Great Wilderness, to establish a city—Great Wilderness City—providing a haven for displaced refugees and bringing them stability and safety. He also gathered the remaining beast tides and organized them into a powerful force, ensuring that no new threats would arise. After several years, they built a grand city housing one-third of the Great Wilderness population—Great Wilderness City—where the people now live and work in peace and contentment.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™