Bump.
This hand’s gonna be a winner for me.
Pingping.
What’s up? What’s up?
You called me over to play cards yourself...
...but you keep spacing out.
Go.
Gather everyone in the clan...
...and grab your weapons.
Wait, no...
Who are we fighting?
Me?
We can’t let a young lady go into danger all by herself.
We’re going to escort her!
So hot-blooded.
Pingping, what a real man.
Brother Meng Chuan...
I’m so glad I came to the Meng family.
Count me in.
Why didn’t you open the gate just now?
Quick!
Hurry up and open the gate!
he,
He’s become a God Venerable.
He...
...has returned.
Meng Mu...
Meng...
Senior Brother Meng...
I’m warning you, don’t do anything reckless.
If anything happens to my young master...
...you won’t be able to bear the consequences.
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you even know who you’ve provoked?
It’s the Bai family of God Venerables!
I’m asking you a question.
Are you deaf?
I...
I am the young master of the Bai family, Bai Zhu!
You...
You mind your own business!
Bai Pig.
Since when did the Bai family...
...produce trash like you?
God Venerable...
Meng Chuan...
Zhu’er...
Father is late.
Dad...
Dad!
Get up!
A true man has gold beneath his knees.
Help the young master back to the army camp.
Yes.
[Ancient Era — Early Stage of the Great Sun Realm]
Interesting.
He actually didn’t dodge.
Are you alright?
Just a small matter.
So that’s the Bai family’s God Venerable...
...Bai Guan’s father.
Where’s that Bai Pig?
Bai Zhu is...
...the illegitimate son of the Bai family God Venerable.
No wonder he’s never home.
He’s been raising a bastard outside.
Meng Chuan...
Don’t go!
That’s a Great Sun Realm God Venerable!
Everyone...
Quick interview.
That Bai Zhu guy...
Good guy or bad guy?
That bastard killed quite a few female mine slaves for fun.
Rape and torture.
Rotten to the core.
Qingfeng...
Long time no see.
You’ve gotten thinner.
Hold this for me.
So you’re Meng Chuan.
You know me?
I’ve heard a little about how you refused to ascend Primordial Mountain.
But you...
...have still become a God Venerable after all.
As for you killing my third brother...
...I can let bygones be bygones.
Meng Chuan...
From now on, the Meng and Bai families...
...will not interfere with each other.
Does Bai Guan know...
...that you’re raising a bastard outside?
Stop him!
Slay the demon!
Kill it!
Meng Chuan!
How dare you!
Here he comes.
Calling for daddy already?
You’re just relying on the Demon Venerable’s regeneration...
...so let them stab away.
Go on, try it.
Nine Worms...
Nine revivals.
Perfect.
This is also my first true God Venerable duel.
Let’s have some fun.
Then let’s have some fun.
You won’t get beaten into the ground like last time.
Meng Chuan...
I will make the Meng family...
...go extinct!
Careless.
Piercing the Sun!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
How is this possible?
So this is the intent of a Great Sun Realm God Venerable?
Perfect.
Let me feel it a little more.
Take it easy.
Once all nine worms are cut...
...you won’t be able to regenerate anymore.
You’ll need time for the worms to recover.
I know what I’m doing.
This kid...
...how is his speed and strength not inferior to mine?
Even...
...he can gradually keep up with my fighting rhythm.
He can gradually keep up with my fighting rhythm.
He’s only been a God Venerable for three months.
Strange.
Why isn’t this guy manifesting his God Venerable Form?
He’s purely fighting with intent.
He’s gathering combat data on you.
Data.
The higher the level of battle...
...the more important it is to analyze the enemy’s strengths and methods...
...in order to tailor the next combat strategy.
It’s just like playing cards.
You don’t just need to know the cards in your own hand...
...you also need to know what cards the opponent is holding.
Only then...
...can you play your hand better.
I see.
So he keeps using different moves and techniques...
...to force me to respond...
...and see what cards I’m holding.
But he never expected that your biggest card on the surface...
...is your speed.
Instead, it gave me even more chances to study his intent.
Why did you stop?
Don’t stop!
Meng family spawn...
Dodge!
All you know is how to dodge!
He’s getting anxious.
God Venerable Form!
Growth Heavenly King!
An ability only Great Sun Realm God Venerables can master.
God Venerable Body.
He couldn’t hold back...
...and played his card first.
God Venerable Power.
There’s no escaping it.
Same as before.
There’s some power restraining me.
God Venerable Power?
Interesting.
Let’s see if you die this time!
God Venerable Form!
Just like everyone’s God Venerable foundation in the mortal world...
...each has a different God Venerable Power.
Compared to foundation power...
...it’s even more mysterious and powerful.
And the God Venerable Body...
...corresponds to the foundation posture.
It comprehensively strengthens the physical body.
That’s right.
Only after reaching the Great Sun Realm...
...can one be considered a true God Venerable.
Otherwise, Primordial Mountain wouldn’t have set the rule...
...that those below Great Sun Realm...
...are not allowed to descend the mountain.
There’s even such a rule?
What kind of creature are you exactly?
Can’t even kill you.
Be careful.
Fighting a Great Sun Realm...
...and you’ve already died three times.
Don’t worry.
No need.
Saber Intent.
Thunder Pierces the Sun!
I have...
...learned it.
My intent...
How could this be?
How could you...
It’s quite simple.
Meng Chuan...
I now have reason to suspect...
...that you’ve been possessed by a demon.
Otherwise, there’s no explaining why you can’t be killed.
That’s an ability only the demon race possesses.
Looks like you’ve played all your cards.
Next...
...it’s my turn to play.
Mere Indestructible Realm...
...what’s the point of summoning your God Venerable Form?
Ultimate piercing intent...
Overwhelming God Venerable Body...
And inescapable God Venerable Power.
Great Sun Realm...
...truly is the dividing line for God Venerables.
But the core of a God Venerable is still the God Venerable Form.
Your realm may crush me...
...but my God Venerable Form...
...will crush you.
With majestic divine might...
...I command you by imperial decree!
Thunder roars...
Universal Transformation Heavenly Venerable!
Six...
Six-Character God Venerable Form?
How could you possibly have the Six-Character God Venerable Form?!
No...
Growth...
You are not allowed to kneel!
You defective fool...
The Heavenly Venerable is here.
Heavenly King, get lost!
Meng Chuan...
If you’ve got the guts, just kill me!
Want to die?
You parasites...
Come out!
My lord...
Earth Net...
Send him to the border.
If he wants to die...
...then let him die on the battlefield.
Understood.
Send me to the border.
Meng Chuan...
Who do you think you are?!
I returned home with over ten thousand merits of honor!
So what if it’s the Earth Net?
Even the Earth Net has no right to decide where I go!
The Patrol Lord didn’t permit you to stand.
Dog.
Why would the Mountain Lord’s shadow guards appear here?
Why are they following this bastard Meng Chuan?
How dare you directly call the Patrol Lord by name!
Patrol...
Meng Chuan is the World Patrol.
Impossible...
Why bring him to me?
Just follow the Patrol Lord’s orders.
Yes.
What?
Have you gotten used to the Patrol identity that Qin Wu forced on you?
What Patrol?
Primordial Mountain is always like this.
That word “Patrol” is full of arrogance.
As for us...
...we’re just demon slayers who walk the world.
Demon slayers?
You originally...
...should have been the King of East宁.
Isn’t that the same?
Zhuang Sheng...
What?
Charge!
Even the King of East宁 is still a demon slayer.
According to my nature...
...even if I became a king...
...I’d probably still be running all over the world,
slaying demons and saving people.
Demon Slayer Meng Chuan...
Next, we’ll have to leave the Great Zhou Dynasty...
...and head to the Dayue Dynasty.
We’re going to reinforce Two Worlds Island.
Once we leave...
...who knows how long it’ll be before we return.
Achuan...
Clan Leader...
Young Master!
Qian Fang...
Meng Chuan...
You’re back!
Yeah.
I’m back.
How have you been doing at the Meng family?
Xiao Ye...
The Meng family is great.
All the elder grandpas are doing well.
But...
...the newly arrived Jade Sun Palace Master
is not so good.
Giddy-up!
Palace Master!
Palace...
How urgent is it...
...that you’re panting like this?
Meng Chuan...
...has returned.
Senior Brother has returned!
Meng Chuan...
[Azalea/Yingshanhong — Evil Dragon Clan]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™