[Previously on…]
All he ever wanted was to become a God Venerable.
All he ever wanted
was to become a God Venerable.
Have you all prepared
to face death?
Then let the
Primordial Mountain trial...
...officially begin!
Only after entering Primordial City
did I truly understand...
They want you dead.
Idiots.
Whoever kills Meng Chuan...
I'll personally escort them
up Primordial Mountain.
Send off...
Young Master Chuan to the afterlife!
Trash like you...
...don't deserve to be
a God Venerable.
This so-called trial...
...is nothing but a farce
full of assassination, gambling, and schemes.
The wickedness of the human heart is far more chilling than the brutality of the demon race.
After three rounds,
we'll see who comes out on top.
In the end, only ten people
will ascend Primordial Mountain...
...and become God Venerables.
Your Highness...
Will you...
...remember how many times
the flowers have bloomed?
You are my God Venerable.
Yuanbao...
Don't leave me...
To hell with ascending the mountain!
With my own power alone...
...I will walk the triple cultivation path
of Body Refining, God Venerable, and Demon Venerable!
I will walk the triple cultivation path of Body Refining, God Venerable, and Demon Venerable!
I shall create the God-Demon Body!
And still exterminate
every demon in the world!
God-Demon Body...
...activate!
The Cangyuan World has long been riddled with holes.
The Two Worlds Island
can barely hold on any longer.
You won't save it?
Then just sit up there
and watch carefully.
Watch how I, Meng Chuan...
...will save this world!
My descendants...
...all quite like the Cangyuan World.
They say...
Human necks...
...snap so easily.
I shook my head in disdain.
They say...
Human life is full of wonders.
I opened my mouth and yawned.
But...
Actually...
I'm so jealous I'm going insane.
And now...
I've been in the Cangyuan World
for three months.
This...
...has been the happiest time
of my entire life.
Everything about humans...
...is just so fascinating.
Cangyuan...
Qianqu...
Three months ago...
I thought after saving Yan Baimao...
I could head straight to Dayue...
...and reinforce Two Worlds Island.
Come out!
Earth Net dogs.
We greet the Patrol Lord!
What Patrol Lord?
Get lost!
Good dogs don't block the road.
My lord...
Xue Ku's corpse has vanished.
Thousand Demon Sage...
...is still in the Cangyuan World.
Meng Chuan...
Last time, even you and
King Anhai together...
...couldn't do anything to me.
This time, just you alone
won't be enough.
Why don't you let me go this once...
...and let me have a little more fun?
Sure.
I'll...
...play you to death.
Achuan...
This Qian Demon's strength...
...has at least recovered
to the level of a top-tier Fourth Firmament Demon King.
Don't worry.
I can kill you.
You scared the hell out of me, Meng Chuan!
The power you're displaying now...
...is enough to match a Seamless Realm God Venerable.
Even if you've grasped the power of a Demon Venerable...
...you shouldn't have grown this fast.
Your current state...
...is very wrong, Meng Chuan.
Neither fully god nor demon.
Killing intent soaring to the heavens.
I see now.
You've fused the paths of God Venerable and Demon Venerable...
...and forged an entirely new cultivation road.
Not bad insight.
God-Demon...
You really are reckless and bold.
You don't even understand Demon Venerables,
yet you dare fuse with them?
Achuan!
The God-Demon Core is rampaging again!
There's still time...
Meng Chuan...
You're underestimating the power of a Demon Venerable.
It will devour everything...
Including...
...you.
You.
The moment you become a Demon Venerable...
Your world is destined to be destroyed.
The Demon Venerable has begun to devour you, Achuan!
What God-Demon path?
Just slowly turn into a monster...
...that only knows how to devour.
Meng Chuan...
See you again if fate allows.
But before that...
I'll devour you first.
Meng Chuan, have you gone mad?!
Stop it now!
Devour away...
I'll generously gift you this clone for now.
Let's see how much you can actually swallow.
That Qian guy...
...really poured oil on the fire.
Don't panic.
I'll come in right now...
...and put out the flames.
Achuan...
Below...
Whoa...
So this is...
...the space that represents the Demon Venerable?
Zhuang Sheng...
That is...
...your Three Corpses.
Three Corpses, huh...
Then there are still Nine Worms.
So many ugly monsters inside my body...
They say the Three Corpses are hard to sever...
...and the Nine Worms cannot be destroyed.
They are the root cause of a Demon Venerable losing control.
What's he doing?
Provoking you.
Just a few worms in my gut...
With majestic divine might...
...I command you by imperial decree!
Thunder roars...
Universal Transformation Heavenly Venerable!
And the three of you...
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
These filthy things...
...are actually quite capable.
It seems...
If I cannot sever the Three Corpses...
...this God-Demon path will be extremely difficult to continue.
They might even take advantage of the moment
you activate the God-Demon Body...
...to devour your physical form.
And if I want to sever the Three Corpses...
...my God Venerable power is still not strong enough.
No wonder Qin Wu said...
I must reach the Enfeoffed King realm...
...to balance the powers of God Venerable and Demon Venerable.
According to the notes left by the Ancestral Master...
The five realms of God Venerable are...
Pill Cloud...
Indestructible...
Great Sun...
Dark Star...
Seamless...
And within the final two realms...
...exist specially powerful beings...
...known as Enfeoffed Marquis and Enfeoffed King.
Enfeoffed Marquis wield abilities known as Divine Weapons.
As for Enfeoffed King...
What’s so special about Enfeoffed King?
Come on, tell me!
It’s not written above.
Knowing it now won’t help anyway.
Better to focus on advancing
to the Great Sun Realm first.
Great Sun Realm...
Shouldn’t I advance to the Indestructible Realm first?
You’re already at the peak of Indestructible Realm.
Wake up already.
It’s already been seven days and seven nights...
...since the battle with Qian.
Seven days and seven nights?
Look around you.
No wonder Qian said...
...the Cangyuan World would be finished.
I think I finally understand...
...why the demon race wants to invade Cangyuan.
Their world...
...has already been devoured.
We won’t let that happen.
I’ll slaughter them all.
♪ No matter how turbulent tomorrow may be... ♪
♪ ...even if it blinds my eyes, so what? ♪
♪ I may not see the movements of fate... ♪
♪ ...but my heart remains bright and clear. ♪
♪ I hold my heart in both hands... ♪
♪ Ignoring her... ♪
♪ Exchanging sun and moon... ♪
♪ Whether black or white, I see with my own eyes. ♪
♪ I see all living beings... ♪
♪ ...and grant their wishes. ♪
♪ I know where you’re heading... ♪
♪ Heading above the layered clouds... ♪
♪ There is still a sky... ♪
♪ One world... ♪
♪ We shall go there together. ♪
♪ Body without bright moon... ♪
♪ With mountains and rivers by my side... ♪
♪ I don’t know why I am... ♪
♪ I only want this moment of clarity. ♪
♪ Having seen all the hardships... ♪
♪ With my own body... ♪
♪ I exchange for you by my side. ♪
♪ No need to ask about the color of the sky... ♪
♪ If there is no light... ♪
♪ I will become the Milky Way. ♪
♪ To think I directly broke through... ♪
...from mid Pill Cloud Realm
all the way to peak Indestructible Realm.
This devouring power of the Demon Venerable...
...really is shamelessly overpowered.
Next, I just need to comprehend Saber Intent...
...and I can advance to the Great Sun Realm.
Saber Intent, huh...
I’ll need to find someone who understands it.
Out here in the wilderness...
Where am I supposed to find such a person?
Just go home and ask!
Home...
So chasing Qian...
…actually brought me near Dongning Prefecture
I wonder how everyone’s doing...
...and if they’re all well.
Two Bing!
Hu La!
Come on, come on...
Pay up! Pay up!
I have no money...
Only one life to give.
Found you!
You little brat...
How did you know where I hid my secret stash?
Stand right there!
Clan Leader Grandpa...
That’s all the tricks you’ve got.
Aren’t you embarrassed?
Stop! Stop!
You stinky brat!
Grandpa Meng...
Uncle Qian...
Xiao Ye...
It’s getting late.
Let’s continue our game another day.
Qingping...
You’re still going to the mines?
this one,
That newly arrived Jade Sun Palace Master...
...said the Wang family would jointly manage the mines with us.
But right now, only the Bai family still has a God Venerable.
That mine...
...is clearly being handed over to the Bai family.
In East Dongning Prefecture...
...the Bai family reigns supreme.
Clan Leader Grandpa...
Meng Chuan...
Still no news?
The old master really is...
He only told us not to worry...
...but never said where the young master went.
He didn’t make it to Primordial Mountain...
...so why hasn’t he come home?
Meng Chuan...
Qingping.
About the mine...
...you’d better not go.
But I heard people have been disappearing there lately...
...and they’re all young girls.
I’m afraid the Bai family is behind it again.
Then this old man will accompany you.
No need, Grandpa Meng.
The Meng family...
...doesn’t need to get dragged into this mess.
Sister Qingping...
Miss...
Let’s go.
Sister Wei...
You all better remember this.
You people from Dayue...
...should be grateful you can even beg for scraps here.
Otherwise, if you’d stayed in Dayue...
...you’d only have a path to death.
So work your asses off and be thankful!
People checked.
Checked.
Get on it.
Here.
If it’s not enough, come get more.
Bai Zhu...
Sister-in-law is here.
What brings you here, sister-in-law?
Looking for your little brother-in-law?
Bai Zhu...
I heard women have been disappearing at the mine lately.
What exactly is going on?
About that matter...
I’ve already sent people to investigate.
If sister-in-law is worried...
...you can stay and investigate with me.
Together.
I know this has something to do with you.
I will get to the bottom of it.
Yun Qingping...
Looks like you still don’t understand the situation.
In East Dongning Prefecture now...
I, Bai Zhu, call the shots.
You, Bai Zhu...
...are nothing but a bastard the Bai family God Venerable
sired outside.
How do you know...
...he doesn’t have a second one?
Fine.
You brought this death upon yourself.
Miss...
I told you not to come.
She...
...couldn’t just sit back and do nothing.
What’s wrong?
Why did we stop?
Demons...
Why...
Why are there so many demons rushing over here?!
Take the green bamboo.
Root Technique.
Rakshasa Eight Methods.
Run into the mine!
Open the gate!
There are demons!
Open the gate, quick!
Bai Zhu!
Open the gate!
Brother Zhu...
Are you really not opening it?
What’s wrong?
Can’t bear to lose your sister-in-law?
Bai Zhu...
With majestic divine might...
...I command you by imperial decree!
Thunder roars...
Crush them!
It’s a God Venerable!
It’s him!
God...
God Venerable...
Why didn’t you open the gate just now?
[By tempering the body and refining the blood, one awakens the latent power within the bloodline; through this force, a cultivator can comprehend the principles of heaven and earth, harmonize with the natural order, and gradually transcend mortal limits, ultimately manifesting a divine form and attaining a higher state of existence.]
[“The blade slays evil; the brush paints all life.”]
[The Divine Venerable Form is the core manifestation of a cultivator’s power, formed through the convergence of spirit, will, and comprehension of the Dao; although it appears as a single form, it contains countless variations depending on one’s path and insight, and only by fully understanding and stabilizing this form can one grasp true strength, refine it into reality, and ultimately inscribe one’s complete and perfect name within the realm of the divine.]
[All demons must die.]
[All forms of cultivation ultimately rely on the use of divine power, yet each individual’s foundation and strength differ, resulting in vast disparities; only by continuously refining and accumulating this power can one grow stronger, break through limitations, and fully manifest the Divine Venerable Form, transforming it from an intangible concept into a true and stable existence. The Divine Venerable Form originates within oneself and gradually transforms through cultivation; although the aura it emits may differ in strength and nature, it ultimately reflects the cultivator’s inner will and foundation, and only by continuously refining both body and spirit can one stabilize this power, allowing the Divine Venerable Form to take shape, evolve, and fully manifest its true potential.]
[On the path I tread, nothing can stand in my way.]
[Techniques are the methods through which a cultivator applies their power, integrating their understanding of heaven and earth with personal faith and experience; by mastering various forms of combat arts and skills, one can refine these techniques into distinct realms, each representing a different level of strength and application, ultimately allowing the cultivator to fully express their power through perfected technique.]
[“I will guide all beings across—free from suffering.”]
[The path of Divine Venerable cultivation is divided into five major realms: the Pill Condensation Realm, the Indestructible Realm, the Great Sun Realm, the Dark Star Realm, and the Boundless Realm; each realm represents a profound transformation in power and understanding, marking a cultivator’s steady ascent from mortal limits toward an unfathomable and limitless state of existence.]
[Upon reaching the Pill Condensation Realm, a cultivator begins to give rise to their Divine Venerable Form, though it remains incomplete; advancing into the Indestructible Realm allows this form to stabilize and take shape, while entry into the Great Sun Realm marks the first true manifestation of its power; only after breaking through to the Dark Star Realm can one fully refine and control it, and upon stepping into the Boundless Realm, the Divine Venerable Form becomes complete and perfected, representing the pinnacle of cultivation.]
[After reaching the Boundless Realm, a cultivator may condense a true Divine Venerable Form and step into the level of a titled Divine Venerable; at this stage, one gains deeper control over divine power and begins to establish their own Dao, while continued cultivation allows the form to evolve further, ultimately transcending all limitations, breaking free from the constraints of realms, and achieving a state where one’s Divine Venerable Form stands beyond all boundaries.]
[“I am all beings—and all beings are me.”]
[The Sword Sect follows the path of the sword as its core cultivation system, progressing through stages such as Sword Qi, Sword Light, Sword Intent, Sword Form, Sword Heart, and beyond, each representing a deeper mastery of swordsmanship and understanding; by refining these stages, one advances along a path of unmatched sharpness and precision, where a single sword can break all techniques, reaching a realm where the sword becomes absolute and invincible.]
[“If I die, it will be on the path of slaying demons.”]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™