Impressive.
To fall asleep even like this?
Getting old is like this.
My grandpa was the same.
No matter how many times I look,
it still feels unbelievable.
The God Venerable Statue...
is actually...
being imprisoned.
Resplendent and mighty,
obeying my decree of pardon.
The words "Decree of Pardon"...
likely conceal a great secret.
Looks like I'll have to ask
the Pink Hair Ancestor next time.
Sever the chains upon it,
and I can ascend to the Great Sun Realm.
Correct.
Only attacks containing insights
into Heaven and Earth
can sever the chains
binding them.
Blade Intent—
Thunderbolt Piercing the Sun!
Why?
Why didn't it work?
I'll try once more.
Useless.
It seems
we'll have to seek guidance
from the elders at home.
The elders at home...
What's wrong, Chuan'er?
Chuan'er, this is...
You succeeded in your breakthrough?
Clan Leader,
Great-Grandmother,
did you leave behind
any cultivation notes
from the God Venerable?
After Third Sister left,
after Third Sister departed,
I sealed this courtyard.
Nothing inside has been touched.
I only come every few days
to personally clean it.
The cultivation notes you mentioned—
I have seen them.
They are on the desk.
Go take a look for yourself.
So this is Great-Grandmother's room?
It doesn't look much different
from mine.
Chuan'er,
your Great-Grandmother may not have
given you a pleasant look,
but...
believe in her regard for you.
She knew you were a good child.
But precisely because of that,
she worried.
Your character,
your nature—
made her believe that even after she was gone,
the Meng family, under your leadership,
would not tarnish the integrity
of our Meng lineage.
I never doubted
your qualification to become
a God Venerable.
I did not doubt
whether you could maintain
a kind heart.
But I feared...
that you would suffer terribly
at Yuanchu Mountain.
That place is full of people
like Li Huainan.
In fact,
even that guy counts as decent.
Yuanchu Mountain...
high peaks wrapped in clouds,
it makes one easily lost.
That place...
is not suited for you.
I had considered...
having you abandon the Yuanchu
Mountain trial,
and instead join the army
at the border.
Accumulate military merits
to enter the God Venerable Blood Pool.
Great-Grandmother,
Meng Chuan.
Great-Grandmother has matters
but...
I may not live until that day.
If you ascend Yuanchu Mountain,
those military merits
will automatically transfer
to your name.
You must not speak of this.
I told Pingping and the others
that we spent all our military merits
to exchange for
that God Venerable Jade Marrow Liquid.
But secretly, I saved a portion.
Also, my cultivation insights
from these years...
Hopefully,
they can be of some help to you.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Great-Grandmother cannot do much for you,
but Great-Grandmother
will fight with all her might
to protect you.
and safeguard you all.
Zhuangsheng,
to be born into the Meng family...
is a blessing.
Let's go.
We must make the most of our time.
The book Great-Grandmother left says
that to advance to the Great Sun Realm,
one must comprehend
their own Blade Intent.
The ultimate extreme of form
transforms into intent.
This move is not just about power;
it can also be called
appropriateness.
That "Thunderbolt Piercing the Sun,"
though a Blade Intent,
that "Thunderbolt Piercing the Sun," though a Blade Intent,
was stolen and learned from Baigu.
Its intent is not genuine,
nor is it suited to you.
That is likely the reason for your failure to advance.
My own intent...
the style most suited to me—
the techniques I cultivated before,
whether the Wind Chasing Blade,
the Falling Leaf Blade,
or the Thunderbolt World-Destroying Blade,
even the secret art I comprehended,
"Three Autumns Leaf"—
they can all be called Swift Blades.
they can all be termed Swift Blades.
Even my Thunderbolt power,
even my Thunderbolt power,
prizes speed above all.
also values speed as supreme.
My combat style
has always been to suppress enemies with speed,
seeking one-hit victory.
Among blade techniques,
which move
emphasizes speed
and pursues a one-hit kill?
Among blade techniques,
there is indeed one move
that emphasizes speed
and seeks a one-hit victory.
It is the First Form of the Blade:
The Draw Cut.
How strange and peculiar.
A God Venerable disappeared.
One day has passed,
yet this new Palace Master of Yuyang,
shows no concern or inquiry.
That's right.
This Baigu—
didn't he have a close friendship with that Marquis of Evil Flowers?
If not for that,
he wouldn't have given the mine to the Bai family.
This Marquis of Evil Flowers, Yingshanhong—
for him to come to a small place like Dongning Prefecture...
for the new Palace Master of Yuyang
to be a Marquis of Evil Flowers...
Exactly.
I've heard Grandfather mention
that the Palace Master of Yuyang
is usually held by a God Venerable of the Great Sun Realm.
But why...
has a Marquis-level God Venerable been sent this time?
A Marquis...
You guys say,
this new Palace Master of Yuyang,
is a Marquis-level God Venerable—
Correct.
This new Palace Master of Yuyang
is the one titled Marquis of Evil Flowers,
Yingshanhong.
Either Yuanchu Mountain,
due to your influence, values Dongning Prefecture's safety,
or perhaps there is some other crisis.
This matter...
leave it to me.
Rest assured.
A Marquis, eh?
This is getting interesting.
I hope this Marquis of Evil Flowers
is not a problem.
If I have to face a Marquis,
without using the Godfiend Body,
I'm afraid I can't handle it.
Whether there is a problem or not—
let's inspect the goods first.
Pupil of Primordial Intent.
That is...
The Yuyang Cave Heavens.
They are utilizing the Yuyang Cave Heavens.
They are making use of the Yuyang Cave Heavens.
Concealing what?
I have some suspicions.
Ah Chuan.
What is it?
I still feel something is off.
Find someone to double-check.
Earth Net.
Cheng Gou.
Milord.
Above Dongning Prefecture,
is there a Space-Time Rift?
Just as you predicted.
Milord.
After the Dongning Prefecture battle,
we discovered
above Dongning Prefecture,
a Space-Time Rift had formed.
Though the rift is small,
it is exceptionally stable.
Master, just in case,
specifically dispatched Marquis of Evil Flowers
to garrison here.
This Marquis of Evil Flowers...
is he trustworthy?
Rest assured, Milord.
The Marquis of Evil Flowers
is worthy of trust.
Anyone might betray,
but the Marquis of Evil Flowers
never would.
Why are you so certain?
You do not understand her past.
The Marquis of Evil Flowers harbors
a bone-deep hatred
for the Demon Race and even the Sky Demon Gate.
Can you open the Yuyang Cave Heavens?
This...
Only the Palace Master of Yuyang
holds the method to open
the Yuyang Cave Heavens.
Milord.
Food that runs away.
Qingfeng.
I appreciate it.
Senior Brother,
catch.
Use this
to leave the Yuyang Cave Heavens.
Meng Chuan.
Marquis of Evil Flowers.
Knows me?
You are the World Inspector;
how could this Palace Master
not know you?
Yet Cheng Gou was pounding his chest,
swearing
the Marquis of Evil Flowers
would never rebel.
But Palace Master,
you are filled with...
Demonic aura!
Inspector.
This Palace Master is a law-abiding citizen.
Why is it that the moment you arrived,
you slander me?
She was secretly expanding
the Space-Time Rift.
If you hadn't discovered it early,
a hundred thousand demons
would have appeared in
Dongning Prefecture.
Daring to dig a pit in Dongning Prefecture—
no matter what Marquis you are,
I will execute you on the spot.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™