♪When spring blooms
merge into a moonlit night♪
♪Let tears no more fall,
go dance in pure delight♪
♪Life's but a dream,
savor it, don't just fight♪
♪Be as gentle as moonlight, so bright♪
♪No breeze? Then be the breeze♪
♪Seek dreams without any chains♪
♪No glow? Then be the glow♪
♪Illuminate your own heaven's show♪
♪If I sprint toward the distant call♪
♪Whisper softly, lest I
forget the moon's soft pall♪
♪Dance lightly, let the past
be like a skirt's flow♪
♪Set off with firmer steps, don't slow♪
♪Towards distance, towards home's door♪
- Eclipse of Illusion -
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Minors are advised to watch
with guardian's consent.]
[Do not imitate.]
[Previously on Eclipse of Illusion]
Wait.
Sister and Xian Guang are in danger.
I have to stop Fengyi Wenxue.
In all lifetimes,
I, Shu Yu the White Dragon,
have never regretted helping you.
Shu Yu!
I can't stay with you for now.
Someday,
we'll meet again.
Episode 21
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Shu Yu asked you
to wait for her.
Long'er,
you promised to stay with me forever.
I'll wait, no matter how long it'll take.
After that great battle,
I was gravely wounded.
Only a fragment
of my consciousness remains.
Xian Guang, Sister.
Let's give our daughter a name.
How about Wangshu?
Wangshu? Such a lovely name.
Hush, don't cry.
You'll have more new clothes.
It's a pity my body is still asleep…
Or I'd pull Yun Luoxuan's ears.
The winner of this year's
sect contest is
Yun Wangshu!
Mother.
Wangshu.
Mom…
Sister, wait for me.
I'll recover one day
and come back to you.
No.
Body, move!
I trade my thousand years of cultivation
for a few fleeting moments of your life.
Long'er, you were always there.
But I…
Goddess,
you've obtained the power of the Lumina.
But the divine artifacts
are not yet complete.
Guess this is the end of you.
No… The Sacred Tree
absorbed demonic spirit as it slept.
Lots of that spirit
still remains in it
beside the devine power.
In grief and anger,
the goddess absorbs it carelessly,
letting the demonic spirit enter her body,
awakening her inner demon.
Goddess, stop!
Breaking through with demonic spirit
and inner demon?
Delusional.
You think the inner demon
can be easily tamed?
Purity and corruption entangle,
channels reverse…
The Lord of Splendor Capital
has stepped into demonhood.
Today, let me end you in Heaven's stead.
Oh, yeah?
Seems like you didn't get enough fun
at our last match in the Silent Court,
Elder Fengyi.
Sorry about that.
Heaven-Breaking Stone.
Cloud-Shattering Firestorm!
Fengyi Wenxue?
Everyone's here. What a lively scene.
I'll take my leave then.
Are those tears?
That's not like you.
It shouldn't be like this.
Long'er saved you again.
You finally got Shanhai back,
but he's dead.
You've trained so hard for sixty years,
yet lost even more than before.
The weak should all go to hell, right?
Yan Che was so driven by justice,
but every step he took met resistance.
How are you any different?
Chiyang Huaming saw you as a friend.
But you used her
for the sake of your revenge.
And Lu Qizhao,
a mind as deep as an abyss,
friend or enemy unknown.
He's your greatest threat.
And of course… you.
You failed to protect those who mattered.
You deserve to die most.
Let me live on in your place.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Hold her down!
Lord Xi He.
Master, Lord Xi He is demonized!
Yes.
She's reached Primal Origin Phase.
That's right.
What should I…?
Just cheer for me.
I'll leave you to it then.
God-Binding Mantra!
Let me show you my power.
The power of slaughter.
Xi He.
Goddess, don't!
Lord Xi He!
Yun Wangshu, your methods are too weak.
There's no room for hesitation in revenge.
You must be ruthless, determined.
Assassination.
Murder.
Poisoning.
Ambush.
Framing.
Get them at any cost
by any means necessary.
Even if it means
wiping out an entire sect by mistake,
slaughtering an entire city,
or destroying the whole continent,
you must make them die in the most brutal,
the most painful way imaginable.
For the Sect,
for father,
for Shanhai
and Long'er,
they all must die!
I will kill them in the most vicious way!
Grind their bones
to dust!
Goddess!
Wake up, or I'll…
Lord Xi He, wake up!
Long'er?
I told you.
I'll always be with you.
Long'er, thank you.
Cut what must be cut.
Don't cling to delusion.
Reflect the heavenly light.
Clarity shatters illusion.
Sister, please be happy.
Sever cause, slay the demon.
Now see the true self!
Restrain!
If I go too hard, she'll be hurt,
but right now, I have to…
Master Lu, wait!
Sorry.
It's okay.
Long'er, you saved me again.
Master Lu,
please take Yan Che to the Skyward League.
And tell the Young Master,
Fengyi Wenxue may be plotting against her.
She should be on guard.
Be careful.
Lord Xi He, take care.
Long'er,
have a good rest here.
I'll be back.
Goddess, that inner demon…
I've barely suppressed it.
But the Sacred Tree's power
makes my spirit unstable.
Now, come with me
to retrieve the Life-Pillar Sigil.
Fengyi Wenxue, Yan Qingfei.
I want them torn to pieces.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[Next Time on Eclipse of Illusion]
♪No night so dark
can hide the flame in sight♪
♪Fallen walls crash
down beneath my stride♪
♪Heart torn apart,
reforged blade shines bright♪
♪Why must I yield to marks
I bear by birth♪
♪Why must I accept betrayal
from the earth♪
♪Why is a true heart left unseen,
unheard♪
♪Torn in wastelands, lost in between♪
♪Grasp the sword,
break the chains that bind♪
♪Nightmare or step,
climb the heights to find♪
♪With faith I spark flames♪
♪To burn through all those lies♪
♪Every pain makes bones
more strong and dire♪
♪A single teardrop
reflects the will not to tire♪
♪I cast my challenge into the deep♪
♪I tear the world of chaos, no sleep♪
♪Echoes respond, all things decree♪
♪No night so dark
can hide the flame in sight♪
♪Fallen walls crash
down beneath my stride♪
♪Heart torn apart,
reforged blade shines bright♪
♪Fate may change,
our souls keep the moonlight bright♪
♪Through endless trials,
we break the cocoon's blight♪
♪At the world's peak,
we reach for the sky♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™