♪When spring blooms
merge into a moonlit night♪
♪Let tears no more fall,
go dance in pure delight♪
♪Life's but a dream,
savor it, don't just fight♪
♪Be as gentle as moonlight, so bright♪
♪No breeze? Then be the breeze♪
♪Seek dreams without any chains♪
♪No glow? Then be the glow♪
♪Illuminate your own heaven's show♪
♪If I sprint toward the distant call♪
♪Whisper softly, lest I
forget the moon's soft pall♪
♪Dance lightly, let the past
be like a skirt's flow♪
♪Set off with firmer steps, don't slow♪
♪Towards distance, towards home's door♪
- Eclipse of Illusion -
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Minors are advised to watch
with guardian's consent.]
[Do not imitate.]
[Previously on Eclipse of Illusion]
Breaking through with demonic spirit
and inner demon?
You think
the inner demon
can be easily tamed?
Let me live on in your place.
I told you.
I'll always be with you.
I've barely suppressed it.
Come with me
to retrieve the Life-Pillar Sigil.
I want them torn to pieces.
Episode 22
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Xi He absorbed the Sacred Tree's power,
reached Primal Origin Phase
with demonic spirit and inner demon.
My soul was unstable.
I couldn't fight her off.
Though I retreated at once,
she still got me pretty good.
Her power
is nothing like before.
Xi He's holding three
of the five divine artifacts.
Next, she'll definitely come
for the Life-Pillar Sigil.
She'll never see me coming.
Xi He,
time for us to meet.
The Life-Pillar Sigil is hidden here.
It's said that the blood
of Lumina Goddess can break the seal.
My phoenix blood…
Goddess,
your condition is still unstable.
Maybe…
Time's running out.
I can't wait any longer.
Who is there?
So you are here.
Your blood can unlock
the Sylvane Clan's ward.
Seems you did absorb
the Sacred Tree's power.
Lord Xi He,
the Life-Pillar Sigil is mine now.
I'll gladly
take your life too.
Don't be delusional.
Seems you've changed quite a lot.
Kill her!
Don't let that witch steal the sigil.
I've got your back.
Finally,
I found it.
This relic can revive the fallen,
return lifeless wood to spring.
With it in hand…
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Xi He,
I knew
you wouldn't die that easily.
But coming to get killed again?
That's just arrogance.
We'll see
who gets to live.
You've grown stronger,
but how long can you last?
You stole what was mine.
Now,
it's time to pay the price.
Crimson Shackles.
See the gap between us now?
You're bound by your attachments.
I am not.
Trapped in all your emotions,
you'll never defeat me.
Take your obsessions
and die with them.
I'm about to finish
what he asked.
What?
Attachments and obsessions
are also power.
Why couldn't I sense her?
She should be unable to hide her rage.
Such terrifying killing intent…
That's it.
You haven't disappointed me.
You're a worthy opponent.
Xi He,
you just fueled my bloodlust.
Goddess!
Trying to get yourself killed?
Bring it on then.
Grabbing at straws.
How troublesome.
This place will be your grave.
Mortal joys and sorrows
churn like a tainted tide,
yet you think mere frost and snow
can cleanse the sky.
She blocked it?
Out of your depth.
That speed…
My body
can't move…
No.
No!
You…
Xi He!
Heartfire never ends.
Black Flame, devour the sun!
I'm gonna strike you
with everything I got!
For you,
I have no mercy.
Does killing me
make you happy?
Don't think you've won.
It's just
the beginning.
Goddess,
your wounds.
Take me to Long'er.
Yan Qingfei is gone.
Fengyi Wenxue is next.
Long'er,
I'll keep going.
There's trouble in the Azuren Clan.
It's likely Fengyi Wenxue's doing.
But I have to return at once
to contain it.
I'll bring the Earthwake Sigil
to you as soon as I can.
Fengyi Wenxue must have a few moves left.
Be careful.
[Next Time on Eclipse of Illusion]
♪No night so dark
can hide the flame in sight♪
♪Fallen walls crash
down beneath my stride♪
♪Heart torn apart,
reforged blade shines bright♪
♪Why must I yield to marks
I bear by birth♪
♪Why must I accept betrayal
from the earth♪
♪Why is a true heart left unseen,
unheard♪
♪Torn in wastelands, lost in between♪
♪Grasp the sword,
break the chains that bind♪
♪Nightmare or step,
climb the heights to find♪
♪With faith I spark flames♪
♪To burn through all those lies♪
♪Every pain makes bones
more strong and dire♪
♪A single teardrop
reflects the will not to tire♪
♪I cast my challenge into the deep♪
♪I tear the world of chaos, no sleep♪
♪Echoes respond, all things decree♪
♪No night so dark
can hide the flame in sight♪
♪Fallen walls crash
down beneath my stride♪
♪Heart torn apart,
reforged blade shines bright♪
♪Fate may change,
our souls keep the moonlight bright♪
♪Through endless trials,
we break the cocoon's blight♪
♪At the world's peak,
we reach for the sky♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™