♪When spring blooms
merge into a moonlit night♪
♪Let tears no more fall,
go dance in pure delight♪
♪Life's but a dream,
savor it, don't just fight♪
♪Be as gentle as moonlight, so bright♪
♪No breeze? Then be the breeze♪
♪Seek dreams without any chains♪
♪No glow? Then be the glow♪
♪Illuminate your own heaven's show♪
♪If I sprint toward the distant call♪
♪Whisper softly, lest I
forget the moon's soft pall♪
♪Dance lightly, let the past
be like a skirt's flow♪
♪Set off with firmer steps, don't slow♪
♪Towards distance, towards home's door♪
- Eclipse of Illusion -
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Minors are advised to watch
with guardian's consent.]
[Do not imitate.]
[Previously on Eclipse of Illusion]
Such terrifying killing intent…
Out of your depth.
Don't think you've won.
It's just
the beginning.
Episode 23
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Fengyi Manor]
Lord Fengyi,
the young leader is about to make a move.
She knew you have something to do
with the former leader's death
and secretly ordered Elder Huang
to mobilize forces.
We intercepted this Mindlink Token.
She was asking Xi He
to join forces against you.
Fools.
They'll never escape my grasp.
Yan Qingfei is on her way to kill Xi He.
Come with me to the Skyward League.
I'm gonna ask our young leader, Chiyang,
for something.
Fengyi Wenxue, you're despicable!
How dare you frame the young leader
with this evil formation?
Now it looks like
Chiyang fell into demonic cultivation,
colluded with the demoness Xi He,
conspired with the demon clan,
and sought to plunge Mulingor into chaos.
Today, I'm taking command
as the Fourth Elder
of the Skyward League.
Stand down.
I'll at least leave you in one piece.
Fengyi Wenxue…
Fengyi Wenxue!
You filthy liar!
[Fusang, the Sacred Tree]
The Life-Pillar Sigil
does suppress demonic spirit.
Lord Xi He,
Fengyi Wenxue has broken
into the Skyward League.
Elder Huang burned through his cultivation
to send me here for you.
Lord Xi He, help our young leader.
Hurry, go help Chiyang.
[Altar of Dawnlight, Skyward League]
Well, your mother was cautious indeed,
[Heaven's Core, Central Seal Nexus]
hiding the Heaven's Core
inside your very soul.
No wonder…
Hahaha.
I searched everywhere and found nothing.
Fengyi Wenxue,
what do you want with the Heaven's Core?
Trying to break the seal?
Who do you think you are?
I'm the last surviving bloodline
of the Fengyi Family.
That's why I wanna break the seal
and welcome
Lord Luo Hou.
For a thousand years,
my family has held down the Qiumina rift.
But this world
isn't worth my sacrifice.
Since all their lives were saved by me,
then today,
I'll take them back.
You really are…
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[Gate of Pilgrims
The Front Gate of Skyward League]
One blade, myriad arts!
Charge!
Shatter the void.
Silence the world!
Where's Chiyang?
If you dare hurt her,
I'll slaughter your whole clan!
Well, well, well,
Xi He,
you're taken over by your inner demon.
Someone, seize her!
Fengyi Wenxue!
She's gotten stronger.
[Puppet Form of Chiyang Huaming]
Chiyang?
Such sisterly love.
Let me deepen that bond for you.
A mutual destruction.
Isn't this scene delightful?
Heh heh, hahaha!
He's got the key to the seal,
the Heaven's Core.
Stop her.
[Zhou Wendao, Elder of Terra Sect
Lu Boyan, Elder of Aurora Sect]
If the Life-Pillar Sigil
can suppress demonic spirit,
it can definitely wake Chiyang.
Wake up, Chiyang.
The Sigil needs one incense's time
to purge the taint.
Chiyang, hang on.
[Chiyang Huaming's Mindscape]
Sigil spirit, purify the chaos!
As expected, without the Sigil,
my inner demon…
Xi He!
Oh, no, it's the inner demon.
Xi He,
I'll help you.
Hmph.
Xi He…
Chiyang,
join me.
Let's kill Fengyi Wenxue together.
Okay.
We end this today.
♪A dream that blooms at night♪
♪Fed by vengeance taking root in spite♪
♪Who will calm all my pain♪
♪Ruins blossom in my dreams again♪
♪Tonight the moon is veiled and low♪
♪Fires rise and blaze in a crimson glow♪
♪Blades carve through the bending sky♪
Tai Chi Yin-Yang Formless Formation, rise!
♪Once the sword is drawn,
there's no retreat♪
♪Side by side, we make it to the end♪
♪If you bar our path, steel won't pretend♪
♪My mind is set. Mercy denied♪
♪What fear have I♪
♪What fear have I with miles so wide♪
Heaven and earth hold righteousness.
♪War-flames rise in every land♪
How dare you two speak of it?
♪Don't you dare beg for grace♪
Insolent brats. Cease your nonsense.
♪Time to atone the buried sins you keep♪
Suppress!
♪Who would dare to block my stride♪
♪Let fallen souls fill
all the road I ride♪
Chiyang.
Okay.
♪Though scars on flesh begin to rot♪
Dawncloud Ninth Form.
Sinking sun.
♪My heart still burns♪
Burn the sky!
♪And storm and snow♪
♪From ash I rise♪
♪A cocoon aglow♪
♪My life forged♪
♪Through trial's blaze♪
♪My fate won't bow♪
♪My soul won't fade♪
♪Faith lights up my path of rebirth♪
♪My path of rebirth♪
♪This strike of mine you can't evade♪
♪You can't evade♪
♪What fear have I♪
♪What fear have I with miles so wide♪
♪War-flames rise in every land♪
♪Don't you dare beg for grace♪
♪Night grows deep♪
♪Time to atone the buried sins you keep♪
♪Come scorn me♪
♪Come mock me♪
♪Come break me♪
♪Come face me♪
♪As long as breath still burns in my soul♪
♪You'll never see me lose control♪
♪Everything ends here♪
[Nexus Realm
Hidden Realm of Heaven's Core]
Demon Lord,
our deal is due.
♪What fear have I♪
♪What fear have I with miles so wide♪
♪War-flames rise in every land♪
Em.
♪Don't you dare beg for grace♪
♪Night grows deep♪
♪Time to atone the buried sins you keep♪
You two really don't know when to quit.
Fengyi Wenxue, your turn.
♪What fear have I with miles so wide♪
♪War-flames rise in every land♪
Suspended Breath.
♪Don't you dare beg for grace♪
♪Night grows deep♪
Falling Blaze.
♪Time to atone the buried sins you keep♪
Chiyang, thanks for holding her off
for a moment.
Xi He,
do you know advancing
to Primal Origin Phase with inner demon
is a shortcut to death?
[Mid Primal Origin Phase]
Mid Primal Origin Phase?
He was early phase back in the Chasm.
Rainbreaker!
If one day
[Rainbreaker, Legacy of the Former Leader]
you must fight to the death,
[Early Primal Origin Phase]
use the power inside this dagger.
Mother, thank you
for the strength you left me.
Your mother was really something,
leaving you two fail-safes.
Fengyi Wenxue,
pay for what you did.
And that one…
Heart ripped out, power sealed,
yet you clawed your way back from hell.
Am I right?
Yun Wangshu?
Die!
[Early Primal Origin Phase]
Our strength is worlds apart.
Your struggle is nothing but a joke.
Arrogant fool.
Chiyang, together.
Sunbird, wake the sun!
Candles, move the moon!
Did you find that murderer
with the lightning scar?
He
is Fengyi Wenxue.
[Bonded Heart Token]
It's a secret art from ancient texts.
[Secret Technique in Ancient Texts]
It fuses two techniques,
your Sunbird art and my swordsmanship.
What?
They are striking together?
Shield!
A dual-technique?
Dawn of Wangshu.
Zenith of Chiyang.
Sun and moon in balance!
♪Shining stars, guide my stride♪
♪Burn clean this field
where blood once dried♪
♪Back to back, our spirits flare bright♪
♪Shining stars♪
♪Bear witness here tonight♪
♪Burn down this masquerade♪
♪These foul marks time has made♪
♪Our sharpened light♪
♪Will be the final verdict laid♪
That move is almost
late Primal Origin Phase.
Shame. It's too late.
The time has come.
Ninefold twist of Heaven's Core,
sky, break!
♪Flames roar high and never cease♪
♪This is the mercy I release♪
♪Dawn breaks near♪
♪His puppet-charm♪
♪Burns out in this night♪
♪Flames roar high and never cease♪
♪This is the mercy I release♪
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
[Crystal Diary
Heaven's Core]
[The master key
that upholds the Qiumina Seal,]
[which has been passed down
through generations of League Leaders.]
[It can close any remaining rifts.
Reversing its ninefold rotation]
[briefly opens the outer layer of the
seal, granting access to the hidden realm]
[where the Lumina Goddess placed
the true formation a thousand years ago.]
[After the former Leader
Chiyang Jin's unexpected death,]
[the sigil's whereabouts were concealed
by the Immortal Alliance.]
[It resurfaced in the hands
of the young leader, Chiyang Huaming,]
[when the Qiumina rift erupted
at Mist Moon Sect.]
[Next Time on Eclipse of Illusion]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™