- Martial God Asura S2 -
Episode 9
[Battle at Sword God Valley]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Azure Dragon Sect.
Ancestral Tomb Mountain)
(Ancestral Tomb Mountain)
Today,
I'll destroy your ancestors' tombs
to avenge my son's spirit!
(Azure)
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth.
I'll make Sword God Valley pay.
I'll go with you.
This journey is full of danger.
I can't let you take the risk alone.
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth.
You said that yourself.
If you're willing
to risk your life for me,
then so am I for you.
Okay.
(Azure)
(Tea House)
Shoo!
Do you think this is a charity house?
Boss, give me a pot of Immortal Brew
and some peanuts for my boys.
So, do you think the Azure Dragon Sect
will show up?
Probably not.
When our Valley Master
stormed their sect,
not a single soul was there.
They ran off clean.
Zhang Tianyi killed the Young Master,
took the Divine Wood Sword,
and now he's hiding like a coward.
Digging up their ancestors' graves,
even roasting their bones
over the sword-forging pool?
Our Valley Master is ruthless.
Cross Sword God Valley,
and that's your fate.
Kid, how dare you splash wine
on my face?!
It's wasted on scum like you anyway.
What a waste of good wine.
You!
Why won't it come out?!
It won't budge?
You're Chu Feng of Azure Dragon Sect?
What are you doing?
What's the meaning of this?
Take this!
I've got no grudge against you.
Why draw your blade on me?
The Divine Wood Sword?
Could it be...
What a nice move
that Lightning Triple Strike is!
It just so happens that I know it too.
Hahaha!
After all these years,
I never thought that after me,
Azure Dragon Sect
would finally produce another
who mastered Lightning Triple Strike.
Stop, Senior Tianyi.
I didn't mean
to make things difficult just now.
Sword God Valley is extremely dangerous,
so I had to test you.
That makes some sense
but I'm still not pleased.
Besides,
I've heard this whole disaster
for Azure Dragon Sect
started because of you.
Did you really kill Murong Yu?
We wagered the Divine Wood Sword
and sparred,
but I never harmed him.
Yet rumors say
someone witnessed it firsthand.
Something's not right.
What they saw...
was indeed you.
Murong Yu's death
was Yan Yangtian's doing.
He used this strange artifact
to disguise himself
and pin the blame on you.
He deliberately stirred conflict
between the sects,
so those behind him
could control all of the Nine Provinces.
Both Azure Dragon Sect
and Sword God Valley were just pawns?
But Sword God Valley struck first,
without regard for right or wrong,
and then desecrated our ancestral tombs.
This injustice must be repaid.
Then we'll wipe them out
to the last man.
(Sword God Valley.
Underground Stone Hall)
Ancestor,
all external disciples
have been recalled.
Everything is in place.
We're just waiting for Zhang Tianyi
to walk into our trap.
But he has always kept a low profile,
and now Azure Dragon Sect
has been pushed to this point.
Murong Yu's death seems suspicious.
Yu was Sword God Valley's only future.
(Murong Heng,
Ancestor of Sword God Valley)
(Heaven Martial Fourth Level)
Now he's been killed,
and you're cowering in fear.
Jow will you answer to our ancestors?
But Azure Dragon Sect
has the Jiang Dynasty backing them.
It's just a hollow dynasty,
all show and no substance.
What is there to fear?
Whoever Sword God Valley wants dead,
dies.
Yes, sir.
(Sword God Valley.
Valley Entrance Square)
Their ancestral graves were dug up,
their remains stolen.
Those Azure Dragon Sect cowards
are too scared to even show up.
With the Sword God Formation
left by our founding ancestor
protecting the valley,
no matter how many come,
they'll all die.
Sword God Valley,
your end is here!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Murong Yi, get out here!
You've got some nerve showing up here.
Insolent brat, you have a death wish!
Kill them!
- Kill them!
- Kill!
Avenge the Young Master!
I'll go teach
that blind old fool a lesson
for not knowing right from wrong.
Zhang Tianyi,
I'll rip out your heart today
to honor my son!
You can't even tell right from wrong,
and you dare call yourself
a Valley Master?
I'll deal with the small fry.
(Found it.)
(It's underground.)
(There's a powerful surge
of mystic power.)
It's released by someone at least
at the Heaven Martial Fourth Level.
(Let's split the ground open first.)
Run!
Ancestor, they're here!
Perfect timing.
Today,
I'll use these Azure Dragon Sect scum
as living sacrifices
to activate the Sword God Formation
and avenge my grandson!
Chu Feng, they're being controlled
by the formation
like walking dead.
I'm not afraid of the living.
You think I'll fear the dead?
The remains.
Trying to take them?
Dream on!
You're courting death!
Hahaha.
And you call yourself a Sword Saint?
Why not hand that title
over to me instead?
Zhang Tianyi,
your life ends here!
I'll kill you!
Then try it.
Yi!
You brought this on yourself.
Zhang Tianyi!
First you killed my grandson,
then my son!
Today, I'll carve you to pieces
and grind your bones to ash!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™