- Martial God Asura Season 2  -
Episode 6
[Legendary Warriors Appear]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Location: Misty Forest of the Ten Thousand Demon Mountain]
What about the others?
They’ve all returned to the manor.
Just take care of yourself first.
What’s wrong with you?
This girl hasn’t slept a wink all night.
She worked really hard to save you.
I’m fine.
I just need some rest.
Ziling...
I...
If you want to thank me,
then do me a favor.
It’s the treasure in Ten Thousand Demons Mountain, right?
I only want one martial technique.
You can have everything else.
Right now, Ten Thousand Demons Mountain is full of danger.
It’s clear someone is plotting in the shadows.
But that technique
is extremely important to me.
One extra person
means one more chance of seizing the divine weapon.
Fine. I’ll help you.
Are you sure there’s a secret treasure here?
No mistake.
On the map the Demon Monkey King gave us,
this spot was specially marked.
There must be something unusual about it.
It’s right here.
This statue feels strange.
Better not touch it carelessly.
My grandfather once told me
that my mother’s pipa playing
was unmatched in the world.
Ziling, this statue really shouldn’t—
A mechanism!
Oh no!
This is a realm spirit from the Immortal Spirit Realm.
Its strength is unfathomable.
Hahaha...
This evil spirit’s aura is bizarre.
At least at the first level of Heavenly Martial.
We can’t fight it head-on.
We have to fight with our backs to the wall.
Find its weakness.
You okay?
Hahaha...
Why did she stop attacking?
She’s protecting the statue.
Looks like that’s the key to breaking this.
I’ll draw the evil spirit away.
You take the chance to destroy the statue.
Ziling, be careful!
Dandan,
lend me your power!
First, deal with that evil spirit.
Mm.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Perfect timing.
Trying to run?
White Tiger Assault Art!
Ziling!
You...
Forget about me. Go, quick!
No. I still owe you my life.
I won’t abandon you.
It’s dangerous! Go!
If you want to take her life,
forget it!
Chu Feng...
Good thing it was just an illusion.
Otherwise, someone as foolish as you
wouldn’t have enough lives to spare.
I’m fine. Don’t worry.
A thousand years have passed in the blink of an eye.
Finally, someone has passed the trial.
This is...
the master of this place.
Young man, the path of martial cultivation is endless,
yet in this world, there is only one thing—
love—
that can defy fate
and triumph over heaven.
To save her,
you were willing to give your life.
That is true affection.
The martial technique I left here
is now yours.
Mm.
But you saved my life.
This technique should be...
We had a deal.
I never go back on my word.
Nine-stage martial technique: Phantom Sound Art.
It can disrupt a person’s mind
and even create illusions.
I’m afraid no one across the Nine Provinces has ever seen it.
This array is draining our spiritual energy.
Jie Yan, for your own selfish desires,
you charged in recklessly
without caring if we all die!
Sigh... forget it, forget it.
Let’s go.
That kid really stepped in dog shit luck.
We’re leaving.
Something feels off?
I was thinking...
How could those Demon Kings set up such a meticulous ambush in advance?
You’re suspecting there’s a spy inside the Supreme Manor?
The elite disciples from every sect
were nearly wiped out in Ten Thousand Demons Mountain.
Once you return to the manor,
you must be extra careful.
Then...
I’m going back to cultivate.
We’ll meet again.
Before I break through to the Heavenly Martial Realm,
you’d better not get into any trouble.
Mm.
Saving people comes first.
Brother Jiang.
Jiang Wushang.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™