(Adapted from the Yuewen Group's Qidian Reading novel "Wu Dong Qian Kun")
(Copyright Statement)
(This work is adapted from Yuewen Group's original novel "Wu Dong Qian Kun")
(All characters, visuals, video, and music in this series)
(and all other elements are intellectual property)
(of Shanghai Yuewen Film and Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Minors, please watch only with guardian's permission)
(All content in this film is created by computer simulation)
(Do not imitate in real life)
♪The twists of this fate♪
♪Unwilling to be pulled by illusions♪
♪Thunder patterns reforging my bones♪
♪Refusing to be dull and gray♪
♪The burning between my brows♪
♪Tempering the colors of destiny♪
♪Breaking the shackles on my soul♪
♪Oaths boiling in my blood♪
♪All defiance points to you♪
♪Never kneel to fate♪
♪Never retreat an inch♪
♪Never extinguish my wild heart♪
♪Fight Destiny♪
♪In a flash, martial power moves♪
♪Changing the name of heaven and earth♪
♪Gasping in adversity♪
♪Branded as a mark♪
♪Writing myself at the peak♪
♪My name♪
♪Breaking the shackles on my soul♪
♪Oaths boiling in my blood♪
♪All defiance points to you♪
♪Never kneel to fate♪
♪Never retreat an inch♪
♪Never extinguish my wild heart♪
♪Fight Destiny♪
- Martial Universe S6 -
- Sect Legacy -
Episode 01
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Ancient Secret Treasury Entrance)
(You Quan Dynasty, You Qing, Second Nirvana Realm)
(Hong Huang Dynasty, Hong Lie, Second Nirvana Realm)
(Mo Yan Dynasty, Shi Kun, Second Nirvana Realm)
Gentlemen,
Greetings.
Brother Shi Kun,
I heard your Mo Yan Dynasty has run into some trouble lately.
Just a minor issue.
Thank you for your concern, Brother Hong Lie.
Spending a million Nirvana Pills to hunt a kid from a lesser dynasty—
That’s more than just a minor issue, isn’t it?
You jest, Brother Hong Lie.
A million Nirvana Pills is nothing to Mo Yan Dynasty.
But I heard
you suffered heavy losses fighting Wu Ji Dynasty for the Ancient Secret Key.
If you need, I can lend you some Nirvana Pills, worthy brother.
The Ancient Secret Treasury is full of dangers.
If your strength falls short,
you may enter alive
but not leave alive.
You worry too much, Brother Shi Kun.
Our Hong Huang Dynasty has powerful allies.
Gentlemen,
The fourth key holder still hasn’t appeared.
If he doesn’t show up,
aren’t we all wasting our efforts?
With Brother Shi Kun’s methods,
that kid from the lesser dynasty probably won’t make it.
I wonder which dynasty will catch that fat sheep.
Someone’s finally here.
Someone’s arrived.
Gentlemen,
Which dynasty are you from?
Da Yan Dynasty.
(Da Yan Dynasty, Lin Yan, Lin Dong, First Nirvana Realm)
Lin Dong.
(That’s Lin Dong.)
What?
Lin Dong?
Isn’t he the one Mo Yan Dynasty is hunting?
He’s the fourth Ancient Secret Key holder.
That kid actually survived.
Sorry
to keep you all waiting.
Ran into a few minor troubles on the way.
Brother Shi Kun,
Looks like you won’t be spending that million Nirvana Pills.
Now that all four key holders are here,
let’s open the treasury.
Wait.
Lin Dong,
You killed my brother Shi Xuan.
Today, you’ll pay for it.
Treasure is won by strength.
Shi Xuan failed to take my Ancient Secret Key.
He simply wasn’t strong enough.
You seem quite confident in your strength.
That guy—
Has he reached the peak of Second Nirvana Realm?
Second Nirvana Realm, huh?
Die!
(This kid…)
Essence Energy!
Get lost!
First Nirvana Realm.
Celestial Rune Master.
Big brother!
Don’t worry, Xiao Yan.
He can’t do anything to me.
Second Nirvana Realm.
Doesn’t seem so impressive.
Arrogant!
Purple Shadow Nine Breaks!
Petty trick.
Back off!
Didn’t expect
that kid Lin Dong is actually something.
Golden Demon Heaven Blade!
Slash!
Great Wasteland Heaven Imprisoning Finger!
Five Fingers Move Heaven and Earth!
Break!
Gentlemen,
We struggled to find the Ancient Secret Key
not to watch you settle personal grudges.
Please, that’s enough.
Let’s open the treasury first.
Sister You Qing is right.
We’re all here for
the treasures and martial arts in the Ancient Secret Treasury.
Wasting time here benefits no one.
How about you both take a step back?
Lin Dong,
Our feud isn’t over.
Don’t think you’ll leave the Ancient Secret Treasury alive.
Anytime.
Let’s begin.
Please, everyone, present your Ancient Secret Key.
This…
This is truly spectacular.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
A treasury of this scale—
must hold countless treasures.
Everyone,
If we meet while searching for treasure,
Hong Huang Dynasty will show no mercy.
Let’s go.
Yes.
Why does that guy’s aura feel so familiar?
Go.
Yes.
Senior Brother
What should we do?
Finding the treasure comes first.
We'll deal with that kid later.
Let's go.
Yes.
We should head out too.
This Ancient Secret Treasury
is truly massive.
Xiao Diao
Any ideas?
A sect this size must have
all kinds of rare pills.
Let's go to the Elixir Chamber first.
But where is the Elixir Chamber?
Just follow Master Marten.
Let's move.
Xiao Yan
Kid
Look!
Is that the sect's Elixir Chamber?
Master Marten smelled the strong
scent of pills from far away.
Let's hurry.
(Elixir Storage Pavilion)
Those guys move fast.
They worked hard to get
the Ancient Secret Key.
Of course, they want to profit here.
Big Brother
What should we do?
We go in, of course.
Alright.
Get lost!
All the pills here belong
to Hong Huang Dynasty.
Kid
Stop!
Big Brother
Aren't we taking those Nirvana Pills?
The rare pills must be deeper
in the chamber.
No need to fight them here.
Got it.
Kid
You finally get it.
After seeing the Pill River,
these Nirvana Pills
aren't much anymore.
Looks like broadening your horizons
helped.
Yan Sen
The pills here—
You won't take a single one.
Beat me first, then we'll talk.
The fighting here is even fiercer.
That is—
a pill furnace.
Let Master Marten take a look.
What's wrong?
Xiao Diao
That's—
the Life-Death Cycle Pill.
Life-Death Cycle Pill.
Is that a rare pill?
If a cultivator gets
the Life-Death Cycle Pill,
even if their meridians are broken,
and their Origin Dan shattered,
they can recover completely with it.
That's amazing.
If Master Marten gets it,
he can restore his physical body.
If that's the case,
let's seize the Life-Death Cycle Pill.
Don't worry.
Xiao Diao
Leave the Life-Death Cycle Pill
to me and Xiao Yan.
Second Brother
Your problem is my problem.
You guys—
(You Quan Dynasty Yan Sen
Second Nirvana Realm)
(Hong Huang Dynasty Tian Zhen
- Stop him!
Kid
Wait!
What?
Kid
Looking for trouble!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Climbing the mountain's peak♪
♪Seeking the light at dawn♪
♪Guiding me to a boundless future♪
♪You make me no longer♪
♪compromise for injustice♪
♪With my hands, I place my faith
and chase my dream♪
♪Crossing this wild land♪
♪I find my heart blooming
like a field of flowers♪
♪The journey of dreams never stops♪
♪Passing through endless night♪
♪Lost at times, but still passionate♪
♪With you by my side
to the world's end♪
♪Lucky to walk this path♪
♪With every sunrise and moonset♪
♪You're always by my side♪
♪Heading toward the next journey♪
♪Every moment intertwines♪
♪I'm always behind you♪
♪Looking back from afar♪
♪Defying the world with my choice♪
♪Carving my sincere path♪
♪With you at the world's end♪
♪By my side♪
- Martial Universe S6 -
- Sect Legacy -
(Next Episode Preview)
(Thunder and Wind)