(Adapted from the Yuewen Group's Qidian Reading novel "Martial Universe")
(Copyright Notice)
(This work is adapted from Yuewen Group's original novel "Martial Universe")
(All characters, images, video, and music in this show)
(and all related elements are protected by intellectual property rights)
(Owned by Shanghai Yuewen Film and Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Minor viewers, please watch only with your guardian's permission)
(All content in this film is created through computer simulation)
(Do not imitate any actions in real life)
♪The twists upon this fated road♪
♪I will not yield to hollow pulls♪
♪Thunder marks recast my very bones♪
♪I refuse to live a faded gray♪
♪The burning blaze between my brows♪
♪Tempers and dyes the hue of fate♪
♪Break the shadow chaining my soul♪
♪Oaths are boiling in my blood♪
♪All my wild defiance points to you♪
♪I will not kneel to fate♪
♪I will not yield an inch♪
♪My raging heart will never fade♪
♪I battle destiny♪
♪In a martial breath, an instant♪
♪I trade the world's name and fate♪
♪Gasping within adversity♪
♪Branded as my mark♪
♪At the peak I will inscribe♪
♪My name♪
♪Break the shadow chaining my soul♪
♪Oaths are boiling in my blood♪
♪All my wild defiance points to you♪
♪I will not kneel to fate♪
♪I will not yield an inch♪
♪My raging heart will never fade♪
♪I battle destiny♪
- Martial Universe Season 6 -
- Sect Inheritance -
(Previously on this story)
Darn it
It is a dead end
Here
Why are there so many stone statues here
They guard the sect
Even if it means dying together
- They will not hesitate
- Disciples of the Eight Extremes
I can see it
This is the Eight Extremes Sect
That red array
I think I know where the array core is
The Nirvana Sky-Burning Array
As long as we shatter that stone figure
We should
be able to break the array here
Forgive the offense
To be able to dispel the array here
Brother Lin Dong, you truly have skill
This guy
He can actually control those stone statues
What is going on
It is the guardian beast of this sect
What sustains it
should just be a remnant soul inside its body
You are saying
it is not truly alive
Heaven is truly helping me
Episode 4
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Watch out
This is really troublesome
Brother Lin Dong
Where did that aura you had just now
suddenly disappear to
Just relying on the Demon Dragon Dog
you still dare act so arrogant
Even now
you still dare be this arrogant
Wind-Thunder Seal
Thunder
For me
back off
This brat
Beast
Behave yourself for me
That guy
seems unable to fully control the Demon Dragon Dog
The remnant soul inside it is resisting the Soul Control Art
That fellow's spiritual power
probably will not last much longer
Then let us give him another push
Xiao Yan
Let us go
Okay
You are courting death
(Great Wasteland Heaven Imprisoning Finger)
Great Wasteland
Heaven Imprisoning Finger
Five fingers
move heaven and earth
You think Creation Martial Arts alone can challenge the Demon Dragon Dog
Keep dreaming
To fight me
you are still far from worthy
Darn it
You ambushed me
Get lost
Jerk
You lot
All of you must die
This guy
actually burned out all his mental power
This time
you are dead for sure
Kill them
You asked for it
It seems
there is still a fierce battle ahead
Bring it on
It is finally time for Lord Marten to act
Careful
How can this be
Good boy
Let me give you something nice to taste
Not bad, not bad
It seems
it is a sensible demon beast
Truly
Xiao Diao
What on earth is going on
This kind of Demon Dragon Dog
is not rare in the Demon Domain
Though they carry dragon blood in their bodies
and are very powerful
their temperament is extremely loyal
So many demon clans
use them as guardian beasts
But
how did you tame it so quickly
I guess this Demon Dragon Dog
was also brought from the Demon Domain by someone
Of course it recognizes Lord Marten’s demon power
Remember
Lord Marten is of the Heavenly Demon Marten clan
Any demon beast that sees me
has to behave and show some fear
Lord Marten really is amazing
I am impressed
Second Brother
You are really strong
In that case
we can enter the Eight Extremes Sect’s hidden trove
and see what is inside
What
I understand now
Your duty
is to guard this stone gate
right
What a pity
the sect you are guarding
has long since ceased to exist
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
How about this
come with us instead
Now you have only a single remnant soul left
If you keep staying here
you will only fade away completely
All right, all right
Since you agree
then Lord Marten
will take your remnant soul away
You really are a sensible demon beast
Even though the sect has been destroyed
this Demon Dragon Dog
still guards this place loyally
It is truly admirable
Its master must have
treated it very well
for it to guard this place even now
Let us go
Let us see inside the stone gate
and what is hidden there
Big Brother
Look, quick
Go
There are so many manuals here
This place
what is it
Essence of the Eight Extremes
Those fated may obtain it
Who is there
Boy
Do you still remember before
when you used mental power to gain the sect’s memories
(Eight Extremes Sect mysterious old man)
Greetings, senior
May I ask where this place is
The place of trial
No need for more words
Nirvana Golden Body
Several hours have already passed
Why has Big Brother still not woken up
Stupid tiger
You stand guard here
Lord Marten will go in and take a look
Senior brother
They are from the You Quan Dynasty
Search this place
Yes
What kind of trial is this
He is clearly trying to kill me
Wind-Thunder Seal
Wind
What
So strong
This is
Xiao Diao
Kid
Hang in there
Xiao Diao
That old man is really strange
My attacks
Have no effect on him at all
That body is just a remnant will
Ordinary methods obviously cannot deal with it
Then what can we do
Since he left his remnant will here
He must have hidden some secret within it
Careful
He is attacking again
Kid
Do not clash head on this time
Try to take that palm strike
What
Are you trying to get me killed
When has Lord Diao ever screwed you over
(As expected)
Kid
Suppress that power
Draw it into your Yuan Dan
Easy for you
To say
Lin Dong
Use the Great Sun Thunder Body
To subdue the energy in your body
What do I do what do I do
Go tell Senior Brother Shi Kun
We found something here
Yes
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Climb to the peak of forested hills♪
♪Seek out specks of dawnlight♪
♪Guiding me more firmly to endless futures♪
♪You make me no longer♪
♪Compromise with what is unfair♪
♪With my hands I let faith rest and chase one dream♪
♪Stride across this desolate wild realm♪
♪Then feel my heart in bloom like fields of flowers♪
♪Ah this road of dreams never ever stops♪
♪Passing through these endless nights♪
♪Lost at times yet still burning with fervor♪
♪With you by my side to the land and sea’s end♪
♪Lucky to travel this stretch with you♪
♪With every rising sun and setting moon♪
♪You are always here beside me♪
♪Rushing toward the next road we long for♪
♪As every fleeting moment intersects♪
♪I still stand right behind you♪
♪From afar you turn your head and look back♪
♪At the choice to go against this world♪
♪Etched full with footprints of pure hearts♪
♪With you at the world’s edge of mountains and seas♪
♪With me♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™