(Adapted from the Yuewen Group's Qidian Reading novel "Wu Dong Qian Kun")
(Copyright Statement)
(This work is adapted from Yuewen Group's original novel "Wu Dong Qian Kun")
(All characters, visuals, video, and music in this series)
(and all other elements are intellectual property)
(of Shanghai Yuewen Film and Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Minors, please watch only with guardian's permission)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
♪The twists of this fate♪
♪Unwilling to be pulled by illusions♪
♪Thunder marks reforging my bones♪
♪Refusing to be gray♪
♪The burning between my brows♪
♪Tempering the colors of destiny♪
♪Breaking the shadow of soul's shackles♪
♪The sound of vows boiling in blood♪
♪All defiance points to you♪
♪Never kneel to fate♪
♪Never retreat an inch♪
♪Never extinguish a wild heart♪
♪Fight destiny♪
♪In a moment of martial movement♪
♪Change the name of heaven and earth♪
♪Gasping in adversity♪
♪Branded as a mark♪
♪Writing myself at the peak♪
♪Name♪
♪Breaking the shadow of soul's shackles♪
♪The sound of vows boiling in blood♪
♪All defiance points to you♪
♪Never kneel to fate♪
♪Never retreat an inch♪
♪Never extinguish a wild heart♪
♪Fight destiny♪
- Martial Universe S6 -
- Sect Legacy -
(Previously on)
Kid, what gives you the right to snatch it?
Do you even know what "first come, first served" means?
Only the capable can claim the treasure.
Life-Death Cycle Pill
I'll be taking it.
Kid
Stop chasing.
That pill furnace is shrouded in the power of death.
Xiao Yan
Come with me.
None of you will get the Life-Death Cycle Pill.
That kid is really crazy.
Kid
Were you trying to get yourself killed just now?
If not for the Stone Talisman protecting you,
you...
I promised you
I'd help you get your body back.
Where is this place?
(Tian Gang Alliance)
We'd better be careful.
I bet the Tian Gang Alliance's ruins
aren't this simple.
The entrance...
is gone.
Help me!
Those spirits are...
Episode 03
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Run!
Elder Brother!
Up ahead!
This...
Are you kidding me?
Kid
Over there!
Go!
That was way too close.
Get out of the way!
Leave here, now!
This is way too intense.
Darn it.
It's a dead end.
Like this, we...
can't hold out much longer.
Don't worry, Elder Brother, Second Brother.
I can still hang in there.
What's happening this time?
Looks like...
there shouldn't be any danger here.
What's going on?
Here...
Why are there so many statues here?
These stone figures are really well made.
No idea who made them.
Silly Tiger
These stone figures
weren't crafted.
Could it be...
these were once living people?
These stone figures
have been here for at least a thousand years.
Maybe they're disciples of this sect.
How did they all end up like this?
That, I don't know.
Maybe it's some kind of curse.
- Or maybe a forbidden ritual.
- Disciples of Ba Ji Sect.
Protect the sect.
Even if it means perishing together.
- Defend to the death.
- At any cost.
Slay all Abyssal Demons.
- Protect heaven and earth.
- Even if it means perishing together.
At any cost.
Even if it means perishing together.
- Protect heaven and earth.
- Disciples of Ba Ji Sect.
- Defend to the death.
- Protect the sect.
Slay all Abyssal Demons.
Disciples of Ba Ji Sect.
Protect heaven and earth.
Protect the sect.
Even if it means perishing together.
- At any cost.
- Disciples of Ba Ji Sect.
- Maybe...
- Protect the sect.
It's related to the formation in these ruins.
Kid
What's wrong with you?
You guys...
Did you hear someone talking?
Talking?
Only Second Brother was talking just now.
You silly tiger.
Kid
Did you hear what was said clearly?
It's like...
there are many voices.
Can't make out what they're saying.
Maybe...
it's the lingering spiritual will of these people.
Kid
Try using your spiritual power
to probe this place.
(Tian Gang Alliance)
Elder Brother
How are you?
My spiritual power
has connected with these stone figures.
has formed a link.
Kid
What did you see?
I saw...
this is the Ba Ji Sect.
And what these disciples were fighting against
is the same as the monsters we saw in the Great Wilderness Ancient Stele.
They're the same.
Is there more?
There is.
That red array
and the massive stone gate—
I think I know where the formation core is.
Let's go.
It's right here.
That one—
should be the formation core.
These people—
they sacrificed themselves to this array.
What kind of array
could be so cruel?
This is—
the Nirvana Sky-Burning Array.
Sky-Burning Array...
Nirvana Sky-Burning Array.
Once activated,
it burns everything to ashes.
These disciples
must have been ready to die
when they triggered this array.
Even if it meant perishing together,
they protected the world.
That person—
must have turned himself into the formation core.
If we break that stone figure,
we should
be able to undo the array here.
It's time for these Ba Ji Sect disciples
to be freed.
How could this be?
Elder Brother—
Let me give it a try.
Maybe brute force
will work better.
Looks like this array
was never meant to be undone.
Xiao Yan!
Step back, quick!
This—
is the first time I've felt heat.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
This—
Stone Talisman actually
has this kind of power?
Don't look at Master Marten.
Master Marten doesn't know all the Stone Talisman's powers.
But it seems
the Stone Talisman might
unlock the Sky-Burning Array's core.
Sorry about this.
Looks like the Nirvana Sky-Burning Array
is finally broken.
Let's go.
Let's see what's beyond the gate.
Kid—
Trouble's coming again.
To break the array here—
Brother Lin Dong, you truly are skilled.
Brother Mu Sha—
Is this how you seize treasures?
That's right.
Treasure hunting is all about skill.
Those words—
were spoken by Brother Lin Dong himself.
I'm afraid you alone
can't handle the two of us.
Seems I've been
underestimated by Brother Lin Dong.
Now—
let me show you
the true power of a You Quan Dynasty Celestial Rune Master.
my real skills.
This guy—
can control those stone statues!
That's the Spirit Driving Technique.
Die!
Watch out!
The techniques of these statues
are no joke.
Let's see how long you last.
Lin Dong!
Find a way to deal with the caster first!
Xiao Yan!
Kid—
You think a sneak attack can beat me?
As expected—
you can only use one mental power at a time.
Jerk!
Wind-Thunder Seal!
Thunder!
I won't let you control those statues again!
Darn it!
What's going on?
What kind of beast is that?
It should be a Primordial Demon Dragon Dog.
I'm afraid—
it's the guardian beast of this sect.
Why did it suddenly awaken?
The array's removal must have released it.
But now, this beast
is just a corpse.
What keeps it moving
is only a fragment of its soul inside.
You mean—
it's dead?
Heaven truly helps me!
Darn it, this is bad!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Climbing to the forest's peak♪
♪Seeking the light at dawn♪
♪Guiding me, more certain, to an endless future♪
♪You make me no longer♪
♪compromise for injustice♪
♪With my hands, I place my faith, chasing a dream♪
♪Crossing this wild land♪
♪I find my heart blooming with flowers everywhere♪
♪The journey of dreams never stops♪
♪Passing through endless night♪
♪Sometimes lost, but still passionate♪
♪With you by my side, to the world's end♪
♪Lucky to walk this path♪
♪Every sunrise and moonset♪
♪You're always by my side♪
♪Heading toward the next journey I long for♪
♪Every moment intertwines♪
♪I'm still behind you♪
♪Looking back from afar♪
♪Defying the world's choices♪
♪Carved with sincere footprints♪
♪With you at the world's end♪
♪Stay with me♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™