(Adapted from the Qidian Reading novel "Wu Dong Qian Kun" by Yuewen Group)
(Copyright Statement)
(This work is adapted from the original Yuewen Group novel "Wu Dong Qian Kun")
(All characters, visuals, video, and music in this series)
(and all other elements are intellectual property)
(of Shanghai Yuewen Film and Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Minors should watch only with guardian's permission)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
♪The twists of this fate♪
♪Unwilling to be dragged by illusions♪
♪Thunder marks reforging my bones♪
♪Refusing to be dull and gray♪
♪The burning between my brows♪
♪Tempering the colors of destiny♪
♪Breaking the shackles on my soul♪
♪Oaths boiling in my blood♪
♪All defiance points to you♪
♪Never bow to fate♪
♪Never retreat an inch♪
♪My wild heart never dies♪
♪Fighting destiny♪
♪In a flash of martial movement♪
♪Changing the name of the world♪
♪Gasping in adversity♪
♪Branded as a mark♪
♪Writing myself at the peak♪
♪My name♪
♪Breaking the shackles on my soul♪
♪Oaths boiling in my blood♪
♪All defiance points to you♪
♪Never bow to fate♪
♪Never retreat an inch♪
♪My wild heart never dies♪
♪Fighting destiny♪
- Martial Universe S6 -
- Sect Legacy -
(Previously on)
The Ancient Secret Treasury is full of danger
If your strength is lacking
You may enter alive
But not leave alive
Sorry
Sorry to keep you all waiting
(That's Lin Dong)
Lin Dong
You killed my brother Shi Xuan
Today you must pay the price for it
Treasure is won by strength alone
He just wasn't strong enough
You two
Please, that's enough
Let's open the treasury first
A treasury of this scale
Must hold countless treasures
A sect of this size
Must have all kinds of rare pills
Let's head to the Elixir Chamber first
Kid
Look quickly
That's
The Life-Death Cycle Pill
Stop him
Episode 2
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Kid
Prepare to die
What gives you the right to snatch it
Ever heard of "first come, first served"?
Who cares about "first come, first served"?
Treasure goes to the capable
Darn kid
Yan Sen
Don't even think about it
Kid
Stop chasing
But
Don't worry
They won't get the Life-Death Cycle Pill
Jerk
Life-Death Cycle Pill
I'll be taking it
This...
What's going on
What
What's that
Master Marten sensed it earlier
That pill furnace is covered in Death Force
Death Force
Good thing you warned me earlier
Senior Brother Yan Sen
Quick
Heal me
Yes
Everyone
Disperse that black mist
Yes
Those fools
Do they really think they can disperse Death Force?
Kid
If we can restart the pill furnace
Maybe
We can remove the Death Force
Start the pill furnace
Xiao Yan
Come with me
There's some Spiritual Power left here
It should be the mechanism to start the furnace
Elder Brother
This thing
Can it still be used?
Hit it with all you've got
Yes
Why panic
Give it to me
It's done
Hurry
Lin Dong
That kid
Stop him
Yes
Exploding Wolf Split
Get lost
The Life-Death Cycle Pill is mine
None of you will get the Life-Death Cycle Pill
Jerk
Elder Brother
He really has a death wish
That kid is crazy
This...
How is that possible
That's
The Life-Death Cycle Pill
Take the pill from his hand
Yes
Leave the Life-Death Cycle Pill
Devouring Thunder Palm
(Devouring Thunder Palm)
How...
What's happening
This is...
What power is this
Xiao Yan
Let's go
Okay
Elder Brother
Lin Dong
I will never let you go
Can't believe that kid got away
Elder brother,
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Just inside the formation,
I suffered some internal injuries.
Kid,
Were you trying to get yourself killed just now?
That was the spiritual fire for pill refining.
If not for the Stone Talisman protecting you,
you...
I promised you
I'd help you recover your physical body.
At least you have some conscience.
What's wrong?
Forget it.
Now's not the time.
Master Marten needs to refine a physical body.
It'll take at least several months.
Searching for martial arts and treasures in the Ancient Secret Treasury
means every second counts.
Let's talk about it after we get out.
Xiao Diao,
you...
Stop wasting Master Marten's time.
Your injuries aren't serious, right?
These minor wounds
are nothing to worry about.
If that's the case,
let's move on to the next place.
Where is this place?
Xiao Diao,
(Tian Gang Alliance)
Tian Gang Alliance.
One hundred and eight sects,
sixteen Guardian Sects,
and four Grand Sects.
Tian Gang Alliance.
Looks like the Ancient Secret Treasury
is the ruins of the Tian Gang Alliance.
So many sects gathered here.
No wonder it's so vast.
This must be one of the Alliance's sects.
Not sure which sect, though.
Let's go in and take a look.
Maybe
there are martial arts manuals inside.
We'd better be careful.
The Alliance's ruins
won't be that simple.
Let's go.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Kid,
did you notice?
Since we entered the ruins,
it feels like someone's been watching us.
Elder brother,
the entrance...
is gone.
This place
is really strange.
Let's check it out.
Get out of my way!
Don't kill me!
Help me!
Those spirit entities are...
Xiao Yan!
(You Quan Dynasty, Mu Sha, Celestial Rune Master)
Wind-Thunder Seal!
Thunder!
(Wind-Thunder Seal)
Senior Brother Mu Sha,
check on them.
Yes.
Darn it!
I am Mu Sha of the You Quan Dynasty.
(He's also a Celestial Rune Master.)
Da Yan Dynasty.
Lin Dong.
Brother Lin Dong,
I suppose you came here seeking treasure too?
Of course.
Looks like our luck
isn't so great.
This whole ruin
is guarded by a powerful formation.
Forget treasure—
it's hard enough just to get out alive.
Since it's a formation,
if we find the formation core,
we can break it.
It's not that simple.
This ruin
keeps changing.
No matter where we go,
we end up back here.
We've been exploring here for a while.
You see the result.
I'll investigate myself.
Maybe
I'll find something else.
Farewell.
Brother Lin Dong,
I have a suggestion.
Your strength is impressive.
I truly admire it.
Why don't we
work together to break this formation?
Work together?
That's right.
If we break the formation,
and get the treasure inside,
we split it fifty-fifty.
That benefits us both.
I appreciate your offer,
but I'll have to decline.
However,
my brother and I
never work with outsiders.
Besides, treasure hunting is about skill.
There's no such thing as splitting.
If that's the case,
then I
won't force you, Brother Lin Dong.
Let's go.
Xiao Yan,
Senior Brother Mu Sha,
What now?
Ungrateful fool!
You'll pay for this.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Climbing to the forest's peak♪
♪Seeking the light at dawn♪
♪Guiding me, more certain, to an endless future♪
♪You make me no longer♪
♪compromise for injustice♪
♪With my hands, I place my faith, chasing a dream♪
♪Crossing this wild land♪
♪I find my heart blooming everywhere♪
♪The journey of dreams never stops♪
♪Passing through endless night♪
♪Lost at times, but still passionate♪
♪With you by my side to the world's end♪
♪Lucky to walk this path♪
♪With every sunrise and moonset♪
♪You're always by my side♪
♪Heading toward the next journey I long for♪
♪Every moment intertwines♪
♪I'm behind you, always there♪
♪Looking back from afar♪
♪Defying the world's decisions♪
♪Carving sincere footprints♪
♪With you at the world's end♪
♪Be with me♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™