(Recommended viewing age: eighteen and above)
(Viewers under eighteen years old)
(Please watch only with guardian's permission)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Copyright notice: Zhen Dao Ge animation and all storylines)
(All characters, visuals, video, music, and soundtrack)
(Are property of Changsha Sansan'erchuan Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(No individual, group, or organization without written permission)
(May copy, modify, or edit for commercial use)
(If infringement is discovered)
(Legal and financial responsibility will be pursued)
♪Farewell, a thousand mountains in one night♪
♪Sword in hand, I sing atop the tower♪
♪Where my spirit swallows the clouds♪
♪Never felt like a foreign land♪
♪Three thousand miles in the cold night♪
♪Don't say I won't stay♪
♪No wind, no snow, just a pot of wine♪
♪No waves, no ripples, in a painted boat♪
♪Once gone from the world, no longing remains♪
♪There should be no sorrow in this world♪
♪No wind, no snow, a cup of wine♪
♪No waves, no ripples, in a traveler's boat♪
♪Old friends gone, the rivers and mountains vast♪
♪Clear river stretches to meet the sky♪
♪No wind, no snow, a cup of wine♪
♪No waves, no ripples, in a traveler's boat♪
♪Old friends gone, the rivers and mountains vast♪
♪Clear river stretches to meet the sky♪
♪I have stories of my life♪
♪Only the bright moon listens♪
- On The Edge Season 3 -
- Lone City, Sealed by Snow -
Episode 10
[Blood Feud, Ghosts Beneath the Sword]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Falling Bird's Nest
Heaven Plate Bing Qi
Earth Plate Six Wu
Wang Xi failed
You killed him
He died in the Eight Trigrams Formation
He brought his own destruction
Wang Xi was truly talented
He shouldn't have died so pitifully
He died because of you
No, it was because of the Blade Demon
If not for the Blade Demon
My father wouldn't have died
If my father hadn't died
Ram Gang wouldn't be in this state today
All the blood, all the debts
Must be counted on the Blade Demon's head
You and your master deserve to die
Every cause has its effect
(Jiyang City · Eight Trigrams Formation · Deadly Spot)
If your father hadn't killed for treasure
How would he have died by my master's blade
Ridiculous
Ram Gang already had immense wealth
Our training ground is paved with gold bricks
Why would we steal the Yi Tribe's worthless junk
A father's murder is an unforgivable feud
He Fangzhi
Today, either you die or I perish
I won't perish
Only you will die
Turning back from a wrong path is wise
Only after right and wrong comes understanding
A prodigal's return is worth more than gold
It's not too late to stop at the edge
He Fangzhi
You were raised by the Blade Demon
You can't tell right from wrong
You've committed many evil deeds
You should be beyond forgiveness
But the righteous path shines bright
You deserve a chance to turn to the light
If you help me kill the Blade Demon
We will let the past go
You can still be seen as a fellow martial artist
You came for the treasure too, didn't you
I only wish, for all martial artists
To seek justice from the Blade Demon
Life's journey is full of turmoil
An empty boat can't help but sink
He Fangzhi
The shore is right behind you
Why not turn back
Trust me
Tell me where Jiang Feng is hiding
And the whereabouts of the Crimson Sand Treasure
I only believe those killed by my master's blade
Were all people who deserved to die
Ridiculous
Even my eleven-year-old nephew deserved to die
Jiang Feng slaughtered Ancient Sword Villa years ago
My brother's family of three was wiped out
Including my eleven-year-old nephew
Liu Muyin
Brother
Sister-in-law
Mu... Muyin
Blade Demon, I want you to pay in blood
I traveled day and night
To return and join my brother and sister-in-law
To rid the martial world of evil
But I was still too late
My brother's family of three
None survived
All these years, I swore to avenge my brother's family
Why are you laughing, you drunkard
I'm laughing
What am I laughing at
I just remembered
I'm laughing at someone talking nonsense
What nonsense are you spouting, drunkard
Talk nonsense too much
You probably can't understand real words
You're an accomplice of the Blade Demon
Today I'll show you Sword Creed Manor's Jian Die Sword
Jian Die Twin Sword Technique
(Jian Die Twin Sword Technique)
Th-these two are the Jian Die Swords
You
How do you have these two swords
Who... who are you really
Uncle Lan Yu
(Liu Muyin)
Look closely at who I am
(Fifteen years ago, Ancient Sword Villa)
(Ancient Sword Villa, Liu Pingjun)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(Liu Muyin)
(Ancient Sword Villa, Xu Xun Yin)
Let's do it later
Don't get sunburned
Darn it, something's wrong
Why are there so many injuries
Who did this
Sister-in-law will make him pay
Where did he run off to again
Ancient Sword Villa
Never ask about right or wrong in the martial world
Your sister-in-law set the rules
You're the only one who doesn't listen
My dear brother
You still have the mood to plant flowers here?
Something big has happened in the martial world.
Master of the Manor.
The Ram Gang leader has been killed.
Nonsense.
The Ram Gang rules the Central Plains,
their numbers are strong.
We've seen Leader Guo Changyuan's blade skills.
Few in this world can defeat him.
Brother.
I saw it with my own eyes.
A swordsman.
With just a few moves,
he killed Leader Guo.
What did the swordsman look like?
He wore wolf fangs.
There were totems on his clothes.
He looked like a Crimson Sand tribesman.
Impossible.
My parents' Jian Die Twin Sword Technique
isn't afraid of that.
Every family has its own grudges.
A great gang leader slain with one strike—
this has shocked many in the martial world.
Master, you should seize this chance.
What chance?
Wait for that swordsman to cause a bloodbath.
First, the martial world is wounded.
Second, he himself is weakened.
Then Ancient Sword Villa's Jian Die Twin Swords
strike again.
Ancient Sword Villa's fame will soar.
We can attract more martial artists.
No.
Ancient Sword Villa can't ignore righteousness.
Brother and sister-in-law want to act now.
Jian Die Twin Swords against a broken blade—
that's no problem at all.
You—
Lan Yu.
What's wrong with you today?
You're usually gentle and humble.
Gentle and humble?
If you hadn't listened to a woman's words,
you'd be digging and planting all day.
You're basically the Xu family's hired hand.
And you even call her the manor master.
Ancient Sword Villa would be famous by now.
Even old Guo Changyuan would come
begging to celebrate my birthday.
Ancient Sword Villa's Liu Pingjun and Xu Xunyin—
he is that swordsman.
Guo Changyuan is dead.
Wang Hanqing is dead.
Twenty more to go.
Let this slaughter end with us, husband and wife.
(Jian Die Twin Swords, Yuanyue Sword, Changkong Sword)
Taiji.
The essence of twin swords is Taiji.
Yin and yang give birth to each other.
Twin swords flow like water.
Can you cut water?
I've done it.
If the blade is fast enough,
it can cut water.
Father.
Xiao Mu.
Promise me.
Spare my son.
I promise you.
Stop! I will kill you.
Isn't living better?
Xiao Mu.
Uncle Lan Yu, he killed my parents.
I want revenge.
Xiao Mu, don't be afraid.
I want to be the master of Ancient Sword Villa.
I want everyone to kill the bad guys.
Xiao Mu, don't be afraid.
Uncle Lan Yu will avenge you.
Brother.
Let the whole family leave together.
Leaving Xiao Mu alone, he'll be lonely.
Ancient Sword Villa.
I'll take care of it for you.
You—
You are Xiao Mu.
Uncle Lan Yu, oh Uncle Lan Yu.
You finally remember me.
Liu Muyin was killed by the Blade Demon
over ten years ago.
I won't let you spread lies here.
If you want to be dead so badly,
(Jian Die Sword Technique)
let my Jian Die Sword send you off again.
Darn it.
What the heck is this?
He Fangzhi.
Today, my father's grudge—
Uncle Huangfu and Wang Xi's grudge—
I, Guo Shengying, will avenge them all.
With those few moves of yours,
you're just an old turtle flailing in the mud.
And you dare call it Jian Die Sword?
Father, mother—
Today I'll use Jian Die Sword Technique
to cleanse our home for you.
Your sword technique—
Uncle Lan Yu—
Why do you seek death yourself?
You're my last family in this world.
Ten years to hone a sword,
yet never cut off the enemy's head.
A broken body burned by fire.
This hatred remains.
Deep.
Every grudge has its source.
It was your master who killed my parents.
Tell me where the Blade Demon hides.
I'll let King of the Border's orders go to hell.
Help you pass through this Eight Trigrams Formation.
Your parents knew their own faults.
They faced death bravely.
They only hoped you'd live well.
Why do you cling to this obsession?
My parents were known for their integrity.
They did no wrong.
He Fangzhi has only a fraction
of the Blade Demon's power.
Yet he's so hard to defeat.
I barely kept my life.
I've chased the Blade Demon for over ten years.
If I really meet him,
how could I avenge my parents?
With a sword, there is life.
I respect it.
Honor it.
Love it.
It protects me.
Shields me.
Cares for me.
Slowly,
I become it.
It becomes me.
(Duan Hun Three Techniques, Madness)
He Fangzhi.
Just kill me.
I won't kill you.
If you have the skill, seek my master
for revenge.
You are free to go.
I was once like you.
Stepped into this whirlpool.
My hands were stained with blood.
Since you survived disaster,
then live well.
As long as you live,
the Jian Die Sword Technique and Ancient Sword Villa
will endure.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Moonlight shines on all sides♪
♪Illuminates the vast waters of the world♪
♪Winds rush, waves rise high♪
♪Families torn, scattered far apart♪
♪Mountains far, waters long♪
♪Life and death meet today♪
♪Hearts uneasy, minds adrift♪
♪Bright moon shines at the world's edge♪
♪A journey of wind, a journey of rain♪
♪Mountains and rivers, paths never cross♪
♪Swift green scales, deep parting sorrow♪
♪A fleeting dream, too brief to hold♪
♪Wide river flows, blood runs red♪
♪White waves surge, drifting east and west♪
♪Dark rivers and lakes, bright starry sky♪
♪This light boat sails on, never stopping♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™