(Recommended viewing age: eighteen and above)
(Viewers under eighteen years old)
(Please watch only with guardian's consent)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Copyright notice: Zhen Dao Ge animation and all storylines)
(All characters, visuals, video, music, and soundtrack)
(Are owned by Changsha Sansan'erchuan Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(No individual, group, or organization without written permission)
(May copy, modify, or edit for commercial use)
(If infringement is discovered)
(Legal and financial liability will be pursued)
♪A night's farewell, past mountains without end♪
♪Sword in hand, singing atop high towers♪
♪Where spirit swallows the clouds♪
♪Never felt like a foreign land♪
♪Three thousand miles of cold night♪
♪Don't say I won't stay♪
♪No wind, no snow, a pot of wine♪
♪No waves, no ripples, in a painted boat♪
♪Worldly ties gone, no lingering love♪
♪Life should be free of parting sorrow♪
♪No wind, no snow, a cup of wine♪
♪No waves, no ripples, in a traveler's boat♪
♪Old friends gone, mountains and rivers vast♪
♪Clear river stretches, joining earth and sky♪
♪No wind, no snow, a cup of wine♪
♪No waves, no ripples, in a traveler's boat♪
♪Old friends gone, mountains and rivers vast♪
♪Clear river stretches, joining earth and sky♪
♪I have stories of my life♪
♪Only the bright moon listens♪
- On The Edge Season 3  -
- Lone City, Sealed by Snow -
Episode 11
[Tears of Parted Souls, Hatred of Floating Life]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Jiyang City · Eight Trigrams Formation · Deadly Point)
(General's Mansion)
(In memory of Wang Duo, mourned by his father Wang Lang)
Old friends have gone, returned to their land
Why let new wine recall old sorrow
That year, I entered enemy lines alone, broke their defense
Soon after, my son was born
Great merit from victory
When he turned one
I placed all things before him
Yet he loved only this little peachwood sword
I named him Wang Duo
Hoping one day he'd slay generals and seize banners
Guard the border, reclaim land
When he was five
It was New Year's Eve
I gave him ten coins as New Year's gift
I thought he'd buy firecrackers
But he gave all the coins he'd saved
To the beggars on the street
I asked
Duo, my son
Don't you want to keep some for yourself
Guess what he said
He said, Dad
(In memory of Wang Duo, mourned by his father Wang Lang)
At the end, startled by wind and rain
Poor border, full of snow and frost
It's Wen Tianxiang
He blurted out
It was Wen Tianxiang's poem
At that time
I thought my son would surely become a scholar
How interesting, how amusing
Inside high walls, noble children
Become generals, become scholars
Outside the walls, beggars
At the border, day and night, living on wind and snow
Though I've known Brother Liu for years
I know Old Beggar Liu Wukou seems penniless
But is worth a thousand gold
Helping us this time
I am deeply grateful
If there's anything Brother Liu fancies here
Just say the word
What could I possibly want
I have no children
Living in this world
Just a bowl of food, a ladle of drink
I just want to know
How mad this Blade Demon is
Just how mad
General
Urgent news from the border
Enemy troops move out on a snowy night
They're marching south
(In memory of Wang Duo, mourned by his father Wang Lang)
Jiyang City will face a great battle
Prepare yourselves well
The battle the General speaks of
Is not that battle, right
Soldiers just follow orders
Is the General really abandoning the front fort
Stand down
General
No battle is ever too late
After this, battles will never end
But for Duo's revenge
This is the only chance
(In memory of Wang Duo, mourned by his father Wang Lang)
Is General Wang explaining himself to someone
Just be clear about what you want
All this old beggar wants
Is just a contest
It's New Year's Eve
(The third day)
Someday, I will take the Blade Demon's head
Danger in Kan, enter Kan
Ominous, time is not right
Drowning
Not good
One more drumbeat
The underground palace will be flooded
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Hanqing, go back
Who
No, no, you can't
Grudges can't be ended
Can't be ended
You made a grave mistake back then
Don't make another mistake
I did nothing wrong
I acted out of kindness then
Helped the court escort the Crimson Sand Tribe
What's wrong with that
They did the killing
They did the dirty deeds
I am blameless
Your mistake isn't in the past
But now
A life has been repaid
Grudges are settled
Dust to dust, earth to earth
Grudges can't be ended
A life for a life
If you don't avenge this
How can you live with yourself
I
Little
Little... Little Blade Demon
He... He's here.
Little Blade Demon
You came at the perfect time.
Quick, tell me where the Blade Demon is.
I can let you die with your body intact.
You came at the perfect time.
Little Blade Demon
Quick, tell me where the Blade Demon is.
I can let you die with your body intact.
Every second counts.
Go help Brother He.
Leave these people to me.
Then be careful.
Since we're caught in this mess,
we must be ready to face the consequences.
If you can't bear it,
you'll end up dead and bleeding.
You must always live up to being honorable.
Of course I'm honorable.
But he killed you.
You can let go of your own life and death,
but if I do the same,
that would be dishonorable.
Hanqing
My life lives on in you.
Only if you live, my death has meaning.
Living...
These past ten-plus years,
I've lived in constant fear,
hiding like a rat everywhere.
Every night, nightmares wake me.
I'm tormented by hatred and regret all the time.
This...
Is this really living?
Coward!
Why aren't you fighting?
Hurry, get out!
The water's about to flood in!
All your years of hard training
were for this day, to get revenge.
You still don't understand.
Everything today is the fate we deserve.
If you don't let go now,
the burden will only grow heavier.
- Enough, enough!
- Only by living...
Both of you, shut up!
I've had enough.
Blade Demon
The Blade Demon is here!
Isn't that the old man who worked on the boat?
How dare you!
Open your eyes and look closely.
I am the Green Snake Sword of the Dinghu Sect.
(Dinghu Sect, Wang Hanqing)
Wang Hanqing
Dinghu's lone master, Green Snake smiles.
Sword points at the land, chills the world.
They say Dinghu Sect's skills are unfathomable.
But it's been over ten years since any news.
Some say Dinghu Sect is gone.
But the Green Snake Sword remains.
Who dares say Dinghu Sect is gone?
(Green Snake Sword)
Looks like Dinghu Sect's martial arts are impressive.
You actually survived the Blade Demon.
The Blade Demon kills without mercy.
He never lets anyone escape alive.
I'm still alive
only because he thought I was dead.
(Fifteen years ago, Dinghu Sect)
(Dinghu Sect, Wang Hanjiang)
Master! Master!
You're back already?
(Dinghu Sect disciple, Qi Jin)
So it's Uncle Master.
Where's your master?
Master said the martial world is troubled lately.
He went to find the official from back then to get answers.
Which official?
What kind of leader?
That's all Master said.
Uncle Master
There's someone over there.
Don't be afraid.
Uncle Master will drive him away.
You're Wang Hanqing.
Who are you?
Jiang Feng of the Crimson Sand Tribe.
I've come to take your life.
Jiang Feng
A nobody in the martial world.
Such arrogance.
(A few days later)
(Dinghu Sect, Wang Hanqing)
What are you doing here?
Master
I've been searching for days,
but I can't find Uncle Master's body.
Those big fish you feed must've eaten him.
What happened?
A man named Jiang Feng came a few days ago.
He said he wanted revenge on you, Master.
But before he said much,
he split Uncle Master in two with just two strikes.
Jiang Feng has found this place.
Master
Where is your official leader?
Let's find him and avenge Uncle Master together.
He was a Jinwu Guard back then.
But now, there's no such person in the capital.
Two strikes...
You mean...
Just two strikes
and Jiang Feng killed my brother?
Master
Are you scared now?
Afraid to avenge Uncle Master?
No.
That's not it.
I can't leave my brother unavenged.
I want...
I need to plan carefully.
Only you know he killed Hanjiang,
not me.
Master
Back then, I acted with you
all to serve the court.
Who knew we'd anger that demon?
But the court abandoned us.
You don't know his whereabouts either.
Pity my brother who died in vain.
You've been hiding for fifteen years.
Has your hatred
ever faded?
It's been years since we met.
Your skills have improved so much.
Now you're deceiving my brother again.
What's your motive?
You know where the Blade Demon is.
In one month,
the Blade Demon's disciple will be trapped in Jiyang City.
Kill him,
and the Blade Demon will surely appear.
Go or not,
it's your choice.
Darn it, it should've been me.
I'm a wandering, lonely soul.
I've roamed this world for so many years.
Back then, I just wanted to serve the court.
But it ended up like that.
It wasn't my fault.
No one ever gave me an answer.
Yet I have to bear all of this.
It's not fair. This isn't fair.
Since I've hidden for so many years,
why can't I let go of grudges?
Why suffer, old and weary, traveling so far?
Coming to this bitter land, just a pawn.
Grudges can't be settled.
No, I can't.
No.
I am Wang Hanqing, the Green Snake Sword.
I, Wang Hanqing, Green Snake Sword,
have always served the court loyally.
Is that wrong?
If I can't escape,
then I might as well root out the problem.
Big demon, little demon, none shall remain.
I, Wang Hanqing, am an upright man.
But now, a tiger fallen is mocked by dogs.
Must I take lessons from a youngster like you?
Brother Zhou.
(Soul-Severing Three Ultimates, madness)
Wind-Breaking Saber Technique.
I've pondered for fifteen years.
Now, it means little to me.
The past was just a dream.
There's no Jiang Feng.
No He Fangzhi, either.
Not even myself.
Tomorrow, when I wake,
nothing will have happened.
Dinghu Sect still stands.
Everything remains.
Hanqing.
Dinghu Sect truly remains.
Dinghu Sect still stands.
Qi Jin, head south.
Go as far as you can.
Don't look back.
Master.
I'm no longer your master.
Go.
It's over. Let's leave.
Brother Zhou.
Why aren't you leaving yet?
When the flood comes,
even wings can't save you.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Moonlight bright, shines all around♪
♪Shining over endless waters below♪
♪Winds rush, waves rise high♪
♪Families torn, scattered far apart♪
♪Mountains far, rivers long♪
♪Life and death meet today♪
♪Hearts anxious, minds adrift♪
♪Moon shines bright at the world's end♪
♪A journey of wind, a journey of rain♪
♪Mountains and rivers, paths never cross♪
♪Green scales swift, parting sorrow deep♪
♪A fleeting dream, gone too soon♪
♪Rivers wide, blood runs red♪
♪White waves surge, east and west♪
♪Dark rivers, bright stars above♪
♪This light boat sails on, never stopping♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™