♪Light♪
♪In a world of darkness, light guides
the lost along their way♪
♪Heavy dust covers old wounds
deep inside my heart♪
♪Time turns to streams, merging
into rivers, flowing away♪
♪Staring at my reflection,
I seem more ordinary each time♪
♪Death to blasphemers♪
♪Searching for light in the darkness♪
♪Even if all that's left is stubbornness♪
♪Who decides good and evil,
and by what measure?♪
♪Dreams and reality are in conflict♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪Even if all that's left are wounds♪
♪Blood sweeps the land—how do we resist?♪
♪Dawn will break through confusion♪
- Purple River S2 -
- King of Light -
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, please watch with guardian's consent)
(All content is set in a fictional world)
(Skills and mystical powers are fictional)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Adapted from Lao Zhu's epic novel "Zi Chuan")
(Previously)
Why do you have Blood Eye too?
Because
We are the same kind
Lu Di
These two hundred fifty thousand troops
How do you plan to handle them?
Talan Fortress
And my fifty thousand soldiers
I can help Your Highness make them surrender
Defend the city
We do not accept Demon Race's surrender
And we won't help that darn Lu Di
defend Talan Fortress
You lead your troops over
I'll handle the supplies
Attack the city
What's happened?
Lu Di's men have rebelled
Confiscate their weapons
Send them to the POW camp
Duke
Those Jinglan Towers
My Lord
Leave it to me
(Talan Fortress)
Episode 19
(Talan Battle, Part 2)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Imperial Year 782, June 27)
Hurry
This darn weather
Has delayed us almost a day again
No idea how things are for My Lord
No routed troops along the way
Means the fortress is still ours
Roger
I have an idea
Baichuan
You're not my type
I like
Alright
Go ahead
Talan Fortress is besieged by Ross
If we enter now
Aren't we walking into a trap?
You mean
We split our forces
I bypass Talan Fortress
and strike directly at Ross's rear
(Talan Fortress)
Attack with My Lord from both sides
You lead the Huo Regiment to raid Yalu City behind Ross
Without supplies from there
Ross, win or lose
can't stay in the Far East
Good idea
But detouring
may cost us another half day
When in the field
Act as needed in emergencies
It's settled
If My Lord blames us, I'll take it
(Ross Legion, Oule Legion, King of Light Legion)
Once the enemy is in range
Open fire for cover immediately
Yes
Brothers
See those big ones?
- Yes
Take them down
Fire
Cease fire
Get ready to blast 'em
Bring the bow
Zhaocai
Take out the Jinglan Towers
- Yes
Storm
is coming soon
My Lord means
we're in for a tough fight?
Darn tough fight
Once it rains
How do we burn the Jinglan Towers?
Archers
Fire!
My Lord
Enemy is two hundred meters from the north gate
Could attack any moment
My Lord
Rebels inside the city are rioting again
Your Highness
We can't do this without you
(Baichuan)
(Why aren't you here yet?)
Green-skinned Barbarians
Come on
I'll give you good food
Zhaocai
We
didn't let My Lord down
Lord
What now?
Send in all our troops
I don't believe
two hundred thousand troops
can't take Talan Fortress
(Ross Legion, Oule Legion, King of Light Legion)
What is that darn Oule doing?
Why aren't they attacking?
Lord
Stop fighting
Let our Tarta Tribe survive
Oule is clearly sending us to die
So you think
Who should be sent to suppress the rebellion?
So it's Your Majesty's scheme
No wonder
Retreat
Third Regiment
Hurry
They're retreating
Finally, they've retreated
Follow me out of the city
Yes
Why leave the city?
Take the brothers
home
What about the battering logs?
The full assault is about to begin.
Gu Lei.
Move all the troops from the north gate.
Th-th-then...
What about the north gate?
Lu Di.
What about those rebel soldiers?
They're here.
You don't mean to have them defend the city?
Make them all stand on the city wall.
Don't issue them any weapons.
Yes.
(Baichuan)
Attack the city!
- Sem Hei Lin!
Lord.
What is it?
The east gate has launched a full assault.
What should we do?
Should we attack the city?
How are the Tarta Tribe's casualties?
Heavy losses.
Ross has been like a madman these days.
He keeps sending waves of attacks.
At least a third of their forces are lost.
No rush.
Wait until their casualties are over half.
Then we'll make our move.
Yes.
Kill!
(Ross Legion, Oule Legion, King of Light Legion)
Hold the line!
I'll fight you to the end!
Sem Hei Lin!
Hold fast!
Hang in there!
The gate is breached!
- Long live the King of Light!
- Kill all these green-skinned bastards!
- Kill!
(Ross Legion, Oule Legion, King of Light Legion)
Lord.
A large Far East Army is charging from the rear.
What?
Feng Regiment, listen up!
Left wing, follow me to aid the east gate.
Right wing, strike straight at the north gate enemy.
Yes.
Then...
Are those our people?
Hold formation.
Enemy reinforcements have arrived.
Counterattack out of the city!
Wait for my command!
Lord.
Retreat.
Retreat!
Enemy attack!
Regroup and counterattack!
Where is everyone?
Hold your weapons tight.
Lord.
This is bad!
The Far East Army is attacking!
Where did the Far East Army come from?
Quick, protect the Lord and break out!
My cricket!
M-my Lord...
My Lord.
Bai...
General Baichuan and his men...
...are coming.
Second Division, clear the battlefield quickly.
Everyone else, assemble at once.
Follow me into the city.
Bai... Bai...
Just get to the point.
M-my Lord said...
...for you to...
...set up camp outside the city.
(Li Wangwu, Jiang Jia)
M-my Lord...
Lord Baichuan.
...is outside.
Let her in.
Yes.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
My Lord.
Is something the matter?
Baichuan is here to ask for forgiveness.
You have done nothing wrong.
You saved us.
You saved Talan Fortress.
You deserve merit.
I missed the marching date.
I was two days late.
Because of the heavy rain.
I know.
I changed the marching route on my own.
I didn't follow your orders.
I didn't come to Talan Fortress to join forces.
Baichuan.
Do you know...
Duke is dead.
I know.
Then why didn't you come as I ordered?
If it were you, My Lord...
...what would you have done?
If you had entered the city earlier...
...maybe Duke and the others would have survived.
As for military tactics...
I don't want to explain further.
You know more about this than I do.
All I can say...
...is I made the best choice.
In your mind...
...the lives of those soldiers...
...whose lives matter more or less?
The higher your position...
...the fewer choices you have.
That's what you said before.
You're right.
Get up.
My Lord.
There's something I shouldn't say...
Since you returned from Shangdu...
...you've become...
...cold and suspicious.
Is that so?
If you can't accept my ways...
...you can leave at any time.
I've prepared pensions for all of you.
Enough for you to live out your days in comfort.
My Lord.
You must not...
...insult someone who follows you with their life.
If we make mistakes...
...you can scold or punish us.
But our loyalty to you is always pure.
I have overstepped my bounds.
No matter what, I disobeyed orders.
I am willing to accept punishment.
To uphold your authority.
(Duke, Zeng Xiaotian, Buzhen, Lin Chuan)
Sorry
You really have quite a temper
My
Lord
My Lord
What's wrong
A letter
For you
Where did it come from
That day
The one wearing
The man in the black cloak delivered it
Black cloak
It was him
(Far East
Wasteland Hills)
Lord
What do we do now
We've lost Yalu City too
Those Far East Army men are like madmen
They've chased us for five days and nights
We really can't run anymore
Lord
The Far East Army is catching up
How many
One
Just one person
He says he's
King of Light
Lord
Long time no see
You have real courage
This battle
You really made me lose badly
The one who put you in this position
Wasn't me
It was Your Majesty
I wonder, Lord
What do you plan to do next
Next
The Tarta Tribe, second largest of the Demon Race
Has always been the Demon God Emperor's main concern
Even if I withdraw my defenses
Do you think
He would let you go
What do you mean
I'm afraid you don't know, Lord
The Demon God Emperor has announced
Support for your nephew, Rod
To continue as Tarta Tribe chief
I heard you and Rod have always been at odds
And now you've suffered a great defeat
Returning home this time
I'm afraid your future is uncertain
Are you trying to sow discord
Whether it's discord
You'll know once you return, Lord
I came here
First, to see you off
Second
To give you a reminder
Whether you believe it
Is up to you
You really plan to let us go back
Of course
Why
We in the Far East hope
To have a more
Wise and merciful Demon God Emperor to lead us
And personally
I sincerely hope that person
Is you, Lord
If you wish to vie for the throne
We of the Far East
Will be the first to pledge loyalty
Farewell
Your Highness, King of Light
Why did you just now
Say "long time no see"
Have we met before
It was you
It was me
(One month later
Demon Race Demon God Castle Imperial Garden)
Your Majesty
Ross killed his nephew
And declared war on our Senea Tribe
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪War horses rush, smoke sharpens blades♪
♪In troubled times, where can longing meet♪
♪Life slips by, years cannot be held♪
♪Just to keep the homeland's flame burning bright♪
♪Treading the path of war and fire♪
♪Only for wild ambition♪
♪Brave and loyal, fighting everywhere♪
♪Virtue guards our faith♪
♪Who still gazes at their homeland♪
♪Waiting for hoofbeats past the window♪
♪Waiting for a heart to speak its truth♪
♪Wandering through life's warmth and cold♪
♪Singing, unafraid of wind and rain♪
♪Zi Chuan, forged in a hundred battles♪
♪A lifetime of passion and grandeur♪
♪You and I, unmatched in our blood♪
♪Filling the joys and sorrows of time with glory♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™