♪Light♪
♪In a world of darkness, light guides
the lost to walk their path♪
♪Heavy dust covers old wounds
deep inside my heart♪
♪Time turns to streams, merging
into rivers, flowing away♪
♪Staring at my reflection,
I seem more ordinary each time♪
♪Death to blasphemers♪
♪Searching for light in the dark♪
♪Even if all that's left is stubbornness♪
♪Who defines good and evil,
and by what measure?♪
♪Dreams and reality are clashing♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪Even if all that's left are wounds♪
♪Blood sweeps the land—how do we resist?♪
♪Dawn will break through confusion♪
- Purple River S2 -
- KING OF LIGHT -
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, please watch with guardian's consent)
(All content is set in a fictional world)
(Skills and powers are entirely fictional)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Adapted from Lao Zhu's epic novel "Zi Chuan")
(Previously)
Lu Di lost Far East—
and even tried to kill the messenger
seeking help at Telan Fortress.
The Divine Race isn't just our Senea Tribe.
For example, the Tarta Tribe.
Their strength is nearly equal to ours.
This inevitably stirs those
who covet the Divine Emperor's throne—
they're starting to make moves.
I am willing to lead the Tarta forces—
to Far East, to quell the rebellion.
This time—
the Tarta Tribe
is no longer a threat.
From today on, Lu Di
will be loyal to His Highness, King of Light.
No betrayal, ever.
Who?
Zi Chuan Xiu.
(Telan Fortress)
EPISODE 18
(Telan Battle, Part 1)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Someone, help!
There's an assassin!
My lord!
Catch him—quick!
I didn't expect—
you're still alive.
What?
Surprised?
A little.
Don't look at me like that.
I won't kill you.
Why should I trust you?
If I'd been at the door just now—
I’d probably
be in pieces by now.
My target was the King of Light,
not you, Zi Chuan Xiu.
Is His Highness, King of Light, alright?
Don't hide it from me.
Only His Highness can teach
the Ripple Technique.
No one else can teach you.
Before I answer you—
you must answer me first.
Why do you have Blood Eye too?
Because—
we are the same kind.
I hate speaking in riddles.
Can you be more direct?
His Highness is there.
Gu Lei.
You arrived at just the right time.
Let go, let go!
Release my lord!
If one day—
you find you have nowhere to go—
don't forget—
Zi Chuan isn't your only choice.
Lin He.
The Demon Race has sent 250,000 troops
to attack Far East.
Take care of yourself.
Da, da, da—
My lord!
You, you, you—
Are you alright?
Before you came—
I was fine.
Your Highness.
Governor, what are you doing?
You sure have the mood to eat and drink.
No matter how tough, we still need to eat.
I figured the Demon God Emperor would send troops.
But I didn't expect he'd send two hundred fifty thousand.
Lu Di.
You're worth quite a lot, huh.
Of course.
I am, after all...
This army of two hundred fifty thousand—
How do you plan to handle them?
The Telan Fortress.
And my fifty thousand troops.
I can help Your Highness make them surrender.
Then hold the fortress and defend.
Why do you think
they would surrender?
They've been my men for years.
I trust them.
Alright.
Ross is five days away from Telan Fortress.
You leave today.
You must take the fortress before Ross arrives.
Capture Telan Fortress.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
Lu Di.
Right now, we
are like grasshoppers tied to the same rope.
No, my lord.
This is too risky.
Bai Chuan.
All the way till now,
when have we not taken risks?
Besides,
we can only rely on the fifty thousand Demon Race troops in Telan Fortress.
Only then can we fight the Demon Race.
Otherwise,
all our efforts in the Far East
will be wasted.
I'll lead the Xiuzi Battalion ahead at full speed.
Arrive at Telan Fortress before Ross.
Meet up with Lu Di.
You two
hurry back to Koerni.
Bring the Feng Regiment and Huo Regiment.
Get there as soon as possible.
What if Lu Di suddenly betrays us?
If Lu Di deceives me,
I'll strangle him myself.
Why does that sound so much like a jealous wife?
Alright.
But, my lord,
please be careful.
If things get out of hand,
don't force it.
You must come back alive.
To us,
you're worth more than a hundred Telan Fortresses.
Bai Chuan.
Since when did you care so much about me?
Since the day you borrowed a thousand silver coins.
(IMPERIAL CALENDAR YEAR 782, JUNE 21)
Brothers,
Move faster!
(IMPERIAL CALENDAR YEAR 782, JUNE 21)
Within three days,
reach Telan Fortress.
- Yes.
What's going on?
The army's been assembled for half a day.
Why is there no sign of the supplies?
It's those jerks from Soth.
I've talked till my mouth is dry.
They just won't send the supplies.
(FAR EAST
TELAN FORTRESS)
My lord.
Lu Di isn't playing us, is he?
Why isn't he out yet?
He's coming out.
(LU DI)
(Is he really willing?)
(After entering the city)
(Will an ambush be waiting for us?)
(And a sudden falling gate?)
(If we don't enter...)
I'll say it again.
Today we must head to Telan Fortress at once.
Every minute you delay here
puts my lord in more danger.
Then I'll say it again too.
We won't accept the Demon Race's surrender.
And we won't help that damn Lu Di
defend Telan Fortress.
As for sending troops,
we don't agree.
This is the lord's order.
It's not for you to agree or not.
Alright.
What we say doesn't matter.
Someone else will decide.
Bran.
The elder said
the Demon Race is always cunning and cruel.
He asks the King of Light to think twice.
As for accepting the Demon Race's surrender,
the elder said
he still needs to consult God Audi.
My lord.
Are we entering the city or not?
M-m-my lord!
Look!
That must be Ross's Demon Race army.
Enter the city.
- Greetings, Your Highness King of Light.
Lu Di.
You did well.
Rise.
Enter the city.
My lord.
Don't speak.
Mind your bearing.
Bran.
General Bai Chuan.
You don't need to say more.
We must obey the elder's orders.
I just ask you—
If Telan Fortress falls,
and my lord dies,
do you think we
can stop the Demon Race invasion?
You lead the troops over.
I'll handle the supplies.
We've lost a whole day.
No idea how things are on my lord's side.
Set out overnight.
We should still make it in time.
(ROSS LEGION, OULEG LEGION, KING OF LIGHT LEGION
IMPERIAL CALENDAR YEAR 782, JUNE 26)
People in the city, listen up!
Lu Di has betrayed the nation and joined the enemy.
His crime is unforgivable.
You must execute him at once.
Open the gates and let the army in.
You may be spared.
Lu Di.
Letting him shout down there like this—
might someone really want to take your head for credit?
And your fifty thousand troops turning into five thousand—
we'll settle that with you later.
Archers!
Loose arrows!
Attack the city!
- Sem Hei Lin!
Crossbows, hurry!
Archers, take your positions.
Where are the fire arrows?
Darn it.
What are you doing?
Fire!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Sir.
Should we call reinforcements
from the North Gate?
I think Lu Di's side
can't hold much longer.
Don't worry.
With the battle at this stage,
Lu Di has even less way out
than we do.
Strange...
Why aren't the enemy at the North Gate
attacking yet?
Lord.
Still not attacking?
If we keep waiting,
Te Lan Fortress
will really fall to Ross.
(Demon Race, Second Corps, Oule)
Relax, Ross isn't that capable.
It'll take at least seven or eight days.
He can't take it that fast.
So...
What are we waiting for?
Do you really think His Majesty sent us
to help Ross?
No.
His Majesty doesn't want the Tarta Tribe
to win.
But he doesn't want them to lose either.
You get it now?
Retreat.
Pull back for now.
(Ross Corps, Oule Corps, King of Light Corps)
Sir.
The Third Division has retreated.
Darn Lu Di.
Useless at quelling rebellion,
but fights us
like his life depends on it.
How's Oule's side at the North Gate?
They haven't attacked yet.
What the heck is going on?
Pull back.
Rest for the night.
Attack again tomorrow.
What have we even done?
Lu Di's afraid His Majesty will blame him,
so he sided with the rebels.
Why should we follow him
and become traitors too?
I can't fight this war anymore.
Zhaocai.
Eat more.
Once we're on the battlefield,
don't embarrass the boss.
Remember.
Lu Di and the King of Light
must be captured alive.
Catch those two,
and His Majesty won't punish us.
Who knows,
he might even grant us a title.
Break in!
Kill!
Kill the traitors!
Brothers!
Follow me!
What's happening?
Sir.
Lu Di's men have rebelled.
What?
Rebelled?
Aren't these all your men?
How did you let this happen?
Your Highness.
Please don't be angry.
Careful not to hurt your hand.
How many are there?
Hard to say.
At least a few thousand.
But don't worry, sir.
We've already followed your orders
and stationed troops at the southeast gates.
If anyone tries anything,
our men will strike immediately.
Good.
You go keep watch too.
Yes, sir.
My Lord Lu Di,
those people outside—
what should we do?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Leave it to me.
Capture Lu Di alive!
- Sem Hei Lin!
Not good!
It's an ambush!
Why did you rebel?
You're the rebel.
We're acting for His Majesty,
to eliminate traitors.
Wait.
Spare their lives.
Confiscate their weapons.
Send them to the POW camp.
Such a big show of force—
are they planning a final battle?
Any news from Bai Chuan?
No.
What are they doing?
Look over there!
Since when did the Demon Race
have such advanced siege weapons?
Quick, destroy them!
Don't let them near the walls!
Fire arrows!
And...
Catapults.
The catapults aren't ready yet.
No matter what,
just take them out!
- Yes!
We can't destroy these things
from a distance.
(Insufficient defensive equipment)
(The garrison is far from enough)
(If these new Demon Race siege towers reach the walls)
(Te Lan Fortress will fall)
(This is the Demon Race's gateway
to retake the Far East)
(We)
(can't hold it)
Let me show you the power
of my Well Tower Formation!
How about...
I send men outside the walls
to destroy those things?
Are you sure the men you send
won't just surrender to Ross
once they're out?
Duke.
Hold this place.
Those Jinglan Towers—
Governor Lu Di and I will go ourselves.
Sir.
It's not time for the commander
to fight in person yet.
Let me handle it.
Duke.
Don't worry, sir.
I won't let you down.
Hey!
Got any fire oil?
Get me plenty of it.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Amidst war and chaos, blades sharpen in smoke♪
♪In troubled times, where can longing meet?♪
♪Life slips by, helpless against the years♪
♪All to keep our homeland's flame burning bright♪
♪Treading the path through fire and war♪
♪Driven by wild, unyielding ambition♪
♪Brave and loyal, we fight on every front♪
♪With virtue, we guard our faith♪
♪Who still gazes toward their distant home?♪
♪Waiting for hoofbeats to pass the window♪
♪Waiting for a heart to speak its truth♪
♪Wandering through the world's warmth and cold♪
♪Singing, undaunted by wind and rain♪
♪Zi Chuan forged through a hundred battles♪
♪A lifetime surges, burning and grand♪
♪You and I, unmatched in our passion♪
♪Filling the years' joys and sorrows with glory♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™