[Previously]
This is the Blood of the Living Immortal.
It will help you enter the Severing Self realm.
Use the immortal blood to refine this strand of light
into your finger.
Go beyond the pass and temper yourself first,
then enter the Severing Self realm.
Call out all the top-ranked young kings.
It’s not just Huang.
Another vicious god has arrived.
Today, right here,
I will slaughter half of the young kings.
The will of heaven manifests.
An origin ancient artifact and a sacred relic
of the same source are about to appear.
Whoever obtains it can shatter the heavenly abyss
and open the path to emperorship.
We vow to seize the sacred relic.
And break the Emperor Pass.
To fulfill our ancient ancestors’ long-cherished wish.
Mere child’s play.
How could it rival my Immortal Heaven Blade Art?
It’s you.
Too late.
Martial Heaven King, hold on!
We’re here to help you!
Brother Wu.
He’s clearly just a nameless nobody,
yet he managed to seal Brother Wu’s primordial spirit.
Huang, I have bitterly cultivated for three years
and comprehended the true meaning of immortality.
This chain shall sever evil spirits
and sever my past shame as well.
Turn to dust!
Now it’s your turn.
Come at me together.
This guy won’t last much longer.
Even Huang is too afraid to show himself.
This realm is already at its last gasp.
I’ll trouble you two seniors to keep count for me.
Ah!
He’s already slain four of the top ten kings.
Counting that lion,
that makes five.
Someone has slain five kings in a row.
All Dragon Slayers, hear my command!
Surround and kill this beast!
The foreign army has arrived.
All of you, retreat.
Don’t linger here.
What about you?
I’m naturally going to slaughter to my heart’s content.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Five great prodigies have fallen in a single day.
The army’s morale is already shaken.
Could the heavens truly be changing?
But it was Huang who made a move.
No.
It was a human youth we’ve never seen before.
Besides Huang,
there’s actually such a genius.
Could it be that beings from another realm
are meddling again?
This humiliation is even greater than the defeat at Great Scarlet Heaven.
How can we allow him to keep trampling our clansmen’s corpses
to establish his might?
We humbly request the Imperial Clan prodigies to emerge.
Suppress and kill that human and Huang.
Restore our army’s prestige!
The Imperial Clan…
is not someone you can simply summon at will.
Then may I ask if Brother He Ziming,
who ranks first, is willing to act?
Ziming is at a critical moment in his breakthrough.
Who would dare disturb him?
The consequence would be death of both body and Dao.
No need to worry.
Everything inside and outside the Emperor Pass
is within sight.
The experts from the Five King Clans have already emerged.
We will surely use this person’s head
as a blood sacrifice to our fallen heroes.
Besides, with the grand array being slaughtered day and night,
how much longer can the Nine Heavens hold?
Once our realm’s reinforcements arrive in force,
both Huang and this youth
will be finished.
Just who was it that slew the five great kings of the foreign realm?
Truly remarkable.
Do you even need to ask?
It must have been Huang.
Not necessarily.
I have mastered the Heavenly Ear Passage.
I just heard them say
that a cultivator from some mysterious ancient land
seems to have entered our Emperor Pass.
Could it be a being from the Forbidden Zones?
Heh.
No one around.
I no longer need to keep up the disguise.
I’ve been marked.
The attack isn’t strong,
but I can’t shake it off.
This person is likely a One Escape realm expert.
To leave the Emperor Pass, one must pass through the array platform.
Everyone who does will carry this special immortal light.
Could this person actually be from inside the Emperor Pass?
The more pressure this sword embryo receives,
the greater its power becomes.
I’ll use it to break through.
Break!
Not a bad sword.
It’s mine now.
Dream on.
What rotten luck.
You actually alerted the Ironblood Ancient Tree.
Moon…
No, wait.
You didn’t stumble in here by accident.
You took one look at the map and dared to risk your life
betting on the Ironblood Ancient Tree as your way out.
You’ve got some nerve.
Senior flatters me.
Escorting this junior all the way here
must have been exhausting.
What’s wrong?
Not planning to show your true face?
So I can at least know who my benefactor is.
Sharp tongue.
In that case,
you can just stay inside and behave yourself.
I’ll go call for help right now.
I wonder which family is behind this little scheme this time.
The location marked on the treasure map is nearby.
I need to hurry.
Before the foreign realm’s people arrive,
I must find that mysterious supreme treasure they’re after.
This mountain range is truly terrifying.
Not only are there shape-shifting divine herbs everywhere,
even the flying birds are One Escape realm powerhouses.
They could wipe out an entire divine mountain with one strike.
This is the power of the Immortal Dao.
Just what kind of monster is hidden in this place?
A little calf formed from Yellow Dao Immortal Gold.
Looks like it’s mine now.
Be good and slow down.
You…
What?
Wait—stop! Sit… sit down!
Hey, I don’t know what’s going on,
but today my heart suddenly feels so warm.
Just a light bump
and it inflicts origin Dao injury.
I’m afraid most people couldn’t bear this kind of “affection.”
Inside the Emperor Pass,
there are actually people who understand true righteousness.
Willing to work with us to merge the two realms.
This is truly a blessing for our realm.
You flatter me, my lord.
I simply wish
to fight for a slim chance of survival for the younger generation of my clan.
The spiritual essence of this world
is truly…
captivating.
The Great Dao resonates with me so perfectly.
A natural land for achieving the Dao.
Forgive my rudeness.
So you are a fairy.
This is the power of immortality.
Fairy, your great righteousness
will be etched in our hearts.
When our realm rules supreme one day
and the two realms become one—
we will certainly not mistreat you or your clansmen.
This shall be my certificate of allegiance.
I’ll take my leave first.
In the future, should you have any orders,
my Wind Clan will gladly go through fire and water for you.
Hahahaha!
So it really is Huang.
He’s trapped inside the Divine Herb Mountain Range.
Heaven is helping me!
What a magnificent gift.
It fits perfectly with our realm’s grand plan.
Hahahaha!
Assemble!
Right here.
Surround and kill Huang!
Understood!
[Shrouding the Heavens – First Theatrical Film: ‘Battle Against the Heavens’ — See You on the Emperor’s Path, April 4, 2026]
The so-called Emperor Path
is not one of invincibility.
[Shrouding the Heavens – First Theatrical Film: ‘Battle Against the Heavens’ — See You on the Emperor’s Path, April 4, 2026]
Ye Fan…
It’s truly a shame
that we were born in the same era.
If you want to fight, then fight.
Why make so many excuses?
[Shrouding the Heavens – First Theatrical Film: ‘Battle Against the Heavens’]
[Perfect World: The Crisis Arrives]
[Phoenix Nirvana: After the Phoenix Nirvana, the old self is shed, the soul is reborn, and one is reborn from the flames. Afterward, the phoenix transforms, rising again with a stronger body and greater power. It is said that the phoenix, after nirvana, can evolve into an even more powerful being and reach a higher realm.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™