Today, I'll repay blood
with blood.
A tooth for a tooth.
Let you all taste
what it's like to be prey.
No one remains undefeated forever.
Come on!
I'll gather enough for
a perfect tonic soup.
He Wushuang's true blood
is only worth this much?
Might as well feed it to pigs.
They're here.
Ancestors,
terrible news!
The first barrier of the Three Thousand Provinces
has fallen.
The sealed city did not appear.
The border wasteland
is in grave peril.
My family is still
in the Three Thousand Provinces.
This is bad.
That's the most critical pass
into the Nine Heavens and Ten Lands.
They must have lured us here on purpose,
preventing us from aiding the border.
If the border falls,
the Nine Heavens will not hold.
The Ten Realms Diagram
and the Immortal King's burial shroud
are both here.
Failing to reinforce the border immediately
is indeed troubling.
Hahaha!
We succeeded!
This is the news
I came here to announce.
Elders,
the time has come to cross realms.
Time to slay our enemies.
Enough for today.
Next time we meet,
I'll cut you down myself.
You dare stay?
I'll split you in half right now.
Their plan was to lure the tiger
from the mountain.
But we must save the border.
It might be a feint—
forcing us to choose one side to defend,
so they can strike the weak point.
This place cannot fall either.
Everyone, take the Ten Realms Diagram
and the Ancestral Dragon Horn.
Rush to reinforce
the Three Thousand Provinces at once.
Great Elder,
may I join the battle
and do my part?
No battlefield is insignificant.
If Great Chitian is breached,
there will be no barrier left behind.
You stay.
Guard this line with me.
Great Elder,
are we just going to wait here?
They will return.
How boring.
Even pretending to leave
and ambushing us again
would be better than this.
Soul Summoning Scripture
Are they trying to revive someone?
We welcome the Ancient Ancestor!
Hahaha!
You're too late.
The ritual is complete.
We welcome the return
of Ancient Ancestor Luomo!
It's been far too long
since that battle.
This is an Ancient Ancestor
from the Foreign Realm.
The Foreign Realm has manifested
his remnant soul again.
They must have some scheme.
Until we see the truth,
none of you act rashly.
The border defense
cannot be compromised.
Lord Luomo,
we will march straight into this realm.
We need to know how strong
the one who killed you was.
Please enlighten us.
The one who fought me
has long since fallen.
The past is sealed
in this ancient realm.
An Lan and Yu Tuo must have calculated
that the seal is weakening today.
Go open it yourselves
and investigate.
We've tried breaking the seal
several times,
but failed each time.
Lord, could you assist us?
It's only a remnant soul—
it could dissipate at any moment.
Summoning me back is useless.
Or perhaps
you have other intentions?
Your descendants have always
been protected by Ancient Ancestor Yu Tuo,
remaining a powerful clan.
If we gain your aid,
our realm will dominate the heavens.
They will be even more revered.
You can rest easy now.
The Key to the Emperor's Path
lies within that realm.
If we obtain it,
our realm will dominate the heavens.
None will dare defy us.
Dominate the heavens—
all for your selfish desires,
using my remnant soul
as a stepping stone.
Hahaha!
Scheming against a dead man.
An Lan, Yu Tuo—
you truly have great skill.
A dead man can still form seals.
A supreme warrior's blood
never fades.
Even in death, obstructed,
it can instinctively unleash its might.
Even if this path leads to certain death,
one day, I will tread it.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
The ancient realm's seal is broken.
What Ancient Ancestor Yu Tuo
sent us to find
may lie deep within this realm.
Could treasures from the Immortal Antiquity
be hidden here?
The Foreign Realm rattled us
at Great Chitian,
attacking both fronts
to sow confusion.
It wasn't just to lure the tiger away—
it was for this treasure.
This is bad.
The Foreign Realm is entering.
They outnumber us.
We only have the Great Elder.
How can we hold them back?
This realm
suppresses us too greatly.
You have lived tens of thousands of years.
Your cultivated Dao is deeply rooted,
clashing violently with this realm.
Before breaking the boundary wall,
you will be repelled.
Bring forth the Immortal Refining Pot.
The opportunity must not be missed.
He Ziming,
you juniors take the Immortal Refining Pot
and enter the ancient realm first.
Hm.
This blood is quite special.
I should collect some to take back—
it might be useful
to Ancient Ancestor Yu Tuo.
Ah!
Why don't we go in too?
We might snag something good.
Great Elder,
the ancient realm may have laws
that restrain the strong.
Why not take this along—
both offense and defense.
And allow us to accompany you,
just in case.
This blood seems left by an Immortal King.
It can nourish the war banner,
helping it fully transform.
Immortal King blood flows
the moment it's opened.
What kind of existence fell
in this ancient realm back then?
The greater matter comes first.
This is a True Phoenix.
This beast can control the blood.
In that case,
refine this blood—
leave not a single drop.
The boundary wall suppresses artifacts too.
Even our supreme Immortal Refining Pot
cannot collect this blood.
It's no surprise it harbors killing intent
toward Foreign Realm invaders.
But as a descendant of the Ten Fiends,
how can it not distinguish friend from foe
and attack us as well?
Must we stop here today?
Hahaha!
Heaven aids us.
It's just like the one
that defected in the Immortal Antiquity era.
A fallen Blood Phoenix.
It's exhausted.
Capture it now!
It must have been tainted
before hatching—
its immortal egg shell stained
by battle blood.
Hence its bloodthirsty nature,
hard to subdue.
The border already faces enemies on two fronts.
We cannot let this realm's power
fall into Foreign Realm hands.
Its mutated bloodline
is somewhat similar to mine.
An immortal must have lived here once,
leaving such rich True Immortal aura.
Sadly, it's not true immortal qi.
If we excavate the treasures in this grave,
it might compensate
for the death of the Ten Kings.
True Immortals here equal the undying.
Even fallen, their might lingers.
Acting rashly could bring dire consequences.
Don't ruin the greater plan.
When our realm's main force arrives,
we can overturn today's losses.
This is an ancient battlefield.
Someone here struggled
in their final moments,
manifesting
their heaven-piercing true form.
A hand reached into the cosmos,
plucking down stars.
Under the sweep of immortal Dao laws,
all life was extinguished.
This must be the true blood
left by Ancient Ancestor Luomo.
Its divine power is completely gone.
Could something have devoured it?
Chaos blood...
Legend says this blood rivals
seven-colored true blood.
Ancient Ancestor Luomo faced
such a monster back then?
It's not pure enough—
only traces of chaos blood.
Otherwise, how could Luomo
have struck it down
and perished together?
What's wrong?
I sense the aura
of my clan's blood here.
The rumors were true.
The Guardian's blood—
both divine and demonic.
So your ancestor was the one
who killed Luomo
and guards the treasure here?
Indeed, someone fought Luomo here
in a heaven-shaking battle.
My kinsman was not his match—
he was merely caught
in the aftermath
and fell here.
He did not belong to this place.
He came from the Origin Land.
A Guardian.
If you learned the cruel truth of that year,
you might want to draw your blade
against those behind you.
My clan's bloodline is no tool
for your slander.
Our ancestor did not die
fighting for you.
Right and wrong—
I will judge for myself.
A stray dog with no way home
still dares to speak so boldly.
Pathetic.
The stele inscription is resonating.
Unfortunately, I've been chosen
to take action.
There is no returning now.
Victory is certain,
yet the path home is severed.
Trapped deep in the game—
how can one know if it's sacrifice
or mere futility?
Severing my own immortal path,
clinging to life—
is this the Dao you seek?
Even if I could sever
one finger of the chess player,
what would it achieve?
Calamity approaches.
Who else dares cross the sea?
Perhaps only when the heavens collapse
and samsara ends
can new life emerge.
What exactly happened in the past?
The one who carved the stele
clearly perished with Luomo.
If so,
who is playing the qin?
[Spirit Vein Immortal Maiden: The Immortal Maiden of the Spirit Veins was born in ancient times. She once guarded countless primordial spirit veins, holding dominion over the purest essence of heaven and earth. Her form is ethereal and otherworldly, like jade sculpted by divine hands. With every movement, spiritual energy flows like water, nourishing all realms. She is deeply connected to the origin of the world’s spiritual veins, and her presence alone can stabilize lands, mend shattered ley lines, and awaken dormant vitality. Legends say that wherever the Immortal Maiden appears, spirit veins flourish, divine treasures are born, and cultivation prospers. Yet she is rarely seen—appearing only when the balance of heaven and earth is threatened, or when fate itself calls her forth.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™