(Copyright Notice)
♪Smoke and fire sweep
across endless wastelands♪
♪Whose body will quell
this great catastrophe?♪
♪Countless hands uphold
a single shared belief♪
♪Sparks ignite, daring
to face the abyss♪
♪Hear the youth's wild heart,
braving all alone♪
♪Bones shattered, yet
he fights upstream♪
♪Mountains and rivers drift,
tempered by fire, undaunted♪
♪No god or demon
can stand in the way♪
♪Heroes through the ages,
loyalty pierces the sky♪
♪Though the night is dark,
pride sings in the bones♪
♪Countless eyes behind,
vowing never to retreat♪
♪This body burns with yours,
silencing all noise♪
♪Form fades, but embers remain,
never to die♪
♪Never retreat,
never yield♪
- PERFECT WORLD -
- ON THE BRINK -
(This animation is adapted from Chen Dong's novel "Perfect World")
EPISODE 241
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Minors, please watch with guardian's permission)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Previously on...)
This is the Yuanmu Cauldron
Whoever can lift it
will be granted a chance at the core inheritance
He is like my Tianjiao Ant clan
able to lift what far exceeds his own limits
The Immortal Scripture is the Tianjiao Ant clan's legacy
Once mastered, even heaven and earth cannot bury you
Undying, immortal
Countless ages
At last, I have met you
(In ancient times, at the start of the Luangu Era)
To resist the Foreign Realm
My beloved wife
Our children have all fallen in battle
Now
I too will soon pass
Only this one child remains
Taken from his late mother's womb
I beg the heavens to show mercy
Willing to trade my life
for my child's survival
My child
Though born weak
he must inherit the Tianjiao Ants' courage and honor
Refine his body with his father's blood
When you are strong enough
you may begin the inheritance
and seek the Immortal Scripture
Before I depart
I gazed into my child's future across endless ages
Wishing to see him once more
And I saw you in the future as well
Therefore
I will not punish you for trespassing
You are the Tianjiao Ant elder
What did you see?
(Xiangu Battlefield)
Ah
This is the Tianjiao Ant elder's memory
Are you warning me
about the most terrifying enemy to come?
(Not too dull)
(This aura...)
(It's the one who killed me in the river of time)
(The Tianjiao Ant elder was once entangled by him too)
(Chifeng Spear, Immortal King An Lan's immortal weapon)
(There is yet another)
(far stronger than the previous two)
(This is the Era-End Great Calamity battle)
The three supreme Foreign Realm warriors attacked together
and besieged the elder
Back then, we Ten Fierce matched the Xian Wang's power
slaying countless so-called immortals
but drew treacherous ambushes
Now, our descendants have forgotten the enemy's might
And those three still live today
They will return in force
The spear wielder is the most terrifying
He once broke through all the great worlds alone
slaughtering billions
I glimpsed the future
Saw my child and you fighting side by side
Saw you pursue the ultimate limit
Surpassing the strongest
You remind me of my younger self
So I warn you today
What was the outcome of that war?
Fate is hard to divine
I only saw the calamity you alone must face
Greater than all Xiangu has endured
The darkest age is coming
Are you ready?
Are you afraid?
One day, the enemy will be defeated
What is there to fear?
But if one day
all heavens fall silent
and all worlds are mute
In the vastness of heaven and earth
only you walk alone
fighting the heavens alone
bearing the blood calamity alone
Battling from youth until your hair turns white
Your blood and spirit exhausted
Will you still fight on?
Is this my future?
What about the others?
Why am I the only one left?
I refuse to believe this is the future
I only believe all enemies must be destroyed
and rewrite the fate of ages
I saw two possible endings
What you saw was only one of them
Your fate is tied to many others
Countless destinies entwine around you
Overlapping and unclear
Even I cannot distinguish them
Elder
I want the Immortal Scripture
Alright
Back then, I did not obtain the full scripture
So I never reached perfection
(Immortal Peak)
I hope you reach Immortal Peak
and bring out the complete scripture
to one day achieve true immortality
leaving no regrets
By then, you will realize
the real battlefield is not the Nine Heavens Ten Earths
but something far beyond imagination
(Now)
Roar
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Hmph
Not very big
But quite grumpy when waking up
What's happening to me?
Did you find the Immortal Scripture?
I've got a lead.
But it's in a distant place.
Are you willing to come with me?
You want to trick This King into leaving with you.
Go or not, it's up to you.
Master the Immortal Scripture,
your body remains unbroken,
uncorrupted through endless calamities,
and can nurture your former spirit again.
I'm not eager to share it.
Wait.
That's my family's scripture.
Don't think of keeping it all to yourself.
If that's the case,
This King will reluctantly go with you.
And see what this era is capable of.
Don't you want to know how I got the news?
No need to say more.
This King only needs to know the target's location.
(Half an hour ago)
If there's anything useful here,
you may take it.
Thank you, elder.
Elder.
Won't you acknowledge it?
No need.
Crying only dulls its edge.
My bloodline should stand tall and proud.
Alone, it holds up the ancient sky.
(Truly father and son.)
So many students have gone down.
What will be left for us when it's our turn?
The two elders guard it fiercely.
No one can get in.
Don't get too cocky.
There are many terrifying beasts outside.
Don't end up as someone's snack.
Impossible.
On the Xiangu Battlefield, there was a glorious Foreign Realm Blood Phoenix Lion.
After my siblings joined the battle, it vanished.
It must have been slain by them.
This King won't be any less.
Huang, is that on your shoulder...
the Tianjiao Ant?
It is This King.
Now leaving here with my mount.
Seeking fortune.
Hey, who's the mount?
Huang, join my Immortal Academy.
It'll help you go further.
Open up new horizons.
I refuse.
Nonsense.
He's already found his own path.
Doesn't need you at all.
Huang, your body is strong.
Best suited for the Way of the Present.
Join the Sacred Academy,
and you can read any scripture.
Still not interested.
Huang has walked the Body as the Seed path.
Why be bound by the Way of the Present?
Don't you already have the Lunar Jade Rabbit and the young Qilin?
That Qilin is sealed.
Can't be studied at all.
The outside world is way too enthusiastic.
Begging and shouting for people to come.
Hmph.
Don't forget,
you were once a battle servant of my Wang Clan.
(Wang Manglong, Void Dao Realm)
Descendant of the Ten Fierce.
Should belong to my Wang Clan.
Burp.
The last Tianjiao Ant in the world.
(Yuan Qing, peak Sever-Me Realm)
Must be well protected.
Longevity Clan
far more reliable than a kid who makes enemies everywhere.
(Yuan Qing is here too.)
(Still suspects Yuan Feng's death.)
(Came here just to block me.)
Young friend,
for the Tianjiao Ant's safety,
please let us keep it safe.
(Feng Yingluo, Feng Clan Elder, peak Sever-Me Realm)
Also,
about my missing brother and nephew,
I'll be asking you about them soon.
(Wang Clan, Feng Clan, Yuan Clan)
(All my enemies are here.)
(Ready to surround and kill me.)
Get lost!
Hahaha.
That's hilarious.
Huang and the Tianjiao Ant are protected by Tianshen Academy.
Why are you all so eager to interfere?
(Xu Mingxuan, Emperor of the Longevity Dynasty, father of Princess Yaoyue)
My apologies.
So it's Emperor Xu.
But the Tianjiao Ant is a serious matter.
Even if an elder arrives,
don't blame our three clans for not showing respect.
(Sever-Me Realm experts from Feng, Yuan, and Wang Clans)
(All are Sever-Me Realm.)
Elders, what do you mean by this?
For the sake of the academy,
the Tianjiao Ant's Blood of Strength's Limit is too important.
There's really no other way.
Afterwards,
Huang will be compensated.
(No way.)
(The Primordial True Scripture can't quickly reverse high-level Dao laws.)
(Should I risk manifesting the Great World or One Qi Transforms All Life?)
(But if I run out of strength,)
(I'll be at their mercy.)
Courting death!
How dare you disrespect This King!
Who dares to cause trouble in Tianshen Academy?
Great Elder
Emperor Xu arrives
Tianshen Academy should give a grand welcome
Hahaha
Great Elder, you flatter me
I've brought the treasure you requested
Your disciple is truly remarkable
Young in age, yet exceptionally gifted
Outshines many ancient sages
Emperor, you praise me too highly
Such terrifying pressure
Rumor says Meng Tianzheng is half a step from True Immortal
It seems that's not exaggerated
Hmph
Climbed to high places
And forgot your mine slave origins
You dare make a move
Aren't you afraid of the Wang Clan's revenge
Afraid? Hell no
Let Wang Clan's top ten geniuses come at me
I'll kill them all the same
(Is this person a Supreme Realm expert)
Haha
Punishing them myself is satisfying
But let me play the villain
Xu Mingxuan
You dare
Why wouldn't I dare
Is Wang Changsheng using this youngster's words
To reignite our ten-thousand-year feud
Senior, wise and mighty
Peerless in all the world
You just now descended like a god of slaughter
Now you're quite the flatterer
Little one
Why do you keep staring at me
Do we have a grudge
Why embroider a lizard, not an ant
This King is clearly more majestic
Hahaha
I know you're seeking fortune
Now no one should dare trouble you
Go on, then
Don't lose this ring
You may need it someday
Remember
About the anomaly in the Flame Ancient Cave
Do not tell anyone
(So mysterious)
(What's really inside that cave)
(Why is the Great Elder so serious)
Eh
Where do we find the Immortal Scripture
Deep in the North Sea
Stone Forest
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(Perfect World: A Dream Through Ages Special - Battle with He Wushuang)
♪The battle song echoes on the march♪
(Xu Mingxuan, Lord of the Xu Longevity Dynasty, father of Princess Yaoyue)
(One of the Nine Heavens Ten Earths' supreme beings, bold in character)
(Righteous and loyal, the Great Elder's staunchest ally)
(Especially favors the rising star Huang)
(Model showcase: back view, side view, Xu Mingxuan, facial close-up)
War on the frontier is about to ignite
Those who wish to uphold the pact and face the Imperial Pass
Scan the QR code
Join me in battle
♪Rust-colored clock hands push me toward pale light♪
♪Fate, like a cold tide, silently covers♪
♪Palm lines engraved with silent monologues♪
♪Yet in the long river, I see you coming♪
♪Starlight in your eyes lights up the mist♪
♪In a frozen world, my only hope♪
♪Even if the road ahead is covered in dust♪
♪My gaze paints colors only for you♪
♪Disassembling fate's cold remains♪
♪Just to reach the pass that leads to you♪
♪No matter if the ending is empty waiting♪
♪I'll still chase the light in your hair♪
♪Fate is a heavy chain, hard to bear♪
♪Love is starlight, determined to break the gloom♪
♪This desolate universe is too pale♪
♪You are my endless sea of stars♪
(Next episode preview)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™