It's you.
[Previously]
Too late.
Your turn has come.
Surround and kill this cur!
I no longer need to disguise myself.
You escorted the juniors here.
You've truly worked hard.
This is my "Certificate of Surrender."
It is... Huang!
What a magnificent gift.
With this meager skill,
you dare surround and kill?
This little bull is forged from Immortal Gold.
Capture it quickly!
Present it to the Ancient Ancestor.
Seems I was injured right down to my origin.
There are many Dungyi Realm cultivators here.
To escape and heal,
I'll have to rely on wit, not force.
"Raise the stone for a thousand days,
use it for one."
It's your turn to take the stage.
Hey!
What's happening?
The so-called "most dangerous place"
is actually the safest place.
I'll leave this little guy to deal with them.
I'm going to borrow its cave to heal.
This wound is strange.
Could it be that the little bull's Immortal
Dao energy carried a complete Great Dao,
injuring my origin so severely?
Although I escaped just now,
it's like adding frost to snow.
That little fellow's cave...
is actually formed entirely from
Yellow Dao Stones, which birth Yellow Dao Immortal Gold!
This is still a primordial source land,
brimming with infinite vitality.
Could it be nurturing a new
Immortal Gold spirit?
Gathering a whole nest, perhaps?
Carvings, as I thought.
This place wasn't naturally formed.
It was artificially created with
Immortal methods—a Life Pool.
I wonder for whom it was prepared.
Regardless, I've stumbled upon a bargain.
This wound is actually generating deathly energy.
If I don't absorb it using the
Secret Realm of the Wheel Sea,
I fear it won't heal.
The little bull gored me with a Dao wound,
yet its cave brings vitality.
Is this some kind of "Karma cycle"?
Back in the Lower Realm,
Little Tower often mentioned those two words.
He even traded with me,
risked everything because of it.
Is it that the stronger one is,
the more they are bound by
this invisible Karma?
Little Tower was like this,
and so was Willow Deity.
You guys...
where exactly did you go?
Will there be a day we meet again?
No.
If there truly is an invisible force
blocking my path,
I will simply sever it.
The green rust from the Lower Realm's
Immortal Palace
shattered my Great Dao origin once.
I almost died and lost my Dao.
This injury today
means nothing in comparison.
Though this injury is severe,
hard to recover from,
once I endure it, the rewards
will be immense.
It might even trigger an all-around
transformation.
My Immortal Qi is surfacing on its own...
and it's so restless.
Something's wrong.
This is...
The first wisp of energy that vanished
when I condensed Immortal Qi back then?
When anyone condenses Immortal Qi
for the first time,
they lose that first strand of Primordial Qi.
But for you to actually glimpse its form...
It's truly unheard of.
The One begets the Two,
the Two begets the Three,
the Three begets all things.
These three strands of Immortal Qi you have
are all imprints transformed
from that first strand.
If you forcibly keep the Primordial Qi,
attempting to hoard everything,
you will surely suffer backlash in the future.
It will become a burden to you.
This damn thing
has been hiding inside me all along.
Choosing this exact moment to emerge.
Though it can mend my injuries,
excess is just as bad as deficiency.
It ends up harming my origin again.
I wonder what the mystery of this pool is.
It can actually nourish that strand of Primordial Maternal Qi.
Since I can't avoid it,
I'll figure it out and take it all.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Earlier, during the siege,
I personally witnessed Huang suffer severe injuries.
His origin was damaged.
This is a heaven-sent opportunity.
We must take advantage of his wounded state
to eliminate this future trouble forever.
There must be a shocking secret at the bottom of this pool.
I'm going all in.
But what method can get me inside?
It's that ball of flame.
Immortal aura...
What a terrifying restriction.
It can even injure Divine Sense.
In that case,
I'll use the dragon scale as a shield.
This entire war chariot
is actually forged from Yellow Dao Immortal Gold.
They're treating Immortal Gold like scrap metal.
Golden horns,
a bull's head...
Why is there another Immortal Gold bull?
These scars were all left by Immortal Dao energy.
An Immortal bull is actually being used to pull a cart.
They truly don't recognize quality.
Could it be that the Immortal Gold bull outside
used this place to resurrect via Nirvana?
Perhaps I can make use of this as well.
He is the master of the Immortal Bull.
What an imposing aura.
Why does this senior look so familiar?
It's the Six Paths Reincarnation Immortal King!
Is this the battlefield of the Immortal Ancient era?
This is definitely not a power of the mortal realm.
This man is an Immortal King.
Yet such a powerful figure
actually died here.
I'm afraid we will never meet again.
No Primordial Spirit...
Could it be...
that it was sucked away by this black hole?
I should return to my main body first.
Worthy of being the mother of the Three Dao Qi.
What terrifying power.
With the aid of this pool water,
using the body as the seed,
and physique as the gate,
the second Great Dao Fruit
has finally condensed!
This Dao Fruit governs slaughter.
It is one with my very being.
Once I wield it freely, my combat strength will surge violently.
Oh no.
The moment the second Dao Fruit was born,
this calamity struck.
Enough.
I won't think about it too much.
For now, focus on cultivation,
and repairing my origin.
What a terrifying marrow washing and bone replacement.
They are actually using my body as a crucible.
Immortal mist serves as the furnace fire,
immortal mist serves as the furnace fire,
and the bone marrow is the substance being refined.
Such tempering—
transforming the marrow into a great medicine for the human body,
and then replenishing myself with it.
Supreme Blood.
Could it be growing another Supreme Bone?
What a pity.
It seems I thought too much.
Rather than birthing a Supreme Bone,
it's better for this blood to disperse throughout,
nourishing my entire body.
After consolidating it a bit more,
I can charge into the Slay-Me Realm.
The little fellow is back.
It seems this place is unsafe to stay long.
Huang is right here.
Follow me to kill this little beast!
You suffered a Great Dao wound,
yet you can still block one of my palms?
Fortunately, the Great Nirvana was perfect.
To be fearless of a Dungyi Realm palm—
with this physique,
once I break through,
I shall dominate those of the same rank,
even those a realm higher!
Merely a fluke, escaping once.
Hand over your life!
Now that the ultimate treasure is found,
set out immediately.
Great Elder,
several batches of expedition teams have rotated out,
but Huang still hasn't returned.
With the异域 (Foreign Realm) stirring so fiercely,
Huang's journey is far too dangerous.
It is time to exit seclusion.
[Perfect World — Endless Burning Heavens]
[Shi Hao — Six Realms Combined Dharma Form]
[“Five Years Together, A Perfect Encounter”
Perfect World Animation — 5th Anniversary Event Now Open
Submit your messages before April 20, 23:00]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™