Your return has caused this land to
revive.
Triggering changes in the heavens.
[Previously]
This is the other shore of the River
of Time.
Is that you, Huang?
What exactly happened?
Finally, we've waited for the treasure
to emerge.
Invite Ancient Ancestors Yu Tuo and
An Lan to descend.
That direction...
Could it be where Huang went?
This ancient land can actually block
the aftershocks of the Ancient Ancestors.
It's fine that we are unharmed,
but how is this trash still alive?
The Foreign Realm has gone to such
great lengths...
this item must be of great importance.
But he got it in the end.
What a pity.
Ancient Ancestor, be careful!
Creatures from the Burial Grounds
are attacking!
Recognizing thieves as fathers.
What loyalty, you slave.
You fawn over your new master more
eagerly than anyone.
One day, I will take your head
and dig out the rebellious bone
behind your skull.
Impudent!
That Burial King didn't care about
the rotten wooden chest at all.
He came solely to block Ancient Ancestor
Yu Tuo.
Could it be because this object emerged
from the burial grounds?
He doesn't want to be dragged into
this mess.
Stop yapping.
Look!
The Ancient Ancestor's dharma body
is disintegrating.
Our retreat is in danger.
If we drag this out,
we won't be able to bring the chest
back.
These two old jade bastards...
they are ultimately restricted by
the Abyss of Heaven.
Their true bodies can't descend.
A projected dharma body
probably won't last much longer.
Ancient Ancestor An Lan has come to
assist!
What is that thing?
Could it be the King of the Burial
Grounds?
Old Burial once said,
some peerless burial attendants can
shed their deathly aura.
Their descendants become Golden Burial
Attendants.
But some powerhouses remain in the
ominous lands,
surrounded by billowing dead mist.
The one before us is likely the latter.
You...
Do you think my true body cannot come
here?
Everyone, don't panic.
As the Great Elder said,
as long as the Tian Yuan (Abyss of
Heaven) is unbroken,
it is the greatest barrier for the
Imperial Pass.
We just need to hold our ground.
Do not throw ourselves into chaos.
The Tian Yuan has been disturbed.
It is shaking off the Burial King,
and also blocking the descent of An
Lan and Yu Tuo's true bodies.
It is Yu Tuo Ancient Ancestor's Time
Imprint.
It only affects a single instant.
It will dissipate after one strike.
But if we can buy a sliver of opportunity,
perhaps Ancient Ancestor An Lan can
still seize the treasure.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Two Ancient Ancestors...
Failed.
This branch of the burial ground
is within the border wilderness.
Once this Burial King loses control
and goes mad,
it will surely threaten the Imperial
Pass.
Since it is a treasure contested by
Immortal Kings,
it must be entangled with strangeness.
Once fluctuations erupt,
it might turn people into pools of
blood instantly.
They don't dare to act recklessly either.
The situation was perilous just now.
Yet you remained quite composed.
Compared to those wastes,
you have some redeeming qualities.
This chest is bizarre.
Anyone acting alone might fall into
a trap.
For the grand plan of our realm,
how about we temporarily ally
to take it first?
After securing it,
we can compete based on our own abilities.
How about it?
Why are you dragging your feet?
One word:
Are we doing this or not?
If you don't, plenty of others will.
To be frank,
to have gotten this far,
both of us have made contributions.
We are merely contending for priority.
Since you have doubts,
how about...
Don't thank me.
For the sake of the Ancient Ancestors,
I am willing to use the blood of the
Imperial Clan as a covenant.
Listen carefully:
Today, we shall jointly retrieve the
wooden chest.
Neither party shall harm the other
during the process.
Should anyone violate this oath,
their spirit and form shall be
annihilated.
Completely unharmed?
You clearly came prepared.
I knew something was off.
You invited me to get close,
how could I refuse such kindness?
Perfect chance to settle everything
at once.
It's you!
Huang!
You dare to secretly learn the taboo
secret arts of my realm's Imperial
Clan!
A rebellious lineage that has knelt
for too long,
forgetting your own origins,
truly treating the Foreign Realm as
your ancestral soil.
My clan long ago fought its way out
of the Nine Heavens.
You, dogs of a defeated clan,
have only death awaiting you.
Today, I shall slay you to establish
my name!
No backlash.
I can directly seize that chest.
Huang,
do you really think you are invincible?
Using my ancestral arts to seal this
place,
you have no escape.
Get lost!
Slay him!
I alone am enough.
Arrogant!
Watch as I kill every single one of
you!
So the Skull Fruit had something to
do with this anomaly after all.
Fortunately,
it wasn't an issue with the chest
itself.
This chest used to move on its own.
Don't even think about leaving.
So this Undying Medicine didn't just
want to use me as a weapon,
it wanted to take the treasure too.
Hey!
If you don't leave that chest,
I'll stew you for sure!
Let's see how far you can run this
time.
What the hell is this place?
We accidentally entered a branch of
the burial grounds.
Good thing we didn't barge into a den
of burial attendants.
Otherwise, we'd be in deep trouble.
Speak of the devil, and he appears.
Out of the wolf's den and into the
tiger's lair.
Identity exposed.
You will be refined into a burial slave
by the Golden Burial Attendants.
Worse than death.
And I'm going to be made into coffin
planks for the Burial King.
Don't panic when trouble arises.
If we cooperate,
pretending to be Golden Burial Attendants
might buy us time.
There's a chance we can get out of
this.
Yeah, right, I trust you.
These vengeful spirits are already at
the Dun Yi (Escape One) Realm.
How could they not tell I'm a plant?
Become my divine pet.
Use your primordial spirit to teach
me the Ancient Burial Language.
Mutual benefit.
I'll guarantee your escape.
Oh, so cooperating meant pretending
to be Golden Burial Attendants?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
So these are the ones who shed all
deathly aura,
able to walk under the sun—the Golden
Burial Attendants.
Calling this clan vengeful spirits
is less accurate than calling them
descendants of Demon Immortals.
The Ancient Burial Language...
Teach me the Ancient Burial Language.
Or we'll be exposed immediately.
I wondered why an Undying Medicine was
wandering alone out here.
Turns out it already had an owner.
Shen Ming, you're happy for nothing.
My name is San Zang (Three Stores).
May I ask how to address this Daoist
brother?
I am Huang.
I was previously engrossed in appraising
treasure,
and was careless, letting this medicine
escape.
So that's how it is.
I thought you were from outside the
domain.
Those guys get refined into burial
slaves, you know.
Interesting.
Such a unique aura.
Please, stop dawdling! Walk faster!
The most dangerous place is often the
safest.
Why don't we look around first,
swap out some burial artifacts,
and then play it by ear?
[Episode 266 — Power Rankings - 1.Funeral King, 2. An Lan Projection / Yu Tuo Projection, 3.Shen Ming / San Zang, 4.Huang (Shi Hao)]
[Perfect World Animation — 5th Anniversary Merchandise
Official sale begins April 30 - Bundle purchases include exclusive animated character skins.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™