[Previously]
Such a massive operation in a foreign land...
this item must be of utmost importance.
You have no escape.
Watch as I kill every single one of you.
So the Elixir of Immortality wants to snatch the treasure too.
We've stumbled into a Burial Earth tributary.
I am Sanzang.
I am Huang.
I was just admiring the treasures.
I thought you were from a foreign domain.
The Golden Burial Soldiers have marked you.
Your life is almost gone...
and you still have the mood to shop?
Since we're here, why panic?
Strolling openly and confidently...
is safer than skulking around like a rat.
What did you think of that stone and the Withered Blood?
Those are Burial Earth treasures.
Can you even afford them?
You mean the leaf from the Elixir of Immortality?
Do they want it?
I advise you to be a decent human being.
I'll fight you!
Don't think you're the only one with immortal medicine leaves.
So familiar...
Wait.
You brat, showing off with *my* leaf?
Immortal Medicine is so rare...
even the two of us combined only brought one plant.
Brother Huang's strength is truly extraordinary.
It seems Brother Huang's purpose...
is also to enter the Burial Abyss for treasure.
The Golden Burial Soldiers all know...
that the Immortal Moon Wheels we nurtured...
can withstand the Death Light of the Abyss depths.
To retrieve celestial treasures and burial relics from within.
If you don't understand, speak less to avoid mistakes.
Naturally.
Listening to him...
the Burial Abyss is a land of treasures.
Ask fewer questions.
The medicine in that woman's hand probably belongs...
to the one deep in the Ancient Burial Domain who raises chickens.
She has quite the backing.
What's scary about raising chickens?
He keeps True Phoenixes as chickens...
free-range at that, by the giant wall.
If they aren't his descendants...
they must have a Burial King backing them.
They are not to be trifled with.
Kid...
they are still watching you.
Sooner or later, they'll realize you have no Burial Artifacts to trade.
By then, our identities will likely be exposed too.
I'm leaving first.
Can this item be exchanged?
Such precious Burial Earth...
only a Burial King could obtain it.
Brother Huang truly has a noble status.
You spendthrift!
You had Myriad Soil and didn't tell me?
I'd strip every leaf off to trade for it!
What treasure has Brother Huang found now?
Once we enter the depths of the Burial Abyss...
if we truly find the Origin Item...
that allows one to become a Burial King...
I hope you'll show your little sister some mercy.
Within the Burial Abyss...
lies the power to achieve the status of a Burial King.
Hahaha!
The Burial Abyss opens!
Brother Huang...
it is time to depart.
The Grand Elder sighed that our world's Dao is flawed...
unable to take the final step.
If we can find this item...
will it help the Grand Elder?
Don't go.
The Origin Item is taboo even among Burial Kings.
If you value your life, flee!
Don't drag me down with you!
Once the Abyss opens...
rare burial treasures will surge forth.
Everyone, take them by skill.
As for the deep secrets and treasures...
we may only enter once the Abyss is fully open.
These auroras are an omen...
that burial treasures are about to emerge.
If Brother Huang doesn't want to fall behind...
now is the time to strike.
It is your turn to act.
Now is not the time for me to strike.
That Nine-Eyed Burial Stone of yours...
will naturally attract Burial Weapons to worship it.
So the stone he selected earlier was the Nine-Eyed Burial Stone.
Its value surpasses even Myriad Soil.
I actually missed that...
So ferocious, this burial treasure.
Even though it only comes to worship...
with no intent to attack...
merely its presence...
is enough to sever ordinary Burial Soldiers.
Don't you have a body protection technique?
Haven't you heard that different fields have different specializations?
My protection method isn't designed against burial weapon aura.
It won't hold.
Bad news.
Too many Burial Weapons have been attracted.
We'll be chopped into scallions by the burial qi.
Quick, take out that Withered Blood!
Force them back!
We're safe now.
Is it possible the burial artifact is gone too?
Hiss...
This isn't my fault, you know.
Brother Huang...
this way, I fear none of us will gain anything.
It is not too late to use the treasure after entering the deep palace.
That palace hall, throughout endless ages...
has seen few who could enter.
Too dangerous.
Precisely because it is dangerous...
true opportunity lies there.
Since Brother Huang came to the Burial Abyss for treasure...
you must surely be prepared.
Aside from the Immortal Medicine...
why haven't I seen any other burial artifacts for protection?
Why not take them out...
so we may broaden our horizons?
Quick, check.
Which of my weapons can pass for the real thing?
None of these will work.
They have no relation to burial artifacts.
Wait...
this one...
This is an incredible Ancient Burial Artifact.
Quick!
Take it out fast!
What happened?
Brother Huang, you are so boring.
I wonder which Burial King's kin...
hides their identity...
making this little sister look like a fool.
This fluctuation...
probably buried a True Immortal of the Undying Race.
Tell me, Brother Huang...
what exactly is your origin?
To be able to pocket such burial treasures.
Just an old trinket.
Hardly worth mentioning.
Opportunity lies before us.
Priority should be taking the burial treasures.
Could the Dark God Son have been a Burial Soldier?
Perhaps.
The Underworld is also related to the Burial Earth.
This burial soil nurtures the vitality of the Primordial Era.
Not only does it nourish immortal medicine...
it also allows us Burial Soldiers to leap in cultivation.
Apologies, Brother Huang...
but I must get there first!
Tsk.
This damn competitive spirit.
Er Xue...
use the Nine-Eyed Stone...
to collect all this burial soil.
Then open the cauldron to collect the treasures.
Brother Huang, show mercy...
share some with us, will you?
You fool.
Such top-tier burial soil, and you give it away so casually?
Stick with me...
and forget this silver sand...
even my one-zhang cube of Myriad Soil...
is yours to take root in.
Ah...
Thanks for showing mercy, Brother Huang.
With more burial treasures for protection...
once the Burial King restriction lifts...
we can also go stir up trouble in the foreign domain.
Though the Burial Soldiers didn't collude with the foreign lands...
their temperament is eccentric.
Once they emerge, I fear they will cause waves of turmoil again.
This aura...
why does it feel so familiar?
The Dark Cage...
a living being is escaping from inside.
A supreme being has emerged!
Dodge!
It is the legendary...
Lord Ru Gu, who was about to become an Immortal!
He has also lost his soul!
(Ancient Burial Language)
What is he shouting?
His accent is too thick...
how would I know?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
A Burial Soldier of this level...
could crush us to dust with a wave of his hand.
Run!
What is the origin of this chest?
It's so sturdy.
Ask less about what you shouldn't ask.
If this chest were so easy to destroy...
it would have rotted away in that grave long ago.
Suppress.
Looking at the direction that Lord came from...
could it be the rumored Lord of Our World...
sealed deep within the Burial Abyss?
Such overwhelming power just now...
was merely a flick of my Lord's finger.
Brother Huang...
what kind of burial artifact is this chest?
It is indestructible.
Truly extraordinary.
I am very interested in the patterns on its surface.
Might I observe them for a moment?
Please.
How wondrous.
These patterns bring clarity to the mind...
making one feel on the verge of enlightenment.
Yet the chest itself...
inspires disgust.
Such a contradiction.
It seems this chest is indeed related to the Burial Soldiers.
Old Medicine...
what do you know?
Ah...
between knowing and knowing...
there are differences.
Some things, once known, can be said.
Others, once known, are not necessarily sayable.
And some things are...
things you wouldn't understand even if I told you.
I knew the Burial Abyss opening would be unpredictable...
finding the Great Dao amidst life and death.
That is the path a warrior should walk.
This martial fanatic...
Brother Huang, care to join?
Inside the Abyss lies not only the Burial Five Opportunity...
but perhaps also the truth behind this rotten wooden chest.
Let's go.
Everyone saw it.
The giant hand that shocked the Heavenly Abyss...
appeared precisely where Huang had gone.
He is most likely colluding with the foreign domain...
to create such an omen.
Huang once severed ten Kings...
bearing a blood feud with the foreign lands.
No matter who the traitor is...
it can never be him.
Whoever splashes dirty water on my brother...
calling him a defector to the foreign lands...
is clearly a thief crying "stop thief."
Who told Huang to return so late?
Someone used the Imperial Pass teleportation array to go to the foreign domain.
This is ironclad evidence.
We will not wrong a good person...
nor let a bad person go.
G...
Until the truth is revealed...
no one is to leave the pass.
Since it is confirmed that the traitor is not Huang...
we should bring him back immediately.
You lot are clearly trying to obstruct the rescue.
Huang recklessly charged into the Sacred Medicine Mountain Range...
and now you want to waste the elite of Imperial Pass to save him?
Are other people's lives not lives?
A bunch of cowards.
I will ask my Master to act personally.
I don't believe we can't save Huang.
Ignorant fools.
You have no right to speak here.
A student of my Heavenly God Academy...
needs no discipline from the Wang family.
Pass my greetings to your Master.
However, given the current situation...
there is no need to disturb the old man.
I will go alone...
and bring Huang back.
Senior...
your severe injuries are not yet healed.
It would be best to go to the Ancestral Altar...
and invite one or two Supreme Beings to assist.
Huang is my disciple.
Naturally, I must act personally.
If others from Imperial Pass suffer losses because of this...
my heart will not be at peace.
He is burning the Supreme Battle Blood within him.
That terrifying power from before...
was not even his full strength.
He broke through again.
This is the invincible bearing that suppressed an era.
And yet...
he is still getting stronger.
Senior Meng actually succeeded in reversing aging...
and regained his youth!
The Grand Elder was so handsome when he was young...
radiating brilliance.
Now that is a true hero.
I hope...
I am not too late.
[Episode 267 — Power Rankings - 1.Funeral King, 2.Bone Sovereign, 3.Shi Hao (Full Power) 4.Golden Supreme / Tu Mingxuan 5.Wang Yu, 6.Huang]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™