(Adaptation of iReader Literature's author Fengwu Jiguang's novel Back as Immortal Lord)
- Return of Immortal Emperor -
(All the dangerous moves and actions
in this video were made by virtual technology.)
(No human performers were hurt during this process.)
(Minors should be accompanied by their parents to watch.
Do not imitate in reality.)
Episode 5
(The Second Mouse Enjoys the Cheese)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Is that...?
This terrifying heavenly soul strength.
Darn.
Your cultivation should've been destroyed
when you breached the spatial barrier in reverse.
Why do you still have such pressure?
How dare you suspect us?
Azure Blaze,
don't you just have a bit of a soul left?
You only have the corporeal soul,
so you can't devour me.
You were so stupid
when trying to break into my Cognition Sea.
If Fengwu Jiguang hadn't separated me from my body,
I would've swallowed you entirely!
Still boasting in front of us.
I...
I am sorry.
Keep this in your lava head.
If you offend an Immortal Lord,
you are doomed even if you have a thousand souls.
I remember that.
I remember that!
Where did Fengwu Jiguang take your body?
Xingkong Academy.
But I can't locate it precisely.
Maybe
its sense is blocked by a seal.
Xingkong Academy is the most famous and oldest academy
in the Tianyuan Dynasty.
It was built by Fengwu Jiguang three thousand years ago.
So it's reasonable he sealed your body
at that place.
You have two choices now.
First,
be executed right here.
- Second... - Master.
- I choose the second. - Well.
Attaboy.
I'm at your service.
I'll put you in my Cognition Sea.
Don't idle there.
Learn this Utmost Technique,
Clouds Spirit.
When I bring your body back,
your soul may return to it.
Thank you, Master.
With the complete Azure Blaze,
it will help me regain the Lord State.
Don't bother yourself with it.
I'll blend in your Cognition Sea myself.
It'll be a bit spicy.
Hang in there for a moment.
Hot! So hot!
Holy cow.
The young man is on fire.
Done.
The soul of Azure Blaze
has totally integrated into my Cognition Sea.
Though it's not complete,
it has upgraded my cultivation by a level.
Now I'm in the Ninth Phase of the Star State.
(The Ninth Phase of the Star State)
Where is his body then?
Let's get out of here first.
(Back as Immortal Lord)
Are we going to this Xingkong Academy?
It can wait.
I need to enhance my cultivation first.
This place is kind of interesting.
What is that dishonoring game?
The young people have so many tricks.
You know so much.
Search carefully,
or I'll whip you so hard.
You are so smart
to let the stupid man and woman wear pig masks
to look for Purple Seven Gods Fruit for us.
Thank you, Master.
Because they stole our Tianyuan Academy's treasure map!
(The treasure hunting squad of the Tianyuan Academy)
(The treasure hunting squad of teachers and disciples
from the Outer School of the Tianyuan Academy)
No wonder Tianyuan Academy
could cultivate a brilliant graduate like Lin Wei.
What a method.
The Purple Spiritual Mushroom?
That's it.
This spot must be the hidden entrance
to the Seven Gods Cave.
Master.
Let's go inside.
These burglars are useless now, right?
Kill them.
Keep the woman
for our master first.
Then we'll have a taste of her.
Let me go.
Please!
It's a shame for a pretty girl like you to be a burglar.
I have to cleanse you carefully.
Kill the man, and tie up the woman.
When we get the Purple Seven Gods Fruit,
let's come back to celebrate it.
A wise decision, Master.
We must enter the cave before Huo Dun and his people.
An in-fighting?
How do I
deserve such a solemn salute?
Master.
You are...
Who are you?
How dare you assassinate a master of Tianyuan Academy?
I wouldn't call it an assassin.
It was just a sneeze of my servant
that killed an evil for the people.
Sorry for that.
Did the Lins send you to save that stupid pair?
The Lins?
Now it's funny.
Humph.
Whoever you are,
you will die
for killing my master.
Dao.
That spiritual beast looks strong.
I'm afraid that rascal is not weak.
If we run away, we'll be executed by the Academy.
But if we distract him with the Trap Formation
and take away his beast,
we may be rewarded.
Young man.
That's a brilliant plan.
You are scheming against me?
Want to die?
Is Tianyuan Academy full of wusses?
We are all in the Ninth Phase of the Star State.
You don't seem to have reached the Moon State.
So it is easy for us to defeat you together.
I've never heard someone
talk about bullying by numbers in such a grand way.
Our Trap Formation
will never lose.
Rascal.
Go to Hell!
Good. I can use you
to try the power of Azure Blaze.
What did you say?
Ninelayers Palm!
He has learned the skill of changing Spiritual Qi into palm?
What is your cultivation?
What a coincidence.
I'm also on the Ninth Phase of the Star State.
Then how could you learn the upper human-grade skill?
You also have such strong pressure.
Have you really acquired Azure Blaze?
You know so much.
It's a shame
you used your intelligence for the wrong thing.
Stop now,
or I'll kill your spiritual beast!
Even I can't kill it.
Do it
if you can.
You think I dare not?
Am I too kind to you?
Didn't flee when you had the chance.
Pathetic fool.
Thank you for saving us.
Don't.
I didn't plan to save you.
It was just a coincidence.
Now go.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
All right. I can eat the Seven Gods Fruit.
Sh.
Listen carefully.
An.
Are you sure of that?
Yes.
It's definitely Yun Qingyan.
I saw him three years ago.
Beihua was killed by him a few days ago.
So,
if we find a way to kill him,
we'll be big heroes of the Lins.
But he saved us.
Besides,
he looks too strong.
Rong, take it easy.
I have a plan.
They just mentioned another group of Tianyuan Academy.
Well.
I see.
It's just
that you will suffer a bit.
So naughty.
Those ingrates.
How could there be a good egg
in the snake pit of the Lins?
Like I thought.
It cost me some strength
to use Azure Blaze just now.
I can take a break now
and then defeat them
in their game.
Great.
I like games.
(The Seven Gods Cave)
The Purple Seven Gods Fruits?
They are also the highest purple grade.
Thank Heaven.
(Huo Dun, the first bane of disciples
A master from the Outer School of the Tianyuan Academy)
The two people
are useless now.
Master Huo.
It was Yun Qingyan who killed our peers
and master.
If you really had killed that old bastard and his brats,
I would've thanked you.
Please let us go
since we've led you here.
Noisy.
It served them well.
Shut down the Cognition Sea
and wait for the good show.
Master.
Let me pick the fruit for you.
Hold on.
That's the rarest treasure in this world.
You don't
taint the fruit.
The fruits are emitting Spiritual Qi.
Open all your Cognition Sea,
and your cultivation will be improved greatly.
Amazing!
Wait a minute.
I read it in a book.
That is...
Spiritnibbling Fern!
What a vicious master.
You
should've read the whole book.
A little knowledge will only get you killed.
The Seven Gods Fruits
could have the rarest purple grade
all thanks to that Utmost herb,
the Spiritnibbling Fern.
It secretes psychedelic spiritual spores
to lure people into the mire
and become the fertilizer for the fruits.
Using a Violet Gold Pearl of the king grade
or closing your Cognition Sea can resist the illusions.
A herb uses your power
to control so many people instantly,
so I guess you can stand no longer.
I'll get rid of you
and make you into soup
to nourish myself.
You are Yun Qingyan?
Have you watched enough?
That extra-curricular practice
is outstanding.
Thank you.
I heard Lin Wei has you in his sights.
Let me watch it
when you two have that duel.
I'm afraid you can't see it.
Right.
If you compete with me,
a fighter of the Moon State, for the fruits,
you will die here.
Lin Wei is such a lucky tyke.
Prayer.
All the masters of Tianyuan Academy
are talented
with sweet words.
I want to pluck out his tongue
to admire it.
You won't be lonely in another world
since you'll die with your servant.
We're less than you since you are admired by your disciples.
You...
It takes the Seven Gods Fruits
300 years to bloom, 300 years to bear fruit,
and 300 years to take an immortal shape.
Besides, they have absorbed too many lives' Spiritual Veins
and are murderous.
It's a redemption for them
to be picked by me.
One Purple Seven Gods Fruit
can upgrade a Moon State fighter by one level.
When I take them all,
I'll peak the Moon State.
Guess what I want to do the most then.
Not so interested.
Those useless maggots and hypocrites from the Inner School
looked down upon us masters of the Outer School.
Those wasters also tried
to compete with me for the fruits.
I guess they also wanted to take me down!
When I reach the peak of the Moon State,
I'll carry out a bloodbath in the Academy
to reorganize it.
So ambitious
and kind of unlucky.
The Spiritnibbling Fern's spiritual spores are still here.
You need your Cognition Sea to use your Spiritual Qi,
but you will die.
I'm different, however.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™