(Adaptation of iReader Literature's author Fengwu Jiguang's novel Back as Immortal Lord)
- Return of Immortal Emperor -
(All the dangerous moves and actions
in this video were made by virtual technology.)
(No human performers were hurt during this process.)
(Minors should be accompanied by their parents to watch.
Do not imitate in reality.)
Episode 6
(The Unique Beauty)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
The Spiritnibbling Fern's spiritual spores are still here.
You need your Cognition Sea to use your Spiritual Qi,
but you will die.
I'm different, however.
So close.
I could barely shut down my Cognition Sea.
How detestable.
No wonder Lin Beihua was defeated by you!
Don't worry.
I'm a fair person.
Since you've closed your Cognition Sea,
I won't use the Violet Gold Pearl.
Why don't we
fight a melee battle?
Oh, no!
Something went wrong in the Yuns.
Grand Elder. Could you tell me
why I am summoned in such a hurry?
A merry thing, of course.
You encouraged Yun Qingyan to ruin my cultivation
and kill my son.
Today I will have my revenge.
So it's certainly a great merry thing.
What do you mean?
Kill him now!
Who are you scoundrels?
How dare you attack me on the Yuns' turf?
It's the two of you.
Our land has many unusual issues.
Have evil people sneaked into it?
Somebody help! Help!
What's happening? Who are they?
The Ironwolf's young master, Hei Luo,
leads his men to attack here.
They've got Feifei.
What?
The mountain gate is strictly guarded.
How could it be breached so easily?
Die!
You...
Go to Hell.
What's up?
In a hurry?
Yes.
So you must die right now.
Very well.
I'll give you a physical cultivation class.
The tuition
is your life!
Join that vile pair in Hell.
Yun Qingyan.
You haven't reached the Moon State yet.
How could you have such strength?
When I just entered the Immortal Realm,
I started with physical cultivation.
They are just muscle memories.
Full of nonsense.
Have you inhaled the psychedelic spores?
Believe it or not.
Idiot.
The Seven Gods Fruits
are close at hand.
Spiritnibbling Fern, have you slept enough?
Time to work.
I can turn the tide
by eating one.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Cheesy.
Are you stunned?
So you wait to die?
Master Huo.
Your class
was brilliant.
You were so urgent
to defeat me
and opened your Immortal Cognition
to release your Spiritual Qi to use the lightness skill.
When you breathed,
you were dragged into the illusion by the spiritual spores.
Then you were scared by the ghosts in your heart,
and you cut off your legs.
It served you well.
All right.
Don't keep your disciples waiting.
Go now.
Want the Seven Gods Fruits?
Eat your own bad fruit.
Good boy.
I want one.
Keep one for Xuan.
The First Phase of the Moon State.
(The First Phase of the Moon State)
I have reached it.
Let's go.
Is that...?
(Back as Immortal Lord)
What is your stupid Ironwolf Gang?
When Qingyan returns,
all of you will die.
I've brought my men here to propose to you.
How could you have the heart to refuse me?
(Hei Luo, the first Daddy's boy in Tianyu City)
(The young master of the Ironwolf Gang,
the strongest sect in Tianyu City)
Hei Luo.
Don't even think about it.
Get out of here!
The chief and my dad will come to my rescue.
Yun Han and those silly old men
are taken care of by my men.
I'm afraid they are all dead now.
Ha-ha.
As for your dad,
my prospective father-in-law,
he is quite satisfied with this marriage.
Let me go.
Will you obey or not?
I'll be dead before I go with you.
How could I let you die?
By the way,
your dad said
that the Yuns' Spiritual Herbal Garden
and the Darksteel mine you've just got from the Lins
will be your dowries.
The Four Elders
helped me greatly today.
Here is my love token for you.
Xuan.
That waster Yun Xuan?
How do you
have a new hand?
Both your hand
and Cognition Sea have recovered?
Thanks to Qingyan.
He made the Spiritual Recovery Pellet for me a few days ago
and taught me the Primordial Skills
to regenerate my hand.
That's great!
Waster.
Let my wife go!
Xuan.
You've just recovered.
Don't use your spiritual power again.
Don't step up
for a woman since you are weak!
Wolf pup,
don't you take Feifei away.
You are not dead yet?
Those old bums of the Yuns
are really not reliable.
The mere young master of the Ironwolf Gang
dares to run riot here?
So rude.
Your brats are too fragile.
Remember to take them back for burial.
Good-for-nothings.
It's our last favor
for Hei Kui to let you leave in one piece.
The three old bastards are desperate.
It's not over.
Well. A mistake.
It's a mistake.
How could I hurt Feifei's family?
My dad will come to propose formally soon.
Wait for me, Darling.
Supreme Elder.
You are severely wounded, too.
I'm fine.
I'm taking Yun Meng to heal.
Thank you.
Dad.
Are you all right?
The situation was dire.
The Four Elders colluded with the Ironwolf Gang
to attack us suddenly.
But your wound...
It's my fault.
The Ironwolf has taken the Lins' side.
You are just their excuse to attack us.
As the Third Elder, my dad
did it with the other Elders.
It doesn't matter what he did,
you are still a good child whom I've watched grow up.
The Ironwolf Gang attacked us with the Four Elders
to cripple us.
I'm sure Hei Kui will lead his major force
with his hall leaders to attack here soon.
Our force is weakened greatly,
and Xuan hasn't fully recovered.
Now,
we can only hope that Qingyan may return in time.
But there are so many people in the Ironwolf Gang,
and they usually attack in groups.
Even if Qingyan makes it back,
will he...?
I have faith in him.
Qingyan
is our whole clan's hope.
We've got company. This is no good.
Pace up then.
Luckily, my lightness skills
have improved after I entered the Moon State.
Lady.
I'm in a hurry to help my family.
So I have no time for this game.
(Li Ranzhu, a unique and mysterious beauty)
What a unique and mysterious beauty!
I'm hunting and intercepting you.
So it's not a game.
Fair enough.
Give me
the Azure Blaze.
I like your straightforwardness.
But no.
No way can I give up what I've required.
Not to mention the Azure Blaze
has been integrated into my Cognition Sea.
If I really throw it up,
I'll suffer so much.
Then I'll kill you first.
Nice bow. Nice skills.
I didn't expect
there to be such a magical weapon in the Tianyuan Dynasty.
It's called Tornmoon.
Would you tell me your name, too?
Even the strikes
of that beauty are beautiful.
You are gross.
Stop dodging.
Attack me.
Don't attack.
You are so wordy.
That bow is an Utmost weapon at least
and is as powerful as my Skyslash.
So this lady is somebody.
You don't have a weapon?
Just a sheath.
Now it's fair.
Then it'll be so rude to refuse you.
Thousands of Palms!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™