FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Stars reverse their course—
celestial light overturned.
Primordial chaos, cosmic void—
one sword conquers the eight realms!
Heaven’s Cauldron, Tianyu Peak—
vast and boundless.
I’ll shatter the heavens—
defy the laws of cultivation!
Crimson inferno, karmic flame—
accompany me here.
stand with me now.
Lord of Heavenly Flame!
I’ve never feared karma—
—nor the fruits of mortal deeds.
Truth—
—shatters the void!
Why heed the past?
Heart drowned in demon’s grace—
—am I god or demon?
God or demon?
Am I god...
...or demon?
Hear the thunder roar!
On the day I return—
heaven and earth shall tremble!
Through trials unending—
—I tread the path of immortals,
—marching through the Celestial Realm,
—undaunted and proud.
Still wild, still bold.
Today, I avenge my fallen brothers!
You—
—you called your buddies
just to watch you die?
How embarrassing!
Six!
You’re seriously something!
Pretty boy!
Today...
...I’ll teach you a lesson—
—a simple truth:
fists beat big talk any day!
Bear Fists of Domination!
Even in death,
my brothers get no peace!
Feint left—strike right!
I’ve been waiting
for this exact trick!
Where’s your backup?
Still not here?
Pretty boy...
Is that supposed to be a scratch?
Kinda tickles, actually!
You’ve got no idea
what you’re up against!
Then enjoy it while you can.
This kid’s been infected
with a low-grade demon seed.
Stinks like a wet cat!
Demon-seed cults...
—even bandits are doing it now?
You monster!
Why won’t you just die!?
Savor your last few breaths.
Since when—
—how...?
Weren’t you enjoying the “scratching”?
You damned monster!
Your brothers are here!
Say your goodbyes!
Chief Liu Liu!
You alright?
Alright my ass!
All of you—attack!
Kill this pretty-faced punk!
Look—
so many fools
coming to hand us victory!
Free points? Don’t mind if I do!
Go get the boss!
Call the Big Chief!
You—
—save yourself the trouble.
We’ll be paying your Big Chief
a visit shortly.
Huang Qingfeng,
leader of your gang.
I’ll show you the way, big brother!
I know Qingfeng Stronghold
—like the back of my hand.
You go to hell!
Don’t worry about us!
N-no! Please!
My mom said—
—the day I was born,
auspicious signs filled the sky!
Nine breathtakingly beautiful
heavenly maidens
descended on clouds of mist—
—they touched my mother’s belly and said:
“This child—
—is the reincarnation
of a nine-times-sainted soul!
His divine power shakes the heavens!”
He’s destined to rule
the entire Tianxing Continent!
Why not say those nine maidens
were your lovers from each past life?
Oh mighty saint—
—any idea
what’s happening right now?
At the gate—
—imposing!
If I didn’t know better,
I’d think this was a noble manor!
Thought we'd walked into
a royal resort!
Playing the Empty Fort Strategy?
Could it be...
my divine might scared them off,
packing up and fleeing overnight?
Smells like something burnt...
What is this?
People...
What'd you say?
Traces left after instant carbonization.
Damn...
Killing and cremating on the spot!
Looks like tonight's guests
at Qingfeng Stronghold
aren't just us from Starry Sky Academy.
Help!
Fight that old monster!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Brother Tu Tu!
I knew you'd come
be the hero saving the beauty!
Pfft!
I'm just worried you'd die ugly
and embarrass the academy.
Brother Tu Tu's all soft heart,
hard mouth.
I'll go fetch reinforcements!
You picked a good day.
While Starry Sky Academy clears
the small fry bandits,
you strike the heart
to harvest demon seeds.
What?
There are demon seeds here?
In this guy's body...
besides one second-grade demon seed
at Lunar Realm sixth stage,
I also sensed
five third-grade ones
cultivated to Lunar fifth stage.
Seems he just collected them.
So many...
Not worried about indigestion?
Turning Qingfeng Stronghold
into a demon seed breeding ground...
Tian Yuan Academy
sure excels in demonic paths.
Quick!
Kill him!
I crave the demon seeds
in his body!
Hold on...
I found something interesting.
You seem very interested
in demon seeding.
Want to be my disciple?
Always playing the mentor...
Whoa!
Save me!
I bet...
the demon seed in Qingfeng leader
Huang Qingfeng's body
was long ripe,
but he refused to let you harvest it.
So...
you seized today's chaos
to ambush him in panic,
swallowing both man and seed
to eliminate threats.
Yun Qingyan...
You do have some brains.
Much sharper than him.
Congrats...
Your demon seed just broke through
to Lunar seventh stage, right?
Not bad.
Today, I'll dispense justice
and slay you, great demon!
Save him!
Got it!
Finally, some alone time.
Worthy of Tian Yuan's top genius—
ruthless hand.
Figured out who I am?
If I'm not wrong...
Iron Wolf Gang's Hei Kui
and his son Hei Luo,
plus Lin Wei's demon seed—
all tied to you, right?
Vice Dean Jia...
Too bad...
I snatched them all.
Ruining my plans again and again,
even killing my beloved disciple Lin Wei—
you'll pay with your life!
So fond of your dear disciple...
no wonder you planted a demon seed in him.
That advisor...
That useless spy—
I saw potential in him,
so I made slight use of him.
Who knew...
practicing demons turned him
neither man nor ghost—
wasting all my efforts!
So kind-hearted...
but you just used Lin Wei
as a demon seed incubator,
waiting to harvest when ripe.
Pity...
Lin Wei never saw your true face
till death.
Fine then...
Since that's the case...
Then you'll take Lin Wei's place...
and become the new vessel
for my demon seed!
Blood Brake Golden Core!
It's over.
Blood Puppet Technique!
I've cultivated demon seeds
in Qingfeng Stronghold for years.
This one I've refined...
nurture it well for me.
As expected...
That old fox really planted
a second-grade demon seed in me.
Quite lively!
Come chase me, big brother~
You can't drive me away.
Just accept me peacefully.
Drive away...
Can you leave or not?
That depends on the other one.
Since you're here...
stay and play nicely.
You two...
just stay put in there.
Wait to be slowly refined.
Sit tight...
little mouth...
shut up.
No, no!
So noisy!
Ran Zhu...
What are you yelling for?
This is Sister Ling Xue.
It's fine...
Senior Brother Yun
must have had a nightmare.
Good that he's awake now.
I'll bring some hot porridge later.
It hurts...
You...
Don't bully...
Sister Ling Xue!
Rebelling now?
Brother Yun...
You're finally awake!
Now we're true brothers in hardship...
hearts linked as one.
Didn't expect this girl
to be a true immortal descendant.
And she herself
seems unaware...
of this secret.
Let her uncover it herself later.
[The next day...]
Senior Brother Yun...
My apologies.
That was just a warm-up.
Now I'll teach you
what you asked for last time—
the Phoenix Dance Heavenly Maiden Scripture.
I'm ready.
Clear your mind...
Circulate your spiritual energy
through your body once,
then surge it into the Qianlan acupoint.
Incredible...
Brother Yun is truly incredible!
Barely escaped death...
and already blooming with romance!
Hmph...
Humans...
This Ling Xue...
just entered the genius class,
immensely talented...
and adored by all.
If the genius class ranked by popularity...
those three idiots wouldn't qualify
to carry her foot-washing water.
Maybe...
only second to yours truly.
This Sister Ling Xue...
reminds me of my first love.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™