♪Night pierces the window, light shines through♪
♪Let us follow the long immortal path♪
♪Eight coils, nine bends, now desolate♪
♪All beings ask: does worldly wine break the heart?♪
♪Rebirth from nirvana, written on the page♪
♪With flesh and blood, I break the vast waves♪
♪Heaven is vast; born ordinary, so what?♪
♪Cold eyes, when will the Dao run wild?♪
♪Deep in the cliffs, wind and thunder swirl♪
♪Much to ponder—life and death, a fleeting dream♪
♪Sword unsheathed, seeking immortal strength♪
♪In this world, all is uncertain♪
♪Fate and cosmos grant a bittersweet truth♪
♪Embrace the seas, swallow the wilds♪
♪In a moment, all is changed♪
♪I fly against the light♪
♪Rewrite a new chapter for all realms and beings♪
♪Mortal or immortal, just a thought apart♪
♪An ant’s body transforms into light♪
♪Grains of sand cross the wild heavens♪
♪Youthful heart braves wind and rain♪
♪I defy fate, become immortal, and battle the heavens♪
- Renegade Immortal -
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, please watch with guardian consent)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Adapted from Er Gen's novel "Renegade Immortal" on Qidian)
(Last episode recap)
(The immortal and demonic powers within remain entangled)
(Balance is hard to break)
(Better to break it with external force)
Stop.
Everyone, stand down.
If they act this way,
we should teach them a harsh lesson.
(Establish authority)
(No need to rush)
You must also
defy your superiors.
Those who defy their superiors
do not deserve to live.
I was reckless.
Please forgive me, Wang Tongling.
To oppose me,
you are not qualified.
(If someone skilled in barriers could help me,)
(success would be certain.)
Episode 114
(Breaking the Barrier)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Wang)
(The thousand-armored demon crystals within me)
(Thousand-armored demon crystals)
(If fully fused into immortal power)
(and combined with all my Immortal Jade)
(it’s barely enough to reach Late Soul Transformation)
Halt, stranger.
I have urgent business with Wang Tongling.
The elder is in seclusion.
Please leave.
Fellow Daoist Yao barged in rudely.
Is this not improper?
I was presumptuous in this matter.
Fellow Daoist Wang, please don’t take offense.
But I truly have an urgent request.
If it were not urgent,
do not blame me for being rude.
Fellow Daoist Wang,
this matter is highly confidential.
I must take precautions.
Please don’t mind.
This land of demon spirits
was once home to an Immortal Manor.
After the immortal realm collapsed,
it fell silent.
I chanced upon the site of an old Immortal Manor.
But I cannot break the barrier outside alone.
I heard Fellow Daoist Wang is skilled in barrier arts.
If we succeed in entering,
we split the immortal treasures half and half.
What do you say?
(The Immortal Manor is worth exploring)
(but this person is not trustworthy.)
(I must investigate further.)
I am at a critical point in my cultivation.
I cannot help.
Forgive me.
I suppose Fellow Daoist Wang is striving for Late Soul Transformation.
But Immortal Jade is scarce here.
To show my sincerity,
I am willing to offer you
all the Immortal Jade needed for Early Ascension.
This is a deposit.
Enough to help you reach Late Soul Transformation.
Help me enter the Immortal Manor,
and the rest
will be given to you after success.
(No wonder she’s the Blood Ancestor’s daughter)
(such a generous offer.)
This matter is unpredictable.
Forgive me, I do not wish to take the risk.
If you worry for your safety,
you may take this Blood-Soul Elixir.
It will keep you safe.
(Blood-Soul Elixir)
(A treasure refined by Blood Ancestor’s secret arts)
(Even if the body is destroyed, they say)
(and the soul is annihilated,)
(this elixir can restore you anew.)
(Completely unharmed.)
(With this life-saving treasure,)
(death holds no fear.)
Blood Star’s supreme treasure.
I’ve heard of it.
How is it used?
This is my blood clan’s secret art.
I cannot reveal it easily.
Unless you agree to go with me.
I can give you one more
as payment.
Agreed.
Follow the instructions inside.
Leave a mark within the Blood-Soul Elixir.
Later, your soul and body will be linked.
You’ll be restored at my clan’s nearest formation.
In three days.
At the third quarter of the Purple Demon’s rise.
Meet at Drum Mountain.
(Holding this item,)
(I feel my blood merging with it.)
(Three days later)
(Wang)
I’m heading out for a while.
While I’m gone,
you two stay in the Black Armor Battalion and wait for me.
Focus on your cultivation.
Yes.
(Drum Mountain, Land of Demon Spirits)
(I’ve given him enough Immortal Jade)
(Three days have passed)
(and he still hasn’t reached Late Soul Transformation.)
(It seems he’s nothing special.)
When the Purple Demon shines brightest,
blood light will appear on the compass.
Stay close.
(Outside Qinglin Immortal Abode, Land of Demon Spirits)
Sit in meditation.
Comprehend your own domain.
Once the Golden Rune accepts you,
you may walk the Path of the Honored Beast.
(Golden Rune merges into the body)
It's your turn.
(On Yao Xixue's body)
(There is a trace of Immortal Lord's aura)
(I only gained three strokes of the Golden Rune)
(He actually obtained six strokes)
(Could his domain surpass mine?)
(How is that possible?)
Let's go.
(Yao Xixue is very familiar with this place)
(It's clearly not her first time here)
(As the Blood Ancestor's beloved daughter)
(She has all the Immortal treasures she needs)
(Why would she risk coming here?)
(Path of the Honored Beast, First Platform)
(She is fixated on this Immortal Manor)
(She must be acting on the Blood Ancestor's orders)
(Her goal is much greater)
There are twelve layers of seals here.
You and I will take turns breaking them.
I'll handle the first layer.
Seal.
(This statue's cultivation rivals a Nascent Soul cultivator)
(Yao Xixue can seal it so easily)
(The Blood Star artifact truly lives up to its name)
(That's...)
(Golden Rune)
(The Golden Rune inside the statue)
(is almost identical to the one gained from comprehending the domain)
(Could it be that this Golden Rune infused with Immortal power)
(is sealed inside the statue?)
(If that's true)
(these twelve seals may not be obstacles)
(but incredible opportunities)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Second Platform)
(It really is a Barrier construct)
(There must be a way to break the Barrier)
(With his mastery of Barriers, he could break the formation directly)
(Why is he still struggling with the statue?)
(As expected)
(This is the formation's core)
Release.
(Why is there a Golden Rune inside the statue?)
(This Golden Rune)
(seems to be layered atop the rune from the first platform)
(A lucky coincidence)
(Just good luck)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Third Platform)
(Just smashing the statue)
(What's so hard about that?)
(This time it's three strokes of the Golden Rune)
Where did it go wrong?
Why can't I produce the Golden Rune?
(Path of the Honored Beast, Fourth Platform)
(Four strokes of the Golden Rune)
(Indeed)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Fifth Platform)
What did he actually do?
(Path of the Honored Beast, Sixth Platform)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Seventh Platform)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Eighth Platform)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Ninth Platform)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Tenth Platform)
(Path of the Honored Beast, Eleventh Platform)
The last one.
Twelve strokes of the Golden Rune.
This is...
(Qing Lin)
The character "Lin"
I am Qing Lin.
(The former master of this Immortal Manor must be Qing Lin)
(Qing Lin)
(Something's off)
(These twelve layers of Immortal Restriction)
(get harder with each layer)
(but with Yao Xixue's abilities)
(she could easily pass through alone using her artifact)
(Why insist on bringing me along?)
(The Barrier statues aren't the final trial)
(Here)
(there's another danger)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(The fierce wind blocks the path)
(There's no way back now)
Take three sword strikes from me.
Only then are you qualified to enter the Immortal Manor.
Each of us will take one strike
and the last strike together.
Alright.
First person.
Step forward.
Fellow Daoist Wang
Please.
What if I refuse?
You've seen it yourself
The way back is sealed.
Anyone who receives the Golden Rune mark here
has only one way to survive—enter the Immortal Manor.
So
inviting me to break the Barrier was just a ruse
you really want me to block the sword for you.
We just need to withstand these three Ascendant sword strikes together
then we can enter the Immortal Manor.
Fellow Daoist Yao, you flatter me.
I am only at the mid-stage of Nascent Soul Transformation
How could I withstand the Ascendant sword strike?
Wang Lin
Break through with me
It's your only chance to survive.
Succeed and you live
fail and you die.
You
have no choice.
Don't worry.
Didn't you already take the Blood-Soul Elixir?
Fellow Daoist Yao, you're quite calculating.
Likewise.
I hope this time
you keep your word.
With your mid-stage Nascent Soul Transformation
taking one sword strike
won't necessarily kill you.
Quick, use the Blood-Soul secret art
to save your life, Fellow Daoist Wang.
But if you took the fake elixir I gave you
you'll surely die.
This Immortal Manor's location
is a top secret of my Blood Clan.
How could I let you leave alive?
Wang Lin
To sacrifice your life for my clan's cause
is your honor.
The first strike
you've passed.
The second strike
Are you ready?
Come.
I've entered this place several times
The Barrier statues
can all be overcome with artifacts
but these three sword strikes
I can only withstand two, no matter what.
Now that Wang Lin blocked one for me
there's no suspense in this battle.
The final strike.
Father
I did not let you down.
I made it.
Blood Clan
Hope for ascension
Thank you, Fellow Daoist Yao.
For helping me withstand two strikes.
You're still alive.
I suspected it long ago.
The Blood-Soul Elixir you gave me was fake.
Such a precious item—
How could you give it to me so easily?
And you were so concerned for my safety.
You probed me with your divine sense
to make sure I took the elixir.
If the elixir was fake,
then the Immortal Manor is likely real.
So I didn't use your Immortal Jade to reach Late Soul Transformation.
Instead, I turned it into Immortal Crystal and stored it within.
To use it for survival.
So you used Immortal Crystal to withstand the Ascendant sword aura.
You feigned falling into the abyss with the sword's force.
Waited for me to take two strikes,
and be gravely wounded.
Then you reaped the benefits.
Zhou Wutai once told me
the true use of the Liming Hat is to hide one's aura.
Don't waste your strength.
I've sealed your meridians.
Right now,
you can't use any immortal power.
Wang Lin
You may as well kill me.
To kill you—
You must have taken the Blood-Soul Elixir.
Killing you just sends you back to some blood array.
I will bind you with the Domain of Life and Death.
I won't kill you.
Then the Blood-Soul Elixir loses its purpose.
You—
(She schemed tirelessly)
(using Ascendant sword aura and a fake Blood-Soul Elixir in tandem)
(to set a deadly trap for me.)
(What immortal treasures lie within this manor?)
(That the Blood Clan would go to such lengths?)
Remnant soul of the Immortal Manor
Welcomes its master.
This is the Immortal Manor token.
With it, you may freely enter and leave the manor.
Master
Please enter the manor.
(Qing Lin)
(This token is nearly identical to the one from the tides that day.)
(Almost no difference.)
(Token)
(Master of the Immortal Manor)
(No wonder.)
(Qinglin Immortal Abode, Land of the Demon Spirits)
(Just like a palace of the Immortal Realm.)
(Entirely crafted from Immortal Jade.)
(The barriers here are complete.)
(Standing apart.)
(Must be the legendary Immortal Restriction.)
(With my current power,)
(I can't shake it at all.)
(It seems the previous master once broke through here.)
(This technique—)
(Could it be the ancient Plum Blossom Eighteen Restriction?)
(I used a predecessor's chance to obtain this wine vessel.)
(Though only ten drops remain,)
(it is immortal wine,)
(not a common thing.)
(The immortal brew is mellow.)
(It can intoxicate the soul.)
(I never expected)
(that this one drink)
would last a whole year.
(Renegade Immortal: Slaying to save his disciple, shaking the demon camp)
If I don't save Thirteen today—
All I, Wang Lin, have ever sought
will become nothing but a dream.
Thirteen!
Where are you?
Take this move: Hundred Waves of the Demon Sea!
Only then are you worthy to speak before me.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪Through endless years, I've seen it all♪
♪Just to glimpse your silhouette♪
♪Reversing the fate within the compass♪
♪Who decided this outcome?♪
♪Heaven erases your traces♪
♪Obsession guides me on♪
♪On this path, I pierce illusions♪
♪Confused by truth and lies♪
♪Lost in the haze, without a pure heart♪
♪How can right and wrong be clear?♪
♪See all beings drift with the current♪
♪See all beings swept away♪
♪Refusing to accept fate, who decides?♪
♪Let the world temper my soul♪
♪If I seek Renegade Immortal, so what?♪
♪Go and fight♪
♪In despair, the ultimate can be broken through♪
♪Today I finally know who I am♪
♪A body stained with blood from slaughter♪
♪Pursuing a lifetime of obsession♪
♪Never looking back at the desolation beside me♪
♪Even if hardship shatters my soul♪
♪How many times have I been reborn in hell?♪
♪Fight again♪
♪Sitting atop the highest throne♪
♪Hard to escape this loneliness♪
♪I've seen moths that chase the Vermilion Bird♪
♪Why would I fear fireflies?♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™