♪As night falls,
its light pierces the window♪
♪The path to immortality
is long and distant♪
♪Former grandeur
has turned to ruin♪
♪A cup of worldly wine stirs sorrow,
such is mortal life♪
♪Nirvana and rebirth
written on paper♪
♪With this body,
I cross the river♪
♪The sky is vast,
so what if I'm born ordinary?♪
♪How long can martial arts
remain so mighty?♪
♪Deep in the cliffs,
wind and thunder rage♪
♪Life and death,
in the end, are but a dream♪
♪I draw my sword
and question the heavens♪
♪The human world
is ever-changing♪
♪Creation, heaven, earth, fate—
all are bitter truths♪
♪Conquering the four seas
and eight realms♪
♪In a moment,
I endure all the hardships of time♪
♪Flying against the light,
I rise up♪
♪I will carry on
a new history for all worlds♪
♪To be human or immortal,
just a thought apart♪
♪A body like an ant
transforms into light♪
♪Grains of sand
cross the edge of the sky♪
♪A boy's heart
fears neither storm nor rain♪
♪Having become immortal,
why fear fighting the heavens?♪
- Renegade Immortal -
(Copyright Statement)
(Minors must have guardian
permission to view)
(This work was created
using computers)
(Do not attempt to imitate)
(Based on "Renegade Immortal" by Lee Geun, Weiwon Group)
(Previously)
Commander Yo-jang
was seeking someone
with a strong body
That barbarian fit
the requirements
So I sent him
to the Yo-jang Hall
He will meet Commander Yo-jang
and ask for Sibsang
He must withstand
my White Wolf technique
to earn the right
to negotiate with me
With the power
of the Immortal Realm
Borrow the east wind
to break their will
Three months later
If I win this Yo-jang contest
I will petition the Yo-je
to appoint you as Commander
and ask for a city
to be granted to you
Episode 116
[Island of Chaos]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Among the nine Yo-ryeong armies,
the Cheonyo Army
holds a Commander contest
every three hundred years
The victor
receives a cultivation technique
and treasure from the Yo-je
But this contest
is different from before
Two hundred years ago
the Cheonyo and Hwayo armies
went to war
Both sides suffered
heavy casualties
We even lost a Commander
and a Deputy
The Deputy naturally
took the Commander’s place
Thus,
the Cheonyo Army now has
two vacant Deputy positions
This time, besides awarding prizes,
two new Deputies
will be appointed
All Commanders
are vying for those seats
Originally, I gathered
eighteen strong men
to train the Eighteen Demon God Formation
But you took Sibsang away
and the technique was broken
Still, I believe
if you help me,
even without the Eighteen Demon Gods,
I can win the Deputy position
What I promised
I will do my utmost to help
But I still have
important matters to finish
In two months
I will meet you again
Alright
Be sure to keep your promise
Master Nojo
Master Nojo has returned
Master Nojo has come back
Master Nojo
Master Nojo has returned
We humbly welcome
Master Nojo’s return
(The current prosperity)
(reminds me of the Yeonhon tribe’s
former glory)
Master Nojo
While you were away,
all disciples devoted themselves
to training as you ordered
Each day, we released soul essence
into the black mist
and grew stronger
Now, the Soul Energy technique
has shown some results
Well done
Sibsang, you have awakened
Master Nojo, are you alright?
Thank you for saving my life
I know everything
Over the past year
you have endured much hardship
Because Master Nojo
did not return...
As long as you are safe,
I do not care if I die
There is little time left
In two months,
I must go to the Cheonyo Army
Since both of you are here today,
I have an important task for you
Soul Fusion Arts
have two parts
One is refining the soul
The other is extracting essence
Guhyanghwa
You will continue to lead others
and develop new techniques
You must remember
this technique is only for direct descendants
I will remember
Sibsang
Your cultivation path
is different from others
This is the next stage
of the Beast Horse tribe’s technique
You must further improve your training
Thank you, Master Nojo
Guhyanghwa, Sibsang
- Yes
From today
the Yeonhon tribe will no longer hide
but expand with full strength
When I return next time,
I hope our tribe exceeds one million people
I accept your command
I will never betray
Master Nojo’s expectations
(This journey to the Cheonyo Army
is truly perilous)
(The Soul Protection Seal
is not fully restored)
(but it should still help)
(The Yeonhon tribe)
(for now, must be protected
by another soul seal)
Guard the tribe well.
Go on.
Yes.
Master Nojo.
Hopo...
Maybe already...
He's still alive.
What?
If Hopo had died,
I would have sensed his soul energy.
I scanned Goyoseong with my divine sense before,
but found no trace.
Even with my cultivation, I couldn't find him.
He must be somewhere truly strange.
That's what it means.
(Magic Tower, Cheonyo Army Ancient Battlefield)
Master.
I've found out.
He has already broken through the Great Circle of Spirit Mutation.
With the commander of Goyoseong,
he's entering the commander duel.
(Sanma)
His cultivation speed is astonishing.
Watch him secretly.
Never let your identity be exposed.
What about the others?
No breakthrough for now.
But we've been training new warriors lately,
once they gain strength,
they will surely help your return.
Hopo greets Benefactor.
You're doing well lately.
If you refine all the soul essences in the ancient battlefield,
you'll become a capable warrior for Master.
It's all thanks to you, Benefactor.
You saved me,
taught me your divine arts,
and brought me here to train.
I will always remember this kindness.
(Two months later)
Wangrim.
Speak.
The true use of the Blood Soul Pill—
I'll never tell you.
Just kill me instead.
(Not yet reached the Gate of Enlightenment)
(If forced to use Soul Extraction)
(she could die if it goes wrong.)
If you don't speak,
I could erase you from this world with a forbidden spell.
That would be true living hell.
Wangrim.
Someday,
my father will extract your soul
and imprison it in the land of the dead.
You'll know what real hell feels like.
(To rescue Sibsang, with Mak Yehae)
(agreed to enter the commander duel)
(it's also a shortcut to becoming a commander.)
(But the Soul Mark is damaged now,)
(the Blood Soul Pill is useless,)
(and the Three-style divine power must be used carefully.)
(The only solution is the Slaughter Precept.)
(The slaughter energy refined by the Slaughter Precept)
(harms the body and mind,)
(and is hard to avoid.)
(I've killed many, but)
(I haven't refined much slaughter energy.)
(The slaughter energy I refined before)
(was mostly gained by chance.)
(What is the law behind it?)
Brother Wang.
It's time.
Let's go.
(Cheonyo Fortress)
Greetings, Commander Mak.
After thirty years,
I've finally returned.
Greetings, Clan Leader.
Everyone, rise.
This is my close friend, Deputy Wang.
From now on, when you see Deputy Wang,
treat him as you would treat me.
Greetings, Wang Deputy.
Brother Wang.
Let's go.
(Capital, Cheonyo Fortress)
Blood Soul Elixir.
It's pretty inside.
Let's check it out.
Blood Soul Elixir for sale!
So many demotions here.
Take care as you go.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Isn't that the famous Commander Mak?
Who's with him?
No idea.
But whenever there's a commander duel,
commanders always bring an aide to the match.
If Commander Mak chose him,
he must have special abilities.
He's definitely not ordinary.
Cheonyo Fortress is split into inner and outer rings.
Heaven, Earth, Mystic, and Yellow are the inner ring.
Rain, Universe, Hong, and Yellow are the outer ring.
Civil officials live in the inner ring.
Military officials live in the outer ring.
- I live in the Hong region.
- It fell.
- If you're fine with it,
- Mother.
Stay at our Mak residence.
I'll follow Brother Mak's wishes.
It's been a long time since I came.
The capital is still bustling.
To become deputy this time,
you must be wary of two people.
One is
Mukbi, who guards the Hwayo Army border.
He has many achievements,
and is the strongest among commanders.
The other is
Seokso.
He also guards the border,
and has been my rival for years.
He's skilled in the Six-land Sword Precept,
and his power is unpredictable.
Speak of the tiger and it appears.
(Seokso, Commander, Great Circle of Spirit Mutation)
Thank you.
Even after guarding the border for a hundred years,
your skills haven't improved at all.
Outsider,
what is your name?
Wangrim.
He's my fellow disciple.
Looks like you'll gain another fortune.
Your cultivation has grown fast.
(Before, Master helped me hide my Gate of Enlightenment training.)
(That's how I could enter here.)
(With that skill,)
(how did you end up seriously injured)
(and even your cultivation fell below the Gate of Enlightenment?)
(Be wary of the Great Sword Sect.)
(My injury too)
was their doing.
That person is called Mak Yehae.
He possesses the Three Divine Styles.
The first style is the Ten Collapse Fist.
The second is the White Wolf of Yohe.
The final style—
was passed down directly by the Yo Emperor.
Its power is overwhelming.
If I hadn't been injured,
I could have killed him.
How is your disciple?
He is very strong.
Even in the mid-stage of Spirit Mutation,
he could stand against the Gate of Enlightenment.
Now that his cultivation has advanced,
it's best not to provoke him carelessly.
Since I met you,
I've never seen you praise someone like that.
But even so,
he's no match for us.
(Makbu, Cheonyo Fortress)
Even after mass slaughter,
you're asking for a place where it won't be a problem?
What are you planning to do?
I've seen this technique before.
What is this, exactly?
It shakes the soul armor,
and stirs the life force within the body.
Does it shake my heart?
Even five strands of gray smoke
can disturb your mind and body.
If you master this technique completely,
you'll command a thousand strands of gray smoke.
Imagine how powerful that would be.
There is a place for slaughter—
there is one such place.
Hongok.
(Hongok, Cheonyo Fortress)
It's one of the four great prisons of the capital.
It holds felons and those sentenced to death.
But the security is strict,
so I can only buy you seven days.
Tonight at midnight,
go to the gate of Hongok.
Someone will guide you.
Clan Leader.
Everything is ready.
Wang Jang should be able to enter Hongok smoothly.
Clan Leader.
Hongok is a strange place.
If Wang Jang goes in there,
won't it be too dangerous?
If he gains fortune,
that is Wang's destiny.
The deputy contest is a grave matter,
so we have no choice but to take risks.
(Hongok)
(Heo Hoecheon, Hongok Warden, Great Circle of Spirit Mutation)
Are you the one Mak Yehae mentioned?
Yes, I am.
Follow me.
(Hongok)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪To see your face♪
♪Through all the years gone by♪
♪A compass spinning in reverse♪
♪Who decided this ending?♪
♪Heaven erases your story♪
♪Obsession led me on♪
♪Illusions I realized in the past♪
♪Confusion with no truth to find♪
♪Lost in the mire,
my original heart gone♪
♪How can I tell right from wrong?♪
♪Led by time,
we drift like water, all beings♪
♪I watch as souls sink away♪
♪I don't believe in fate set by heaven♪
♪My soul is refined by the world♪
♪To become immortal,
why not defy the heavens?♪
♪Just fight back, that's enough♪
♪In the jaws of death,
I reached the highest realm♪
♪And learned who I truly am♪
♪Through blood-soaked slaughter♪
♪I've never bent my will in life♪
♪I never turn away from loneliness♪
♪Even if pain shatters my soul♪
♪I am reborn in hell, again and again♪
♪And fight once more♪
♪A place higher than the peak♪
♪Loneliness I cannot shake♪
♪A moth that has seen the Vermilion Bird♪
♪Why would it fear a firefly?♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™