♪Night pierces the window, light shines through♪
♪Let us follow, the immortal path stretches on♪
♪Eight coils, nine bends, now desolate♪
♪All beings ask, a jug of murky wine breaks the heart♪
♪Rebirth from nirvana falls onto the page♪
♪With flesh and blood, I break the vast waves♪
♪Heaven is vast, I was born ordinary, so what?♪
♪Cold eyes, when will the Dao run wild?♪
♪Deep in the cliffs, wind and thunder stir♪
♪No need to ponder, life and death are but a dream♪
♪Sword drawn, ask the immortal force♪
♪In this world, all is uncertain♪
♪Fate and cosmos grant a tragic truth♪
♪Embrace the four seas, swallow the eight wilds♪
♪In a moment, all vicissitudes pass♪
♪I fly against the light♪
♪Continue the story, a new chapter for all worlds♪
♪Mortal or immortal, just a thought apart♪
♪An ant’s body transforms into light♪
♪Grains of sand cross the wild heavens♪
♪Youthful heart braves wind and rain♪
♪I defy fate, become immortal, and battle the heavens♪
- Renegade Immortal -
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, please watch with guardian’s consent)
(All content in this film is computer-generated)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Adapted from Er Gen’s novel "Renegade Immortal" on Qidian)
(Previously on)
I learned of an old Immortal Mansion
If we enter successfully
We split the immortal treasures half and half
(These twelve seals may not be obstacles)
(But a great opportunity)
Take three of my sword strikes
Only then are you qualified to enter the Immortal Mansion
Blood Clan
Hope for ascension
Thank you, Daoist Yao
For helping me withstand two sword strikes
Master
Please enter the mansion
(The Immortal Wine is mellow)
(It can intoxicate the soul)
(I didn’t expect)
(This one drink)
(Would last a whole year)
Episode 115
[Storming the Palace]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Six months ago)
We can’t wait any longer
The Patriarch still hasn’t returned
Sima Yan’s men are getting restless
More and more unruly
It’s only a matter of time before they target us
Thirteen
I’ll ask you one last time
Are you leaving or not?
The Patriarch’s orders
Are to wait for him in the camp
Stubborn fool
Just sit and wait for disaster
I won’t stay with you
Tian Yao Province military rule number one
Anyone who deserts the camp
Is executed
I’m not one of your demon soldiers
My return to the tribe today has nothing to do with you
Stop
Tian Yao Province military rule number eight
Anyone who defies their superior
Is executed
The Patriarch is the commander of this camp
Wait for his return
Today’s events will be investigated
Such a loyal dog
Too bad your useless master has been dismissed
He won’t come to save you
Jerk
You can kill me
But you cannot insult the Patriarch
Courting death
Sima Yan
Stop
(He Kun, new Black Armor Camp leader, 100,000 demon power, Nascent Soul Transformation mid-stage)
(How did I get drunk?)
(I don’t know how long I slept)
(Wang Lin’s avatar, Nascent Soul Transformation peak)
(My cultivation)
(Just one drop of Immortal Wine)
(Helped me reach Nascent Soul Transformation peak)
(The remaining nine drops)
(Must be stored carefully)
(Take control of the Immortal Mansion)
(Break through cultivation)
(And Yao Xixue’s storage pouch)
(This adventure)
(Was truly rewarding)
(With my current cultivation)
(I can easily break Yao Xixue’s spiritual mark)
(This is—
(All are immortal jades)
(These immortal jades)
(Will help me reach the top in the future)
(Half an hour later)
(These three storage pouches)
(Have over a thousand blood talismans)
(Several blood soul pills, real or fake unknown)
(And even a blood compass for entering and leaving)
(Such strong killing intent)
(No, that’s not right)
(On this restriction
(Should be her father’s spiritual mark)
(If an outsider opens it)
(They’ll be instantly killed by this spiritual mark)
(Blood Ancestor)
(Such a clever trick)
(This teleportation array was just inscribed)
(Li, Qian)
(Must have been Yao Xixue’s doing earlier)
(Blood Ancestor sent her to set up the teleportation array here)
(Reinforcements will surely come later)
(Li)
(Erase the array directly)
(It might be noticed)
(So instead)
(If someone from Blood Star really teleports here)
(These restrictions)
(Can give them a surprise)
Sir, you command the troops well
In your half year in charge
Everyone in Black Armor Camp is convinced
Looks like my camp
Has changed hands
Wang Lin
He
How did he come back?
Dares to barge into my camp
(He)
Kill on sight
First battalion ready
Second battalion ready
Third battalion ready
Fourth battalion ready
Retreat
(He)
(What realm has this person's cultivation reached?)
(Only when facing the Demon General himself)
do you feel such overwhelming pressure.
What exactly are your intentions?
This is my barracks.
What do you think I intend to do?
(He)
You've been missing for over a year.
The Demon General has long dismissed you
from your command.
(So I was in that Immortal Mansion)
for a whole year.
Where is my attendant?
(If I retreat now,)
I'll lose my position as commander.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Your shell
isn't tough enough.
Nascent Soul Transformation
Great Perfection
You tell me.
Six months after you left,
the two of them disappeared.
I don't know where they went either.
Stop!
This person has a unique physique.
He might be useful to the Demon General.
Sir.
That Hu Pao is nowhere to be seen today.
Fine.
Alright.
Where is Thirteen being held?
You mean that brute who trains his body?
The Demon General ordered
to find people with strong bodies.
I thought that brute fit the criteria.
So I sent him to the Demon General's manor.
Commander Wang,
if you want to kill or torture me,
I, He Kun, won't even blink.
But if you want someone,
go ask the Demon General yourself.
You saved Thirteen's life,
then handed him to the Demon General.
Your merits and faults cancel out.
I won't kill you.
The Demon General has been in seclusion
for half a year.
He refuses all visitors.
If you break into the palace,
you'll die for sure.
(As expected,)
(the teleport arrays to the Demon General's manor
are all shut down.)
(If I want to rescue Thirteen,)
(I must break through the six gates
of Ancient Demon City head-on.)
The Demon General is in seclusion.
This gate is under strict guard.
Take one more step,
and you'll be killed without mercy.
Demon General,
Wang Lin requests an audience.
(Ancient Demon City)
(I brought Thirteen and Hu Pao
to Ancient Demon City.)
(My unexpected slumber in the Immortal Mansion
dragged them into this.)
(I may have endangered their lives.)
(A cultivator)
(should avoid trouble)
(and seek heavenly fortune.)
(To fight and storm the palace for strangers,)
(defy the Demon General,)
(challenge the Tian Yao Army's rules,)
(is not worth it.)
(But in this world,)
(some things must be done,)
(and some must not.)
Fire!
(I, Wang Lin, walk between heaven and earth,)
(not seeking to follow rules,)
nor to pursue the heavenly path.
I only wish
to live without regret.
Someone is breaking into the palace!
Quick, inform all the commanders!
This is a demon crystal I found
in the other tribe.
I offer it specially to the Immortal.
Those who disrespect the Patriarch
are all enemies.
You may kill me,
but you must not insult the Patriarch.
(Bound by human ties,)
(bound by obsession,)
(maybe I'm not suited for cultivation.)
(But once obsession arises,)
(I must act on it.)
Patriarch.
(If I don't save Thirteen today,)
The Patriarch is the chief commander
of this camp.
- (What I, Wang Lin, seek in life)
- is to wait for his return.
Today's events will be investigated.
(will become empty wishes.)
Charge!
♪I defy fate, become immortal, and battle the heavens♪
How dare you!
The Demon General is in seclusion.
Wang Lin!
What are you trying to do?
I want to see the Demon General.
I demand justice for Thirteen.
You're insane!
You destroy my city gates,
break our city rules,
and make enemies of all Ancient Demon City,
just for a servant as insignificant as an ant.
You've got some nerve!
(Li Tao, First Commander of Ancient Demon City,
150,000 armored demon power, Nascent Soul late stage)
Since you refuse to listen,
then today
will be the day you die.
Prepare to die!
Yellow Springs!
(Here it comes.)
Nascent Soul Transformation, Great Perfection.
Finger technique divine power.
Not bad.
But that's not enough to spare your life.
It's still not enough.
Demon General,
long time no see.
Take this move, Hundred Waves of Demon Sea.
Only then are you qualified to speak before me.
(The power of this Hundred Waves of Demon Sea)
(is far greater than the previous Ten Collapse Fist.)
Can't handle it already?
Show me your true skills.
(Is this...)
(a golden talisman?)
(Why does it shake my soul so much?)
(As if it's about to burst out of my body.)
(The rune activates on its own now.)
(It must be a protective divine power.)
(This power came from the Immortal Mansion.)
(Might as well let it activate freely.)
(Maybe it can withstand the Hundred Waves of Demon Sea.)
(This move drains the Mark of Life too much.)
(Hard to use repeatedly.)
Good.
Wang Lin.
I underestimated you.
This rune seems to have many changes left.
Show me all you've got.
Let’s fight to our hearts’ content.
Thirteen.
Where is he?
We’ll talk after the fight.
Hundred Waves Thunder Rush!
Raging Tide Surge!
Fight!
(Be it Ten Collapse Fist or Hundred Waves of Demon Sea,)
(his techniques)
(all stem from his indomitable fighting spirit.)
(Divine powers alone can’t win.)
(It seems)
(there’s only one move left to gamble on.)
If you press me this hard,
if I use my killing blow,
you’ll surely die.
If you can kill me,
I, Mo, will admit defeat.
I’ve cultivated for many years.
Never seen anyone withstand Demon General’s move.
It’s a pity for such a gifted young man.
He barged in relying on his cultivation.
Unaware of Demon General’s true might,
which is far beyond mere cultivation.
This kid
brought this on himself.
This is...
the power of a Celestial Palm.
Borrowing the east wind to shatter his spirit.
This divine technique—
you haven’t mastered it yet, have you?
You—
Why not try again?
(Such a divine power,)
(if used with Nascent Soul Transformation cultivation,)
(will surely cause severe backlash.)
(That’s why he only cast a phantom palm.)
(In just one year,)
(his cultivation rivals mine.)
(His powers are even more unfathomable.)
General Mo.
Can you tell me now—
Thirteen—
where is he?
No need to be so formal.
Brother Wang.
From now on, we’ll call each other brothers.
This time, my seclusion
was to refine the bodies of the strong.
Your follower was last in line.
He hasn’t been refined yet.
I can return him to you.
But you stormed the palace today,
destroyed my city towers,
I can’t let it go so easily.
What will you do?
In three months,
at Tian Yao City, capital of Tian Yao Province,
among all the Demon Generals,
there will be a Demon General Tournament.
Brother Wang,
I want you to help me.
(Though he’s domineering,)
(he’s truly genuine.)
Alright.
From today on,
Wang Lin
is my First Deputy Commander.
If I win the Demon General Tournament,
I’ll ask the Demon Emperor for a general’s title for you.
One hundred thousand armored troops,
and a city of your own.
♪Through endless years, I see it all clearly♪
♪Just to glimpse your silhouette♪
♪Reversing fate’s compass, that ending♪
♪Who decided that outcome?♪
♪Heaven erases your traces♪
♪Obsession guides me on♪
♪On this path, I pierce illusions♪
♪Confused by truth and lies♪
♪Lost in the haze, without my true heart♪
♪How can I tell right from wrong?♪
♪See all beings drift with the tide♪
♪See all beings swept away♪
♪Refusing fate—who decides?♪
♪Let the world temper my soul♪
♪If I defy the heavens to ascend, so be it♪
♪Go and fight♪
♪In despair, the ultimate can be broken through♪
♪Today I finally know who I am♪
♪Bloodstained by slaughter♪
♪Pursuing a lifetime of resolve♪
♪Never looking back at the loneliness beside me♪
♪Even if hardship shatters my soul♪
♪How many times reborn in hell?♪
♪Fight again♪
♪Rising above the throne at the peak♪
♪Hard to escape this loneliness♪
♪A moth that’s seen the Vermilion Bird♪
♪Why fear a firefly?♪