- RENEGADE IMMORTAL -
(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, watch only with guardian consent)
(All content is created via CGI)
(Do not imitate in real life)
(Adapted from Er Gen’s novel “Renegade Immortal” on Qidian)
(Last time, on Previously)
Heavenly Demon Province
Every three hundred years, a Demon General tourney is held
Beyond the rewards for this contest
two Vice Marshals must also be chosen
I, Wang, will give you my full support
Hu Pao, he…
might already be…
He is still alive
Hu Pao greets his Benefactor
You asked me to find a place to slaughter many
without stirring up trouble
(Flood Prison)
You are the one Mo Lihai mentioned
That would be me
Come with me
(Flood Prison)
EPISODE 117
[IMPERIAL SWORD]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(The deathly qi here is so dense)
(The murderous aura, so fierce)
(over ten times stronger than outside)
A newcomer
All fair and tender
I love peeling this kind of soft skin
The taste of an outsider
Perfect, I can kill one more
And drink his blood
These are vile criminals soon to be beheaded
Fellow Daoist Wang, act as you please
(I wonder, if I kill all the condemned here)
(how many strands of Slaughter Aura I can forge)
(Five days later)
(Just now this place teemed with murderous qi)
(Could it be)
(under this Flood Prison)
(there lies some hidden mystery)
(Slaughter Immortal Art)
(Use Murderous Aura to temper vitality)
(Turn that vitality into a Mark of Life)
(Why, after killing everyone here)
(do I gain only useless deathly qi)
(What exactly am I lacking)
Because your Killing Heart is too weak
If you do not steep yourself in slaughter
and temper a true Killing Heart
you will never give rise to Murderous Aura
No effort will help you then
Refine the heart through killing
Use that heart to turn into a demon
That is my path of slaughter
If you wish to learn true slaughter
I can grant you a stroke of fortune
Whether you grasp it or not
depends on your own fate
My condition
As the Prison Warden
I cannot take a single step from Flood Prison
If you succeed
I want you to use the way of slaughter
to kill Demon General Shi Xiao
All right
Come with me
(Such dense Murderous Aura)
(It can stir the Slaughter Aura itself)
(Seems what he said was true)
This is where the Imperial Sword is fed
(Slaughter Blood Pool, Flood Prison)
Personally opened by the Emperor
Its Murderous Aura is savage
Enough to invade the mind
If your heart is not firm
you will likely end up like them
a hollow body, a walking corpse
None who enter this place leave
Have you truly decided
(The place that feeds the Imperial Sword)
(What a slaughter‑filled place)
(This blood mist is refined Murderous Aura)
(A perfect source to train Slaughter Immortal Art)
(Why can I not fuse with it)
(Or is it that)
(the blood energy is lacking)
(No, that’s wrong)
(Three days later)
(Still not right)
(The method to turn blood energy to Slaughter Aura)
(What exactly is it)
Who goes there
(With such a cultivation)
(how is he trapped here)
(What a vicious sword force)
(Could this silver dragon be the Imperial Sword)
Let me
out of here
(So that’s it)
(If I want to leave here)
(I must first pass the Imperial Sword)
(No wonder he said none leave this place)
(The Imperial Sword is truly strong)
(I must not face it head‑on)
(That blood mist is what feeds the sword)
(But it’s born from mutual slaughter here)
(Once people are gone, it dries up)
(Why would the Imperial Sword drain its own pond)
(Could it be)
(in the blood pool they cannot die)
(and so they slaughter each other endlessly)
(thus feeding it endless blood mist)
(Who knows how many years they’ve been trapped)
(If I want to get out)
(I must perfect the Slaughter Immortal Art)
(only then will I have a chance)
(Hai)
(Zi)
(Chen)
Prepare to die
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(Si)
(Wu)
(Wei)
(Zi)
(Chou)
(Wu)
You cannot get out
What on earth am I missing
(Wu)
Turn death into life
From life, return to death
This is the cycle that feeds the Imperial Sword
Slaughter Immortal Art
It mimics some unknown‑grade Immortal Art
It matches your Domain of Life and Death
so it suits you well
(Zi)
(No wonder)
(Use killing intent to reap lives)
(Refine vitality into a Mark of Life)
(Use life to birth death)
(Use death to turn to life)
(The Slaughter Immortal Art)
At last, I am free
You
can even make the blood pool your own
(So the key to Slaughter Immortal Art)
(is also the path of life‑death rebirth)
It’s useless
The Imperial Sword is coming
You still cannot escape
Slaughter Aura
Emerge
It is over
This might of the Imperial Sword
even a Demon General
could never withstand it
Turn death into life
Mark of Life
He actually endured the Imperial Sword’s might
Save me
Farewell
(Sword Pavilion, Heavenly Demon City)
(Imperial Sword)
How badly has it been wronged
to be enraged to this extent
What is this
When the Imperial Sword rages,
corpses cover a million
and blood flows for a thousand li.
This sword
in the eyes of you two,
(Hai Zhu, Daluo Sword Sect disciple,
Nascent Transformation Late Stage)
(Weiyang, Daluo Sword Sect disciple,
How strong is it?
Not weaker than Master’s sword.
(Mo Fei, Demon General,
Nascent Transformation Great Perfection)
(That direction…)
(Flood Prison…)
(Imperial Sword…)
(Could the Imperial Sword be after Wang Lin?)
(With Wang Lin’s cultivation,)
(how could he draw the Sword itself?)
(I must be overthinking it.)
If you want to live, don’t go that way.
Stay close to me.
(This mess is way too big now.)
(How did this guy even lure the Sword?)
(If he gets caught,)
(I’ll surely be dragged down too.)
Move, quickly.
Do not forget our agreement.
Is there a place to seclude myself?
Come with me.
Many thanks.
(It really is him.)
(Five days later)
Three thousand seven hundred ninety‑two
strands of Slaughter Aura
have been formed.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪ Through endless years I see through all ♪
♪ Only to glimpse your silhouette ♪
♪ In the reversed compass, that ending ♪
♪ Who decreed that final fate? ♪
♪ Heaven wiped away all your traces ♪
♪ Obsession alone now guides me ♪
♪ I pierce illusions along this road ♪
♪ Truth and lies both twist and blur ♪
♪ In this murk, without my first heart ♪
♪ how could I judge right from wrong? ♪
♪ All beings drift on with the currents ♪
♪ All beings sink and are drowned ♪
♪ I refuse Heaven’s so‑called decree ♪
♪ Let the world temper my soul ♪
♪ To defy Heaven and ascend—so what? ♪
♪ I will fight on ♪
♪ At the brink, I grasp the utmost ♪
♪ Today I know I’m truly me ♪
♪ Blood‑stained with endless slaughter ♪
♪ Bearing one life of obsession ♪
♪ Never look back at the desolation ♪
♪ Though tribulation shatters my soul ♪
♪ How many rebirths from this hell? ♪
♪ I’ll fight again ♪
♪ High above, on the peak’s lone throne ♪
♪ I still can’t cast off this solitude ♪
♪ A moth that’s seen the Vermilion Bird ♪
♪ How could it fear fireflies? ♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™