Even if I die today...
...turn to ash and vanish...
...my Dao shattered forever...
...I will still—
—hold fast to my path.
I am the soul of an ancient demon.
I need you
to retrieve my soul fragments
from the other eight sacred relics.
Help me become whole once more.
Destroy the Dao.
This crystal—
...born of obsession...
...will aid you
on your final journey.
Seven hundred years
of seeking the Dao...
...and I’ve finally reached Ascension.
Little one...
This—
You think enduring heavenly wrath
was the end?
Now...
...the true trial begins.
Possession starts now.
Not a chance!
Your spirit...
...belongs to me.
For countless years...
...every cultivator
who reached Ascension here...
...has been devoured by me.
This technique is truly sinister.
If I hadn’t used killing intent
to anchor my mind...
...my soul would’ve been ripped out
by now.
I must leave—now.
This arm...
...somehow breached the immortal manor’s
barriers to reach here.
It can’t be ignored.
I’ve only just Ascended...
...my cultivation unstable.
I should seek the ancient demon first...
...and have him help me find
a secluded place to cultivate.
He broke free...
An inverse cultivator...
...truly troublesome.
This body is gravely wounded.
I need primal energy
to restore my cultivation.
But that energy...
...only appears when an outsider
achieves Ascension here.
A newly Ascended cultivator—
rare as a phoenix feather!
How could I possibly let him go?
My teleportation art—
it’s been disrupted!
Who the hell is this?
This is...
Crimson Madness Fruit.
Legend says it briefly boosts power...
...but awakens murderous intent.
At best—lose control...
...at worst—go mad with power.
At worst—fall to demonic madness.
I’ve seen this fruit
on the Vermilion Bird Star.
Didn’t expect it here
in the Demon Spirit Realm.
Persistent pest!
The Ominous Star has finally summoned me!
If I succeed this time...
...he’ll surely forgive
my past betrayal.
Who dares harm my master?!
Master!
Save me!
Demonic Transformation!
This cursed thing—
—must be destroyed.
Something’s wrong.
That armor—
it’s the true source of demonic energy.
You...
...are mine.
Master, watch out!
Cycle of Life and Death!
That sound—
—truly repulsive.
In this daze...
...she’s the blade...
...and I’m the meat.
You’re mine.
I must...
...stay清醒.
If ordinary methods won’t work...
...then—
—I’ll crush it
with killing intent!
You...
Cycle of Rebirth...
...Annihilate!
Dare to shatter my art
with killing intent?
Madman!
This boy’s gone demonic.
The cost to capture him...
...might exceed the primal energy
he holds.
Taking him by force...
...just isn’t worth it.
Fine.
My accumulation
over millions of years...
...must not be risked.
Trying to run?
Found you.
M-Master!
Shouldn’t we...
tend to your wounds first?
What?
N-nothing!
What I meant was—
Now’s the perfect time to strike—
catch him off guard!
Oh no...
That Ominous Star from the Demon Sea
has returned!
No—
—he’s far more terrifying now.
Whoever dares disrupt my Ascension...
...must die.
A mere Ascendant—
—dares challenge me?
Ten Thousand Demons—
Devour His Heart!
Is this all you’ve got?
Back then, one drop of immortal wine
knocked you out for a year.
Now you gulp down four drops?
You’re insane!
Come on!
Good!
Even better!
His body is dead...
...his spirit shattered...
Yet fueled by Crimson Madness Fruit
and immortal energy...
...he’s gone utterly mad.
At this pace...
...as expected—
—he’s reached the Fire Demon Plains.
Such reckless arrogance...
The Fire Demon Realm
will surely take notice.
He’s walking straight to his death.
An Ascendant—
—and so gravely wounded...
Heaven-sent opportunity!
If I devour his Ascendant spirit...
...my sword spirit’s power
will surge beyond measure!
All troops—
—stand by. Rest in place.
Such fresh...
...killing intent.
You’re badly injured,
sir—
why keep fighting?
Why keep fighting?
Thanks for the “medicine.”
Commander...
...is dead.
Kill him!
Avenge the commander!
Annihilation!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Your Majesty—
The Rat Division...
...has been annihilated.
He slaughtered 30,000 of our demon troops!
I—
—will have his heart and bones!
Issue the order:
Summon 100,000 demon soldiers!
I’ll paint my realm
in that madman’s blood!
I’ll stain my lands
with his crimson!
Such potent killing intent...
You killed our commander...
...slaughtered our troops...
Today, I—
—by imperial decree—
—will execute you on the spot!
Hellfire Abyss Formation!
Silence!
A mere early-stage Ascendant—
—you dare swagger in my Fire Demon Realm?
This Hellfire Abyss Array
draws upon 100,000 demon soldiers...
...and uses an Ascendant
as its core eye.
It can slaughter even peak Ascendants—
let alone you!
Forget late-stage Ascendants—
—this array kills them instantly!
All troops!
By the Emperor’s command—
—follow me!
...and tear him apart—
—leave not a soul!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
This killing intent...
...is intoxicating.
Impossible!
He’s trying to break the array
with brute force!
One Finger—Yellow Springs!
This can’t be!
He just reached Ascension—
—how can he already have his own Dao?!
Dao manifesting as Yellow Springs!
Today, empowered by Crimson Madness Fruit,
immortal wine...
...and the army’s bloodthirsty aura...
—he’s brushed the threshold
of the second step of the Heavenly Dao!
His will has solidified
into tangible reality!
Fascinating...
From this day forth—
—I, Wang Lin, will cultivate
neither Heaven nor Earth...
...neither immortals nor gods...
—I shall cultivate only my Dao.
Those who seek my death—
—enter my Yellow Springs.
Bathe in my Cycle of Rebirth.
Bound by neither Heaven nor Earth.
With only early-stage Ascendant power...
...he’s carved a river of Yellow Springs.
Wang Lin...
You truly astonish me.
Yuan.
Master, your command?
It’s time to greet our guest.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™