[Previously]
Immortal Force is sufficient.
Awaiting enlightenment of Artistic Conception.
to step into the middle stage of Inquiry Tripod.
Since you insist on dragging me
into this affair,
you must show sufficient sincerity.
They're here.
The Huan family has truly arrived.
Extinction.
I am a personal guard of Lady Huan Mei.
If you harm me,
Lady Huan Mei will never spare you.
Friend Xu,
Now that Huan Dong is dead,
the Huan family will surely investigate.
Within three months,
I will return.
Issue the command:
Effective immediately,
seal off all starry sky channels
of Ran Yun Star.
Not a single ant
is to be allowed to escape this seat.
Death Qi...
The Goldflame Ore is a
yang-attributed treasure.
Upon this Cloud Glow Star,
why is the Death Qi so dense?
Cloud Glow Star is not a remote,
borderline location.
How is it that not a single trace
of human habitation exists?
That is...
Moon Gazer.
How can a Moon Gazer exist in this place?
In Tu Si's memories,
the Moon Gazer is a parasitic entity
unique to the Ancient God race,
surviving by sucking
the blood of Ancient Gods.
Moon Gazers cause no damage
to the massive Ancient God bodies;
they can even be driven
like magic treasures.
But once the Ancient God dies,
the Moon Gazers mostly
vanish into smoke.
Survival is nearly impossible.
Back then, Tu Si had passed away
for too long,
so that within the Land of the Ancient God,
no traces of Moon Gazers remained.
Could it be that within
this Cloud Glow Star...
lies the remains of an
Ancient God corpse?
If that is truly the case,
how could the great powers
of the Rotating Sky Starfield
possibly turn a blind eye?
This place is strange.
I must find that Goldflame vein quickly.
It really is a Goldflame vein.
This...
This entire vein belongs to us?
Master,
we've struck it rich!
What are you waiting for?
At your command,
Little Xu Zi will start mining.
Wait.
This Goldflame vein...
is buried far too shallowly.
Any Inquiry Tripod cultivator
scanning casually could detect it.
Such a precious treasure—
how could it remain unclaimed
for millions of years?
Furthermore,
if it were naturally formed ore,
it should not be so pure
and orderly.
This substance...
resembles a section of bone.
It is not a tree.
It is a tentacle.
This Cloud Glow Star...
is a slumbering Moon Gazer
formed from an entire
Goldflame vein as its bone.
If we had tried to excavate
the Goldflame vein just now,
we would have surely startled
this Moon Gazer awake.
Facing such a colossal beast,
I would have no path to survival.
Throughout history,
all who mined the Goldflame vein
likely perished right here.
But the Goldflame vein is crucial
to the Rebellious Sky Pearl.
I am determined to obtain it.
As for how to extract it,
I must find another method.
Huan Mei.
After the blood exchange,
you
will truly become one of the Huan family.
In your actions and conduct,
do not fail the blood of the Huan family.
Square illusion as soul,
Myriad blood as guide.
Huan Wuqing of the Huan family's
twenty-sixth generation,
hereby beseeches
the ancestral spirit bloodline.
In the primordial past,
my Huan family were immortals
of the Thunder Immortal Realm.
Though the Immortal Realm is destroyed,
the bloodline remains.
This blood exchange ritual...
From tens of thousands of disciples' blood,
refine the purest bloodline.
Condensing it into a Blood Talisman
imprinted upon one person.
Today, this old ancestor
even lowered my own realm,
personally infusing vast amounts
of essence blood into this seal,
to cleanse her veins.
For her sake,
why must we pay such a price?
Myriad Illusions,
Formless.
The Old Ancestor's Myriad Illusion
Formless Dao
is the pinnacle of the Huan family,
yet it has no successor.
Could it be that the Old Ancestor's
grand commotion to bestow power
is to cultivate a successor
who possesses this Dao?
Impossible.
How could that be?
Her artistic conception...
is sublimating.
Sublimating!
The divine abilities of artistic conception
left to our clan by the ancient immortals—
the Heavenly Demon and Formless Paths.
Of these, the stronger Heavenly Demon Path
has long been lost.
Yet the artistic conception on this woman...
Could it be...
Artistic conception sublimation?
Unheard of!
So the Old Ancestor's scheme
was aimed at this.
Mei'er.
I thank the Old Ancestor
for the grace of recreation.
You truly did not disappoint
this old man's expectations.
Venerated Ancestors,
do you see this?
The Myriad Illusion Heavenly Demon Dao,
lost to the Huan family for eons,
has reappeared in the light of day!
Huan Mei.
This is your first battle
as a member of the Huan family.
Go to Ran Yun Star.
Slaughter your way to fame!
Don't waste your strength.
With just the three of us,
this Lockstar Grand Formation
cannot be broken.
Then what do we do?
If this formation isn't broken,
are we just to wait for death?
This move...
I'm afraid it is to establish Huan Mei's might.
Friend Xu Mu said
that in three months,
he will return.
Before the Huan family arrives,
that man will flee at the first sign of wind.
Will he really come back?
He's here.
The ancestors of the three Ran Yun clans...
Is it you?
She is...
Huan Mei.
My Ran Yun Star—
is it to be utterly destroyed
by a delicate woman?
Brother Sun, Brother Zhao,
now that disaster looms large,
let us simply fight with all we have.
Even in death,
we will have no regrets in this life.
Brother Ran is heroic.
Since you burn your Primordial Spirit,
I, Zhao,
will accompany you.
Enough.
I, Sun,
cannot lag behind.
I appreciate your resolve.
That you are willing to fight to the death
saves me a considerable amount of effort.
Dao Thought!
You...
Want to burn your Primordial Spirit?
Then burn it completely!
Brother Zhao!
Wake up!
Brother Sun!
Hurry, assist me!
Just what...
kind of Dao Thought is this?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
You could have clouded my mind,
yet you chose to keep me sober,
only to be brutally slaughtered
by allies.
What vicious methods.
This battle—
did I ever lift a finger?
You three fought each other.
What connection does it have
with me?
The Myriad Illusion
Heavenly Demon Dao.
I have never needed anyone to assist in battle.
Wherever I go,
countless cultivators fight for me.
And die for me.
With the abilities of you three,
it would be impossible to kill Huan Dong
without a sound.
At that time,
who else was present?
You three offered your main bodies
as sacrifices,
using the self-combustion of your
Primordial Spirits as a smokescreen.
Did you really think I couldn't see through it?
Did you leave behind avatars to preserve
your lives?
Please, spare my life!
That man was named Xu Mu.
At that time,
the one who killed your clan's
guard, Huan Dong, was him.
However, he left this place days ago.
If you wish to find his traces,
I...
can help you.
No rush.
Once stained with the blood of the Huan family,
no one escapes.
Days ago, when I left,
this Restriction did not exist on Ran Yun Star.
This formation is quite complex.
Breaking it will take some time.
But to barge into the formation—
that is not difficult.
It's her.
Peak of Inquiry Tripod.
To fight her...
I have no certainty of victory.
But I used the Immortal Guard's method
to alter my appearance.
She shouldn't be able to recognize me.
This true life-saving avatar—
I have never revealed its location
to anyone.
This woman...
how on earth did she find me?
Self-combusting your Primordial Spirit,
yet falling into your own desires.
Fighting to the death,
yet leaving behind a life-saving avatar.
Your display of noble righteousness—
how much of it is real?
This is truly fascinating.
Friend Xu!
Save me!
Friend Sun!
You had an avatar,
yet you didn't inform me?
This...
I imagine you were scheming to have me
fight the Huan family to the death.
Regardless of success,
you could use these avatars to survive.
Did I get that right?
Though you lacked benevolence,
since I accepted your Immortal Jade,
I shall protect you this once.
I advise you not to meddle further.
Now,
leave Ran Yun Star.
Unexpected.
Your cultivation has actually reached
the Inquiry Tripod realm.
You really thought that by masking
your appearance,
and altering your aura,
I wouldn't recognize you?
Wang Lin.
But early Inquiry Tripod...
you are destined to perish here.
Back on Vermilion Bird Star,
when you destroyed my Artistic Conception,
I used the Myriad Illusions
Heartless Art
to glimpse your Obsessive Desire.
Today,
I shall only destroy your Dao Heart,
and shatter your Obsessive Desire,
to vent my hatred!
Wang Lin.
I shall send you
to reunite with that Li Muwan.
Seeking death!
What kind of sorcery is this?
Observing with Divine Sense,
this person seems just like Hongdie.
Just an illusion.
Putting on a mystical show.
Uncle...
You...
You want to kill Little Rujiu?
Illusion.
This is also an illusion.
Disciple,
remember to pass down the
Soul Banner Art.
Spread the Soul Refining Sect
and carry it to greatness.
Wang Lin.
Brother...
Illusion.
Son.
Senior Brother.
Return.
Myriad Illusion Heavenly Demon Dao.
Borrowing the opponent's memories,
igniting the fire of the Primordial Spirit,
burning the body and mind.
Waiting for the mind to lapse,
so one becomes a fish on the chopping block.
Wang Lin.
The fire of your Primordial Spirit
is already lit.
The outcome
is already decided.
Thunder...
In his Primordial Spirit,
how can there be Thunder power?
How is this possible?
When causality is settled,
and the heart holds no regrets,
one may return to silence.
But if causality is unfinished,
even facing the Will of Heaven,
one must defy it.
During the Inquiry Tripod stage,
I comprehended this Dao.
My Obsessive Desire—
how could it be restrained
by your mere Artistic Conception?
Though your cultivation
was forcibly elevated,
your Artistic Conception
is worlds apart.
Your Artistic Conception
cannot break Wang's Dao Heart.
Your Illusion Arts
cannot burn
Wang's Primordial Spirit.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™