[Previously]
They want to pin the sins of that day
along with the risk of exterminating the clan
all on you.
Huan Dong.
Though this matter is small,
it is my first act for the Huan family.
It must be swift and decisive.
An eighth-grade quasi-divine pill...
should be enough to propel me straight into mid-Nascent Soul.
This scheme is treacherous,
yet I have no choice but to enter it.
That person's cultivation...
is formidable.
If he joins the fray,
he will surely help Ran Yunxing
survive this calamity.
The Sun family has given the order:
the auction of this item
must not be interfered with.
If no fellow Daoist bids again,
this eighth-grade spiritual pill will be withdrawn.
I bid...
one immortal jade.
One immortal jade.
Has he lost his mind?
Who is this guy?
He's openly humiliating Baohe Tower!
He actually made a bid.
But that price...
Accept it.
Baohe Tower's reputation will be ruined.
It would tell everyone there's fraud involved.
Don't accept it.
The ancestor strictly ordered that this item must be sold.
Brother Xu...
Brilliant.
I’m impressed.
Since...
only this fellow Daoist has bid,
sold!
The eighth-grade spiritual pill
for one immortal jade
now belongs
to this fellow Daoist.
It’s sold.
Why did Baohe Tower accept it?
That was an eighth-grade quasi-divine pill!
Baohe Tower is treating this like a joke.
Fellow Daoist Sun, if there’s nothing else,
I shall take my leave.
Wang.
What is it?
Inside here
are the fifty thousand immortal jades I’ve saved over the years.
There are also some of my lifelong insights
on pill refinement and artifact crafting.
I originally thought that one day
I might find an opportunity
to restore a portion of my cultivation.
But now… they’re of no use to me.
I’ll give them to you.
Life and death.
Strength and weakness.
Kindness and resentment.
Cause and effect.
I greet my master.
Karma...
After comprehending the intent of the cycle of life and death,
is this what follows?
This is the true origin of life and death.
The cause of yesterday
becomes the effect of today.
Sun Tai came here because of me
and found peace because of me.
This...
is karma.
Nearly three hundred thousand immortal jades.
That should be just enough to break through in cultivation.
Array...
activate!
Shatter!
Such terrifying power...
Is this a warning to us?
My immortal energy is sufficient.
All that remains is to comprehend the intent.
Then it will come naturally.
I will step into mid-Nascent Soul.
Since you insist on dragging me into this affair,
you’d better show enough sincerity.
My actions just now
must have made those three people
realize what’s at stake.
A true breakthrough...
One test will tell.
Immortal guard,
go.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
If he wanted to kill me,
that palm strike earlier
would have already destroyed my body and soul.
Just what is this person’s cultivation level?
The Huan family has truly arrived.
I am Huan Dong,
second-grade clan guard of the Huan family
from the Thousand Illusions Main Star.
Huan Dong.
Nascent Soul cultivators of Ran Cloud Star,
come forth and pay your respects at once.
Scram.
Scram!
Courting death!
Who are you?
How dare you obstruct the Huan family?
My name...
You are not worthy of knowing it.
Silent Extinction.
Condense!
What kind of lightning is this?
This person’s cultivation is definitely
not mid-stage Nascent Soul!
Run!
I must escape.
Report back to the young miss!
With your meager strength,
you dare oppose my Huan family?
If you don’t release me at once,
you will all die without question.
The Huan family’s retaliation is already inevitable.
We cannot possibly resist them.
Fortunately, Xu Mu is here today.
Fellow Daoist Huan,
May I ask what business brings you
to our Ran Cloud Star?
Business?
Ran family Patriarch,
you should know exactly why.
Four years ago,
my Huan family’s people
were indeed killed by you.
Ran Xuefeng,
Sun Xi,
Zhao Chuanwen.
Zhao Chuanwen!
The bloodlines of your three families
have reached their end.
Fellow Daoist Xu,
This man...
Why don’t you hand him over to us?
Fellow Daoist Xu,
Our Huan family’s ancestor has already returned.
How dare you act this way?
Could it be that with your mere Nascent Soul cultivation,
you actually believe you can oppose our ancestor?
Your Huan family ancestor...
What is his cultivation?
The ancestor has stepped into the second major realm of cultivation.
Thousands of years ago,
he had already reached the Yin Void Yang Solid stage.
This person is yours.
It has nothing to do with me.
I still have important matters to attend to.
I’ll take my leave first.
I am a personal guard of Young Miss Huan Mei.
My young miss
is the closed-door disciple that the ancestor took in
when he traveled to the Alliance.
If you dare touch me,
Young Miss Huan Mei will never let you go.
Huan Mei...
What was this person’s original name?
Spare me,
and I’ll tell you.
Soul Search!
Liu Mei.
This girl has truly obtained a great fortune.
Coming all the way to the Luotian Star Domain...
Fellow Daoist Xu,
Since Huan Dong is dead,
the Huan family will definitely investigate.
Within three months,
I will return.
Clan guard Huan Dong’s soul lamp has been extinguished.
Confirmed fallen.
Location of death:
Ran Cloud Star.
Requesting the ancestor to issue orders.
Dispatch troops to Ran Cloud Star.
Raze its stars to the ground.
Destroy its Dao lineage.
Ran Cloud Star
is but a tiny speck of land.
Destroying it
would be as easy as flipping my hand.
Huan Dong
belongs to Huan Mei.
This grudge
shall be avenged by her personally.
Understood.
The ancestor is wise.
However, Young Miss Huan Mei’s
Blood Exchange Grand Technique has not yet...
Then begin it ahead of schedule.
Once the Blood Exchange Grand Technique is complete,
Huan Mei
will personally handle this matter.
We shall respectfully obey the ancestor’s decree.
Pass down my orders.
Effective immediately,
seal off all star passageways
leading to and from Ran Cloud Star.
Deploy the Star-Locking Grand Array.
No one is allowed in.
No one is allowed out.
Not even a single ant
is permitted to escape from me.
[Cloud-Hidden Star]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™