[Previously]
I heard you took quite a tumble in your early years.
Your cultivation has been stagnant since.
Your fists may shatter walls,
but they won't break the laws of our Great Sui.
Young master, your martial realm is low,
yet your fist intent is solid.
Quite remarkable.
I wonder if this return to your hometown
will ignite within you
a heart set on slaughtering every pest?
If the Ninth Realm cannot subdue you,
then smash right through it.
If the Human and Demon races ever go to war,
I ask that Lord Bai
review this first
before deciding.
Milady.
Last year's New Year phrase was 'Jia',
and this year it is 'Tao'.
So, speak an idiom
containing the word
'Li', and you shall be rewarded.
Peaches and plums do not speak,
yet a path is formed beneath them.
Lush and blooming peaches,
peach cheeks and apricot face,
common peaches and vulgar plums,
to return a peach for a plum.
To substitute one thing for another,
Absurd!
Utterly absurd!
As expected...
the moon shines brightest at home.
Our mountains...
are prettier than anywhere else.
I'm back.
Old Master takes the fool,
back to the ancestral home!
Was I not magnificent?
Just standing here,
those beasts didn't dare move!
Wei Bo.
Milord.
Is someone here to cause trouble?
Of course not.
Wei Bo,
what are you doing here?
Fate brought us together.
I moved to Mount Piyun
to be your neighbor.
From now on,
please look after me.
What about the bamboo house
you asked me to build?
How is it coming along?
It was finished ages ago.
No cutting corners, I assure you.
The view is expansive,
and the scenery is beautiful.
Sneaking around like a thief...
doesn't look like a good omen.
In the future, our Luopo Mountain
will be quite lively.
Luopo Mountain isn't yours.
Right, right.
You, Chen Ping'an, are the owner.
I'm just a guest.
Enough.
Nowadays, every mountain sect in town
is busy establishing their turf.
I had picked a treasure spot for my house,
but alas,
Luopo Mountain's Earth God shrine
took it first.
Making excuses one after another...
I'd like to see what kind of bird
this flashy display actually produces.
This is my bamboo house.
From now on, Luopo Mountain
is half your home.
Stay as you please.
Changing your tune already?
Who was it that said earlier
Luopo Mountain wasn't ours?
For the esteemed Earth God to argue
with me...
is quite beneath you, isn't it?
Could this be bamboo from the
Bamboo Sea Cave Heaven?
Milord, you truly hide your talents.
Milord, Milord!
The view here is spectacular!
Can we live here?
I knew Chen Ping'an was no ordinary man.
Milord,
next, should we visit
some specific palace or manor?
Why are we heading straight for a grave?
Much has happened on this journey.
I'll tell you slowly later.
Though you probably won't believe it...
I actually met Gu Can's father.
Perhaps...
Milord,
I once read in a book
that after people die,
their souls might return to the
ancestral temple
to endure via sacrifices.
I need to stop by the blacksmith first.
Miss Ruan is a very good friend of mine.
When you see her later,
address her as Sister Ruan.
Later,
I'll give you each an extra Snake
Gallstone.
Alright!
I'm old enough to be her ancestor,
why should I call her sister?
She is Saint Ruan Qiong's daughter.
If you wish to die,
I won't stop you.
Ruan Qiong?
You mean the immortal from
Fengxue Temple?
I will treat Sister Ruan with utmost
respect.
I wouldn't dare embarrass Milord.
Milord is surrounded by important
figures.
Where is my chance to earn merit
and claim a reward?
Blind fool!
How dare you provoke my lord!
You wretched woman!
Just because you're a water spirit,
you think you can fight me?
But once this old master touches water,
I become invincible in body training!
Got you!
Come back.
This woman has a slender waist
and round hips...
Take her as a maid.
Let go.
I am the newly appointed River God
of Dragon Whisker River.
I was merely patrolling
as per my duties.
I meant no offense.
I beg the Immortal
to show mercy.
We were the ones out of line.
My name is Chen Ping'an.
I'm a local who just returned
from a long journey. I didn't know
when the town built this shrine.
May I ask, Lady River God,
where are you originally from?
We mountain and river deities
have severed ties with the mortal
world.
If Young Master Chen needs anything
in the future, just let me know
by the river. I won't refuse.
Don't know what's good for you, huh?
Bullying my kind-hearted lord?
Young Master Chen.
Ptooey!
A little bastard whose parents died
early.
Why didn't you just die on your
travels?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Miss Ruan.
You're back.
I took the liberty of bringing back
some chicks from your neighbor's place.
But wild cats got to them...
snatched away two.
It's fine.
My skills have improved greatly.
I'll make soup for Miss Ruan
later.
No killing, no killing!
They're very well-behaved.
I've even given them names.
My father took in three new disciples.
That long-browed youth
is a descendant of the Xie family
in town.
Xie Ling.
Look at your tiny chicken heart.
No ambition at all.
And you're any better?
This is called hiding our strength
You don't know squat.
Greetings, Uncle.
I am a maid serving Lord Chen Ping'an.
What are you chatting about?
So lively and cheerful.
What are you looking at?
I'm warning you,
Miss Xiuxiu is my lord's sweetheart.
You're just a blacksmith.
If you dare have improper thoughts,
I'll beat you half to death with one
punch.
I'm talking to you!
Old man, how old are you?
Have some shame!
Come, come,
don't just stand there like a log.
Let's exchange blows.
Master Ruan.
Saintly Master, please accept
this lowly one's deepest kowtow.
I'm accompanying Chen Ping'an to town.
We're about to forge iron.
Come help out.
Father,
the hour isn't right...
I make the decisions here.
Don't ask questions.
I'll fetch you some wine.
Escaping death,
you're destined for fortune.
Milord,
did you forget to prepare a gift
for Miss Ruan?
Or do you think it's too cheap?
Unlike you, I'm thorough.
I prepared it long ago.
This is a Moonlight Vase.
It gathers the essence of the sun
and moon.
Give it to Miss Ruan,
it will surely yield twice the result
with half the effort.
Then, under the dreamlike moonlight...
Dream my foot.
Milord, wait—
Let's go.
Miss Ruan,
I couldn't think of what to give you.
There are many delicious things outside,
but they don't last.
So I had no choice but to make this.
Don't dislike it.
It's ruined.
I like it very much.
It hasn't changed.
That's good.
It would be even better if you carved
"Chen Ping'an gifts to Ruan Xiu"
on it.
Cui Ci,
Cui Minghuang sent you to be my page,
not to laze around.
You're here.
Young Master.
If it were Second Young Master,
he would have chatted for a while
and complimented my new hairpin,
said it was pretty.
Milord,
sometimes when girls say they like
something,
they aren't being sincere.
It's not that the bamboo slip you gave
is inferior...
I just...
I just feel
a vase suits a beauty better.
If Miss Ruan takes those things back,
her Master might misunderstand.
He might think I have ulterior motives.
What do you mean
"might think"?
What do you mean "might think"?
Your intentions toward Ruan Xiu
are obviously impure!
What nonsense are you spouting?
Don't kill me to silence me!
I promise to keep my mouth shut.
I'll be tighter-lipped than Li Baoping.
Tighter than a sealed vase.
What happened to my Baoping?
Is she hurt?
My lord is Li Baoping's Junior Uncle.
So I admire her especially.
And who are you?
You must be Chen Ping'an.
I am Li Xisheng,
Baoping's eldest brother.
Baoping wrote letters constantly
about how kind her Junior Uncle was.
As her brother,
I am deeply grateful.
Brother Li,
these are "Mountain Crossing Carp"
for Baoping.
I never imagined I would witness with
my own eyes
the miraculous sights described
in ancient texts.
Rest assured,
I will take great care of them.
When Baoping returns home,
she will be overjoyed.
I hear you like reading.
I picked out a few books from my
collection for you.
No rush to return them.
Take your time reading.
Joking is fine,
but remember,
loose lips sink ships.
Every word in this world
carries power.
In fact,
the Great Dao lies within them.
Stop putting on airs!
Always acting like a teacher.
Why not go be a saint at the
Confucian Academy?
So I must first pass the imperial exams,
and climb step by step.
As for whether I can become a Confucian
Saint in the future...
That is too distant.
I dare not hope for it.
Teacher,
then why is it that when we read,
we suddenly fail to recognize certain
words?
Because those words
were secretly borrowed by a Saint.
Teacher, if you don't know the answer,
do not offer random explanations.
To know what you know
and to know what you do not know,
that is wisdom.
Brother Li,
don't be angry.
She isn't usually like this.
This is good.
If you have any questions in the future,
come ask me again.
Now that you've returned from your
journey,
you are still Chen Ping'an.
That is wonderful.
I see the green hills are full of charm,
and I suppose the hills see me the same.
What a beautiful day.
Did I...
embarrass Milord just now?
Silly Girl,
you think too much.
Us staying alive is already a miracle.
Were you asking...
if your parents could be like Gu Can's
father,
with their souls remaining in town
after death?
No.
Why?
Because...
it is not worth it.
Qi Jingchun painstakingly hid you away.
What was he planning?
This deal...
I agree to it.
The richer the family,
the more they like hiding their
talents.
Those unaware would easily be fooled.
Isn't that right, Silly Girl?
Steady, steady.
Don't panic.
Chen Ping'an must be loaded.
Silly Girl,
do you think I'm really foolish?
Tell the truth.
Am I being tricked by Chen Ping'an?
Swallowed, swallowed...
All swallowed.
Forget the Eighth or Ninth Realm,
even the Tenth Realm is possible!
Oh, my heavens!
Great Master!
Yours...
Milord,
this is perfect.
we agreed on just one
fine Snake Gallstone for me.
I am your lord.
Do I need a reason to give gifts?
Keep it safe.
What can a mere Saint do to me?
And I fear no small-time Junzi.
If you have the guts,
come punch me to death!
Alright!
O-O-O-
Milord!
Hurry, hurry,
come quick!
Do you know who repaired the Cao
family home?
What about it?
If a house is broken, shouldn't
it be fixed?
Whether it's fixed well or not
aside...
have you ever heard
the saying "digging up a sacred site"?
Truth be told,
I, Cao Jun, possess a unique talent.
I can sense certain precious
existences.
For instance...
that sword blank.
I'll give you some time.
You better offer a high price.
That sword blank...
it has quite the origin.
If I'm not mistaken,
isn't that the one from the Mountain
God of Sui Shan?
So valuable?
No wonder you won't sell it.
Then I have no choice but to rob you.
Brother Li,
regarding the books I gave you,
there are many annotations and doubts
of mine inside.
Try not to read those parts,
lest you misinterpret the original
meaning.
I've taken note.
Step back a bit further.
Just watch.
You can talk philosophy all you want,
but don't draw your blade lightly.
Yet my philosophy
resides within this scabbard.
Rest assured,
when I, Cao Jun, draw my sword,
I rarely kill.
So you are from the Cao family.
Your ancestor, Cao Xi, was a
generation's Sword Immortal.
Truly formidable.
In that case,
I, Li Xisheng,
would like to see how profound your
philosophy is.
First question:
what is your current cultivation realm?
Between the Eighth and Ninth.
Sword...
Sword Cultivator...
Eighth or Ninth Realm?
We're finished.
Relying on a powerful ancestor,
yet daring to break my rules.
You court death.
Master,
should we stop that Cao family member?
Wait until he injures someone,
then I'll beat him to death.
That's the proper procedure.
Master,
how can such a villain
become such a powerful Qi Practitioner?
You haven't read many books,
so don't lecture me on good and evil.
Remember this:
such concepts hold no weight
on the mountains.
Frog in a well.
You are merely Middle Fifth Realm.
I'll suppress my realm
so when you eventually climb out
of that well,
you'll realize that a person like me
deserves the title
of "honorable."
Getting interesting.
Chen Ping'an,
please step back a little further.
Forty or fifty paces would be best.
With a formidable foe before you,
you still have the leisure for
idle chatter?
Seventh Realm.
You Li bastard!
Since when does a Sixth Realm
Qi Practitioner
use simple Daoist spells
to withstand a Seventh Realm
Sword Cultivator's philosophy?
If word gets out,
I, Cao Jun, will be laughed at
by swordsmen across the world!
Perhaps your philosophy
just isn't high enough.
Very well...
Eighth Realm!
A treasure like this
is not something you should possess.
None of your damn business.
Impressive indeed.
If you have any life-saving treasures,
use them quickly.
Otherwise, you might die without—
That actually works?
Are you a leaf merchant or something?
Apologies.
My younger sister loves collecting
such things.
It seems your sword's philosophy
is flawed.
Regardless,
we should at least decide a winner.
My friend is waiting for me.
Then I won't hold back.
You insignificant Sixth Realm
Qi Practitioner.
No matter how many treasures you have,
or how vast your powers,
my sword
breaks ten thousand methods.
Breaks ten thousand methods!
Unless you are a banished immortal
of the Three Teachings Patriarch level,
you couldn't control so many objects
at once.
Who exactly are you?
You break ten thousand methods
with one sword...
Then I shall use Spring Leaves,
Summer Thunder,
Autumn Wind,
and Winter Snow
to accumulate
Ten Thousand and One Methods.
So that's it.
Using Yin-Yang divination
to predict my attack trajectory,
then defending with precision.
Otherwise, with just Sixth Realm
cultivation,
it would be impossible to control
so many objects at once.
Impossible to control so many
simultaneously.
Then I'll just break your Ten
Thousand and One Methods.
Edu...
You were given to me by Lord
Literary Sage.
Unless I give you away myself,
no one
can snatch you from me.
Cai Jinjian of Yunxia Mountain.
Greetings, Lady Ning.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™