[Previously]
Only after walking this path did I finally understand...
It's not about how much you know.
It doesn't make a person good.
Proximity to vermilion makes one red, after all.
That's why the Literary Sage
hopes Cui Dongshan can stay by your side.
Serve your teacher well on the journey home.
There will be plenty of rewards.
The student asks:
"Crabs have six legs and two pincers"—
Did I write that wrong?
The teacher replies:
A poor scholar...
is always short on money.
If you're willing to truly protect
Bao Ping and the others,
then I accept.
You may become my student.
After all these twists and turns...
I've gained yet another teacher.
A teacher must practice what he preaches.
You and I...
shall encourage each other.
Li Bao Ping is simply lawless!
She actually drew a blade and beat three students...
One of them being
the precious son of Marquis Huaiyuan.
Who stole Li Huai's clay figure?
Hand it over!
Who hit Li Huai?
Step forward!
You there.
Put down those straw sandals.
Fine then.
Kneel and beg me!
The eldest legitimate grandson of the Chu clan
wanted to settle things with Li Bao Ping.
But on the way, he was beaten unconscious
by Lin Shou Yi.
A whole group ganging up on one little girl...
The students of Great Sui
are truly impressive.
Today I'll teach you mud-legged bumpkins
a lesson you'll never forget!
This is Great Sui,
not Great Li!
When Lin Shou Yi was being beaten,
I didn't see anyone stopping it.
The way Young Master Pan acts
is no different from a mountain bandit.
You Great Li barbarians
dare to run wild here?
A sneak attack...
is indeed lacking in martial virtue.
But the ban on private brawls
has only just been issued.
So thank you very much.
You beat Young Master Pan
until blood flowed from all seven orifices.
Where is the scholarly grace in that?
What?
The sons of noble houses in yellow and purple
are allowed to fight,
but children studying far from home
can only suffer in silence?
What suffering?
These foreign students
have the teachers looking after their studies below,
and above, they even received precious gifts
personally bestowed by His Majesty.
On the contrary, it's the local students of Great Sui
who feel wronged.
Because of this incident,
the students who followed Elder Mao
when the old academy migrated from Great Li
have all taken Li Bao Ping's side.
They stand in sharp opposition to the local students.
Cliff Academy
is on the verge of splitting apart.
Absurd.
Elder Mao...
Say something!
Then...
so be it.
There must be someone behind this,
secretly fanning the flames.
Great Sui's enshrined tenth-realm Qi cultivator,
Cai Jingshen,
is still guarding the checkpoint at East Flower Mountain.
Is he simply too lazy to intervene,
or is he not allowed to?
Or perhaps the Great Li National Teacher
is secretly meddling,
stirring up trouble between the academy and Great Sui,
intending to completely sever
Cliff Academy's scholarly legacy.
Elder Mao...
The academy student Li Changying
personally went to apologize,
bearing the status of a Worthy and an imperial gift.
I heard that at Viewing Lake Academy
he passed the joint examination
of nine gentlemen
and obtained the title of Confucian Worthy.
Our Great Sui's Right Vice Minister of Rites
personally rode out ten miles from the city to welcome him.
And I also heard
that His Majesty ordered a senior eunuch
from the palace to deliver
a priceless set of the Four Treasures of the Study
as a token of commendation.
I hope this matter
ends here.
Any losses Young Master Lin suffered
I will compensate in full.
I have also collected quite a few
rare treasures.
I’ll deliver a few to Young Master Li
another day.
No need.
This young lady is both intelligent and brave,
truly possessing the spirit of a chivalrous heroine.
However, the academy
is not the jianghu where one acts on impulse.
I hope the young lady will turn hostility into friendship.
Changying
is deeply grateful.
How about this...
I’ll go apologize to them.
Apologize for what?
If Master and Little Shishu were here,
they’d be furious with you.
It was because of me that Lin Shouyi got hurt.
I know this matter isn’t over.
I’m not afraid of being beaten to death,
but if
you, Bao Ping, get hurt as well,
Chen Ping’an would never speak to me again in this life.
Li Huai...
If you’re not in the wrong, don’t apologize.
If Shishu were here,
he would say
“Li Huai, you are right.”
The academy is full of bad people.
If only Chen Ping’an were here...
Our Li Huai, General Li the Great...
crying so miserably.
If you can’t win, just endure it.
It’s not that big a deal.
No choice...
Even if you gave me the Xiangfu Blade,
I still couldn’t beat that Li Changying.
If Chen Ping’an were here,
what would he do?
Chen Ping’an would first reason with them properly.
After reasoning,
if the other party still refused to listen,
Little Shishu
would then use his fists to reason.
Now I understand.
What are you going to do?
On the way here,
Chen Ping’an always took the first half of the night watch,
and I took the second half.
That’s how it was before,
and that’s how it should be from now on.
When we reach Dragon Spring County,
Old Master, could you please not make me
do menial chores like making beds and sweeping?
If my brothers find out,
how embarrassing would that be?
How could I still be the big brother
to all those water ghosts and monsters?
I’m not bragging,
but if Old Master stops by my house on the way,
I’ll give you a grand welcome
with gongs, drums, and the river boiling over!
I didn’t control my strength well.
It’s fine.
To be honest with you,
that huge incident that shook Yellow Court Nation—
I took the blame for my water god brother.
I was chased for over two thousand miles
by the Supreme Elder of the Spirit Rhyme Sect.
Was I heroic?
Was I bold and gallant?
He was using you as a shield.
Do you really not know,
or do you know but simply don’t care?
What does a little girl like you know about brotherhood?
Daring to ruin my image in front of Old Master!
Once I reach the town and eat that stone,
once my realm completely surpasses yours,
I’ll eat you too,
then shit you out later.
However, if you’re willing to warm the bed for Old Master,
I can consider sparing you.
Stop talking nonsense.
Old Master’s lesson is well taken.
Again.
Old Master...
Old Master,
what a fierce punch!
It’s almost on par with a tenth-realm martial artist.
Old Master,
considering how hard I worked feeding you punches
and even held back from eating that silly girl,
could you, Old Master,
once we get home,
give each of us one more snake gall stone?
Why does she get one too?
Then I want two!
Two stones, huh?
Yes.
It’s all gone.
Old Master...
I know I was wrong.
One stone.
Just one stone.
A small token from your student.
I hope Master will graciously accept it.
Don’t worry.
These are just words on paper.
There’s no scheme behind them.
No need to help me.
Just share some of the things
from your book box with me.
That’ll do.
Old Master...
I’m a fire python who’s lived for hundreds of years.
I can even carry an entire mountain on my back.
Old Master...
You’re so stingy.
At this rate, you’ll probably never find a wife.
Want me to help you take in a few concubines or maids?
Don’t.
Old Master...
What if they don’t ask for any betrothal gifts
and even bring generous dowries?
Still not tempted?
Not tempted.
Why?
There’s already a girl I like.
With that personality of yours, Old Master...
The girl you like is probably a bit simple-minded.
Old Master...
How did you two meet?
Don’t tell me
you saved her, Old Master,
and even specially washed her clothes and cooked for her?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
So there are things even Ning Yao can’t do well.
Then there shouldn’t be such a thing as brewing medicine in this world.
If you want to laugh, just laugh.
Later, I ran into trouble.
Not only did she help me,
she even lent me her skirt-presser blade.
That was the most beautiful sight
I’ve ever seen in my life.
And then?
Then...
Then I returned the blade to her.
Old Master...
You’re such a blockhead.
How could anyone like you acting like this?
Even if an immortal from the mountain
tied a red thread between you two,
it still wouldn’t work.
Old Master...
Don’t mind it.
What if she really is a bit simple-minded?
[Clack]
Like a tortoise spotting a green bean—
they hit it off at first sight.
Old Master...
Actually, I’m quite good-looking too, you know.
Silly girl.
Quick, lend me some rouge and powder.
Disappear.
The night is long...
This lord has no desire to sleep.
A spring night is worth a thousand gold pieces.
Silly girl.
How about you become my wife?
You stinking pervert!
What the hell?
This is a heaven-sent blessing!
Your ancestors’ graves are smoking with good fortune, you know?
You think I actually like you?
If I wasn’t coveting that snake gall stone of yours
that I haven’t even gotten yet...
You’re just relying on Old Master backing you up.
I wonder how Bao Ping, Li Huai, and Lin Shouyi are doing...
How are they?
You’re Yu Lu, right?
You were looking for me?
This is
the money for the medicine you bought.
If it’s not enough,
allow me to owe it for now.
Interesting.
But provoking me right after I apologized...
You had a tiny bit of reason on your side before,
but now you have none at all.
Someone who truly apologizes
would never say something like that.
Rotten wood cannot be carved.
A wall of dung
cannot be plastered.
How fitting for you bunch of
Great Li
barbarians.
According to that guy,
people like you
should be dealt with using fists.
Raise the formation!
Defending with sword cultivator techniques,
shifting with Daoist divine arts,
then meeting the enemy head-on with military combat skills.
Truly eye-opening.
A man without benevolence—
what use is ritual?
Still not stopping?
So young,
yet already so vicious at heart.
Li Huai’s clay figure still hasn’t been found.
Vile insults all poured into Li Bao Ping’s ears.
Despicable methods used against Lin Shouyi.
And the ones who should apologize
haven’t let out
a single fart.
Fine.
This old man wants to see
whether you’ll still have any principles
once you’re lying on the ground.
Sixth-realm martial artist.
Out of respect for academy rules,
I’ll leave you half a life.
I’m begging you to be stronger.
You actually used me as a whetstone to break through?
You’re courting death!
My teacher has matters to attend to.
His disciple shall bear the burden.
Second Master Li.
A pleasure to meet you.
You surnamed Cui.
My son’s matter—
does it have anything to do with the schemes behind you?
It’s hard to say clearly.
Then I’ll beat you to death first.
Right now I’m only Cui Dongshan.
I’m half a fellow disciple with your precious son.
You can’t just hit people recklessly.
Besides, Great Sui has deep foundations.
It cannot be—
I’ll vent their anger for them.
Don’t do anything reckless.
Why don’t you go check on the children in the dormitory first?
If I don’t do something,
as their father,
I won’t have the face to see my son.
Even until today,
not a single family elder behind those troublemakers
has said a word.
If you’re truly angry,
you can go talk to their elders.
Mao Xiaodong.
Are you deliberately trying to disgust me?
Either go inside and pay your respects,
or make the matter clear.
Otherwise, the moment I see your face,
I’ll be your grandson.
Xiaodong...
I came this time just to study properly,
bask in the sun,
play a few games of chess with you,
and take care of those kids along the way.
All I know is
a dog
can’t change its habit of eating shit.
If you don’t believe me, fine.
The dirt on the wall—
do you want me to write a couplet for you?
Be careful—that might be your last words.
Heaven and man are separate.
Transform nature and arouse the artificial.
The other line is:
Ritual establishes hierarchy.
Law reaches hegemony.
Not going to chat anymore?
Better wash your eyes quickly,
or you’ll go blind.
This youthful skin of mine
is truly capable of toppling kingdoms and cities.
For the sake of Teacher and Senior Brother,
I’ll trust you this once.
Cui...
If you dare do anything that harms the academy,
even once,
I will personally kill you.
Great Sui’s intelligence network
is no worse than Great Li’s.
Then I’ll act as an elder from Xie Xie’s sect.
Old man.
Your most proud disciple’s most proud disciple
has run into trouble.
And I’ve been entrusted with an important task by my own teacher.
You’re not going to show some appreciation?
That wouldn’t make sense, would it?
How about this—
lend me the third realm for a bit?
Old man, are you really going to ignore me?
What kind of teacher are you?
You old bastard!
Did you hear that? I’m cursing you!
Truly heartless and ungrateful.
Fine, fine, fine. I’ll say it all.
Chen Ping’an, Li Bao Ping...
Golden Core realm.
Alright.
You even gave me an extra realm.
Guess this Cui was blind.
From today on, this lord shall be called Cui Dongshan,
merely Chen Ping’an’s student.
Mom...
Big Sister...
I miss you both.
They bullied me too much.
Yuan...
The earthworm eats the dust upon the green tendon.
Cui...
Happy?
Surprised?
Teacher didn’t come.
It’s just me, all alone and helpless.
Li Huai.
Chen Ping’an praised you for being brave
and responsible.
Said you’re a proper, upright young hero.
Really?
You idiot.
Would Little Shishu ever praise someone like that?
At most, he’d just give you a thumbs up.
Little Shishu’s compliments
are all saved for me.
Teacher is naturally the best to Bao Ping.
He specially caught a golden ridge-crossing crucian for you.
He said when we return home,
he’ll have your big brother raise it for you first.
I was wondering...
With Teacher’s stingy temper that won’t even add extra oil or salt,
how come when it comes to you all,
he suddenly stops treating treasures like treasures?
He’s not stupid either.
No no no no no!
Chen Ping’an’s letter will arrive very soon.
He even specially instructed:
“My student Cui Dongshan
is still a big scoundrel.
Don’t trust him no matter what.
But if you run into trouble,
you can ask him for help.”
True jianghu chivalry
has never been about seeking momentary satisfaction.
The mountains are high and the rivers long.
There will be plenty of time ahead.
If you make an enemy,
first deal with the enemy himself,
then bully his descendants.
Remember that.
For cultivators,
whether seeking revenge
or repaying kindness,
a hundred years is not considered long.
Hurry,
Now that the serious matters are finished...
Because my teacher was worried about you all,
he couldn’t truly calm his mind the entire journey.
So...
From now on,
you should all focus on your studies in peace.
Don’t worry about anything else.
Leave the rest to me.
Young Master, forgive me.
Sit.
Tell me,
why did you step in to finish it?
First, because I got impulsive
and just did it.
Other mountains’ stones can polish jade.
I used the Great Sui sword cultivator
as a whetstone for my own martial path.
Continue.
Otherwise,
I’ll say it for you.
As long as I don’t die,
in the future Chen Ping’an
will feel he owes me a favor.
Young Master previously said
that Xie Xie and I
are ten thousand miles apart in temperament from Chen Ping’an.
We could never be friends in this life.
I know Young Master
is most likely right.
But I’m not willing to accept it.
I wanted to try.
I just never expected Young Master would turn back.
Please punish me, Young Master.
Killing three birds with one stone.
Well done!
I’m so happy I can barely contain myself.
Why would I punish you?
Young Master...
Aren’t you afraid your identity will be exposed?
Using killing to stop killing.
Using evil to control evil. Got it?
You two, pick one person to leak the information.
For example, Xie Lingyue from the Wind God Xie clan.
Then I’ll appear as an elder from her sect.
If it’s you,
then I’ll be one of the hidden gatekeepers of the Lu Dynasty.
Give Great Sui a seemingly absurd reason
to intervene reasonably.
Just beat them into submission.
Pick me.
Cherish the fairer sex.
Don’t think you’ve already seen through me.
Be careful—one leaf can block your eyes.
But if you can see clearly into the deepest depths,
that would be even better.
You should know
this is actually one of my Great Daos.
One of Cui the National Teacher’s Great Daos.
How could it be small?
If someone truly sees through this single leaf
and perceives the greater whole from the small,
would it really still blind them?
Time to loosen up my muscles and bones.
Loosen up my muscles and bones.
That old turtle bastard Cai Jingshen—
hurry up and come recognize your ancestor!
Your eighteenth-generation ancestor
is here today to teach you family rules and ancestral precepts.
Go bathe and change your clothes quickly.
Kneel and listen to the lecture.
Who the hell is courting death?
Your old ancestor is looking for his turtle grandson.
That’s not courting death.
Get the hell out here!
Good grandson.
Hurry up and roll inside.
Where did this madman come from?
Die!
Cai Jingshen.
Make it quick and clean.
Hurry up and slit your own throat.
Make sure you do it with sincerity.
Who the hell lent you the dog胆 to
dare bully this old man’s disciples?
Not bad, you have some skill.
Come again.
What the hell is this?
This is horse piss from your ancestor.
Still coming?
You madman!
Don’t think I won’t kill you.
Well done!
My good grandson finally knows how to show filial respect to his ancestor.
You brat want to die?
Then this old man will send you on your way.
Nice spear.
Your ancestor will take it for you.
You’d better live long enough to claim it.
Overestimating yourself.
It is impolite not to reciprocate.
A gift from your old ancestor.
Grandson Cai Jingshen,
catch it properly.
What?
Porcelain?
A ritual robe?
Who the hell are you exactly?
You still dare talk back to your ancestor?
Slap your own mouth!
If I speak this Great Immortal’s name,
I’m afraid it’ll scare you to death.
Turtle grandson Cai Jingshen,
listen obediently to the lecture.
The Cai family temple enshrines a clay statue.
Incense smoke produced a stinky pickled vegetable.
Suddenly an ancestor descends from beyond the heavens.
In panic, three bags were changed at the door.
Trying to cover it with wind and thunder.
Instead, the spear tip lifted the piss cover.
With tenth-realm cultivation bullying the young and weak,
shameless, cunning, and rotten.
If not for angering your ancestor into coming,
I’d scold you for being both useless and shameless.
You don’t even know your mistake, nor do you repent.
Today you shall receive your lesson.
With no merit, no virtue, and no face,
you still dare clamor in front of the formation.
Rarely does your ancestor have free time,
hands itchy and body strong.
Then I shall curse my grandson a hundred times.
A hundred times!
Bullshit!
You noisy little brat,
stop acting so arrogantly!
Mao Xiaodong!
Is your academy not going to control this madman?
Then Cai Jingshen will handle him for you.
You just need to collect the corpse.
My teacher doesn’t have many...
Now there’s only one.
Not many fellow disciples catch my eye.
Not many close friends.
Not many beauties worth a second glance.
But I sure have plenty of magic treasures.
Today I’ll properly teach this unfilial grandson a lesson.
Bullying my son like this...
Damn your mother, Great Sui!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™