[Previously]
All forces hunt and kill...
a sword-bearing man named A Liang.
Dare leak the news...
shatter your golden body!
Kill Chen Ping'an...
gain a life of fortune!
If not for Bao Ping...
you'd be dead.
Sheathe your sword.
Don't waste the sword's vital essence.
This...
is sword qi!
Sword, come!
A Liang...
I've decided.
Reading's useless...
so annoying.
Qi Jingchun wants to roam Jianghu with you!
Live free, avenge wrongs...
drink the strongest wine...
wield the fastest sword!
Stop patting my head...
I'll never grow tall!
A Liang...
yes or no?
Give me a straight answer!
I've saved the money...
dozens of silver taels!
Scram, scram!
Still a kid...
spouting big words.
Little Qi...
Master...
why twist my ear?
Who beat you this badly?
That Zuo fellow...
Him?
So heavy-handed...
Lost the argument
and flew into rage?
Second Senior admitted defeat...
but said no matter how much I read...
I'd never surpass you, Master.
Nonsense!
Your knowledge is vast...
but you're old.
I'm young...
One day I'll surpass you!
He wouldn't listen...
said prove it...
surpass you tomorrow.
Infuriated me...
snuck a punch when off guard.
Lost in the end...
Gentlemen use words,
not fists!
Gentle...
men sit straight...
stand proper...
Etiquette adapts...
customs follow suit.
Little Qi...
You'll grow up one day...
become steady.
Just wonder...
by then...
your disciples...
or favored children...
will still have your resilience...
that fire in your bones...
for swift justice.
Father...
Spare him today...
and I'll die for you to see!
Chen Ping'an...
You know...
I've always admired you.
But...
sorry.
It's fine.
We choose our own paths.
This...
this is...
sword qi!
No!
Sword, come!
Stop, stop!
Wasting heaven's gift!
A loving family...
why fight and kill?
You and your father...
return my hero's gall...
and purple qi book...
plus those Li family talismans.
But these...
can only save one.
Zhu Lu...
you choose.
Please, Senior A Liang...
let Zhu Lu go.
I'll atone with my life.
No need to soil your blade.
I said...
Zhu Lu...
must die.
I beg you...
spare her!
What child hasn't caused trouble...
acted recklessly?
Lu'er is just naive...
forgive her, please!
I beg you...
please!
Chen Ping'an...
Lu'er...
is only a child.
Fine.
Some punishments
are crueler than death.
Leave.
I never want to see you again.
A Liang...
got any wine?
Plenty of wine...
but listen...
never drink when heartbroken...
turns you into a drunkard.
Drink when joyful...
and maybe...
become a wine immortal.
You help others...
Hello, Lin Shouyi.
We've met before.
My true identity...
is Grand Elder
of Dali's Changchun Palace...
an immortal in mortal eyes.
I trust you...
so I want to try...
convincing you...
to cultivate Dao arts
at Changchun Palace with me.
Father said a master
would guide me to the capital...
and if I died obscurely outside...
he wouldn't collect my corpse...
a dead man...
isn't worth the travel.
Harsh words...
but true.
Lin Shouyi...
step forward...
and you'll walk the Bridge of Immortality.
Thank you for the offer...
but I waited here...
to decline in person.
Birth sect and name...
weren't my choice.
But my path...
I choose myself.
Pity... such fine cultivation jade.
Lin Shouyi...
Lin Shouyi!
Trouble!
Ghosts!
Chen Ping'an...
Along this journey...
from Qidun Mountain
to the bamboo grove...
I've tested you many times.
Now...
one last time.
A Liang...
you're leaving?
Back at Longxu Stream...
if your character didn't suit me...
even as Qi Jingchun's choice...
I wouldn't have bothered.
Just left the donkey...
and walked away.
Whether you survived
till Wei Jin emerged...
not my concern.
Dead early or late—
still dead.
I don't fully grasp your intent...
but I've figured some.
Because I knew Qi Jingchun...
you cared this much?
Qi Jingchun... he's gone.
I suspected...
but refused...
dared not believe.
He was Qi Jingchun...
Like you...
a true fool through and through.
Not to torment you...
but cultivation tempts too much...
and the human heart...
fragile as glass...
can't withstand scrutiny.
Li Huai’s fortune...
Lin Shouyi’s talent for cultivation...
—all can be sold for coin...
...to become your stepping stones,
Chen Ping’an.
Especially Li Baoping—
—such a sweet girl.
What if her heart shatters
from betrayal by the junior uncle she trusted?
My heart, Ah Liang’s heart—
it’s breaking already!
Since Qi Jingchun chose you...
...and refused to test you too harshly...
—I’ll do it in his stead.
Let’s see if you, Chen Ping’an,
are truly worth tempering a thousand times—
—whether you’re real gold or fool’s silver.
Ah Liang, don’t worry.
I may love money...
...but only what I earn with my own hands.
I’m afraid Master Qi would be disappointed...
...afraid I can’t protect Baoping and the others.
Ah Liang...
...what do you think of me now?
If you think I’m not up to it...
...this job’s yours for the taking.
I, Ah Liang, have always lived freely—
—I don’t like your style.
Your kind of... stuffiness—
—in Qi Jingchun’s words,
—is called “integrity.”
But sometimes...
...the things you do
fill me with joy.
For me, Ah Liang...
—the path must be walked alone...
...the self, shaped by oneself.
You, Chen Ping’an, should be the same.
You don’t have to be just like me...
—but your spine must stay straight...
...your fists, hard as steel...
—and most importantly...
...live long enough to see it through.
Once, I turned down a boy’s request.
I told him...
...he’d find greater success in books
than in swordsmanship.
After all, this tiny martial world
has little worth.
Only the wine’s any good.
But now...
...I feel I should tell you this too:
Trust me—
—you’ll find greater success
with the sword than with fists.
Junior Uncle!
What is it?
See a ghost?
Real—
—real ghosts!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Why didn’t Prefect Xu draw his sword?
Not even a trace of sword qi...
Whether Prefect Xu acts or not
is his own affair.
I, Liu Yu, Director of the Military Selection Bureau...
...will personally twist his head off!
Aren’t you afraid he might be...
...the legendary Twelfth Realm?
I pray he’s that strong!
I’d hate for this fight
to be dull and flavorless!
Chen Ping’an—
—is he your enemy?
Don’t look at me!
Look at Lin Shouyi!
Look at Chen Ping’an!
Or better yet—
—look at Ah Liang!
Ah Liang...
Relax, you little rascal.
This yin spirit has cultivated to high attainment...
...and has followed you all this way.
Someone sent it specifically
to take over my duty of protecting you.
Ah Liang, you bastard!
I’m leaving these kids with you—
—at least escort them
to Yefu Pass on the Great Li border.
Senior...
Why trust a yin entity
of unknown origin?
You look so cold-hearted...
—clearly the kind
who’s warm inside and righteous at heart.
Is it because he reminds you
of your senior?
You’re a funny one.
Minnows and shrimp—
scram!
Li Huai!
Do you step in dog dung every day?
You’re the one who steps in dog dung!
Open that *Duan Shui Da Ya* manual!
Your whole family steps in dog dung!
Study it well...
...don’t waste it.
Where are you going?
Wait for me!
Ah Liang!
What was that fish just now?
Was it powerful?
What abilities does it have?
You’ve got to tell me
how to use it!
Finally...
The donkey?
Who wants it?
A Liang...
you're not dying, are you?
Then leave all your treasures to me!
Get lost!
As far as you can!
Dali iron cavalry...
by imperial decree...
apprehend rebels.
Defiers...
slain without mercy!
Coming to Dali this time...
one more thing.
A Liang...
settle scores with some folks.
Tell them...
what Qi Jingchun didn't care about...
someone does.
Chen Ping'an...
come here.
That strand of sword qi
you used at Qidun Mountain...
I feel bad.
Teach you the Eighteen Stops
qi circulation method...
as repayment.
Imperial brother...
that man's no Wei Jin
from Wind Snow Temple.
Background completely unknown...
likely eleventh...
even twelfth realm danger.
This time...
must it be this big?
No harm.
Dali has White Lord Capital
as national treasure...
just one more sword.
Watch closely.
Qi like dragon veins...
Fire arrows!
Rising from ancestral peaks
of ten thousand mountains...
First Stop.
Swift past three mountains,
six passes...
to Futu acupoint.
Second Stop.
Racing through six caves,
nine mansions...
to Chunyang Mansion.
Third Stop.
Flowing through hundred meridians...
qi pierces Lingtai
to Yuye Palace.
Fourth Stop.
Circling limbs...
through hundred bones...
to Shenmen Mansion.
Fifth Stop.
Qi descends to chest...
gathers at Yunmen Mansion.
Inner and outer harmony,
flowing sword intent emerges.
Sixth Stop.
Qi to abdomen...
returns to dantian.
Warm yet not scorching...
cool yet not congealing...
Seventh Stop.
Qi to waist...
gathers at Quanmen.
This mansion like hidden spring...
stores deep sword qi,
unseen.
Awaits release.
Seventeenth Stop.
Qi follows sword...
sword intent profound.
One sword unsheathed...
all qi returns to root.
Thus...
Eighteen Stops.
Memorized?
Yes.
Mostly.
Once familiar with the route...
try circulating slowly.
Slow...
is the true wonder
of Eighteen Stops.
I'm in a hurry...
come at me together.
Today, dragon's pool
or tiger's den...
I'll charge through!
Stake my cultivation...
not without chance.
Sharp eyes.
Changchun Palace wine
wasn't wasted on you.
Such a foe...
rare in a lifetime.
Martial Selection Vice Minister
Liu Yu...
seeks a bout!
Copying others with tiger tattoos...
dragon over the shoulder...
think you can handle it?
Xu Ruo... Xu Ruo...
you're such a fool.
Met the man you admired most...
yet asked none of your burning questions.
Song Mu...
do you know why...
I fight this battle?
Because...
Mother Empress wants Chen Ping'an dead.
Lizhu Cave Heaven's dragon kilns blaze...
firing natal porcelains one by one.
Factions trade mountains
and territories with Dali...
bags of gold essence coins
fill Dali's treasury.
Dali Song clan's centuries
of managing Lizhu Cave Heaven...
all poured into this.
This White Jade Capital...
Dali's greatest weapon.
So this fight is necessary.
Dali must show all East Treasure Bottle Continent...
any immortal daring to oppose Dali...
must weigh the consequences.
Dali's emperor is interesting.
Impressive.
Little Baoping...
this is a fine sword-nurturing gourd.
For you.
May I borrow...
your narrow blade, Xiangfu?
A Liang...
if the blade breaks...
no need to return it.
Because...
we're friends.
That warms the heart...
I like it.
Don't worry...
A Liang...
more fights coming?
I'll help...
cheer you on!
Told you before...
how strong I am...
how high my swordsmanship.
You didn't believe...
called it bragging.
You kids...
so young and ignorant.
I've never bragged in my life.
Protect them!
Too high a realm...
not always good.
Once I remove this hat,
my cultivation will soon recover.
This mortal world
won't hold me anymore.
A Liang...
Father, Mother, and Sister...
all left me.
I won't curse you anymore...
don't leave, okay?
This brief, trivial time together...
wasn't bad in the end.
You four...
remember this:
Every strong one's freedom...
ends at the weak's freedom.
True strong...
challenge heaven's unseen rules...
worldly power's inertia...
the iron law of birth, age, illness, death.
Never grow strong
by trampling the weak.
Always stronger against stronger...
braver with setbacks.
Like me...
after Dali, off to other places...
fight the strongest.
A Liang...
good man!
Senior A Liang...
I'll cultivate hard!
Chen Ping'an...
so young...
yet so burdened.
Not good.
You're a dashing young lad!
Smile for me.
Gone...
A Liang was that strong?
The unreasonable kind...
of strong.
Kid...
practice sword well...
be as fierce as me...
fiercer...
nah...
too hard.
A Liang...
Don't worry...
you better keep your word!
I'll practice sword diligently!
Got it.
A Liang...
every word you said...
I'll remember it all.
Old man...
you were right.
With them here...
this world has hope.
This world...
is truly beautiful.
Truly beautiful...
Fighting for such a world...
that's what makes me...
A Liang.
With White Jade Capital here...
below the thirteenth realm...
all can be slain.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™