[Previously]
Put down those straw sandals!
Fine.
Get on your knees and beg me!
Rotten wood cannot be carved.
That phrase suits you barbarians
from Great Li perfectly.
For scum like you,
fists are the only language
Once you're lying on the ground,
we'll see if you still want to talk reason.
Who gave you the guts
to bully my disciples?
Shut your mouth,
you insolent brat!
Today, I'll teach you a lesson
you ungrateful grandson!
Bullied my son like that?
Screw your mother's Great Sui!
[I want a real challenger! - Parents in this world are heroes themselves]
Episode 18
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Door slams open]
Mister Qi,
I know the rules.
That wench clawed my wife's face bloody,
and I couldn't swallow that humiliation.
So I went and cursed out her ancestors,
and tore down their Ancestral Hall.
I haven't said a word about it since.
Relax.
I'm not here to call you to account.
I'm here to drink.
Dad,
I'm full.
This wine is terrible.
Forgive me, Mister Qi.
It's good.
Back in my youth,
I used to drink swill like this often.
And my temper back then
was far worse than yours.
Over at the Academy,
there's still no movement.
Old Man Mao only said
he would give His Majesty an explanation.
He didn't mention
when he'd enter the palace.
If Old Man Mao won't come,
I can't exactly pressure the Academy
into serving justice, can I?
This "Turning Page Gale"
is a guest hard to invite.
Where is the Emperor of Great Sui?
Just how strong is this guy?
He's so audacious,
yet he's merely a formidable
Ninth-Rank Martial Artist.
Allow me to test him.
Agreed.
If I lose,
Your Majesty
can simply show yourself.
Just don't make it too ugly.
Unless absolutely necessary,
I won't borrow the Imperial Dragon Qi
of the capital.
I failed to gauge your depth back then.
Exchange three punches.
If you win,
you may meet our Emperor.
I'll let you strike first with two blows.
Good.
You have one punch left.
Don't hold back.
However...
I will also make my move.
All soldiers, fall back to the gate!
A Grandmaster with great courage!
Let's continue.
Please, teach me.
Hold on.
Rice must be eaten one bite at a time.
Compared to Song Changjing,
this whetstone of yours
isn't heavy enough.
Still refusing to call your master out?
Emperor of Great Sai,
either keep hiding,
send someone stronger,
or if you can't manage that,
have everyone come at me at once.
Be careful.
Your Majesty, rest assured.
Activate the Dragon Wall Formation!
Damn it.
I've been suppressed to the Eighth Realm.
It seems that within this
city defense array,
all Qi Practitioners and Martial Artists
will be suppressed by the Gao family's
Dragon Qi,
dropping one or two realms.
No matter.
Dear grandson,
your ancestor still has many
novel treasures.
Don't die too easily on me.
Using a formation
to suppress me to the Eighth Realm,
to elevate his cultivation.
Though it's only a single realm apart,
the price Great Sui's capital has to pay
is significantly less.
You wish to seek an audience
with our liege?
Fine.
But you should never have been
so arrogant about it.
After all, the Great Sai Court
must maintain its dignity.
Are you saying that the fists of
a Ninth-Rank Martial Artist
cannot match the "face" of your Great Sai?
That is precisely correct.
Anyone who steps out
of the Wuying Hall Plaza
and loses...
Well then.
Good fist.
Again.
Your Li Er's fists may shatter walls,
but they won't break the rules
of my Great Sai.
If you want to see our Emperor,
crawl out
and then crawl back in
to pay homage.
A mere Ninth-Rank Martial Artist
dares to run wild and cause havoc
in my Great Sai?
Dream on.
Relax.
I'll take good care of myself.
What a true Grandmaster.
Surrounded by tigers and wolves,
yet he remains utterly unreasonable.
My boy is so sensible, yet he gets bullied.
It's all because I, his father,
lack ability.
If the Emperor of Great Sai won't see me,
then I'll smash his entire
Great Sai to pieces.
How could he...
return to the Ninth Realm?
I only seek justice from
the Emperor of Great Sai.
No matter how hard your fists are,
you cannot break the sky of my Great Sai.
I'll show you what "Dynasty's Face"
truly means.
I'll show you the Thunderbolt
of the Dynasty!
Emperor of Great Sai,
it really isn't easy to see you.
This grand formation is probably...
Old Man Mao,
you've finally arrived!
I have some words in my heart
that I must spit out.
But I'm clumsy with words
and can't explain it clearly.
Then fight it out clearly.
How dare you be so impudent!
Relax.
I'm not here to call you to account.
I'm here to drink.
You remind me of a brother,
a friend of mine.
He was very much like you.
A strong man draws his blade
against the stronger.
I have no blade.
So a strong man throws a punch
at the even stronger.
If Ninth Realm strength can't
force your submission,
then screw the Ninth Realm—
I'll break through it.
Ninth Realm peak...
Li Er breaks through the realm,
not amidst life and death,
but with a fist aimed higher,
releasing a breath from the heart.
All of you, get out of my way!
Good, good.
So Mister Qi saw through it long ago.
The path I, Li Er, have always walked,
yet never realized myself—it was correct.
The feeling of the Tenth Realm is sublime.
Compared to eating chicken legs
left by my son,
the taste is certainly superior.
Rest assured,
I dare not claim to teach Li Huai
much scholarly knowledge,
but I guarantee he will be a good man.
His temperament won't be inferior
to his father's.
Mister Qi,
that is enough.
If I could just drink with Mister Qi again,
then...
that would be even better.
Emperor of Great Sai,
if you don't come out now,
don't bother coming out at all.
You little bastard, are you finally stepping in?
Ancestor, I'll discipline you
some other day, you turtle grandson!
Bah!
The fist of a fiery Martial Artist
is truly extraordinary.
I am the Vice-Principal
of Cliffside Academy,
Mao Xiaodong.
I am here specifically
regarding the matter of Li Huai.
Are you willing to follow me
to meet with His Majesty?
But we'll have to fight one more bout
before that.
If Great Sai believes it stands on the side of reason,
then let's continue fighting.
I know Great Sai has deep pockets
..and can withstand the hardships of life."
But I, Li Er, find it bizarre.
If all the officials in Great Sai are
such useless trash,
what kind of scholar will my son Li Huai become
studying in a place like this?
Do those noble families need to
publicly apologize to Li Huai?
A group of high-ranking lords
apologizing to a child—
how does that even work?
And I don't want my son
unable to study in peace
at Cliffside Academy.
Mister Li Er,
you are indeed reasonable.
I should have met with you sooner.
I am no "Mister."
Old Man Mao and the tutors teaching
Li Huai at the academy are the real deal.
I'll wait right here.
Your Majesty better not try
to stall me deliberately.
I...
I will send someone to deliver the message now.
Old Man Mao,
what advice do you have for me?
It's simple.
Have the members of those families
enter the palace
and bow their heads to Li Er in apology.
Old Man Mao,
tell me the truth.
Were you just waiting for today
to watch me make a fool of myself?
To be honest,
even I didn't know
Li Huai had such a father.
Had I known earlier,
I would have entered the palace
to see the Emperor sooner.
Why would things have escalated
to this point?
I am not that muddle-headed.
That Li Er was willing to stop at this point—
Old Man Mao, your contribution is immense.
I...
will order the Ministry of Rites
to commend you.
Unnecessary.
Why?
The way of the gentleman lies
in regulating profit by righteousness,
and controlling material desires
with the heart.
Extensively learn,
inquire accurately,
reflect carefully,
discriminate clearly,
and practice earnestly.
Sincerity means
choosing what is good
and holding fast to it.
This is precisely what our
Cliffside Academy embodies.
For the next decades or centuries,
Cliffside Academy
will continue to teach this way,
imparting the Dao and instructing disciples.
We will nurture scholars
for Great Sai,
protecting and cultivating true seeds
of learning.
I...
on behalf of Great Sai's state,
thank Cliffside Academy in advance.
Mao Xiaodong
accepts this for Cliffside Academy
with a clear conscience.
Elder Li Huai,
we were wrong.
We were truly wrong.
Master Mao has already punished them,
and sent them here specifically
to apologize.
They bullied people like that,
and a single apology
makes it water under the bridge?
We really were wrong.
If you err and don't change,
what good is that?
I won't let you bully me again.
Where are you going?
Keep kneeling.
At home, Mother protects me.
Outside, Chen Ping'an and the others
protect me.
Yet I seem to be
constantly causing trouble for others.
They get hurt because of me...
and it hurts more than if I
were wronged myself.
Why is my courage so lacking?
I have no grudge against you.
You broke in here—
what business brings you?
Damn it, another madman.
Halt.
A "Stopping" Realm Martial Artist.
You... are...
Cai Jingshen,
correct?
No.
I am not.
You...
If you have the skill,
if you have the guts,
come fight me again!
I'm talking to that young man in white
from the other day.
You?
You're not involved.
Mother,
Sister,
I missed you guys.
Son!
My boy!
Dad,
Mother...
What are you doing here?
My Huai'zi has gotten thin.
Mother's heart is breaking.
Alright, alright.
I'm doing great, really.
I have so many wonderful things too.
Come,
let me show you.
Let's go.
Slow down.
Monstrous talents appear every year,
but this year there's an especially
large crop.
What do you think?
It was made for me by Chen Ping'an.
Isn't it pretty?
Aren't you jealous?
Good.
Truly good.
Also...
this one.
On the journey here,
did anyone bully you?
No.
Chen Ping'an protected us.
He is such a good person.
He gave us all the best things.
It's a pity Li Liu isn't good enough
for him.
Lin Shouyi is passable though.
He can even drink with me.
You keep saying "Chen Ping'an."
Who is he?
Is he rich?
Mother,
character matters most
when living life together.
Just like Father.
Though poor,
he treats you so well.
You should cherish that properly.
Mother,
I want to buy a box of rouge.
Didn't you just buy one last year?
You spend money so wastefully.
Who will dare marry you in the future?
This pot is expensive.
Drink this first.
Save the cheap one for the dinner table
later.
Then Mother won't call you a spendthrift.
I was used to staying at home before.
I thought it was only natural
for people to treat me well.
But traveling with Chen Ping'an
opened my eyes.
There are so many villains outside.
Now I finally understand
that a man like you,
who treats Mother,
Sister, and me
so well...
is incredibly rare.
Before...
I'm sorry.
Son,
drink with your dad.
This tastes awful.
Spend these next two days with Mother
and your sister.
Tour the capital of Great Sai properly.
Even if you can't afford nice things,
it's good to look.
Later, when I succeed in my studies,
I'll buy them for you.
I promise I'll buy them.
Don't worry.
I'm doing very well at the academy.
Really.
My son knows how to care for his father now.
I'm happy.
Happier than breaking through a realm
with my fists.
For all these years,
I've been suppressing your talent
and bone structure.
Now, you don't need to hide anymore.
As for how far you ultimately go,
that depends on you.
The Godly Sovereign cleaves the mountain,
creating a Cave Heaven.
What kind of luck does Li Huai have?
Sitting at home,
fortune falls from the sky.
Unlike you, you little money-loser.
You can't even grasp the opportunities
handed to you.
Yu Lu is different from you.
Knowing something is impossible,
he sought to use that old sword cultivator
as a whetstone to break through.
He even managed to make Chen Ping'an
owe him a huge favor.
Perhaps they might even become friends.
Since I publicly declared you
as my disciple,
from now on,
you are Xie Lingyue of the Lu Dynasty's
premier immortal residence.
Understand?
Dragon Confining Nails.
Thank you.
Thank you, Young Master.
Remember this:
From now on, you must fight desperately.
Otherwise, go hang yourself somewhere.
What should be done about her?
How about...
she becomes your mistress?
I'm dying of laughter here.
Thanks, thanks a lot.
Ambition soaring higher than the heavens,
but fate thinner than paper.
Unable to accept your current self...
Even if I remove the Dragon Confining Nails
for you,
how far could you possibly walk?
Unlike my own Master,
whose heart-mind is pure,
and whose Great Dao is full of promise.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Master.
So, Master's Dao favors water...
allowing the Patriarchs of the Three Teachings
to walk side-by-side in harmony.
Master, please accept
this bow from your student.
Old Man,
take a look at this treasure.
The show is about to begin.
Fairy Su...
she is truly the apple of my eye.
Just look at
that figure,
that temperament.
Improper sights should not be seen.
I'll trade her for just one
Snake Gallstone from you.
Deal?
It's snowing.
Life is so meaningless.
Master, Master!
A man and a woman have appeared
on the plank road.
The man seems ordinary,
but the woman... she has intense demonic
aura!
What should we do?
It's a Fox Demon.
Fox demons in this world are known
for their stunning beauty.
Father,
I'll catch you a personal maid
to warm your bed.
Traveling in the snow...
my attendant and I are truly exhausted.
Young Master,
might we rest for a moment?
Granted.
Old Man,
why don't we...
Don't mess around, you two.
My attendant released some demonic aura
earlier.
Consider it a greeting.
Young Master, rest assured.
We mean no harm.
Your Martial Arts realm isn't high,
but your Fist Intent is solid.
Most impressive.
Persist in this,
and the Stopping Realm is within reach.
Thank you for your kind words, Sir.
Do you know how to read this character?
"Learn."
What a coincidence.
Young Master, your Bridge of Immortality
is broken—what a pity.
To repair it...
is harder than ascending to heaven.
Better to find another path
and rebuild one anew.
Old Master Bai,
you just met with the Literary Sage
not long ago,
and now you encounter his disciple?
Could it be...
a scheme plotted by both Saints?
I am merely traveling abroad
to ease my heart,
free of desires and demands.
If they still try to scheme against me,
then I might as well
attack that wall of theirs
and change this world
to have a new master.
What difference would it make?
Although you are of the Demon Race,
you grew up in the Haoran World.
Why are you so obsessed with meddling
in that conflict?
The war between humans and demons,
leaving two worlds devastated,
nine out of ten homes empty.
Is that fun?
Old Master, spare my life!
I don't think it's fun.
Not interesting in the slightest.
Qing Ying.
There are some matters
you cannot interfere with for now.
If not for that tiny spark of karma
from back then,
you would already be dead.
A... a Great Demon!
Holy shit, that's massive!
Bigger than the sky!
And she's just a servant?
Then isn't the man even more monstrous?
Not necessarily.
Our Old Master
isn't as powerful as us.
Oh, right.
Silly girl,
learn to speak properly.
Lu Chen.
Imperial Edict.
Old Master Bai,
it's settled.
Simply a matter of separate waters
not disturbing each other.
Well now,
when I sought you out, you hid.
When I gave up hope,
you came looking for me instead.
I trouble Old Master Bai to keep an eye
on this young man.
If the day comes when Humans and Demons
officially go to war,
please, as a member of the Demon Race,
after observing him,
make your decision.
Sword practice in a dream?
Interesting.
I heard you took a major tumble early on,
and your cultivation has stagnated.
What,
you think forming a marriage alliance
with the Chen family of Yingyin
will let you stage a comeback?
Cao Jun,
it is time for you to depart.
Almost forgot to mention—
my Cao family ancestors
also walked out from Mud Bottle Lane.
I wonder if this return to my roots
will stir up a slaughter,
killing off all the mosquitoes and flies.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™