Sacrifice of Ten Thousand Dragons.
Forge the Body of the Dragon God!
Create the Power of the Dragon God!
Go to battle!
Use this power
to trample the world beneath your feet!
I, Ao Xue,
in the name of the Dragon God,
Summon the Nine Heavens Golden Dragon.
The dragon
is the true ruler of the world.
♪No matter what the weather♪
♪Nothing can stop me
from pursuing the truth♪
♪Cutting through thorns along the way♪
♪People with dreams are remarkable♪
♪I will spread my arms wide♪
♪Without hesitation♪
♪Unafraid of the surging tides♪
♪Resting at the highest peak♪
♪Facing the horizon♪
♪Raising the flag high♪
♪My stubbornness is my weapon♪
♪Enough to shatter doubts♪
♪Not to please anyone♪
♪Forgive me for being too rebellious♪
♪Not defined by anyone♪
♪Being myself♪
♪I possess superpowers♪
♪No preset path♪
♪The future awaits my exploration♪
♪I muster the courage
to chase my passion♪
♪Waiting for the wind to rise again♪
♪Distinguishing highs and lows
from setbacks♪
♪My gaze is resolute♪
♪My passion never dies♪
- Soul of the Dragon -
- Myriad Forms of the Dragon God -
Episode 1
[The Fall of the East Sea]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(In the beginning of creation,)
(the Eternal Flame
lit up heaven and earth.)
(The first dragon in the world)
(was born from it.)
(He became the progenitor
of the Dragon Clan,)
(Naga.)
(The descendants of Naga)
(founded the Dragon Clan of the Four Seas
on the Central Continent.)
(Dragon Clan are born with)
(the power to command celestial forces.)
(This power is known
as the Soul of the Dragon.)
(The great dragon ancestors)
(relied on their mighty
Soul of the Dragon)
(to awe the Three Realms.)
(Nowadays...)
(East Sea Dragon Palace)
Elder Dragon King.
The war between the Gods
and the Asuras grows fiercer by the day.
I'm afraid it will soon spread
to Dragon Clan.
(Manluo)
The one fighting the Asuras this time
is the God of Light Soul.
(Ao Lei, South Sea Dragon King)
The Shadow Gods are not involved.
Their power is immense.
What are you trying to say?
Earlier, the Shadows mentioned
joining forces with us to create
the Celestial Dragon Realm.
Their sincerity is undeniable.
As long as we hand over
the Golden Soul of the Dragon,
we will share a golden era with them.
(Ao Guang, East Sea Dragon King)
Nonsense!
The Golden Soul of the Dragon
is the bloodline of our ancestors!
This matter is not up for discussion.
Guang.
Opposing the Shadows
will only bring annihilation
upon the Dragon Clan.
Silence!
If you dare side with the Shadows,
I will kill you myself!
Useless old fool.
(Ao Yilong)
Ao Yilong.
(Son of the South Sea Dragon King)
Die!
You…
How dare you…
Send the order.
Mobilize the entire army.
(Ao Jiao, East Sea Crown Prince)
Why does Father suddenly want to see me?
(Ao Ye, Son of the East Sea Dragon King)
He…
He's feeling unwell.
He said
he has something to entrust to you.
Where is Father?
He's...
He's just up ahead.
Release the arrows!
(East Sea Third Uncle)
Guang.
Darn it.
Kill him!
I am not here today to kill.
Those who surrender
to the Celestial Dragon Realm
will be spared.
How dare you killed your superior,
Elder Dragon King.
Prince Ao Jiao will never let you go!
Ao Jiao?
I've already arranged for father and son
to reunite in the underworld.
Wretched old thief of the South Sea!
You traitor.
It's Crown Prince Ao Jiao.
Ao Jiao.
Do you think I'm dead?
Your Highness.
Father.
South Sea.
You're looking for death!
Kill all these villains!
Avenge the Elder Dragon King!
Kill!
The Shadow Legion
should make their move.
Your Highness.
The Shadows forces are huge.
We're outnumbered.
We might as well retreat for now.
Gather the Dragon Clan forces
and then strike back.
Retreat!
Perhaps the Soul of the Dragon
that the Great God
of the Red Flame wants is on Ao Jiao.
Hurry!
Father.
From now on,
the lives of the Dragon Clan
will be decided by you.
Shut up!
The Shadows are our heaven.
We're just doing their work.
Uncle.
Both you and the Shadows are heaven.
Please spare
Ao Ye's life.
To show loyalty,
I…
I'm willing to cut off my dragon horn!
Useless eyesore.
I'll kill you!
Wait.
He still has a use.
Send the good news
to the Shadow Gods first.
Yes!
Father.
Then this East Sea...
You handle it within three days.
Three days of city-wide slaughter!
Kill!
(North Sea Dragon Palace)
(Ao Bing, Princess of the North Sea)
(Ao Shun, North Sea Dragon King)
The newly appointed
East Sea Dragon King,
what wind blew you here?
South Sea colluding with the Shadows
and murdered my father.
The East Sea Dragon King is dead.
It's indeed regrettable
about the Elder Dragon King.
If you're not avenging him,
what brings you to North Sea?
I hope the North Sea will send troops
to join me in punishing the South Sea.
I cannot interfere
your internal matters.
Go back.
This concerns the survival
of the Dragon Clan,
not just the grudges
between the South Sea and East Sea.
If we don't resist,
our entire clan will perish.
The flames of war
will soon spread to the North Sea.
Such a hassle.
You go back first.
Let me think it over.
Darn it.
The guy from the North Sea
keeps shirking.
The North Sea Dragon Clan
lives apart from the world.
Even when the Dragon Clan
faces foreign invasions,
they prefer to stay isolated,
and avoid conflict.
So spineless!
Shut up!
Don't slander the North Sea like that!
She is...
The Princess of the North Sea!
Your Highness.
What I just said was out of line.
If it offended you,
please forgive me.
The North Sea has no cowards.
We just don't fight unwinnable battles.
I want to see
if you're worth following.
Ice Soul of the Dragon.
Oh no!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Forgive my offense.
Your Highness possesses
Soul of the Dragon,
if you can come with me...
I will follow you.
See, learn from this.
Please.
Ao Jiao.
Long time no see.
(Manasa, North Sea Queen Mother)
Now you bear
the future of the entire Dragon Clan.
(Flaming Shadow Palace)
Great God of the Red Flame.
(Tianyong Star, the Shadows)
The East Sea Dragon Clan has been taken.
These are high-quality
Soul of the Dragon offered to you.
(Nezha, Great God of the Red Flame)
High-quality?
And the legendary Golden Dragon Soul?
No news yet?
Great God!
Spare my life!
I will speed up the search!
Useless!
Go back and search again.
Present it to me as soon as possible.
Otherwise,
your fate will be miserable.
Yes.
At once!
(Darn it.)
(This won't last long.)
(Qing.)
(Dragon Clan Elder, West Sea)
Dragon Lady, Ao Qing
had an affair with
the Dragon Clan's enemy, Nezha.
Now she dies to atone for her sins.
You forced her to death.
This hatred is endless!
Shame on being the celestial.
Join the Shadows.
Go take revenge.
The stupid rules.
I want the entire Dragon Clan
to be buried with Qing.
Take him down.
Go!
Nezha.
(Primordial Jade Lord)
Use the power I granted
to enslave the Dragon Clan.
Find the bloodline
of the Golden Dragon Soul.
Then you can resurrect your beloved.
From today onwards,
there is no Nezha in this world.
Only the Red Flame.
(I will definitely find
the Golden Dragon Soul)
(and let you be reborn.)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪The sky has turned brown♪
♪The retreat is full of thorns♪
♪My heart is stained with blood♪
♪Holding faith tightly in my hands♪
♪Breaking free from the marks of fate♪
♪Fallen, unable to awaken♪
♪Once I had, once it was enough♪
♪Now all I hear is the sound of crying♪
♪Once hopeful, never retreating♪
♪Relying only on tightly clasped hands♪
♪Once again, I still want to try♪
♪Saving the cruel and immortal ending
in the wild wind♪
♪Fighting fiercely, not yet over♪
♪Racing against the wind,
a desperate battle♪
♪From now on,
this poem will be recorded in history♪
♪No need to call for help,
fearless of wounds♪
♪In the end, only perseverance remains♪
♪Once again, I still want to try♪
♪Destroyed many times,
still holding an undying faith♪
♪Fighting fiercely, not yet finished♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™