[Preview]
Previously on Shrouding the Heavens,
with the full support of the Yin-Yang Sect,
Ye Fan successfully passed the entrance exam
for the Immortal Platform Realm graduate program,
overseen by the three Grand Elders.
Meanwhile, Ji Ziyue revealed her secret technique
for refining Primordial Qi Oil,
which prompted Vice Principal Ji Daoyi—
ranked eighth in the clan—
to force an arranged meeting between her
and the reigning champion, Wang Teng.
Since Wang Teng
activated the Eternal Blue Gold
containing the Void Emperor's blood,
the Ji family believed he was divinely favored.
Wang Teng himself thought victory was assured.
He decided
to force the marriage with Ji Ziyue.
But Ye Fan arrived
just in time, like a rocket slicing through the sky.
Amidst the roaring cheers of the audience,
chanting "How about it? What can you do?"
the battle for the title of
Strongest Graduate began.
After an epic, rage-fueled probing attack,
Wang Teng unleashed his ultimate technique:
the Chaos Ancient Art's
Eternal Banishment.
However, Ye Fan countered
using the Sun Scripture
and the Bronze Coffin Sutra,
breaking the attack completely.
Thus, Wang Teng chose to perform
the "Slay Self, Illuminate Dao"
ritual to ascend to the PhD level.
He published his thesis on the evolution
of the Chaos Ancient Secret Art
under the influence of the Front Word Secret.
Unfortunately, his philosophy clashed
with his mentor, Elder Lun Gu.
Consequently,
Ye Fan—who had mastered the Four Secrets—
found critical flaws in his logic,
resulting in Wang Teng's thesis being rejected.
Furthermore, Vice Principal Ji,
who supported Wang Teng,
was arrested for abusing public office.
And so,
Ye Fan's battle against Wang Teng
to save Ziyue came to an end.
This concludes last week's recap.
Now, let us proceed to this week's events.
Earth.
Brother Ye,
Pang Bo.
So you two aren't from the Big Dipper Star?
Finally...
It's been ten years.
Ye Zi...
I can finally say it out loud.
I was suffocating!
No wonder you were so eager to befriend me.
It was because of my unparalleled
Void Crossing Technique, wasn't it?
You...
Dead dog,
go screw yourself!
Your unreliable teleportation
sent me straight to the Central Plains.
And Tu Fei...
who knows where he's stuck,
digging through some frozen wasteland in the North Plain.
Today, my sister
was able to break the engagement with Wang Teng
all thanks to Brother Ye's aid.
Haoyue is deeply grateful.
However...
my sister...
If Brother Ye has no intention,
please do not give her
false hope that leads to obsession.
Little Moon, who's usually so lively,
why are you alone out here?
[Wind blowing]
Even the moon has its phases.
True.
Ziyue.
Did you know,
in my hometown,
people often gaze at the moon
to send thoughts to distant loved ones?
The moon
is a boat drifting in the heart,
carrying the sorrow
of separation.
Ziyue...
Have you ever considered
that beyond this vast land
and endless cosmos,
perhaps...
this isn't the only realm?
Are you saying
you're not from this world?
Then where exactly did you come from?
Could it be...
the legendary Immortal Domain?
Look at that starry sky.
Pang Bo and I
came from the other side,
from a place
incredibly far away.
A world called Earth.
No wonder...
That explains why,
for the past ten years,
you never aligned with any faction
and kept everyone at a distance.
But these past ten years,
I haven't been truly alone.
There was the Black Emperor,
the Holy Ape,
and Heishui.
What about me?
You and them...
are different.
Different how?
These ten years,
I've traversed the stars
and scoured ancient methods,
all to reunite with my parents.
But I knew that one day,
I would have to say goodbye
to everything here.
Yet, facing you...
on that day of parting,
I wouldn't know how to.
If you already planned to leave,
why risk everything
to come to the Ji family
and break my engagement?
Because at least when I leave,
I want you to have the freedom
to choose your own destiny.
Crossing the starry domain
is no simple feat.
To repay your kindness today,
this Little Immortal
will accompany you across
every corner of the Big Dipper.
I swear I'll help you find a way home.
And if we can't find a way...
then I'll just
create a new "Star Trampling Art"
or something to get you back.
It's a deal.
Then tell me more about
what interesting things exist
on Earth.
Sure.
On Earth,
humans are mortals.
Their lifespan is but a few decades.
They can't fly either;
they travel using vehicles
called airplanes.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Xiao Nannan,
come inside.
That bronze coffin was what
withstood the Ji family's
Void Ancient Mirror head-on.
It's clearly no ordinary object.
This bronze coffin
shares a deep connection with me.
If I can uncover its secrets,
perhaps I can solve
one of the great mysteries
in my heart.
Black Emperor,
do you think you can handle it?
When I handle things,
you can rest easy.
Ye Fan,
let me give you a hand.
Why does it look just like me?
Ye Fan!
Ye Fan, what's wrong?
Brother Ye! Ye Zi!
Let's chase it!
Where is this bronze coffin
taking us anyway?
Ye Fan,
that's the direction
of the Desolate Ancient Forbidden Land!
Just letting it get away like that?
That's the Desolate Ancient Forbidden Land.
We can't just barge in there.
Nine Dragons pulling a coffin...
Good heavens,
those are real dragons!
Such creatures actually exist?
And there are nine of them!
That small coffin
could withstand the Void Mirror.
The corpse inside the large coffin
must be an Ancient Great Emperor.
Otherwise,
who else would be worthy of
having nine dragons pull their coffin?
The Five-Colored Altar.
It looks identical to the one
on Mount Tai.
Five-Colored Altar...
Nine Dragons pulling a coffin...
Pang Bo,
we've finally made it.
Black Emperor.
How to control the altar's runes?
How do we manipulate these glyphs?
I don't know.
But if it's just
about setting coordinates...
Speak quickly.
It's not impossible.
Give me a moment.
Ten years...
Pang Bo,
we can finally go home.
The moment has finally arrived.
Ye Zi...
This time,
I'm afraid I cannot go with you.
Why?
After all these years,
I've grown accustomed to life here.
Besides,
look at me now—
my Demon Race bloodline has awakened.
If I return to Earth,
I'd feel out of place.
For ten years,
we journeyed from Earth
to the Big Dipper.
We endured so much,
all for this moment.
How can you—
Just listen to me.
Even if we part ways for now,
we can both work hard.
Let's strive to
reconnect our two worlds soon.
Then we can meet anytime.
Plus,
Ziyue and the others can visit you then.
Kid,
are you leaving or not?
The key to departure
lies within those runes.
Those symbols must be arranged
in sequence, placed precisely
where they belong.
Although the central pillar
is missing from this altar,
it doesn't affect opening the void.
In that case,
I'll take my leave first.
But remember this:
I'll be waiting for you over there.
This moment...
I've waited ten years for it.
If I miss this chance,
I might never make it back.
Brother Ape,
everyone here
is in your care now.
Take care.
Big Brother, where are you going?
Nannan doesn't want you to leave.
Nannan, don't cry.
Big Brother has to leave for a while,
to go to a very faraway place.
Be good and listen to Brother Heishui,
and to that black dog too.
Black Emperor,
as for you—
be a proper dog.
Stop causing trouble everywhere.
I don't want to hear stories
in another starfield
about how unreliable you are.
What is your problem?
When others say goodbye,
they're polite,
but you just lecture me.
Because you are...
truly one of a kind.
Ziyue.
Earlier, I said I would
travel across the Big Dipper with you,
searching for a way home.
I thought it would take
a year,
maybe two,
or even ten.
I never expected it to happen
so suddenly.
Yes...
This moment—
I didn't expect it to be this abrupt.
There's still so much I haven't told you.
You once told me that
Earth and the Big Dipper are quite different.
But the starry river above...
It should be the same as here, right?
It's the same.
If we share the same starry sky,
then perhaps one day,
when you truly return to Earth,
following the customs of your world,
we could still gaze at the same stars.
Right?
I will never forget
that on the other side of the stars,
there is a beautiful girl
named Ziyue.
No matter when,
I will never forget you.
And I won't forget you either.
At night,
I will look up at the starry sky,
gazing toward the other side,
and pray for you.
Because I know
you are there.
Ye Fan.
I can testify
that he has absolutely
no connection to the Ruthless One.
Ye Fan,
now that we are friends,
if I ever face hardship in the future,
you will surely rush to my aid
without hesitation, right?
Ziyue...
Take care.
I am about to embark on a long journey.
My homeland lies
beyond the starry sea.
Meeting all of you in this lifetime
has been my greatest fortune.
Farewell.
Goodbye,
my friends.
Those days and nights we fought side-by-side,
sharing life and death together,
are forever etched in my heart.
Farewell, Big Dipper.
This land of crisis
and desperate battles
that forged my spirit.
It was precisely these trials
that allowed me to transform,
rising as a true powerhouse.
Goodbye,
to this unforgettable chapter
of my life.
[Shrouding the Heavens Mini-Guide]
[Bronze Coffin: Nine dragon corpses pull a small coffin drifting through the outer layers of the cosmos. About two meters long and less than two meters wide, it appears ancient and unremarkable. Carved with archaic patterns, its surface is covered in verdigris, bearing the weight of endless ages. Though the coffin seems heavy, it contains a primordial aura that resonates with the Dao, making it surprisingly difficult to shake. Its origins are unknown—no one knows who forged it—only that in ancient times, it set sail alongside the nine dragon corpses. Whether it belongs to this ancient history, no one can say for certain.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™