[Previously]
You've killed my Holy Son and Holy Daughter time and again.
Even if my soul scatters to the winds...
I'll drag you down to the Yellow Springs with me!
Not even an anomaly can withstand this Yin-Yang Death Curse.
If my divine sense perishes...
Then everything is over.
Ye Zi...
I'll stay right here and watch over you.
This secret treasure came from an immortal corpse.
It might be worth the risk.
Miss...
This secret treasure has fused with your primordial spirit.
You mustn't summon it lightly.
Zi Yue...
Don't come any closer!
I won't just stand by and watch you die.
Zi Yue...
You don't have to go this far for me.
They all say...
the Death Curse has no cure.
If this ring can still offer even the slightest chance...
No matter how slim...
I have to try it.
Zi Yue...
You've already done more than enough for me.
If I survive today...
only by sacrificing you...
Even if I manage to live...
I'd regret it for the rest of my life.
But...
Zi Yue...
Have you truly decided to do this?
Brother...
I don't know...
I just can't bear to watch him get devoured by the Death Curse...
while I sit here powerless to do anything.
I can't do it.
Sacrificing myself on impulse right now...
would only distract him.
Before...
I also thought he was just an arrogant rogue cultivator who didn't know his limits.
But time and time again...
he crawls out of situations that should have been certain death.
There's something about him...
that we aristocratic heaven's chosen simply don't have.
Zi Yue...
Put the ring away.
The most important thing you need to do right now...
is to believe in him.
Just like you've always done.
Little Ye Zi, hold on!
If we can't break it...
we'll just exhaust the Death Curse's power.
That's right.
What damn Death Curse?
It already claimed the Yin-Yang Sect Leader.
Now we'll exhaust his Death Curse too.
Exhaust his Death Curse...
and make his death meaningless.
Leaving nothing but regret.
I've exhausted every secret art...
yet I still can't extinguish this fire.
My life essence is draining away at terrifying speed.
Wait...
This is...
The density of this divine marrow...
is actually enough to assail the Immortal Platform!
In that case...
I'll seek life within the jaws of death.
I'll summon the heavenly tribulation!
From within and without...
I'll shatter this curse along with it.
He actually refined all the divine marrow...
In a near-death state...
he triggered the heavenly tribulation...
to use it and break through another level.
It really worked.
The great dragon within the human body is taking form.
Leaping upward...
ascending to form the platform.
Entering the final secret realm.
Only by forsaking the body and forgetting the heart...
Forsaking the body and forgetting the heart...
can one prove the Great Dao.
Today...
I shall temper my body with this roaring thunder!
And with this Death Curse...
I shall temper my Dao!
Enduring the agony of the Death Curse burning within...
while also resisting such a terrifying heavenly tribulation...
He's really pushing it too far.
This is...
A palace net formed by the heavenly tribulation.
And what is this?
The legendary ancient Heavenly Court...
This is no ordinary heavenly punishment!
How can something so bizarre and inexplicable be happening?
A mirror...
A furnace...
They look almost identical to the Void Mirror and the Eternal Universe Furnace.
Why is this happening?
Their strength has always been on par with mine.
Never surpassing it.
Could they all be... different versions of me?
Ye Fan...
So you're really not dead yet.
Yin-Yang Sect disciples, hear my command!
Activate the grand formation!
Do not let him survive the heavenly tribulation!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
The moon rises over the sea.
The Ji family's divine body...
Fortune?
Ye Fan...
is a friend of the Ji family.
You Yin-Yang Sect dogs...
dare to act so brazenly here?
Your Holy Son and Holy Daughter...
have been replaced again?
Our Yin-Yang Sect wants to kill the Saint Body.
This has nothing to do with your Ji family.
Your opponent...
is me.
If you want to touch Ye Fan...
you'll have to get through me first.
I've never seen this divine lamp before.
Finally, a somewhat unique weapon.
These three choices...
are flawless mirrors of my future.
Flawless mirrors of my future.
As long as I merge with one of them...
I can survive.
But if I become someone else's path...
would I still be myself?
My friends are fighting desperately for me...
My brothers are battling to the death without retreat.
What they're waiting for...
is definitely not this cold, illusory shadow.
So that's it...
This trial is...
me contending with myself for so long.
Me contending with myself for so long.
I'd rather be myself.
Using the Mother Qi of all things as the catalyst...
drawing ten thousand laws into one.
The cauldron is complete!
This is...
the Immortal Platform realm.
The Desolate Ancient Saint Body...
has actually broken into the Immortal Platform!
And this cauldron...
has even advanced to a Saint Lord-grade weapon.
After enduring heavenly tribulation again and again...
it has already interwoven its own Dao marks.
Ye Fan...
Zi Yue...
It's over now.
I knew it.
A troublemaker like you...
wouldn't die so easily.
Brother Hao Yue...
I'll leave Zi Yue in your care.
Yin-Yang Sect...
You bunch of scum who only know how to kick people when they're down.
You've tried to kill me again and again...
and even harmed my friends and family.
Since he's just entered the Immortal Platform...
everyone attack together!
Now...
Turn to ashes for me!
Holy Son...
Saint Body Ye Fan...
Only this many people came out to welcome me?
Then the rest of you...
I'll go invite personally.
Or you can come out on your own...
and line up to die.
Ignorant fools.
Is the Yin-Yang Sect a place someone like you can barge into?
An immortal legacy...
is not something an ant like you can shake.
You're simply courting death.
Since you're so eager to go down and accompany that old bastard...
I'll show mercy.
and let you reunite with him.
Today...
I shall use your blood...
to announce to the world...
Mother Qi of All Things Cauldron...
shatter their city for me!
From this day forth...
in the Central Continent...
there will be no more Yin-Yang Sect.
There will be no more Yin-Yang Sect.
[Story Recap]
This episode is titled:
Ever since Ye Fan boarded the Nine Dragons Interstellar Express...
and arrived in the Northern Dipper...
he actively participated in the archaeological excavation of the Azure Emperor's tomb,
the extraction and research of Mother Qi of All Things,
the ecological restoration of the Primordial Ancient Mine,
and the systematic extraction of Purple Mountain crude oil
in the Desolate Ancient Forbidden Land,
along with risk assessment for these major projects.
Finally, with the support of Mentor Jiang,
he graduated with outstanding results
from the Desolate Ancient Saint Physique Department,
which hadn't produced a single graduate in ten thousand years.
He even obtained his Four Extremes certificate.
But recently...
perhaps because Ye Fan saved that fox on the snowy mountain,
even the sauce-plate ducks represented by the Little Peng King...
can no longer pose any threat to him.
Even the Point King’s Imperial Armament...
nearly got used to sink the Central Continent, and after that...
the Northern Dipper stock market has been fluctuating wildly,
leaving nothing but wailing across the land.
So...
a certain big player decided
to send Wang Teng — a second-year Immortal Platform graduate
with the potential to become a Great Emperor —
into the fray.
They plan to acquire Ye Fan’s rumored girlfriend,
the Origin Spirit Body Ji Zi Yue,
to pump up the stock price,
and along the way, deal with
Ye — the unstable factor — Fan.
At the same time,
with the full support of the entire Yin-Yang Sect,
amid a wave of cheering bullet comments,
Ye Fan successfully entered the Immortal Platform graduate program.
Thus begins the battle of the strongest graduates.
Stay tuned for
the theatrical sequel.
In a place very, very far away...
called Earth...
Big brother, where are you going?
I will look up at the starry sky...
and send you my blessings.
The strong reign supreme in this world...
I alone am honored!
With just you?
You think you can make me lose?
Four secrets united as one!
I'll send you on your way.
[Shrouding the Heavens – Knowledge Mini Guide]
[Immortal Platform Realm:  The final secret realm of the human body—profound and mysterious. Cultivating within this realm is extremely difficult. Each step forward is like ascending to a higher heaven, and the difference in strength between each level is comparable to the gap between entire major realms. Each level of the Immortal Platform can be divided into nine smaller stages, categorized as early, middle, and peak phases. The first level focuses on condensing and strengthening divine consciousness. From the second level onward, other hidden potentials of the body are gradually unlocked. As for how many levels the Immortal Platform ultimately has, no one knows—it can only be pursued through continuous ascent.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™