[Previously]
Saint Physique...
today, you walk...
We must stop her.
Gain time for Ye Fan.
Success?
No...
This feels like a dead star.
Just a jade pendant...
yet it contains Lunar Saint Power.
Return to the homeland.
Do not bury bones in a foreign land.
Could his hometown be the Ziwei Star?
This hole...
Test it.
So the Five-Colored Altar does not need the Nine Dragons Coffin...
to traverse the star field.
Inside this stone coffin...
what is contained?
Return to the homeland.
Do not bury bones in a foreign land.
So cold...
What kind of place is this?
No good.
If this continues...
before we find the path...
we will freeze into ice cubes.
Nine-Colored Saint Flame...
Even it cannot withstand this cold.
This is...
The Primordial Yin Force from the creation of heaven and earth!
The Ultimate Yin Force from the dawn of creation!
The Taiyin Scripture!
One of the Two Mother Scriptures of the Human Race.
Even Great Emperors of old...
benefited immensely from observing it.
Though this scripture is incomplete...
possessing the Immortal Platform Scroll is sufficient.
Now...
Taiyin and Taiyang gather...
converging on the Immortal Platform.
Perfectly complementing Yin and Yang.
Evolving the legendary Supreme Immortal Platform Art.
Taiyin and Taiyang...
which is weaker, which is stronger?
Yin and Yang coexist...
and the world shall crown you King.
Taiyin and Taiyang...
Two extremes of power.
How overbearing.
These two...
how can they coexist?
Two forces merging...
results only in conflict and self-destruction.
No wonder that Ancient Saint...
cultivated himself mad...
becoming a Human Devil.
The Dao of Heaven and Earth...
uses Yin and Yang to create all things.
The principle of human life...
uses Yin and Yang to nourish the hundred bones.
I shall start from here.
Taiji...
refers to before Heaven and Earth separated...
when the primordial Qi was a混沌 mass...
that is the Great Beginning.
The Great One.
The Dao is the essence...
forced into a name...
it is called the Great One.
I am the Great One.
My body is the Dao.
The tribulation of breaking into the Second Heaven of the Immortal Platform...
come!
Come good!
At my current realm...
if I return to the Big Dipper Starfield...
I shall fear no Holy Lands.
I wonder...
in this vast universe...
how much time has passed.
Is everyone...
doing well?
Did they encounter difficulties...
and turn misfortune into fortune?
Or are they still rushing about endlessly to grow stronger?
Big Black Dog...
what are you staring at?
That unscrupulous guy...
is probably causing trouble and collecting pets again.
You better take good care of Little Nannan...
don't let her be bullied again.
Also...
Ziyue...
Right now...
are you also gazing at the starry sky?
I will most likely be like cosmic dust...
floating forever...
until the end of my life.
It is impossible...
to ever see anyone again.
Return to the homeland.
Do not bury bones in a foreign land.
Return to the homeland...
Send me back to the Ziwei Ancient Star.
Bestow upon you Fortune...
abandoning me as you leave.
A curse for a hundred lifetimes.
Rather than drifting in the vast cosmos...
I might as well go to Ziwei first...
and seek another path.
If Senior can open...
a path to the Ziwei Ancient Starfield...
that would be ideal.
Ziwei Ancient Emperor Star.
The aura of an Ancient Great Emperor.
Success!
I have arrived at the source of life in the Ziwei Starfield.
Th-th-Th-This...
Where did this demon spawn come from...
daring to run wild at my Orthodoxy of the Mysterious Gate?
There are cultivators here?
This junior...
did not intend to offend.
Say no more.
Destroying my mountain gate is a grave crime.
I sentence you to servitude...
guarding my mountain gate for three years.
After the term...
you may leave.
Do you accept?
Not old...
but quite the mouth.
Did your master not teach you...
the way to treat guests?
You...
How dare you be impudent!
Brazen wild cultivator!
Daring to run wild before the Eight Sceneries Palace!
Eight Sceneries Palace...
Legend has it...
that is Laozi's Daoist field in the Profound Capital Purple Mansion.
Could it be that after Laozi left Hangu Pass...
he came here?
If I could meet this Ancient Sage...
perhaps...
I can find the way home.
May I ask, Daoist friend...
is the Lord of the Eight Sceneries Palace...
Senior Li Er?
Li Er? What Li Er?
Who doesn't know...
that the Master of the Eight Sceneries Palace...
is my elder brother...
Yin Tiande!
My elder brother...
closed his gate for merely a year...
and already there are those eyeing the Eight Sceneries Palace?
Can't you see...
what kind of place this is?
Full of wild ravings...
Laozi certainly wouldn't have a disciple like this.
This cauldron...
it contains the aura of the Mother Qi of All Things.
You possess Xuanhuang Essence...
Perfect.
My eldest brother wishes to refine...
a Heaven-Earth Xuanhuang Exquisite Pagoda.
Your cauldron...
arrives at a most opportune time.
Excellent, excellent.
This treasure is too good...
Sometimes, it is also quite troublesome.
Today, you have good luck.
I shall keep this cauldron...
and spare your dog life.
This cauldron...
has already acknowledged its master.
I am afraid it cannot fulfill your wish, friend.
I gave you a chance...
and you did not cherish it.
You court death, you wretch.
Today...
I shall teach you the destruction of body and spirit.
I thought you were just a naive Dao boy...
but you are an old demon.
No wonder you are so overbearing.
Even beating a dog requires looking at its master.
Hand over the Mother Qi Cauldron...
for my elder brother to use in refining his pagoda.
Those who covet my cauldron...
already have grass three feet high on their graves.
If you want it...
you had better have the life to take it.
Purple Qi comes from the East!
Vast and mighty, thirty thousand miles!
The inheritance of Laozi...
I have washed my body in Undying Phoenix Blood.
Today, I will let you witness...
what an eternally imperishable, ultimate physical body is!
Undying Phoenix Blood...
Truly rare.
However...
you are having a bad day today...
meeting me.
Just look at your Vajra Indestructible Body...
how many of my Seals can it withstand?
Aside from my eldest brother...
you are the first person whose physique can contend with mine.
What constitution are you?
The specific constitution matters not...
what matters...
is oneself.
Utter arrogance!
Today, I will show you the true...
Supreme Mystical Arts of the Profound Capital Cave.
One Qi Transforms into Three Purities!
The Taiqing Formless Body!
The Three Ancestors Sever the Dao!
One Qi Transforms into Three Purities!
Every move is lethal, vicious to the extreme.
Since that is the case...
I cannot blame you anymore.
What "One Qi Transforms into Three Purities"?...
I think you barely manage even "One Purity."
Claiming to be the Orthodox Mystical Gate...
yet acting...
like robbers who kill for treasure...
bullying the weak with force...
is this the Dao of your Eight Sceneries Palace?
Suppress!
My eldest brother...
though in closed-door seclusion...
left behind a sacred artifact.
This single weapon...
is enough to crush you dead!
Vajra Bead!
Wait...
This precious bead...
although it has birthed divine patterns...
and become a King-level divine weapon...
it should not be Laozi's Vajra Bead.
It is just far stronger than the imitation...
I obtained at Shaking Light.
Power of Taiyin...
using softness to overcome hardness.
Transform!
Using this bead on you is a waste.
I want to enter the Eight Sceneries Palace.
Come here and lead the way.
No.
My eldest brother will avenge me.
Your life...
belongs to us.
I originally intended to spare your life...
what a pity.
ETO...
The master of the Eight Sceneries Palace...
though not Laozi...
should have some clues.
I should still investigate...
and hope to find a way home.
To think there are Taiqing Restrictions...
Fine.
Since the Eight Sceneries Palace cannot be entered...
I will go down the mountain...
and seek another path.
Why is the city in such chaos?
An evil star fell from beyond the sky upon the Immortal Palace...
Blood-colored demonic clouds obscure the purple dome.
Could history be repeating itself?
In the past, Barbarian Saints came from the wilderness to save us...
What history? What scene?
What should we do this time?
In the era after the Great Emperor's silence...
the Ancient Races invaded Ziwei.
Wherever they went...
they frantically absorbed the essence of all living beings.
Previously, there were Ancient Races...
who descended from the sky...
and crashed onto the Eight Sceneries Palace.
They might have been the vanguard of the Ancient Races.
The Ancient Races are coming!
Hide quickly!
Quick, go!
Run!
The Ancient Races are here!
My accidental crash landing...
was mistaken by them for the Ancient Races.
It seems that past event was terrifyingly abnormal...
they still haven't forgotten it to this day.
When the Ancient Races come, no one survives.
At my current realm...
as long as I do not confront them head-on...
I should have the power to protect myself.
Girls, do not be afraid.
Come quickly into Big Bro Li Tian's embrace.
Big Bro promises...
no danger will harm you.
Girls, don't leave!
I think the biggest danger here is you.
What do you know?
I genuinely want to save them.
The Ancient Races are about to arrive...
the entire Ziwei Star...
cannot escape calamity.
Ziwei is the Emperor Star...
with profound foundations.
How could there be no one to resist?
Emperor Star...
all the major sects of Ziwei...
are just selfish, self-preserving scoundrels.
Who cares about these common people?
Is there no way to stop this disaster?
For many years, no Saint has appeared on Ziwei...
and the Extreme Dao Imperial Weapons...
vanished with the passing of the Great Emperors.
This is Ziwei's destined tribulation.
However, recently outside the city...
a mysterious, unfathomable Saint appeared.
But he...
remains motionless like a corpse.
If this Saint acts...
perhaps...
he can save Ziwei.
Mysterious Saint...
Therefore...
I still urge this Daoist friend...
if you lack the power to protect yourself...
go seek that Saint's...
protection immediately.
Old Madman, Big Bro...
Sixth Bro...
The Ancient Races this time...
are truly descending upon Ziwei Star.
Then we...
Us...
must not clash with them head-on.
Just guard the mountain gate.
The secret treasure in the depths of the North Sea...
is our race's top priority.
Yes.
Stop messing around.
Keep your voice down.
If you anger the Saint...
who will protect us?
Old Madman, Big Bro...
daring to call a Saint that...
are you tired of living?
Come back quickly!
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
This Tianyuan City...
how did it turn into a desert in an instant?
The Ancient Races...
have descended!
History is repeating itself.
Saint...
Save us!
Run!
The Ancient Races are attacking!
Help!
If I act now...
I might struggle to get away.
But...
no one can sit by and watch their kin being slaughtered.
Saint...
Save us!
Don't panic...
run that way!
Such terrifying pressure...
Could it be an Ancient King of the Ancient Races?
Old Madman, Big Bro...
I know not why Old Madman, Big Bro...
remains motionless...
but since I am here...
you wretches shall not harm him.
Ants!
Although our strength is not fully restored...
you are not an ant who can stop us.
This cultivator is tired of living...
How can he fight so many Ancient Races?
Who does he think he is?
An Ancient Great Emperor?
Old Madman, Big Bro...
why are you like one in meditation?
Awaken!
Old Madman, Big Bro...
What is happening?
Did the Saint fall so quickly?
The Saint has fallen...
no one can save us now.
Old Madman, Big Bro...
What Human Race Saint...
is just so-so.
This is...
this silver aura...
could it be...
The Power of Taiyin!
Old Madman, Big Bro has awakened!
The Saint is about to act!
We are saved!
Courting death!
What is happening?
The Human Race has such a strong expert?
Interesting.
So Old Madman, Big Bro...
was using the Power of Taiyin to temper his old body...
returning to youth!
This youthful appearance...
I haven't used it in a long time.
Human Race...
You are alone...
daring to block us, three Ancient Kings?
Do you think you are an Ancient Emperor?
I have been mad for a thousand years...
I have seen too much rise and fall.
Tian Xuan is gone...
and my fellow disciples are no more.
Six thousand years ago...
I lost once...
This time...
I will not retreat.
Power of Taiyin...
Can it block my Divine Phoenix?
Old Madman, Big Bro has become stronger...
instantly...
slaying an Ancient King!
This person...
is far stronger than we imagined.
Old thing...
I think you can't even divide your spirit!
Die!
Suppress!
The Ancient Races are retreating.
We are saved!
The Saint is too powerful...
just like in the past, driving them away again.
Now, the lives of Ziwei...
have been saved once more.
Many thanks, Saint.
Never expected that after parting at Saint Cliff...
we would reunite with you.
Greetings, Senior.
It is you.
How did you come to Ziwei?
This...
is a long story.
This junior is from Earth...
originally intending to use the Five-Colored Altar to return home...
but the star crossing failed.
Difficult, difficult, difficult...
Without cosmic coordinates...
I cannot reach the Earth you speak of.
Thousand-Handed God-Demon...
Once it awakens...
endless lives will perish.
Surely, carnage will blanket the wilds.
It is not over yet.
What?
Senior...
Did you cross the starfield...
having foreseen this tribulation?
It seems what is meant to happen...
will still happen.
That is...
the Purple Copper Warship I encountered in the cosmos.
The Ancient Races...
have been devouring life essence since the Primordial Era.
It happens every tens of thousands of years...
this is practically an iron law.
Even though in between...
there were powerful existences like the Sun Sacred Emperor who stopped them...
destiny cannot be changed.
Let alone a Junior Saint...
it is difficult.
But fortunately...
my Golden Crow race is self-preserving.
There are so many mortals here...
once those Ancient Races are satiated...
they will naturally leave this place.
What is inside that coffin?
What kind of existence...
is sealed within it?
Inside this coffin...
is the aura of a Great Saint!
Draining the essence within a radius of hundreds of thousands of miles...
plants and creatures are utterly dead.
It seems some Ancient Kings...
have fully awakened.
Little friend.
This battle is no longer something you can involve yourself in.
Go do what you must do.
Senior...
What are you planning to do?
Senior!
Everyone, leave quickly!
Human...
You know you face certain death...
yet you still dare to stop us?
Truly commendable courage.
This Ziwei Starfield...
is merely the first step we take upon this sea of stars.
Immediately following...
the Eternal Starfield...
the Big Dipper Starfield...
and all starfields containing life...
we will...
ensure they are...
silenced.
At that time...
all vibrant lives...
will turn into flesh and blood for my race.
And you...
are merely the first batch...
of sacrificial offerings for this feast.
How can the lives of billions of beings...
be casually slaughtered by your Ancient Race?
Today...
with me in Ziwei...
you shall not advance a single step!
No matter how many of your Ancient Race come...
I will kill them all!
Bad...
Old Madman, Big Bro...
is actually fighting two Great Saints alone...
and over a dozen Ancient Kings!
The power of a Great Saint... I cannot contend with it now.
What trump cards do I have left to use?
Right...
The Black Gourd...
legend says that in the Ancient Era...
it slew Ancient Kings.
Not good...
Old Madman, Big Bro is in danger!
I can't care about that anymore.
I have to risk it.
Treasure...
please turn around.
Gourd transforms into a Dao Sword!
Sever!
To think there is a weapon leftover from the Ancient Battlefield...
Such terrifying power.
But this is where your tricks end.
Just die, all of you!
Six Paths Reincarnation...
Samsara Delusion...
Activate!
Six Paths Reincarnation Fist!
Since you have always longed for immortality...
then today, I...
specifically...
will send you into Reincarnation!
Kill him!
Six Paths Reincarnation...
evil ghosts shall be punished!
Open your eyes and look...
this is where you belong.
The eternity you pursue...
relies on sucking the essence and blood of others.
But my Human Race...
has thrived for tens of millions of years...
not through slaughter...
but through the resilience...
passed down through generations.
How can I allow you fiends...
to sever the roots of my civilization?
Your sins are heavy...
you owe a debt of blood...
go to hell...
and repay it slowly!
So that's how it is.
The Six Paths contain the true killing intent of the Six Paths.
This fist technique is truly domineering.
Alone against many demons...
just watching the Saint...
makes my blood boil.
Never expected...
the Human Race...
to still have such combat strength in this world.
Retreat.
You are not his match.
Human...
You are strong.
Extremely strong.
Terrifyingly strong.
But today...
Ziwei Star...
will surely be destroyed.
Bad...
That multi-armed monster has awakened!
Even if I die here today...
you, a ship full of Ancient Kings...
will be buried with me!
Annihilated completely!
Lowly Human Race...
yet you dare be so rampant despite being our former food?
Insolent!
Senior is trading injury for injury...
with the Thousand-Hand God-Demon!
Break, all of you!
Die!
Thousand Hands Shatter Soul Art!
Bad...
The formation is broken!
These Ancient Creatures...
each has the cultivation of the First Heaven of the Immortal Platform.
I need to find a way to repair the formation...
to buy Senior a sliver of opportunity.
The Mother Qi of All Things is heavy as a mountain...
unbreakable.
Although my current cultivation is insufficient...
the Mother Qi is a sacred item of the Great Emperor...
perhaps I can use the Cauldron to try!
Don't come any closer!
Human...
You are a respectable opponent.
But the rising trend of my race...
cannot be stopped by anyone.
Four Symbols Tribulation Annihilation!
Burial of your Human Race's destiny!
Just die!
[Shrouding the Heavens: Mini Knowledge Guide]
[Taigu Clan Cultivation Realms (Ancient Race Realm System)- The Taigu clans cultivate through a mysterious system similar to that of humans,
but the names used for each realm are different. Because the Taigu era is far too ancient, no one can clearly explain the exact names of the realms today. People only roughly know that when members of the Taigu clans reach the realm equivalent to Immortal Platform (Xiantai), they are honored as “Kings.” Among the powerful beings of ancient times, some were also called Kings, while others were known as Ancestor Kings. Just how powerful these Kings truly were remains uncertain; some speculate they were comparable to the ancient Sages.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™