♪ Hear war banners whipping in my ears ♪
♪ See fate coldly waiting for me to kneel and beg ♪
♪ Like a teardrop lost in the vast sea ♪
♪ I'll shatter storms, thunder, and lightning ♪
♪ No master, no disciple, no law, no heaven ♪
♪ I'll face them one by one ♪
♪ I cross heavens and earth, declaring to eternity ♪
♪ I charge forward, leaping into the storm ♪
♪ I ask the immortals: what's hell to endure? ♪
♪ Just fight till I'm old ♪
♪ Born to die, die to live ♪
♪ All to guard the common folk ♪
♪ I laugh with blade raised to the sky ♪
♪ Watch stars fall like rain, dawn ablaze ♪
♪ Through cycles vast, my heart shines clear ♪
♪ Even if waves tower high ♪
♪ I've cultivated a hundred thousand years ♪
♪ The long road—hope will rise again ♪
♪ All laws unite; one leaf blocks the mortal sky ♪
- Shrouding the Heavens -
(Adapted from the novel 'Shrouding the Heavens' by Chen Dong, all rights reserved by Xingyue Chenshi)
[PREVIOUSLY]
Episode 135
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
So many Dragon Transformations—
even half-step mighty fallen.
Your methods are terrifying.
Heaven will punish you.
I only have half a year left—
maybe negatives cancel.
In that case, suppress them all.
It's him!
He planned it all!
Old thief—cunning!
He stole my cauldron, said support him and let him hold it a while.
Shameless brat!
You said support you holding it this time.
This old guy's near death—
let's help him along.
No!
My Wheel Sea is ruined,
but Dao Palace remains.
Still got a century or two.
Relax—
I won't kill you.
This place suits retirement.
Why not
suppress here for a hundred years?
You
can't!
No!
Help!
Good.
Satisfying.
Brother Ye.
I was blinded by rage and fooled by him.
You suppressed him in the latrine—
this avenges
not just
our Jiang family, but little Princess Tingting.
I'll tell her your good intentions now.
[I'll tell her your good intentions now.]
Farewell.
You think you can escape?
I spared you once for the God King's grace.
But you abused family power, growing bolder.
Spare me—
Grandpa offers sources and saint weapons!
Little uncle!
We're blood kin—
beg for me!
Tell me:
who's behind Assassin Dynasty hunting me?
Brother Ye—
honestly, I only know Wan Chu and Zi Fu saints.
Let me go—
I'll spy inside.
Any news, I'll report first.
Deal?
Yichen—come, come!
Good nephew.
Up you get.
A thousand years is too long—
he'd be dust.
Quick—
five hundred years.
Don't fear.
Eat shit!
There!
If you survive five hundred years,
you'll achieve enlightenment.
That Jiang kid—
won't suffocate, right?
Why worry?
Latrine life's his luck.
Make a treasure map, let diggers find him.
Too vicious.
Big mess this time—
lay low here.
Legend says this was the immortal's lair—
head of thirteen bandits.
Good.
Cultivate in seclusion.
Be hermits a while.
[Cultivation Ground of the Leader of the Thirteen Heavenly Demons]
Miss Yaochi grand event?
No Queen Mother's peaches.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Just stars.
Big brother—
what are you watching?
Where I was born.
If you miss someone, look at the stars.
Maybe
big brother watches stars thinking of someone.
Your family?
Where's Nannan's family?
Nannan, don't sad—
big brother is your family.
Earth holds longing,
Big Dipper now ties.
When time comes,
some reluctance.
Yaochi event nears—
invite Brother Ye and friends.
Yaochi could send envoy.
Why saintess personally?
Brother Ye is perceptive.
I'll be blunt:
Yaochi holds stone kings—
Queen Mother and Source Master's odd stones.
Seal time ends.
Need current Source Master with top source arts to reseal.
Hence this bold request.
Yaochi once aided me.
Sealing the stone kings—
I,
Ye Fan, take full duty.
Within Yaochi, we'll protect Brother Ye.
But outside is unpredictable.
If you have concerns,
Yaochi won't force you.
Rumors say
after returning to the holy city,
holy land geniuses formed an anonymous group
called
Slayer Alliance.
Yaochi gathers all talents—
perfect to see who's in this Slayer Alliance.
Thanks for the warning, fairy.
I, have my ways.
Grateful for the sealing favor.
Peaches are ripe—
taste them at the event.
[Entrance to the Holy Land of Yaoshi]
The Saint Body came!
Heard he slew many powers, even two saints.
Dares show up.
Last time,
you lost to him.
Yes.
Must be him.
No one else has the skill or guts.
If Saint Body heals dao wounds [Holy Lord of the Primordial Beginning - Immortal Platform Realm] and enters Sendai, East Desolate shifts big. [Holy Lord of the Primordial Beginning - Immortal Platform Realm]
Yeah.
Bigger than God King Jiang's return.
Act when ready.
This trip won't be calm.
Kid,
watch out.
Trouble!
That saint ape broke into the peach garden!
Sorry, Brother Ye—
neglect.
Back soon.
[Peach Garden of Immortality — Sacred Land of the Jade Pool]
Saint ape—stop!
Saint ape.
After you fulfill the pact, peaches are yours.
Reneging?
I agreed to irrigate with king blood,
but it won't seep into stone king.
Not my fault.
Give peaches—
save my kin.
Yaochi has a plan:
suppress source.
Source families master suppression.
Master Ouyang nears Source Earth.
We'll solve it.
Elder flatters.
[Ouyang Juan — Aristocratic Clan of Source Arts] Our source family [Ouyang Juan — Aristocratic Clan of Source Arts]
will try.
[Ouyang Juan — Aristocratic Clan of Source Arts]
Ordinary stubborn stone—
no need for master.
That old fart again.
Not embarrassed from last loss?
Works?
My patience is limited.
Told you—
apprentice half-trained.
This stone—
I need just thirty percent.
His suppression
far surpasses Nan Gong Qi.
Source family
deep indeed.
Just thirty percent solves Yaochi's crisis.
Master Ouyang—
lives up to Source Earth name.
But deep roots mean old thinking—
block, don't guide.
Trouble.
This—
Master Ouyang, this—
what's this?
You
dare!
The stone I suppressed
is Sacred Spirit clan's nine-orifice stone man.
Don't you know
this stone if born,
brings world chaos—
no escape.
Ancient saints preached to it—
birth in five thousand years.
Then you'll know it's benevolent.
Benevolent?
Ridiculous.
No more delays—
give the peaches.
I'll try.
Who do you think you are?
This stone—
we could suppress,
but it brings disaster.
That's five thousand years away.
Ye Fan, heir to Source Master, sealed odd stones for Yaochi before.
Saint ape—try again?
You.
I owe you for cutting me free.
You're alright—
a friend.
I'll do my best.
Danger inside—
Young Ye, don't overreach
and doom lives.
A Sacred Spirit rivaling emperors emerging—
truly,
the great era comes.
Master—
if he succeeds, our family's reputation suffers.
Let stone king backlash kill him—
then use his arts to suppress it.
Source family tampered with my patterns!
Ye kid—
sacred fetus is birthing!
Let little Nannan try?
Nonsense!
No need.
Ape brother—
watch:
these blocking me block your peaches.
Disrespect my master!
Killing intent toward my friend?
Courting death?
Ape brother—
some blood.
Finish business first.
Sure!
Waste blood anyway.
Old fart—
this debt is noted.
Supreme Mysterious Origin—
eternal life for all.
Source Heaven Art!
Stone king's essence flows via source art
to bottled Nannan.
Black dog thinking again?
Ye Fan—
essence draining!
Don't let it—
Losing essence—no rush.
We're family.
Yaochi's best: indirectly birthed two emperors.
[Indirectly birthed two emperors.]
What?
Slipped.
Big brother—
stone bit me!
Seal!
Done.
(A Secret News from "Shrouding the Heavens")
[The Yaochi Grand Gathering, also known as the Peach Banquet, is hosted by the Sacred Land of Yaochi and convened once every five hundred years. Whenever this grand event begins, lords from all directions arrive, and the world’s strongest gather. The young geniuses and proud talents of the Eastern Wasteland all come to attend.]
[Those who participate in the gathering are given the honor of tasting the spiritual peaches from the Yaochi Peach Garden. This Peach Garden is world-renowned—one of the most famous spiritual roots in all the Eastern Wasteland. For mortals, a single bite of the peach’s flesh can extend life, and for cultivators, it offers immense benefits. It is said that the sacred root of the Yaochi Peach Garden was brought forth from the Forbidden Zone of Life — the Divine Ruins (Shenxu), making it one of the most precious treasures beneath the Undying Divine Medicine itself.]
[In addition to the celestial feast, stone-cutting and source art competitions are also major highlights of the Yaochi Grand Gathering. Yaochi possesses countless mystic stones, and the lineage of the Source Celestial Masters once gifted three Stone Kings to Yaochi—one of which originated from the Purple Mountain’s Immortal Egg, said to seal within it the descendant of an Undying Celestial Emperor.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™