♪ I hear war banners whipping in my ears ♪
♪ I see fate watching coldly, waiting for me to kneel and beg ♪
♪ Like a single tear falling into the sea—so small ♪
♪ Yet I’ll shatter the storm, thunder, and lightning that cage me ♪
♪ No master, no disciple, no laws, no heavens ♪
♪ I’ll face them all, one by one ♪
♪ I cross the heavens and earth, declaring to eternity ♪
♪ I charge forward without looking back, leaping into the storm ♪
♪ I ask the immortals: what hell is there to fear? ♪
♪ It’s just fighting until I grow old ♪
♪ Just fighting until I grow old ♪
♪ Born into death, dying into life ♪
♪ All to guard the common people ♪
♪ I laugh with my blade raised to the heavens ♪
♪ Watch stars fall like rain and dawn burn bright ♪
♪ Through endless cycles of rebirth, my heart remains clear ♪
♪ Even if monstrous waves tower over me ♪
♪ I’ve cultivated for a hundred thousand years ♪
♪ The road is long, but hope will shine again ♪
♪ All laws return to one—a single leaf in the mortal dust can block the sky ♪
- Shrouding the Heavens -
(Adapted from the novel 'Shrouding the Heavens' by Chen Dong, all rights reserved by Xingyue Chenshi)
[PREVIOUSLY ]
We’re already here
Might as well go deeper while we can
And hunt for some rare treasures and immortal troves
Shut it, dead dog
Hurry up
A coffin hidden in this peerless death zone
Could it be the corpse of an ancient Great Emperor?
Ye Fan
Dad...
Mom...
Just a wisp of aura from this place pulled me into an illusion
He said
This is a saint of the ancient human race
We must never let him out
Save me, Ye Fan!
Episode 138
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Ye Fan
Come find this place—now!
Or I’ll kill her
Remember
Come alone
Using Liu Yiyi as a hostage
And he knows how to use a phone
Could it be...
Someone who came to this world with me?
This place...
Lava hiding ice within
If I’m right
It’s in the Central Region of Eastern Wilderness—
Fire Demon Ridge
Like a dog
This Emperor will torment him to death
Still...
The spot my human pet’s beast pet found
Is seriously ominous
This place
Once gave birth to a Fire Race Sacred Spirit
His power reached the heavens, rivaling ancient emperors
But rumor says
He was ultimately slain by the Ruthless Great Emperor
After his death
The terrain here began circulating source energy
Filled with layer upon layer of restrictions
Brother Ye
I’ll slaughter our way in with you
Yeah
If worse comes to worst
I’ll call Big Bandit and the bros
And drag Old Man Tu Tian along
We’ll all go together
It’s useless
They’ll definitely be prepared
Charging in like that
Is the same as telling them to kill the hostage
Ye Fan
This person...
Do you really have to save her?
Yiyi...
Next time we meet
You’ll already be a Divine Bridge cultivator
We’ll definitely meet again
She came from the same place as me
I can’t let her die
Fine
Since
You’ve decided to save her
Then this little immortal
Will reluctantly lend you a hand
I’m actually pretty curious
About people from your hometown
The one who kidnapped Liu Yiyi
Is obviously coming for me
And clearly weaker than I am
But this trap is deadly
No need to drag the others into danger
You’ve been tailing me the whole way
Come out already
Knew you’d try to come alone, kid
If this Emperor didn’t keep an eye on you
You think you’d be fine?
Even Your Majesty came in person?
You just want to tag along and snag a beast pet, huh?
Why are we turning back now?
Ignorant brat
This is the Myriad Luo Gate
The entrance to Fire Demon Ridge
Once you step through, there’s no way out
Unless you’re an ancient Great Emperor
No one can enter and leave freely
A formation pattern master like Your Majesty
Still fears a restriction like this?
Kid
Don’t try to sweet-talk me
This Myriad Luo Gate?
I’m not going in with you
Put
Put me down!
We’re already here
Let’s go
Together we’ll storm right in
Ye Fan
Ye Fan!
Black Sovereign
He really went off to play hero
Brother Blackwater
Protect little Nannan well
Holy Ape
Let’s go give him a hand
Good!
[Fire Demon Peak – Ten-Thousand-Li Pass]
You actually dared to show up
Courting death, scum
Ye has arrived
Why hide like cowards, everyone?
Holy Body
You’re finally here
Ye Fan, run!
Yiyi...
[The Ten-Thousand-Blade Saintess, Zhao Yanran]
Holy body
At last we meet
[The Ten-Thousand-Blade Saintess, Zhao Yanran]
[Heir to the Northern Plains’ Golden Lineage: Jin Chixiao]
Coming alone to the banquet of blades
Being a hero isn’t that easy
[Heir to the Northern Plains’ Golden Lineage: Jin Chixiao]
Don’t end up
Sliced into a dead bear instead
[Holy Son of the Great Yan Sect — Xiang Yifei]
Brother Ye
We’ve known each other for a while
I’ve even prepared your gravestone
Today the cauldron of the Mother of All Things, your enlightenment weapon
Will belong to us
Only this many of you?
Thirteen Holy Sons
Not nearly enough for me to cut down
And since you’re all here
One gravestone won’t be enough
Laughable
Still don’t understand your situation?
After today
I’ll hang your head on the city gate
To mourn our fallen Holy Sons in the afterlife
Let me remind you
Your Holy Lord and Holy Son just died recently
If you perish here too
Wan Chu Sacred Ground
Will go down in history forever
You—
Talking big when death is at your door
[Li Duan, Jiguang Holy Son Candidate]
I’ve already killed thirteen from the Holy Alliance
Today
[Li Duan, Jiguang Holy Son Candidate]
Your life is mine
Good
Since everyone’s here
Long ago the Divine King
Slaughtered thirteen Holy Lords in a single night
Today
Come at me all at once
I’ll send all thirteen Holy Sons on their way
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
This is the Heavenly Demon Blood Chest of our Holy Son
You murdered our Holy Son
And stole our supreme treasure
If you walk out alive today
It’ll take a miracle
A miracle?
Then today I’ll slaughter all of you
And ascend to godhood with your blood
Suppress!
Isn’t this the freeloader from my Li Fire Furnace?
You still haven’t paid your bill
Ye Fan
We lured you into this trap
Of course we’re fully prepared
This formation was built solely to kill you
Accept your death
What?!
My vision phenomenon—
The world knows the Saint Physique’s phenomenon
Can slay immortals against all odds
But after passing the Myriad Luo Gate
The phenomenon can’t be used for a short time
This is bad
Even if I wanted to lay down a Great Emperor formation
This place has too many restrictions
And so many people watching
With so many eyes on me
Breaking out won’t be easy
No problem
Just kill every last enemy and we’re good
My turn
Break!
Yiyi!
This never ends
What the hell is Ye Fan playing at?
Ye Fan
All thirteen of us
Are Holy Son-level geniuses
No one has ever escaped
From thirteen heaven-chosen at once
Hand over the cauldron
And die obediently
I might let her live
You bastard!
Open your eyes wide
And watch him die!
Holy Sons, Holy Lords—
Our great vengeance is finally avenged!
Ye Fan!
You little bastard
What do we do now?!
Fine
You all want this cauldron so badly?
Then today
I, Ye,
Gift it to you all!
Everyone
Don’t fall for this thief’s trick!
Kill Ye Fan first
Then take the cauldron!
Secure the cauldron first!
We elders will guard
Go claim the cauldron!
Yes!
Honored elders
Don’t let him fool you!
Looks like every last one of you really showed up
Thank you all for coming to the show
Now please enjoy
A genuine miracle
He’s triggering a breakthrough tribulation?!
Perfect
This is exactly
How heavenly lightning should be used!
Oh no!
Black Sovereign!
Save her!
You really are black-hearted
You dragged me into the tribulation too!
He’s crossing a lightning tribulation!
Run!
Everyone
No need to rush off!
Let’s all transcend together!
Won’t that be fun?
Ye Fan, you demon!
Why are you even having a tribulation?!
Ye Fan, you’re ruthless!
Do you know how many Holy Sons
And mighty elders are here?!
Who you are doesn’t matter
You set a death trap for me
So be ready to die with it
Friends
Let us transcend together
And ascend as immortals!
Brother Ye!
Ye Fan!
My human pet’s beast pets are all dead
As expected, everyone triggered their own tribulations
You almost got me killed too
Ye Fan
You alright?
I’m fine
Yiyi
I dragged you into this—I’m sorry
So many Holy Sons and elders from sacred grounds fell here
Even though this place is hidden and special
In half a month at most
The whole world will know
This is bad—terrible!
Little Nannan!
What happened to little Nannan?!
She—
After you left
The Yin-Yang Cult broke through the oasis restrictions
Big brother...
Little Nannan!
A Holy Lord-level powerhouse...
Actually...
Tell Ye Fan
If he wants her alive
I’ll be waiting at Yaochi
So many Holy Lords fell at Wanlong Nest
Even if he doesn’t know what happened here yet
Nothing will stop him from coming after you
What are you going to do?
Exactly
They’re clearly forcing you out into the open
Don’t worry
I won’t walk blindly into danger
[Yaoci Holy Land]
Big brother...
Ye has arrived
Release the girl
[Heaven-Shroud Dungeon Hall]
Heavenly Tribulation
Tribulations have been rare since ancient times
Only peerless geniuses breaking through
Will draw heaven’s lightning
To block their path
When tribulation descends
Endless seas of lightning
Blot out the sky and swallow the earth
Able to shatter mountains and rivers
Like the apocalypse itself
Among them
The tribulation drawn by the Primordial Saint Physique
Is especially terrifying
It can even summon nine layers of heavenly punishment
Wherever a Saint Physique tribulation strikes
Thunder roars for thousands of zhang
Purple light pierces the firmament
Within its range
It triggers a chain reaction
Anyone touched by this calamity
No matter where they flee
Distance means nothing
They must endure it together
The chain effect of a Saint Physique’s Four Poles perfection tribulation
Even Holy Lord-level experts
Cannot withstand it
Legend says
The Beginningless Great Emperor
Born with the Innate Saint Physique Dao Embryo
Was constantly struck by lightning back then
Whenever he transcended
Anyone caught in it
Faced total annihilation
The Beginningless Great Emperor
Even created special
Deceiving Heaven formation patterns
To keep his tribulations from harming the innocent
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™