FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
You ate my spirit beast!
Then become my spirit beast!
Divine sense...
- I'll burn your illusory Three Thousand Realms!
Spent force!
All together!
Afraid to face the Ji divine body head-on...
resorting to dirty tricks!
Better off dead!
This seal... it's the Human King Seal!
Heaven Overturning Seal
and Mountain Embracing Seal!
I feel...
you resemble an old acquaintance.
My surname is Ye...
name, Zhetian.
These Heaven, Earth, and Human Seals...
hold supreme Dao principles.
Incredibly profound...
hard to master.
If evolved silently
with the Fighting Saint Method...
perhaps they can become...
a unique supreme divine art.
Heaven Overturning Seal...
embodies heaven and earth's truths...
not an offensive art...
but a binding secret technique.
Upgrade of Mountain Embracing Seal...
attack and defense as one.
Power of mountains and rivers...
all in my grasp!
Human King Seal...
like a Human King emerging...
supreme and unrivaled!
If the three seals interact...
combined in casting...
the power would be greater.
A rare sacred art in the world!
Ye Zhetian...
return my seals and Wanshang Bow!
I'll leave you a whole corpse.
You really don't learn, do you?
Should've stayed hidden at home...
yet come out as a target again.
I've used spirit medicines...
with my Xiao family's secret arts...
to heal Brother Yan.
Your wounds...
are no longer an issue.
In return...
I'll strike...
and slay Ye Zhetian...
to aid Brother Xiao...
eliminate the threat.
A sensible man.
Pity...
strong as you, Brother Yan...
wounded so badly
by this mere lord.
wounded so badly.
At full strength...
I might have fought.
This brat got my Wanshang Bow...
can't get close.
If the Wanshang Bow...
has no room to shine?
Wanshang Bow sealed...
what tricks left?
Mingyuan's your backup?
Two useless fools...
thinking you're something.
You ruined Xiao family plans...
stole our territory...
Today, I'll kill you...
end the threat.
Perfect timing
for my new seals...
test combo on you.
Heaven Overturning Seal!
Mountain Embracing Seal!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Human King Seal!
First bind with Heaven Overturning...
suppress with Mountain Embracing...
finally...
slay with Human King Seal.
This is the true way
to unite the three seals.
Brother Yan makes fine test material.
Excellent!
Come quick!
Yan Yunluan's fighting someone!
Yan Yunluan is a monster...
breaking through in battle!
Using heavenly tribulation to kill!
This Yan Yunluan...
his divine sense enters the lightning sea...
controls the bolts!
Forming a tribulation lightning bell!
Forming a heavenly tribulation bell!
Your tribulation is still lacking.
You're a monster who's crossed tribulation too?
Still not enough...
The lightning's too weak!
Yan Yunluan manifested
a tribulation divine bell!
Terrifying!
Even saint-child level can't escape!
But that guy...
Little Yan...
can you do it?
Hit harder!
In my tribulation...
turn to ash!
This is insane!
I can't watch anymore...
Then I'll reluctantly...
play teacher again...
and give you...
one final lesson.
Four Extremities...
After limbs...
cultivate the spine.
Each vertebra...
forged into heaven's pillar...
heaven's pillar.
From tailbone to neck...
nine transformations to perfection.
Manifest dragon form...
to bear the Immortal Platform.
Only then chance
to tread the ancient starry road...
and return home.
This...
this isn't my tribulation!
Stop him quick!
Ancient starry road...
Immortal Platform realm...
Then today...
I'll transform into dragon!
You triggered great heavenly tribulation...
and use it to transform?!
Who are you really?
Who is Ye Zhetian?
If you want lessons,
I'll teach you.
Xiao Mingyuan...
Running? Where to?
Think you can outrun me?
Ye Zhetian...
I'll burn my cultivation...
to drag you down!
Blood sacrifice this city...
summon Xiao half-step mighty...
to hunt you...
and answer to the lord.
Die with this city's people!
My city...
not yours to sacrifice!
Massacre innocents...
death a thousand times over!
You think...
you can stop it?
Ye Zhetian...
you dare kill me?
Xiao family allies
with Beiyuan Wang!
Xiao Mingyuan was cruel...
deserved death, I know.
But Xiao in Zhongzhou...
prestigious clan.
I'll suppress this matter...
spare you their revenge.
Thank you, Princess.
This Grand Tutor Xiao...
deep and scheming.
Princess...
beware him.
Brother Zhetian...
You drew tribulation
to smite Yan Yunluan...
broke through to Dragon Transformation!
Among those I know...
only East Desolation's Saint Body
rivals you.
Princess Yudie...
Brother Dongfang...
long time no see.
You two know each other?
We trained at Qishi Mansion...
so...
known each other long.
I see.
Benefactor...
You've advanced to Dragon Transformation...
and urgently need
a Dragon Transformation scripture.
My ancient scripture...
is useless to you, benefactor.
Saving me instead...
brought you new enemies.
This humble girl...
feels truly guilty.
Princess, don't blame yourself.
Why not enter the Immortal Mansion world together?
I'll find upgrade materials
for my spiked club...
and help Brother Zhetian
find a Dragon Transformation scripture.
I just came out of the Immortal Mansion...
beasts are rioting there.
Not safe to return.
Princess Qi mentioned before...
the beast unrest...
signals an immortal trove emerging.
On this trip...
I'll do everything I can
to find the scripture for you.
Thank you, Princess.
Qi Huoshui...
Totally forgot about her.
Her brother is Nan Yao Qi Lin...
master of unrivaled arts.
He must have saved her.
You're usually refined and gentle...
yet made Princess Qi—
that fiery chili—suffer.
Pity the beast riot...
broke many barriers in the Immortal Mansion.
Even Qishi Mansion's...
entrance is sealed.
Now...
we need another way in.
Come, follow me!
This way!
That voice...
Duan De!
How is he here?
Fellow cultivators...
this is the Immortal Mansion entrance!
Follow me in...
seek the secrets!
Big bro, let's go!
This fat Taoist...
spouting nonsense again.
How could this be the entrance?
Princess knows him?
He trained at Qishi Mansion too.
This dead fatty...
annoys me most!
Always eyeing my spiked club...
nearly stole it once.
Wish I could rob him back.
Can't I?
Fancy a robbery?
I'll set array patterns
at the cave mouth.
Thanks for the support, friends!
Farewell!
That bastard...
old habits die hard.
Trick people, will you?
Here they come!
Will the arrays hold him?
His array skills look strong.
Don't worry...
tailored by some...
powerful being...
just for him.
Brother Dongfang...
strip him bare!
Doing this...
isn't very nice, is it?
With this fatty...
no need for mercy.
This fatty...
is a living treasure trove!
Heavens...
Nine Divine Weapons!
Fifteen thousand years ago...
the great powerhouse...
Yuhua King's Nine Divine Weapons...
thought long lost.
How did he get them?
That bastard's got skills...
unearthing legendary relics.
Wonder how many ancient tombs
he's robbed.
Finally recouped some interest.
Take what we need...
grab first!
Good!
Some treasures won't budge...
That broken bowl...
really a flawed emperor weapon?
Immeasurable Heavenly Venerable!
This old Taoist has hunted eagles
all my life...
only to get my eyes pecked
by some wild sparrow!
Immeasurable Heavenly Venerable!
[Shrouding the Heavens – Quick Knowledge Guide]
[Immortal Mansion: A site of immortal traces, located deep in the mountains behind Qi Shi Prefecture, overlooking the city below. According to deductions made by the great experts of Qi Shi Prefecture, this place may contain remnants left behind by an Ancient Great Emperor. It is believed that an ancient foundation may give rise to a supreme saintly weapon, making it deeply connected to the immortal domains. The area is filled with profound mysteries from primordial times and is regarded as an unparalleled opportunity for fate. At the entrance of the Immortal Mansion, powerful guardians from Qi Shi Prefecture stand watch. Only inner disciples are permitted to enter and explore the mansion. Outside the mansion lies an ancient forest that has existed for tens of thousands of years. From time to time, the forest emits bursts of divine sound. Legend has it that when the ancient forest resonates with divine tones, the Gate to the Immortal Realm will open, revealing another hidden entrance to the world of the Immortal Mansion.]
I am chosen by the Great Emperor!
Then this old man
will join the fun too.
My apologies...
this treasure...
I'll gladly accept it.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™