[Previously]
Then we'll join forces and shatter it together.
This secret art that devours divine power.
How long do you think
you can last?
An endless stream of heaven and earth power
is converging on him.
It's that young miss of the Ji family.
She possesses the Origin Spirit Body.
The Extreme Dao is awakening.
We have nothing to fear from you!
At worst, we'll sink the entire Central Province!
What he believes in...
I believe the same.
The opportunity has come.
Let me test the power
of the Soldier Character Secret!
Go!
Heaven's will is manifest.
Ten thousand spirits offer their blood.
Protect our Holy Cult!
Earth's mandate stretches eternal.
Ten thousand laws return to one.
May the teachings flourish forever!
Master.
I was wounded by Ye Fan...
The Nine Li Diagram struck my foundation.
Though my injuries have healed...
my lifespan...
has grown even shorter.
Master.
Let us go kill that Ye Fan scoundrel for you.
None of you are his match.
There is no need for further pointless sacrifice.
You...
will inherit my mantle.
Master...
Your master is about to fall.
But the Dao lineage of our sect must not perish.
I have already made arrangements with the Wang family of the Northern Desolate Lands.
Today...
I shall use this broken body to slay the Sacred Body.
The Northern Emperor has promised...
to help you all continue the Yin-Yang Dao lineage.
Another line of northern wild geese flies south.
Old friends...
Without all of you by my side...
it feels like something is missing.
That's enough.
Who are you performing for?
What terrible taste.
Just burn these broken remains.
Erecting a tombstone is too inauspicious.
You've all consumed divine fruits...
and been reborn anew.
But we should still pay our respects.
Why didn't he make one for himself?
Wait...
Surviving under six Imperial Weapons this time...
was only possible thanks to all of you.
This Dreamlike Divine Marrow...
Everyone...
should share it together.
This is truly a priceless treasure.
Ye Fan...
Thank you.
We caused such a huge commotion outside...
We should go home and report to our grandfathers.
Until we meet again.
Alright.
Goodbye, you old bandits!
What about you, young miss?
With your brother making such a scene...
you can still stroll back into the Ji family without a care.
Now you know how powerful this little immortal is, right?
But I'm not going back yet.
Besides...
Without me...
who's going to protect you?
So, what's our next move?
Do you have any further plans?
After this battle...
our fame...
should have spread across the entire Central Province.
Trying to keep a low profile...
is no longer possible.
We might as well head straight to the Singular Scholar Mansion.
Continue investigating clues about the Starry Sky Ancient Path.
You're going to the Singular Scholar Mansion too?
Then...
We'll meet again at the Singular Scholar Mansion.
He truly is an ancient saint from Earth.
Could it be...
that only by reaching their level of cultivation...
can one embark on the journey home?
You damn scoundrel Ye!
You actually dare show up at the Singular Scholar Mansion!
Surround him and take him down!
This girl...
Isn't she the younger sister of the Southern Demon, Qi Lin?
Don't tell me you and her...
It's a long story.
Little Qi.
I'm here for my own reasons.
It has nothing to do with you.
Can you not be so enthusiastic?
You...
You're not leaving here today.
Fighting inside the Singular Scholar Mansion
isn't a good look.
Little Ye Zi.
You're really not doing a great job
as a follower.
Everywhere you go,
people gather to watch.
Who's watching him?
Hey!
Since when did I become your follower?
I'm the one leading you around...
searching everywhere for that Starry Sky Ancient Path.
I wasn't even finished speaking.
Yet here you are,
following right behind me.
Do you people even take me seriously?!
This works too?
You're really going too far!
One flower, one world.
Qi Qi!
Come back!
Let go of me!
Today, no matter what,
I must kill him!
You all should disperse as well.
Withdraw!
Nine Dragons Pulling a Coffin.
Ancient Desolate Forbidden Land.
I've seen you before.
Brother Ye.
Why don't we step aside and talk?
You dozen or so people crossed the star domain...
and emerged from the Ancient Desolate Forbidden Land.
You scattered across the Eastern Wastelands.
You...
are one of them.
How did you know?
My Southern Demon Emperor Hall's Blood Sacrifice Altar...
possesses a treasure
called the Heaven and Earth Dharma Eye.
This treasure...
can cross vast distances...
and peer into the heavens and earth.
Since ancient times...
there have been many legends of visitors from beyond the domain.
I never imagined...
I would witness one with my own eyes.
In that case...
I won't hide anything either.
Brother Qi's family lineage is ancient and profound.
I wonder...
if you possess any method to reach beyond the domain?
Regrettably...
I do not know either.
But every time I gaze at the starry sky...
I can't help but imagine...
what the world on the other side of the stars looks like.
That place is ancient and distant.
Though it is my homeland...
there are still many unknown ancient histories.
Even I know nothing about them.
To never set foot in that world...
would ultimately be nothing but an empty dream.
Brother Ye...
Could you tell me more about the world beyond the domain?
Could you describe it to me?
Since Brother Ye has treated me with sincerity...
when our paths cross on the Imperial Road one day...
if you are defeated...
I will let you leave.
Consider it repayment for today's kindness.
Take care.
Ye Fan...
I didn't expect you and the Southern Demon
to get along so well.
But...
What exactly did you two talk about?
Why is it that every time your homeland comes up...
you always become so mysterious?
Even the big guy starts acting strange.
Ye Fan...
The grudge between us...
Today...
it must be settled once and for all.
Step aside!
Ye Fan!
My Yin-Yang Cult has stood in the Central Province for ten thousand years.
Our Dao lineage continues unbroken.
You have repeatedly killed our Holy Sons and Holy Maidens...
and sought to sever our inheritance.
Today, I cannot let you live.
Do you have some kind of persecution complex?
Those Holy Sons and Holy Maidens of yours...
weren't they all stolen genius seedlings from other sects?
You call that a pure inheritance?
Shut your mouth!
My lifespan is running out, and time waits for no one.
Today, I will eliminate you for the sake of future generations.
You really think...
this is enough to kill me?
Old thief!
Your Yin-Yang Cult cannot tell right from wrong...
and twists the truth.
You should have been struck down by heaven long ago!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Cowardly turtle!
Come out and face me!
Wang Yangzhan was heavily wounded
by the Nine Li Diagram.
His combat strength is far from before.
Burning his lifespan like this
to power the treasure...
He won't be able to hold on much longer.
You're already at your limit.
Now accept your death!
I've got you!
Little brat...
I know how cunning you are.
But all I need is one look at you
from this distance...
and the curse will strike you for sure.
I have already formed an alliance with the Northern Emperor.
In exchange for the life of the Sacred Body...
my Yin-Yang Cult shall enjoy another era of glory.
I will not have died in vain.
It's too late.
This is my Yin-Yang Cult's Yin-Yang Death Curse.
There is no cure in this world.
Ye Fan...
Using this broken body as the medium...
I burn the last of my lifespan to cast the Yin-Yang Death Curse.
Even if my soul scatters into oblivion...
I will drag you down to the Yellow Springs with me!
Yin-Yang Death Curse!
Ye Zi...
Don't come any closer!
Ye Fan...
Ye Zi...
I've been hit by that old bastard's
Yin-Yang Death Curse.
Even my divine phenomenon can barely resist it.
This is bad.
The death curse...
is rushing toward my sea of consciousness.
It wants to destroy my divine sense.
If my divine sense is destroyed...
everything is over.
The Yin-Yang Death Curse...
burns all things...
and destroys all spirits.
Do not approach this barrier...
lest the curse's flames spread to you.
Elder...
Is there any way to break this death curse?
The Singular Scholar Mansion's library is vast.
There must be a method to dispel it.
The Sacred Body commands countless secret arts.
If he reached the Saint Lord realm...
he would be nearly unmatched in the world.
Breaking the Yin-Yang Death Curse would be no problem.
But right now, his cultivation is still too low.
Judging by this situation...
he can only last a day and a night at most.
This person...
doesn't have long to live.
Ye Zi...
You can definitely hold on.
I'll stay right here and watch over you.
If anyone dares speak rudely...
or harbors ill intentions...
I'll be the first to cut them down!
Ye Fan, hold on!
It's useless, Zi Yue.
Stop wasting your energy.
Young Miss...
What are you doing?
This is the ring from the Bronze Immortal Palace.
It might be able to break the death curse.
This secret treasure has fused with your primordial spirit.
You cannot summon it lightly...
nor can you destroy it.
Otherwise you will fall.
Using it recklessly now...
will surely bring great disaster.
This secret treasure comes from the Immortal Domain.
Its power is impossible to fully predict.
Perhaps it's worth the risk.
Ji Ziyue...
Don't go over there!
Ye Fan...
Zi Yue...
Don't come any closer!
Young Miss...
I won't just watch you die.
Even if I have to exhaust every treasure I possess...
I will save you.
[Mini Lecture on Heavenly Knowledge]
[Yin-Yang Death Curse: The ultimate strike used by generations of Yin-Yang Sect leaders at the brink of death. Once unleashed, whether king or ruler, none can escape. The caster kills the enemy—but must also sacrifice themselves, enduring endless torment and refinement before death. This is a curse formed from a lifetime of slaughter. When the death curse is activated, it destroys everything—leaving no solution.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™