FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Ziyue
I heard someone forced you
into an engagement.
I've come to free you from that burden.
Just shake your head and refuse.
Today, I'll take you away.
No one will stop us.
Ziyue.
Do you agree?
Of course I don't.
Ye Fan.
I knew you'd come today.
An Emperor's path without your corpse
would feel too lonely and incomplete.
So in this battle,
I must thank you for making it possible.
This sword
shall cut you down.
Life
is the greatest miracle in this world.
Understand this:
Countless ages ago,
a Supreme from the Primordial Race
sought eternal life and boundless longevity.
They fed on the life essence of the human race.
Millions of humans fell,
their blood flowing like rivers.
Our bloodline was nearly severed.
In that dark era,
the Void Emperor rose.
He protected all living beings in the world.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Void Emperor.
He quelled the chaos.
He fought his entire life,
until his later years,
when he spilled his blood across the cosmic void.
Thus ended the darkness of that era.
Yet the Primordial Race, still lurking in the forbidden zones,
remains
restless and scheming.
Purple Mountain.
Could it be the inheritance of the Unbeginning?
It's coming from Purple Mountain.
[Northern Plains Wang Clan]
A great era is approaching.
My son possesses the bearing of a Great Emperor.
He will surely illuminate this age.
Teng'er.
With all the kings emerging,
the struggle for the Emperor's path will be fraught with danger.
In setting up this scheme,
you must be extra cautious.
If you lack even this much confidence,
what right do you have to vie for the Emperor's path?
The Emperor's path is built upon
unrivaled confidence in oneself.
Others are merely whetstones.
As expected of my son.
In the struggle for the Emperor's path,
with so many whetstones gathered here,
this
is the perfect chance to prove my path to invincibility.
There's something strange at Purple Mountain.
We respectfully welcome the Eighth Ancestor out of seclusion.
Strange movements at Purple Mountain.
Perhaps the Unbeginning inheritance has appeared.
What does that have to do with us?
Let's go eat.
Hey, wait!
Don't you want to fight for the top three
in the Oddities Mansion
to enter the Starry Sky Ancient Path?
Then why not try your luck at Purple Mountain?
Securing the top three would be effortless then,
right?
To open this Starry Sky Ancient Path,
you must battle among the heavenly prodigies
of your generation
and seize one of the top three spots.
Only then can it be activated.
Purple Mountain...
I'll go take a look.
But you
should stay here safely.
No way!
I just helped you build the confidence to go after the treasure,
and this is how you repay me?
Don't think I don't know what you're planning.
Ziyue.
Your Origin Spirit Body has already been exposed.
For the time being,
it's best you return to the Ji Family.
It's precisely because of my Origin Spirit Body
that the Ji Family elders kept me hidden for over ten years.
I finally managed to get out.
I'd rather die than go back.
You...
Brother Haoyue.
You're her brother.
Talk some sense into her.
I...
We pay respects to the Eighth Ancestor.
The rites have collapsed and music is in chaos.
A mere rogue cultivator dares to kill
someone from our ancient family!
The Saint Body and Miss Ziyue
have already headed to Purple Mountain.
Regarding your plan...
Should we...
I have my own arrangements.
The Patriarch is in seclusion.
From this moment on, I shall oversee
all clan affairs in his stead.
Those who disobey shall be executed.
Brother Haoyue.
Brother Ye.
I told you to talk some sense into your sister.
Did you?
I did.
But it was just like
when I tried to persuade her
not to get close to you back then.
You...
Look,
besides...
I don't discriminate against you anymore.
What "Divine Body"?
You're just an incurable sis-con.
Brother...
I know him too well.
He always says it's dangerous,
yet somehow
he quietly collects a bunch of treasures
for himself.
That Immortal Tears Green Gold Book, for example...
This time,
I'm sticking right by his side.
I won't let him
hog all the benefits.
Left side.
Hurry and claim the Unbeginning inheritance.
Purple Mountain is guarded by the Unbeginning Bell.
I'll use Source Arts to clear a path.
Head toward the outer perimeter.
Do not engage them.
Hold steady.
The time has come.
This is yet another slumbering ground
of ancient primordial beings.
Just the outer area
already has so many of them.
Just how mighty were the Great Emperors
of ten thousand years ago
that they could pacify all of this?
What kind of power
does being a Great Emperor
truly represent?
Great Emperor...
This is a secret history from the desolate ancient era.
For some unknown reason, the Primordial Race
began reviving on a massive scale.
Among them appeared beings of unimaginable power.
They brought forth unprecedented calamity.
Later,
it was the human Great Emperors who took action
and quelled everything.
Beings of unimaginable power...
What exactly were they?
Scared now?
Who said I'm scared?
I just feel it's a shame about all this divine source.
Ye Fan,
don't you think so?
This is...
A cosmic star map similar to the one
on the bronze ancient coffin.
The Primordial Race...
Why would they possess a cosmic star map?
Could it be that these purple-bronze warships
were once used for interstellar voyages?
The Primordial Race...
Could they exist beyond just the Northern Dipper?
Earth...
Why is Earth here?
What exactly
is all of this pointing toward?
My Primordial Ten Thousand Races
have been dormant for ten thousand years.
The time for our revival draws near.
Since he wants to use that thing as bait,
then let's fulfill his wish.
Fortune...
Something's wrong.
This fluctuation...
It doesn't feel like the Unbeginning inheritance.
Saint Body... Divine Body...
While I was suppressing all the heavenly prodigies
and securing victory despite heavy injuries,
you brought Miss Ziyue here
to ambush me.
How very clever.
Come on then.
It seems the Northern Emperor's
skill with words is no less impressive than his strength.
Whether we came here
to ambush you or not,
I'm sure you already know the answer in your heart.
A Saint Body as rare as one in ten thousand years...
If it cannot even serve as a whetstone...
That would indeed be my greatest regret in life.
Since you've come here,
there's no point in talking further.
Let's settle this with a fight.
In this world, the strong
stand supreme alone.
To be born in the same era as me
is truly your misfortune.
Wang Teng.
If thick skin could lead to the Dao,
you could ascend to immortality right now.
We can't let him use the Word Secret.
Primordial Spirit Awakening.
Nine Heavens Soul Summoning.
It's the Origin Spirit power again.
Heaven and Earth spiritual energy,
converge into one body.
The power of the Origin Spirit Body
will one day belong to me.
Be careful!
This is bad.
The primordial creatures have been awakened.
Ziyue!
It's the Eighth Ancestor.
Eighth Ancestor!
Eighth Ancestor.
What is the meaning of this?
The Northern Emperor is already heavily injured.
His strength is less than one-tenth of normal.
Besides, the struggle for the Emperor's path
has no room for many contenders.
Northern Emperor, Saint Body...
Let's fight fairly.
Eighth Ancestor!
What are you doing?
Their cultivation realms are completely different.
How can this be called a fair fight?
Are you doing this for Ji Hui?
You old bastard!
If you truly want revenge for that old hag,
then fight me directly.
Why make so many excuses?
How arrogant.
You've merely stumbled upon a few fortunate opportunities,
yet you dare challenge a Great Emperor's family.
How foolish.
Void Mirror!
This pressure...
It's so heavy I can barely turn around.
Today,
I will make you understand
that a Great Emperor's family
is not something you can insult.
Ye Fan!
Young Master.
The plan has succeeded.
The Purple Mountain seal is about to activate.
Let's go, Young Master.
The Ji Family...
Origin Spirit Body...
You're actually this vicious.
Ye Fan has no grudge against you.
Why are you trying to harm him?
Just because of Ji Hui?
How utterly foolish.
You were born into a Great Emperor's family.
You should understand the principle
of cutting off a wrist to save oneself from a snakebite,
or how an anthill can collapse a dam.
Even if Ji Hui deserved to die,
it is not for a mere rogue cultivator
to trample upon our clan's dignity like this.
Nonsense!
Our clan's glory lies in distinguishing right from wrong.
What Ye Fan did
was merely fighting for survival in a desperate situation.
In the past, our clan's Great Emperor
used the Void Mirror to suppress the dark turmoil
and protect the people of the human race.
Yet you, Eighth Ancestor,
today
are using a replica Imperial weapon
to suppress a human Saint Body.
How is that any different?
Our clan's possessions
exist to safeguard our clan's glory.
Our clan's people
should also be used for the family's sake.
Moreover, in this current era,
it is the law of the jungle—
the weak are prey to the strong.
If the Ji Family refuses to change,
we will eventually be wiped out in this great era.
Haven't the events of the past
been enough to serve as a warning?
So many Great Emperor families
have turned to dust in this great era because they clung to old ways.
You all...
are still too young.
If the Ji Family...
becomes one that disregards right and wrong,
extinguishes conscience, and preys on the weak,
then I
would rather leave.
How ridiculous.
You possess the Origin Spirit Body.
You are a vital asset to the family.
How can we allow you to leave so easily?
Your fate
has been tied to the Ji Family
since the moment you were born.
Your destiny is inseparable from ours.
What do you think you're doing?
Let go of me!
I want to find Ye Fan!
Eighth Ancestor!
Let go of me!
Reporting to the Eighth Ancestor.
All the holy lands and ancient families
have learned that Miss Ziyue possesses
the Origin Spirit Body.
They have already taken action.
It won't be long before
every prodigy in the world comes flocking.
Now that the Origin Spirit Body has been exposed,
hiding it is no longer possible.
Instead of concealing it,
we might as well fan the flames
and let the news spread across the Northern Dipper.
The Origin Spirit Body is extremely rare in this world.
It can merge with the origin of all things
and command every source force for its own use.
Such a precious asset
is unfortunately unstable by nature.
It would be best to choose a suitable husband for her.
The timing is perfect.
The Ji Family can use this as an opportunity
to restore our family's former glory.
Miss's marriage is a matter of great importance.
We should ask the Patriarch first
before making any decision.
A great era is approaching,
yet the Ji Family still clings
to outdated rules and conventions,
stuck in the old ways.
For over a hundred thousand years,
has our family ever produced a Great Emperor?
The prodigies of the Eastern Wasteland
are as numerous as carp crossing a river.
Eighth Ancestor, why do you only look toward the Northern Plains?
The bright moon
should naturally shine upon the most brilliant Emperor Star of this age.
The Northern Plains is a harsh and bitter land,
but if they are willing to form an alliance with our Ji Family,
we will spare no effort to support them.
Eighth Ancestor...
With a great era upon us,
having allies will naturally make things much easier.
The Northern Plains is not like the Ji Family.
We do not have ancestral blessings to rely on.
We can only vie for the Emperor's path in this lifetime.
Since the Ji Family has Mingyue,
she should naturally become
the future matriarch of my Wang Family.
I told you last time,
this is not a place your Divine Spirit Valley can visit whenever you please.
Young Master is truly heartless.
Right after we finished cooperating,
you already want to discard us?
And here I specially came to inform Young Master
about a secret from ancient times.
Speak.
In the desolate ancient era,
the Void Emperor once fought a bloody battle
against a Supreme of my Primordial Race
in the outer starry sky.
The Imperial Mirror illuminated ten thousand ages,
and the Imperial Tower could freeze eternity itself.
That battle
shattered the galaxy
and buried an entire era.
The Supreme ultimately perished,
but the fragments of Eternal Blue Gold stained with the Void Emperor's blood
lie hidden in the deepest part of the Ji Family's Void Ancient Hall.
Guarded by an Imperial formation,
yet also forgotten by it.
And the scripture I used you as bait for earlier
can draw upon the supreme laws contained within those fragments.
I know Young Master plans to visit the Ji Family's sacred land.
Why not use the marriage alliance as a chance
to personally enter the Void Ancient Hall
and retrieve
the fortune that rightfully belongs to you?
An opportunity like this
is invaluable.
Speak.
What do you want?
My race's revival is imminent.
What we need...
Others may not know,
but surely the Northern Emperor understands.
The Origin Spirit Body...
We can share it with the Northern Emperor.
We will also
clear all obstacles for you.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
This Void Mirror
looks different from the one Ji Haoyue brought out before.
It seems like a replica.
It looks like the Eighth Ancestor can't freely summon
the true Imperial weapon.
Just a replica of the Void Mirror
was enough to wound me this badly.
And that Wang Teng...
No matter what your goal is,
I will remember this debt
very clearly.
Forget it.
I must leave this place first.
Looks like Young Master was right.
The Saint Body really isn't that easy to kill.
I never expected
that the mighty human Saint Body
would end up in such a sorry state.
I'm heavily injured.
Don't you think it's a bit shameless
to attack me like this?
Times have changed.
You are the fish on the chopping block,
and I am the knife.
I'll slice your flesh piece by piece
and let my race's creatures devour every last bit.
Go to hell!
What?
Weren't you heavily injured?
Though I'm heavily injured and exhausted,
the dragon qi in this place is extremely abundant.
It's more than enough to wipe out you two little shrimps.
This is...
Source Arts!
It's too late to realize now.
Don't get trapped by his Source Arts!
Get in close and fight him!
Speak.
Who sent you?
Saint Body,
your life will be taken sooner or later.
Why should we need anyone else's help?
I'll talk! I'll talk!
It was the Young Master of Divine Spirit Valley,
Zi Tianfeng.
Zi Tianfeng...
Divine Spirit Valley...
What does killing me benefit her?
She's helping Wang Teng.
She knows you have a close relationship with the Origin Spirit Body.
Killing you
is to clear the path for Wang Teng's marriage alliance with the Ji Family.
To remove all obstacles.
Keep talking.
The Ji Family's Eighth Ancestor
wants to
marry the Origin Spirit Body
to
the Northern Emperor, Wang Teng.
So you must die.
Wang Teng...
Saint Body, we...
We've told you everything we know.
We beg you, Lord Saint Body,
spare our lives!
Spare us!
Lord Saint Body, please spare us!
The Ji Family's Eighth Ancestor,
Wang Teng from the Northern Plains,
and Divine Spirit Valley...
Zi Tianfeng.
Three factions working together
just to take my life, Ye Fan.
It's almost too ridiculous to believe.
The most urgent task now is to increase my strength as quickly as possible.
That's right.
Since you two are primordial remnants,
and you've already come here,
you might as well help me decipher these ancient runes.
This...
This is...
The Solar True Scripture!
How could he possibly have the Solar True Scripture?
How could such a Great Emperor inheritance
be in your hands?
Could it be...
that you have some connection with that
old devil Dongfang Taiyi?
Since you recognize these scriptures,
then each of you will translate a copy.
But remember this well:
If there's even a single character difference
in the translated text,
whether I kill you or torture you,
it will be entirely up to me.
Ye Fan...
Lord Saint Body,
the scriptures have been fully translated.
Please review them.
The Solar True Scripture...
It is actually one of the primordial scriptures of the human race.
With this scripture,
I may be able to reach a higher level.
Truly profound.
It washes away all mortal impurities,
refines true yang,
and seizes creation in reverse.
My strange phenomenon
is actually resonating with the Solar True Scripture.
And the divine power far exceeds my current level.
He’s going to...
He’s going to break through!
Congratulations on breaking through and being reborn, Saint Body.
I can let you go,
but you know too much.
I’ll have to erase your memories.
Thank you, Saint Body.
The Saint Body has actually recovered.
For the glory of the Primordial Race,
let’s attack together!
Ye Fan!
Die!
You’ve really wasted your hot blood.
Ye Fan is still alive.
Then let little brother handle it.
We need to add more fuel
to the fire for our Northern Emperor.
No one else decides my sister’s marriage.
Only she can decide.
What is the meaning of this?
Wang Teng.
I am not one of those who fear you.
Fight me.
Come on.
Brother Haoyue, your behavior
is far too improper.
It damages the dignity of the Ji Family.
Haoyue.
This marriage alliance between our families
is for the sake of our Dao lineage’s immortality.
As the Divine Body of the Ji Family,
you should have this awareness.
Did the Eighth Ancestor ever ask Ziyue for her opinion?
Foolish.
Matters of marriage have always been decided by our elders.
How can juniors interfere?
Since I am overseeing clan affairs in his stead,
I must choose for the Ji Family’s brightest pearl
the strongest husband of this era.
Everyone,
allow this old man to ask:
Among the younger generation,
who is currently unrivaled in the world?
Who is qualified
to match our Ji Family’s brightest pearl?
My Teng’er
possesses the bearing of a Great Emperor.
He wields the Chaos Ancient Emperor Scripture.
In his generation,
who can rival him?
In terms of qualifications,
no one can compare.
We have not yet fought.
How can you claim to be unrivaled among your peers?
Defeat me first, then we’ll talk.
Brother Haoyue,
we will soon be family.
It would be a shame to ruin our relationship.
Your sister would be heartbroken.
But if you insist on provoking me,
then come and fight.
Never losing is my Dao.
Northern Emperor, please calm yourself.
Since the Patriarch has not come out of seclusion,
whoever can pass the trial of the Ancient Hall
shall be the one to marry our clan’s Mingyue.
As for whether you are qualified,
why not let
our clan’s Void Emperor decide the answer?
Wang Teng.
I am willing to enter the Ancient Hall and take the trial.
Teng’er...
You...
Good.
If you can make the Ancient Hall resonate,
you will be the heaven-chosen one personally selected by our clan’s Great Emperor.
As for the marriage with Ziyue,
no one in the entire Ji Family
will be able to stop it.
Of course,
if you fail...
Fail?
I have obtained the Chaos Ancient Great Emperor’s inheritance
and hold the Nine Secrets in my hands.
I am a bearer of great destiny in this era.
How could I possibly fail?
There are countless human prodigies.
Why does it have to be Wang Teng?
This child’s edge is too sharp.
He may be difficult to control.
As long as he
enters the Ji Family,
our task will already be complete.
As for the Saint Body...
Ye Fan.
You’ve lost.
This is...
The Divine Son thinks
the Saint Body
will come this time?
Soon.
It would be good if Wang Teng wins,
of course.
But if he loses...
Sister Ziyue
has been taken back to the Ji Family.
[Jiang Tingting — Ancient Jiang Clan]
The clan elders say she’s about to be married off soon.
Big Brother...
Why hasn’t he come back yet?
Tingting.
Don’t worry.
Maybe
Big Brother is just nearby
and will come find us any moment now.
Yezi...
Why haven’t you come back yet?
That bastard Ji Family
actually wants to marry Ji Ziyue to Wang Teng.
Isn’t that just to spite you?
Hurry back...
Still waiting, huh?
Stop waiting.
That Ye guy is already dead.
Yet you’re still deluding yourself.
You Wang Family little bastard.
What did you just say?
You still don’t know?
Well, I guess not.
His body
was completely devoured by the Primordial Race.
Not even bones were left.
Inside Purple Mountain,
his saint blood is scattered everywhere.
You’re courting death!
Little girl,
your Sister Ziyue
will soon
be given to my brother.
And now I’ll send you down
to accompany your Big Brother.
You little bastard!
I’ll crush you to death!
Still don’t believe it?
Kneel!
Wang Family...
bastard.
Quite the tough guy.
I was planning to send you all invitations,
but now
I’ve changed my mind.
I’ll skin you all alive, rip out your tendons,
and turn you into lanterns.
Then place them
at the wedding venue
so you can witness
the grand spectacle of my Wang Family marrying the Origin Spirit Body.
Go down and tell Ye Fan
that his woman
has been graciously accepted by my brother.
It’s the Mother Qi Cauldron of All Things!
Yezi!
Big Brother!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Young Master!
Are you alright?
You’re not dead...
Impossible.
That woman lied to me!
Weren’t you eaten?
Looks like I’m not dead.
You seem very disappointed.
But don’t be too disappointed,
because
you’re all going to die.
The aura on him...
It feels different from before.
Perfect.
Yezi,
kill that little bastard first,
then we’ll deal with his brother.
Even an Immortal Platform Saint Body isn’t that strong, huh?
Ancestral Dragon Seal!
So strong...
You could have killed me in an instant.
Why...
Because
I wanted you to enjoy the beating
before you die.
Big Brother...
Yezi!
I knew you wouldn’t die.
Tell me,
what’s our plan next?
Do we storm the Ji Family to crash the wedding first,
then chop up those Ji Family bastards and Wang Teng together?
No crashing.
But...
I will go ask Ziyue in person
whether she truly wants to marry Wang Teng.
What?
Isn’t that still crashing the wedding?
But the Ji Family has Imperial weapons guarding them.
You’re really going in empty-handed?
That’s why
I need enough trump cards first.
A Great Emperor’s relic.
It bears Imperial blood.
The Great Emperor has chosen him.
He...
is the heaven-chosen one
of my Ji Family.
My son Wang Teng
possesses the bearing of a Great Emperor.
The bearing of a Great Emperor...
Eighth Ancestor.
Speak.
What?
Who did this?
By the time we arrived,
the culprit had already vanished without a trace.
Chong’er...
My Chong’er...
Chong’er!
How could you...
Who did this to you?
Ye Fan...
He’s still alive.
My condolences, worthy nephew.
The marriage alliance between our families
is the general trend.
No one can stop it.
In that case,
this old man will arrange for you
to become engaged to Ziyue
in three days.
If that little thief dares to come,
I will extinguish him once more.
Chong’er...
Zi Tianfeng...
No matter what,
Ye Fan, you are dead for sure.
This time when I go to the Ji Family to face their Imperial weapons,
the Nine-colored Divine Flame of the Fire Domain,
and the bronze little coffin from the Desolate Ancient Forbidden Land
will be my greatest support.
The demon race’s Imperial weapon and the Heaven Swallowing Demon Jar...
How is the investigation going?
The old blind man and the Peacock King
have both sealed themselves in seclusion,
guarded by Imperial weapons.
The Saint Body
has no way to borrow them.
Patriarch Wang.
Greetings, greetings.
Please, come inside.
Good.
As long as there is no Extreme Dao Imperial weapon,
on Ji Family territory,
the Saint Body
will surely bleed across our sacred land.
The Ji Family has survived until now,
but our foundation has already suffered heavy losses.
If we do not produce a Great Emperor soon,
what future does our clan have?
Rather than pinning our hopes on the younger generation,
it is better to rely on ourselves.
At present,
a marriage alliance seems the most reliable path.
Miss,
the auspicious hour is approaching.
Does the ceremonial robe fit well?
We respectfully welcome the Northern Emperor.
I’m so anxious.
Why hasn’t Brother Ye arrived yet?
Don’t worry.
He will definitely come.
Qian Yuan opens fortune.
The auspicious hour is upon us.
Today, the Ji Family’s direct daughter, Ziyue,
shall follow the Azure Luan bearing the sash ceremony
to fulfill the Black Tortoise alliance pact.
Please.
The phoenix carriage departs the pavilion.
This is utterly improper!
Eighth Ancestor,
what is the meaning of this?
Ziyue...
You must not disregard the greater good.
This is my big day.
Of course I’ll wear what I want.
Young Master of the Wang Family,
do you recognize this pattern?
These cloud-brocade motifs
are the Spirit Raft Flower of the Eastern Wasteland.
They symbolize breaking free from bonds
and roaming the starry river.
Their flower language
means longing,
and also freedom.
Someone come!
Take the young miss back to her room to change.
I’ve thought about it carefully.
I’ve accepted everything the family has given me,
so it’s only right that I contribute in return.
But
does contributing only mean marrying someone?
My Origin Spirit Body can help him achieve the Dao,
but if Wang Teng fails to become a Great Emperor in the future,
wouldn’t that ruin my own chances of becoming one?
Besides,
who can guarantee he hasn’t colluded with the Primordial Race?
Foolish girl.
Female Great Emperors have always been rare.
And what does this have to do with the Primordial Race?
Didn’t the Ruthless also become known as a female emperor?
The Primordial Race
naturally wants the Origin Spirit Body to speed up their revival.
Even if I’m wrong,
I still refuse to sacrifice myself for your so-called greater good.
Your greater good...
Why does it always come at someone else’s expense?
Take her away.
Put the ceremonial robe on her.
If she dares resist again,
punish her according to clan law.
What’s happening?
Ye Fan...
You’ve finally come.
It’s Ye Fan’s aura.
Someone must have brought an unparalleled secret treasure
and triggered the Emperor’s residual formation patterns.
Who goes there?
Ye...
Fan.
Ye Fan!
Everyone from the Wang Family, hear this!
How dare you come here and provoke us!
Ye Fan.
Ziyue.
I heard someone forced you into an engagement.
I’ve come to free you from that burden.
Just shake your head and refuse.
Today, I’ll take you away.
No one will stop us.
Ziyue.
Do you agree?
Of course I don’t.
Very well.
Then I’ll cut him down.
Ye Fan.
I knew you would come today.
Today I will use your saint blood
to honor Chong’er’s spirit in heaven.
An Emperor’s path without your corpse
would be too lonely and incomplete.
So in this battle,
I must thank you for making it possible.
Wang Teng.
You claim to possess the bearing of a Great Emperor,
but do you even know
what a Great Emperor truly is?
To me,
you look more like a clown jumping on a stage.
Then let me show you
what the bearing of a Great Emperor really looks like.
Isn’t that just a broken carriage?
Yezi has one too,
and it’s a Mercedes.
Crush him!
What nonsense are you lot spouting?
My son possesses the bearing of a Great Emperor.
You...
You bunch of frogs at the bottom of a well,
spouting such big talk.
So you’re Wang Teng’s father.
Well, my dad is Li Gang.
Everyone knows
my son is...
Wait, no.
My son
is surnamed Wang,
named Ba Gaozi Teng.
He possesses the bearing of a Great Emperor.
Is this all you’ve got?
Not even close.
This sword...
Can you block it?
My body is the Dao.
All phenomena transform into the Dao.
The inheritance of a Great Emperor
is not something only you possess.
The Solar True Scripture
is the supreme secret art passed down by the Solar Holy Emperor.
These two have nearly grasped their highest inheritances at the same time.
This struggle for the Emperor’s path
is becoming more and more interesting.
Well met.
Die!
This sword
shall cut you down.
To wound me this badly,
you can be proud of yourself.
Eternal Exile.
So earlier he was using his flesh body to resist,
buying himself a slim chance.
His true goal was this move all along.
This battle
ends here.
It’s over.
Miss Ziyue,
now that the outcome is decided,
you should give up, shouldn’t you?
If this were before,
I would’ve been sweating for him.
But now...
The real show has only just begun.
Early Immortal Platform stage...
How could you possibly break my Eternal Exile?
Don’t you love arranging engagements?
Then allow me to present this nine-colored gift.
Please accept it.
This is the divine flame from the ninth layer of the Fire Domain.
Even an immortal
would be burned to ashes.
Let alone a Wang Ba Teng like you.
What’s wrong? Too hot?
Looks like your skin isn’t thick enough after all.
Heavenly Emperor Sword.
Slash!
Returning it to you.
Your Emperor’s path
is nothing but illusion to me.
I told you,
I came here
only to take her away.
No one can stop me.
Brother Ye is really trying to anger Wang Teng to death.
So-called number one under heaven?
All nonsense.
With just you?
You think you can make me lose?
There’s something strange about Wang Teng.
Don’t get close.
Better to test him from a distance.
That’s right.
That gourd...
Maybe I can imitate Lu Ya the Daoist from Investiture of the Gods.
Do you have any more big moves?
Feel free to use them all.
Stop hiding them.
If you still won’t come over,
then don’t blame me for making the first move.
Baby,
please turn around.
It actually worked.
Why must the human race be so stubborn?
Our goals are the same.
Why not prosper together?
Give it to me!
Get lost!
Teng’er...
Do you really intend to push yourself
this far?
I was born to become Emperor.
This is my destiny.
My Emperor’s path,
my Dao—
how can it end here?
I am the Northern Emperor.
I have never lost once.
And I absolutely cannot lose.
What’s the meaning of this?
Commit suicide?
Severing Heaven
is my Severing Dao Art.
Sever the Dao!
Ye Fan!
Hurry up and finish off this Wang Ba Teng!
Don’t wait for him to use his big move!
Baby, please turn around.
Baby, please kill.
Baby, please chop him up.
Baby...
Sever my true self.
His aura
is more than twice as strong as before.
The Northern Plains is not like the Southern Domain.
For thousands of years,
no Emperor Star has ever shone here.
Teng’er’s Emperor path
carries the entire Northern Plains upon it.
This is his heavenly mandate.
And he
will surely shoulder this destiny.
Then let’s fight.
Word Secret.
Rise!
Don’t even think about it!
Too late.
Found you.
Not good!
Word Secret.
Refine the primordial spirit.
It can make divine sense immortal.
If cultivated to a certain level,
it can glimpse a sliver of the future.
I won’t give you that chance.
I’ve already seen through you.
Your moves are full of openings.
How could you possibly defeat me?
All paths converge as one.
Two secrets united.
Can you break this?
This is...
What exactly did you do?
As expected.
The Word Secret allows one to glimpse a corner of the future
before striking.
Thanks to your powerful primordial spirit,
the Word Secret primarily cultivates the spirit.
Competing with me in primordial spirit?
You’re courting death.
Die!
I know.
In terms of primordial spirit alone,
you are indeed very strong.
But Source Heaven Divine Art
is more than enough to suppress you.
How is this possible?
Your Source Art...
You rely on a single secret
and dare call yourself unrivaled under heaven.
But don’t forget,
I cultivate four secrets.
Four secrets united.
This will send you on your way.
Combine!
Well done, Yezi!
Well done!
Die!
Why...
Why did you win?
You old bastard!
You finally can’t sit still anymore.
This is wrong.
This is definitely a mistake.
[Void Mirror — Supreme Imperial Weapon]
I won’t allow this!
Eighth Ancestor!
What are you doing?
Eighth Ancestor, think carefully!
Clan rules strictly forbid the reckless use of Imperial weapons!
Ye Fan!
You intrude upon my Ji Family’s sacred land,
slay my Ji Family’s chosen son-in-law,
and bewitch my Ji Family’s brightest pearl.
Three crimes combined,
not even a hundred deaths could atone!
Today, this ancestor
shall borrow the Void Mirror to purge all vermin
and set the record straight.
What a perfect “three crimes combined.”
Old thief,
why don’t you use the Void Mirror to look at yourself?
See that hideous face of yours
and how it tarnishes this Imperial weapon.
You know nothing
of a true Imperial weapon’s power.
Did you really think
I would have no way to resist an Imperial weapon?
Brother...
What exactly is that coffin?
It’s so terrifying.
The terror doesn’t lie in the bronze coffin itself,
but in what sleeps inside it.
[Chaos Qi]
This bronze coffin
actually managed to withstand the Void Mirror.
All Ji Family elders,
join me in activating the Void Mirror
to suppress and kill Ye Fan!
Fellow elders,
the Eighth Ancestor has gone mad and violated clan rules.
Anyone who helps him
is no different from a traitor to our clan!
What?
The Imperial weapon is resisting!
Break!
After all that scheming,
I still couldn’t defeat
an ant.
The Eighth Ancestor has lost.
This bronze coffin is terrifyingly powerful.
It can even contend with the Void Mirror.
Serves the Eighth Ancestor right.
Even the Ji Family won’t help him now.
In the end, relying on him alone,
he naturally couldn’t unleash the Imperial weapon’s full power.
Using a coffin as a weapon...
Brother Ye,
you really are one of a kind.
From now on,
in the entire Eastern Wasteland,
who would still dare touch you?
Ye Fan...
Thank you.
Ziyue.
From today onward,
no one can ever force you to do anything again.
That outfit you’re wearing today...
looks really good on you.
Teng’er...
Teng’er!
Father will take you back to the Northern Plains.
No matter the cost,
Father will do everything to save you.
I lost...
I actually lost.
Why...
Why did it turn out like this?
No...
I will not lose.
I...
absolutely cannot
lose!
What’s happening?
What is this?
Teng’er...
Human, accept my power.
This is not enslavement, but fusion.
This is the true meaning of mutual prosperity.
And you
shall become the ruler of this new order.
This aura does not belong to the current era.
It’s the aura of a Primordial Supreme.
This Eternal Blue Gold
was never any Great Emperor inheritance at all.
It’s an evil relic.
We cannot let it appear in the world.
Quickly exterminate this person!
The heart’s domain shall perish.
Resentment fills the ends of the earth.
Our ancestors tasted both warmth and cold.
I have come to continue the annals of history.
Wang Teng truly was the optimal choice for our race.
He actually triggered the hidden Primordial Supreme aura
within the Eternal Blue Gold.
From today onward,
the Northern Emperor Wang Teng
shall be our race’s representative in the Northern Dipper.
Correct.
He will surely come to understand
that mutual prosperity with our race
is the only chance for the human race to survive.
We will not allow
the human race to produce another Great Emperor of their own.
Void...
For over a hundred thousand years,
the human race will ultimately be ruled by our race.
The Northern Dipper shall become our hunting ground.
You shortened your lifespan and gave up eternal life.
Was it worth it?
The desolate ancient Ji Family will cease to exist.
The era you opened
shall be ended by me.
You...
you deranged demonic creature!
The Origin Spirit Body...
I see.
This can accelerate my recovery several times over.
Annoying pest.
I almost forgot about you.
Wang Teng...
Are you still yourself right now?
Does it make any difference?
Ye Fan...
As long as I can stand at the peak and achieve the Emperor’s path,
I can also prosper together with the strong.
The human race is weak.
Only by merging with other races can we succeed.
Your vision is too narrow.
Only by letting go
can one become invincible.
You underestimate the human race too much.
Even if I fall,
in the future
someone will surely crush you.
Then I’ll crush you first.
Void...
Do you really think
a mere wisp of Imperial might can stop me?
Walking the Emperor’s path isn’t what matters.
Walking your own path
is the true road to invincibility.
If you abandon even your identity as a human,
then everything becomes an illusion.
Very well.
Then with this strike,
let all living beings witness
my rebirth.
A small accomplishment Saint Body is rare.
If you’re willing to submit,
I can immediately send you
to anywhere you wish to go.
With power like yours,
you still dare speak of things even a God King cannot do.
Isn’t that laughable?
As long as I use the Origin Spirit Body to accelerate my revival,
the might of an Ancient Emperor will spread across the universe.
And she won’t die.
You can go home right away.
Idiot.
Is that your condition?
Not bad.
Delusion.
No matter how great the benefit,
or how small the price,
I still
refuse.
Principles
are not meant to be traded.
Teng’er...
What was that just now?
Father will take you back.
We’ll find that old crane.
You’ll be fine.
Teng’er...
Teng’er!
What happened just now?
It seemed like the figure of our clan’s Great Emperor.
And that dream-like space earlier...
Did you all see it?
It must have been the collision of a Great Emperor’s and a Supreme’s imprint.
It fully awakened the power of the Word Secret,
deducing a future that does not exist
and striking down an unknown threat.
The Void Emperor...
was truly powerful.
The enemy who shortened his lifespan by three thousand years back then
must have been terrifying.
Thankfully Purple Mountain was once the Dao field of the Unbeginning Great Emperor.
At its center lies the Unbeginning Bell.
The Unbeginning Bell...
Why is it ringing now?
Seas turn to dust over tens of thousands of autumns.
The Dao transforms, yellowed hair brings worry of longevity.
One dream spans several thousand years.
The immortal path is rugged—where does one wander?
I wonder which exalted one has arrived
at my Ji Family.
I am the last successor of the Unbeginning.
Hearing that a Saint Body exists in this era,
I have come specially to meet him.
He actually came for the Saint Body.
I wish to take him as my disciple
and pass on
the Unbeginning Scripture.
Heavens!
The Unbeginning inheritance!
What a heaven-defying opportunity!
Yezi,
this opportunity is incredible!
Dead dog,
even the Unbeginning Great Emperor
would be angered back to life by you.
The Void Emperor had a lifespan of ten thousand years
but only lived seven thousand.
It was because after battling the nine great Saint Bodies across the heavens,
he bled all the way,
holding up this world alone.
The so-called Emperor’s path
is not about being undefeated,
but about protection.
Throughout the ages,
which of the Great Emperors truly remembered
did not shoulder the tribulations of the world
and safeguard the peace of this land?
The Emperor’s path
has never been a ladder of the strong devouring the weak,
nor a stairway to enslave the world.
Becoming Emperor
is not about reaching the peak
and commanding with a single word.
It is about standing at that summit
and shouldering the mission
to protect the vast rivers and mountains
and all living beings.
[Don’t go away—there’s a bonus scene]
Divine Son.
In a future that does not exist,
the Saint Body defeated Wang Teng.
We were unable to turn that illusion into reality.
It consumed a Supreme’s technique.
Please punish me.
No.
You have already completed your task.
Hiding the true objective was the key to the entire scheme.
Wang Teng carries the inheritance of the Chaos Ancient Great Emperor.
He seeks to become Emperor through defeat.
How could someone walking an undefeated path
possibly win?
Although the Saint Body did not perform as expected,
from the moment Wang Teng agreed to propose marriage to the Ji Family,
we had already succeeded.
Our race’s aura infiltrating the Ji Family
was merely a probe
to see if the human Great Emperors left any hidden countermeasures against us.
And now, after such open provocation,
the human Great Emperors only passively activated their imprints.
With this,
we can begin advancing to the next stage of the plan
and scheme to unify the ten thousand races.
Patriarch of the Wang Family,
why do you look so troubled?
Zi Tianfeng...
The Wang Family’s path
has not yet reached its end.
What do you mean?
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™