(Copyright Notice)
♪I had lost my way♪
♪Looking for a glimmer of light♪
♪The wind brushes against my face♪
♪Love and hate are intertwined♪
♪Endless woes♪
♪Waiting for the light in the night♪
♪I've been hurt,
I've been covered in blood and tears♪
♪I've doubted, and I've started over♪
♪Promised to fate♪
♪Tears may fall,
but my will is resolute♪
♪I'll fight with all my might♪
♪To protect this pulse♪
♪In silence, light the fire of destiny♪
♪The promise of a soulful symphony♪
♪Pour our hearts out,
dismantle all the tediousness♪
♪Let our souls be free♪
(Adapted from Soul Land 2: The Peerless Tang Clan
written by Tangjia Sanshao)
(Underage viewers must seek
parental permission before watching.)
(All content is computer-generated.
Please do not imitate it in real life.)
(Previous Episode)
(Tang Wutong, why do you)
(pay so much attention to him?)
(You can't keep doing this.)
The solidified soul power
will settle in the dantian,
known as the soul core.
Mr. Xuan, I want to try.
Alright, I will personally guard you.
Keep going. I've got your back.
Come on.
(Is this my soul core?)
Episode 127
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Yuhao is going to fuse the first
soul core into the Spiritual Sea,)
(not the dantian?)
(Good.)
(In this way, the second soul core
will have a place to reside.)
Yuhao, you've succeeded!
You've really condensed your first
soul core at the Soul Saint stage!
Comprehend it well.
This kind of realization
is an opportunity that many soul masters
never get in their entire lives.
Mr. Xuan, it wasn't you who was attempting
to form the second soul core...
It was...
This kid, Yuhao.
He might be the first person
in 10,000 years on the Douluo Continent.
A real devil among devils.
Now it's time for these young people
to step onto the stage of history.
Notify all members
of the Haishen Pavilion
to assist Tang Clan
in forming Soul-Guiding Master Corps.
(One Month Later)
(He is ascending.)
(What's going on? My soul power
is circulating on its own!)
Dong'er.
Sorry, I'm Tang Wutong.
It's me who should apologize.
Mr. Xuan asked me to tell you to go
to the Tang Clan when you wake up.
(Tang Clan)
Okay, lower it down.
Senior Brother Bei,
the third batch of materials
sent by the academy has arrived.
Move that box over there.
Okay, quickly send it to the warehouse.
This place is almost full.
First Senior Brother!
Yuhao, you're finally back.
You've been meditating
in the Haishen Pavilion for a month.
We've been so busy.
Senior Brothers, what's going on here?
Did the academy send a lot of materials?
More than that.
Come, let's talk while we walk.
Soul-Guiding Master Corps?
After discussions in Haishen Pavilion
and considering various opinions,
the academy has decided to establish
three Soul-Guiding Master Corps.
Three?
(Just like the Sun-Moon Empire.)
(If one Soul-Guiding Master Corp
has 500 members,)
(equipping three Corps
would mean 1,500 people.)
(It's not easy to produce
equipment for 1,500 people.)
The first Soul-Guiding
Master Corp is named
Tang Clan Soul-Guiding Master Corp.
It's specially approved by the academy
and has the best equipment
among the three.
It has a total of 200 members,
all equipped
with the most advanced soul tools
from the Tang Clan.
It's composed of soul masters
above the soul emperor level.
The leader is Dean Xian Lin'er,
and the deputy leader
is Dean Qian Duoduo.
At the same time,
Tang Clan Soul-Guiding Master Corp
will have a total
of 10 Grand Soul Masters.
All will be supplemented by the academy.
There are 200 people, among whom 10
are Grand Soul Masters.
Even the most powerful national
defense force of the Sun-Moon Empire,
the Royal Soul-Guiding Master Corps,
doesn't have such an exaggerated setup.
Can our Tang Clan meet such
a high demand for soul-guiding tools?
That's why this corp is entirely composed
of close-combat soul-guiding masters.
All the tools equipped are mainly
for enhancing speed and attack power.
The only linked soul tool
is for group defense.
I see. This way, it can indeed
play to its strengths
and make up for its weaknesses.
Then, about the other two
Soul-Guiding Master Corps...
I suppose they are mainly equipped
with long-range tools
and fixed-installation tools.
You're quick, Yuhao.
You got it right away.
About the other two Corps,
one is called the Heavy Artillery
Soul-Guiding Master Corp.
It is equipped with 300 of Tang Clan's
most advanced Zhuge Crossbow Cannons.
The last one is called the Fortress
Soul-Guiding Master Corp.
It has 1,500 soul masters.
It is equipped with one type of tool,
the Terrain Self-propelled Fortress.
There are 300 of them.
These three Soul-Guiding Master Corps
are like three money-devouring beasts.
Nannan, you're starting to sound
like Mr. Qian Duoduo.
Let's not mention
the huge financial cost for now.
To meet the tools of these
three Soul-Guiding Master Corps,
I'm afraid our Tang Clan's
rare metals won't be enough.
Although we took away a batch
of rare metals from the Sun-Moon Empire,
we still lack rare metals
of the highest grade.
Yes, that's why
we urgently called you back.
Got an idea?
Mm-hmm.
Qiuqiu.
Huo Yuhao.
Come with me.
(Shrek City, Sunset Forest, Dragon City)
Our Earth Dragon Clan is located
in the north
of the Heavenly Soul Empire,
near the Arctic Land.
There is a hidden ore vein
in our sect's secret realm.
It's highly likely that a rare type
of rare metal is buried there.
Possible? Hasn't Earth Dragon Clan
detected it themselves?
The temperature in the secret realm is
extremely low and it's very dangerous.
Even a Great Soul Master like my mom
can't go deep inside.
Only a soul master with the ultimate ice
like you can possibly enter.
Since our Earth Dragon Clan
has chosen to join the Tang Clan,
this ore vein naturally
belongs to the Tang Clan.
Moreover...
Moreover?
Dragon City,
where Earth Dragon Clan is located,
has been conquered
by the Sun-Moon Empire.
If the resources within the clan
are not transferred out,
they will inevitably be seized
by the Sun-Moon Empire sooner or later.
We're almost there.
Dragon City, the foundation
of Earth Dragon Clan.
My mom is in a crucial moment
of closed-door cultivation in Shrek City,
so I'm the one bringing you here.
=The Peerless Tang Clan=
Follow me.
(Purple Demon Eye!)
There are guards. What should we do?
I've thought of a way to enter the city.
Firefly's Glow.
(Data Detection System,
Mingdou Mountains, signal normal)
(Warning)
The Navigator has lost contact!
It's okay. New models always
have various minor issues.
It's shift change time.
Where are those two?
Probably gone AWOL. It's so cold.
I don't want to patrol either.
This outfit is so warm.
(Dragon City)
(This Dragon City doesn't
seem to have fallen at all.)
(As a border city near the Arctic Land,
it's quite popular instead.)
(When the Sun-Moon Empire
invaded in force,)
(the entire Celestial Dragon Clan
rose up to resist)
(and assisted the city defense forces
in holding Dragon City.)
(The sect leader, Celestial Dragon Master,
even died a heroic death.)
(Unfortunately, at that time,
our Earth Dragon Sect)
(had already fully
relocated to Shrek City.)
(We couldn't lend them a hand in time.)
(Celestial Dragon Clan...)
(Where's Yu Tianlong?)
(He went missing after the great battle.
I hope he's still alive.)
(This is the City Lord's Mansion.)
(Those are people from
the Sun-Moon Chamber of Commerce.)
(After Dragon City fell,)
(the first batch to enter
the city were these merchants)
(They brought many cold-resistant supplies
and advanced thermal energy devices,)
(which they distributed
at low prices or even for free.)
I'll follow them in and take a look.
Hey,
what about me?
You stay here as a backup.
Give everything to them.
Don't feel bad about it.
The marshal said,
once they get used to living with tools,
they won't be able to live without us.
In a few years, we'll win over the hearts
of the entire city's populace.
(Technological infiltration
is indeed a good strategy.)
(Who exactly is
this mysterious marshal?)
Speaking objectively,
such measures
to improve people's livelihoods
have indeed helped
many civilians in the city.
You're actually siding with them?
(Thermal Energy Device,
Free Distribution Point)
This is a tactic used by many invaders
throughout history.
Kill the resistors
and silence the opposing voices.
Then buy people's hearts with benefits.
Soon, they'll only hear one voice.
Support.
But in the end, it's just to satisfy
the invaders' ambition
of long-term colonization.
As the battle lines stretch,
the people in these colonies
will only become the nourishment
for the war machine.
You seem to know a lot.
The exact same thing happened
on the Douluo Continent
ten thousand years ago.
(Earth Dragon)
Yuhao!
Little girl, I've been waiting for you.
Mountain Python Sect, it's really you.
Sect Leader, capture the young master
of the Earth Dragon Sect
and present her to the Sun-Moon.
Then our sect can secure the position
of the top sect in Dragon City.
So, on the day Dragon City fell,
when the Celestial Dragon Clan
was fighting a bloody battle,
your sect defected
to the Sun-Moon Empire!
Cut the crap. After capturing you,
Nan Shuishui will surely surrender
with her whole sect.
Huo Yuhao, where have you been?
Breath of the Giant Python!
Huo Yuhao, why aren't you
coming out to help?
You can do it. Pull yourself together
and follow my commands.
Aim for the python's vital spot!
An attack from the Kan position.
Retreat to the Li position.
Throw a punch from Kun position.
There's a flaw in the enemy's Xun position.
Throw a palm strike!
Throw a palm strike with your left hand
and gather strength with your right.
Hand of Obliteration.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Rouge Annihilation Sword!
Target the Qian position.
A killing blow in one strike!
You traitorous scum!
You should have died long ago.
Huo Yuhao,
you actually stood by and watched!
Making me deal
with these three stinky pythons alone.
Come in.
Let's go.
(Dragon City, originally the northern fortress
of Heavenly Soul Empire, adjacent to Arctic Land,)
(has abundant mineral resources. It was later
occupied by Sun-Moon Empire.)
(The Earth Dragon Sect, an ancient sect located in Dragon City,)
(inherits the Rouge Dragon
with the power of obliteration.)
(The Sect Leader is Nan Shuishui,
an 82 offensive-type Great Soul Master.)
(The Mountain Python Sect, a local sect
of Earth Dragon Sect, marked by poisonous pythons,)
(has long been in the shadows of
Celestial Dragon Clan and the Earth Dragon Sect.)
With the sound of the cannon,
the Source of Destruction
makes its grand entrance.
I heard you want to join
the Extreme Solo Soldier Plan?
Scan this QR code
and follow Soul Land's official WeChat.
Get official spoilers
and plot developments in advance.
(Scan the QR code
and follow Soul Land's official WeChat)
Even the training secrets
of Shrek Academy are within your reach.
Scan the code quickly!
I'll be waiting for you on WeChat!
(Since the commencement
of Soul Land 2 on 8 Aug 2021,)
(it's been 1567 days since Episode 127 is broadcasted.)
(Total minutes of the animation: 1924)
(Total scene: 44230)
(Total CGI: 14055)
(Total plan of action scene: 8411)
(Total scene model: 416)
(Total character model: 1307)
(Total props model: 984)
(We appreciate
your continuous support and love.)
(The new generation of Shrek Seven Devils
will carry on the mission.)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪The tears you swallow♪
♪Can drown out your weakness♪
♪You vow to be braver,
to hold on to your dreams for life♪
♪Will you still go on?♪
♪Never back down against the wind♪
♪Let the pain live in your eyes♪
♪Don't be afraid
of what the future holds♪
♪Don't forget the hope you once had♪
♪There are as many songs
as there are dreams♪
♪The stormy waves along the way♪
♪Are nothing to fear♪
♪With you by my side through it all♪
♪Burn with passion♪
♪Never forget♪
♪Be brave♪
♪The wind is blowing♪
♪It's calling us♪
♪What are you waiting for?♪
♪Wave♪
♪Goodbye♪
♪Don't look back♪
♪Go after the dreams♪
♪In your heart♪
(Next Episode)
(There seems to be something
underwater drawing me in.)
(This place is indeed a treasure trove.)
The temperature ahead...
I estimate it's nearly absolute zero.
The ice here
seems capable of freezing even souls.
You must be careful!
I must absorb at least half of this
Ten-Thousand-Year
Mystic Ice Essence first.
What did you say, Icy?
How amazing!
- You've regained your memories?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)