[PREVIOUSLY]
Congratulations, Wutong.
My Title will be "Dragon Butterfly."
Xuan Lao, you've broken through?
What I must tell you now
is another method to condense
the second Soul Core.
I'm going to see that person again.
The other reason I gathered you
is for an extremely important matter.
Assassinate Xu Tianran.
The child is teachable.
This is Sky Sun Douluo,
from the Dou Ling Empire.
Now that everyone is here,
let us discuss the operation plan.
let's discuss the action plan.
The operation is codenamed
"Operation Destroy Emperor."
Although Xu Tianran is young,
he is a true warlord.
As long as he lives,
future war is inevitable.
But if we can assassinate Xu Tianran,
the Sun-Moon Empire will surely plunge
into internal chaos.
His several brothers
will inevitably start
a succession struggle.
After all, Xu Tianran's son
was just born.
He is too young to stabilize the throne.
Xu Tianran has a son? Then doesn't that mean...
Whoever helps me avenge my father
will be my benefactor.
Xu Tianran is not your father.
Sister Orange, why torment yourself so?
Our spies in the Sun-Moon Empire
recently brought news
that in seven days,
Xu Tianran will serve as the chief officiant
at the Sun-Moon Empire's
Sacrifice to Heaven ceremony.
That is our optimal timing.
The altar is located
in the southern suburbs of Mingdu.
To lure Xu Tianran's surrounding experts away,
we need a feint to the east,
striking in the west.
Our target is here.
This is the largest arsenal
in Mingdu.
The fifteen Titled Douluo
from our three nations
will be divided into two teams.
Senior Sky Sun will lead one team
to attack this arsenal,
creating a disturbance to draw away
Xu Tianran's nearby experts.
Senior Ontology will lead
four Titled Douluo
to prepare for the thunderous strike
against Xu Tianran.
This action plan is far too crude.
The Sun-Moon Empire possesses
two Limit Douluo!
Even if one is lured away,
the remaining one is still enough to handle
Du Bubai and the four Super Douluo.
Furthermore, an arsenal explosion
wouldn't attract that many experts.
Yuhao,
your task
is to lead everyone into
the Sun-Moon Empire.
Once you enter Mingdu,
your mission ends.
Entering Mingdu shouldn't be difficult.
However, I hope that until we reach Mingdu,
at the very least,
everyone will follow my command.
Only then can I guarantee
I will lead everyone to their positions.
Follow your command?
Kid, how old are you exactly?
Age brings wisdom. In terms of stealth,
we admit we are inferior to Yuhao.
We are not as skilled as him.
I agree to let him command
before we enter Mingdu.
Kid, are you so confident?
I also agree to let Huo Yuhao command.
Brother Du,
there's no time to delay.
We set out first thing tomorrow morning.
Yuhao.
Come, sit.
This operation is very dangerous,
Yuhao.
If your role weren't so critical,
I would never have asked Shrek Academy
to let you come.
Remember this:
Your task is solely to bring them safely
into Mingdu.
Hiding your identity is sufficient.
When they act, you do not participate.
If you sense the situation turning bad,
flee immediately.
Do not concern yourself with the others.
My Lord Duke, why speak like this?
I cannot explain much to you.
Just remember to do as I say.
Prioritize your own safety above all else.
Alright, I understand.
It seems this operation
has major issues.
The White Tiger Duke is warning you.
This "Destroy Emperor Operation"...
there are details he cannot disclose.
He seems to care for you deeply.
Your hostility towards him
isn't as intense as before.
Indeed.
Though I'm unwilling to admit it,
that is the truth.
During the days you were missing,
I returned to Star Luo City.
I discovered he had restored
my mother's grave.
Later, fighting in the Star Luo Empire,
we interacted with him more frequently.
I have indeed changed my impression
of him somewhat.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Brother Du,
you seem to value
that kid Huo Yuhao greatly.
You are very tense.
If not for that,
you wouldn't fail to see that child's potential.
His soul power is capped at Rank 89,
yet his soul power intensity already rivals
that of a Titled Douluo.
His spiritual power is comparable
to a Super Douluo.
A Super Douluo?
Moreover, he has already condensed
a Soul Core.
With his talent,
in less than ten years,
his cultivation will surpass yours.
You are too impatient and restless;
your perception has declined drastically.
Indeed.
The national strength of the Dou Ling Empire
doesn't match the Tianhun Empire.
If the Sun-Moon Empire redirects its offensive,
Dou Ling Empire absolutely cannot hold.
This operation...
is gambling the future of the three original
Douluo nations.
Saying I'm not nervous would be a lie.
I never expected we'd fall to such a state.
There was a time
I had absolute confidence
we could keep the enemy beyond our borders.
But now it seems,
how laughable that was.
Being a frog in a well has left us
far too behind.
We can only stake everything on this one throw.
Brother Du, is the intelligence
from the Mingdu side reliable?
Absolutely certain.
Once you succeed, flee immediately.
Don't mind me.
Alright. Be careful in everything.
Sun-Moon scum! Blood debts
must be repaid in blood!
Senior Du, take care on the road.
Your Excellencies, I wish you a smooth journey
and a triumphant return.
Return victorious soon.
Yuhao.
We're at the border.
Spiritual Detection Shared.
What powerful spiritual force.
Extending vision across
the entire Mingdou Mountains.
A 360-degree field with no blind spots.
Every minute object is crystal clear.
This kid's spiritual power
is truly unimaginable.
Shrek Academy truly lives up to its name.
Worthy of being called
the Monster Academy.
Impressive, Little Friend Huo.
Sorry for raising my voice earlier;
please don't take offense.
You flatter me, Senior.
Huo Yuhao's Spiritual Sharing
not only assists fifteen Titled Douluo
simultaneously,
but also projects a unique action route
for each individual,
each path not interfering
with the others.
This is...
Multitasking with terrifying
spiritual control.
Your Eye of Destiny has awakened further.
What a pity, what a pity.
If only you had met this old man
a bit earlier,
I would have gladly taken you
as my final disciple.
Then I wouldn't have had to let
that old geezer Mu En snatch you away.
Senior Du, mind your words.
A teacher for a day
is a father for life.
Even if Teacher is no longer with us,
I will not switch allegiances.
You don't need to be displeased.
Even if Mu En were still alive,
I would still address him that way.
If not for him, my elder brother
would not have died.
Senior Du Bubai,
seems to have lost his former vigor.
Even when facing the Beast God Di Tian,
he was never this dejected.
Enough, that's all ancient history.
Lead the way.
Alright.
Second Soul Skill: Simulation.
Group invisibility.
Fortune.
Once we reach Mingdu,
everyone changes their appearance.
Disperse and settle in.
Groups of three.
Maintain contact using the prepared
Communication Soul Tools.
Use coded language when contacting.
Yuhao and Tang Wutong, stick with me.
The previous Mingdu Explosion
was terrifying.
Yet now, Mingdu has fully recovered.
Moreover,
it exudes a deeper, more dangerous aura.
Like a steel behemoth.
Teacher Xuan said
the most advanced place
for Sun-Moon soul tools
is not Mingde Hall,
but the Royal Worship Hall,
controlled by the royal family.
Also called the Royal Research Institute.
Nearly all Class 9 soul engineers
in the Sun-Moon Empire
are members of this institute.
With it, the foundation of the
Sun-Moon Empire remains secure.
Long Shangtian!
Precious treasures...
Sun and Moon in tandem,
Imperial Heaven's blessing.
Sacrifice to Heaven Ceremony,
national fortune prospers.
Breaking ground, expanding borders,
prestige spreads far and wide.
Your Majesty's merits shine
bright as the sun and moon.
It's those Royal Guards again.
How hateful! They treat us
like less than human.
Recently, His Majesty is to hold
the Sacrifice to Heaven Ceremony.
These Royal Guards have been leaving
the palace grounds frequently.
But it's we who suffer for it.
The Royal Guards—
their soul tool configuration rivals
the Hand of the Nation-Protector.
Just how much hidden depth
does the Sun-Moon Empire possess?
Detection soul tools cover nearly
the entire city of Mingdu.
It seems the Sun-Moon Empire
takes this ceremony very seriously.
Good evening, Sir and Madam.
Huo Yuhao, the Pavilion Master requests your presence.
Enter.
Sit.
Well? Did you find anything
on your stroll outside?
Aside from detection soul tools
blanketing the entire city,
there is nothing unusual within Mingdu.
The imperial son born to Xu Tianran
and Orange is named Xu Yunhan.
Shortly after his full moon ceremony,
Xu Tianran established him as Crown Prince.
Senior Du, why tell me all this?
The Crown Prince represents
a nation's future.
Since Xu Tianran is disabled,
having a Crown Prince is even more critical.
After establishing the heir,
dissenting voices from the royal family
quickly vanished.
And the Empress, Orange,
possesses outstanding military talent
and illustrious battle merits.
She has become the Commander-in-Chief
of the Three Armies.
This has made Xu Tianran's throne
even more secure.
Xu Tianran seized power through coup,
so his foundation was originally unstable.
Yet through this series of actions,
he has become the emperor in Sun-Moon's
history
with the most stable imperial authority.
We came to Mingdu this time
not only to assassinate Xu Tianran,
but also for another mission.
Another mission?
[Huo Yuhao in Disguise]
[Tang Wutong in Disguise]
The operation is named...
"Destroy Emperor Operation."
Groups of three.
Once in Mingdu, everyone changes
their appearance.
Wherever the continent reaches
is His Majesty's territory.
Crush the Three Douluo Nations,
unify the continent.
You wolf-hearted cur! Today,
this old man acts on heaven's behalf!
I will collect you, you vile beast!
Enough killing, Old Poison.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™