Come on, Yuhao.
Although I don't hold much hope...
Let me see just how far you can go.
Seeing how the Tang Sect has developed...
I'm truly happy.
With the medicinal effect of the
Qiankun Creation Pill...
Extending Teacher Xiaoya's life by three years
shouldn't be a problem.
The Qiankun Creation Pill helped Wutong
successfully break through the level 90 bottleneck.
She's just one soul ring away
from becoming a Title Douluo.
Wutong, have you decided on your title yet?
I decided long ago.
My title...
Will be Dragon Butterfly.
Dragon Butterfly... what a fine name.
Congratulations, Wutong.
Not long ago, Teacher Xuan also broke through.
Senior Brother Ji's cultivation has reached level 89 as well.
Yuhao, you can't fall behind now.
You've been stuck at the level 89 bottleneck
for quite a while, haven't you?
It's my own fault for condensing my first soul core
too early.
It made breaking through to Title Douluo
much more difficult.
Yuhao.
Senior Brother.
Yuhao, the academy wants you to come over.
Apparently Elder Xuan and the others
have come out of seclusion.
Elder Xuan has come out of seclusion?
Elder Xuan, you've broken through!
I finally broke through that barrier.
It really wasn't easy.
This bottleneck had troubled me for countless years.
Breaking through in a single stroke
feels like being reborn.
Congratulations, Elder Xuan.
It's not just me.
The Qiankun Creation Pill you sent...
Also helped Shaozhe and Lin'er break through
their current bottlenecks.
Their soul power increased by one level.
Thank you, Yuhao.
Beibei, Yuhao, Wutong...
The reason I called you here today
is for another extremely important matter.
A few days ago, the Heavenly Soul Empire,
Dou Ling Empire, and Star Luo Empire
simultaneously sent envoys to our academy.
They hope we can lend a hand
and take part in a secret operation.
A secret operation?
To assassinate Xu Tianran.
The current situation on the continent
is turbulent and unpredictable.
Although the Sun Moon Empire
hasn't expanded the war for now...
They've deployed a large number of
high-altitude surveillance soul tools
along the border.
All the signs point to them preparing
for an even larger war.
At this moment,
launching a decapitation strike against
the Sun Moon Empire...
Is the most economical and effective method.
And once Xu Tianran falls,
the Sun Moon Empire will inevitably fall
into long-term chaos.
For the Heavenly Soul, Dou Ling,
and Star Luo Empires...
Ending the war in one fell swoop
might not be impossible.
It's too risky.
As emperor, Xu Tianran is sure to be protected
by a large number of top experts.
And he himself is a Title Douluo-level powerhouse.
Although the original three empires of the Douluo Continent
have always stood together with Shrek Academy...
For us to join such a risky and aggressive operation...
If Shrek is to participate as well...
We're not asking you to join directly.
The envoys from the three empires
only have one request.
Assistance.
For this operation,
Yuhao's Spiritual Detection Sharing...
Is the support ability they need most.
With this ability, the chances of the operation
succeeding will increase dramatically.
Alright, I accept. I'll go with them.
Yuhao...
As Dean Xian said,
assassinating Xu Tianran...
Is indeed the most economical way
to prevent the war from expanding right now.
That man is cunning and paranoid by nature.
He played a decisive role
in the Sun Moon Empire launching wars abroad.
If we can eliminate him...
The Sun Moon Empire's war machine
will very likely grind to a halt.
Besides, I've been stuck at the level 89 bottleneck
for a long time too.
I need real combat experience
to find an opportunity to break through.
Then the seven of us Shrek Monsters
should go together.
We seven are one. We live and die together.
No. This operation is extremely confidential.
If all seven Shrek Monsters move out together,
the number of people would be too many.
It wouldn't be appropriate.
Senior Brother, thank you for your kindness.
Don't worry. I'll definitely return safely.
Alright... you must come back safe and sound.
Yuhao...
I'll go with you.
No, it's too dangerous.
My cultivation isn't below yours,
and I have ways to protect myself.
Didn't we agree that we'd face
anything together?
Fine.
We'll discuss the specific action plan later.
Yuhao, Wutong, come with me.
The most important step in breaking through
to Title Douluo is condensing a soul core.
Yuhao, you condensed your first soul core
very early, back when you were still a Soul Saint.
So the difficulty of condensing a second soul core
is easy to imagine.
And if you wish to charge toward
Limit Douluo in the future...
You may even need to condense
a never-before-seen third soul core.
If only I hadn't condensed my first soul core
so early...
No. That step wasn't a mistake.
Condensing your first soul core
during the Soul Saint stage...
Has made your soul power
extraordinarily solid.
If you successfully condense
a second soul core...
Your strength will far surpass
that of an ordinary Title Douluo.
Directly reaching the level of a Super Douluo.
And on that foundation,
if you condense a third soul core...
No one on the entire Douluo Continent
will be your match.
Not even a Limit Douluo.
This time, when I successfully broke through
to Limit Douluo...
I gained a much deeper understanding of soul cores.
Listen carefully. I'm sure it will help you.
Thank you, Elder Xuan.
The first soul core is an extreme compression
of your soul power...
To achieve a qualitative leap,
making it the core of your soul power.
The second soul core, however,
is completely different from the first.
Because when you condense the second soul core...
The first soul core has already become
the core of your soul power.
The second soul core will inevitably
interact with it.
The slightest carelessness could cause the two soul cores
to collide, leading to your body exploding.
Back then, the method Elder Mu taught me
for condensing the second soul core...
Was called homotopic resonance.
Simply put, the second soul core
submits to the first soul core...
And revolves around it.
That way, the second soul core
will inevitably be much smaller than the first.
Correct.
Therefore, anyone who condenses their second soul core
using the homotopic resonance method...
Will never be able to condense a third soul core.
Yuhao, what I'm about to tell you now...
Is another method to condense the second soul core.
Yin-Yang complementarity.
Yin-Yang complementarity?
The so-called yin-yang complementarity...
Means the two soul cores depend on each other
and revolve around one another.
A second soul core condensed this way...
Will be far stronger than one formed
through homotopic resonance.
At the same time, the condensation process
is also much more dangerous.
Please teach me, Elder Xuan.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Using this method to condense the second soul core...
You must completely resist the attractive force
of the first soul core during the process.
It will require tremendous willpower.
Furthermore, the total soul power of the second soul core
must be exactly the same as the first.
At the same time, the rotation direction of the second soul core
must be completely opposite to the first.
Ultimately forming an extreme balance
of yin-yang complementarity.
Elder Xuan, does the Beast God Di Tian
have yin-yang complementary dual soul cores?
Very good. It seems you already have
some understanding of yin-yang complementarity.
Di Tian indeed possesses yin-yang complementary dual soul cores.
The reason he succeeded
is because his physical body is strong enough...
To withstand the extreme pulling force
from the first soul core...
During the condensation of the second.
At the same time, his lifespan is long enough...
To allow him to slowly accumulate
the second soul core over a long period.
And it is precisely because his soul cores
are yin-yang complementary...
That Long Xiaoyao and Ye Xishui
are not his match.
Even if the two of them join forces.
Even two Limit Douluos working together
are no match for Di Tian.
Di Tian is actually that powerful?
Regrettably...
Di Tian’s cultivation method
cannot be applied to you.
You don’t possess his supreme bloodline
or his powerful physique.
Nor do you have his extraordinarily long lifespan.
You must comprehend your own path.
I will definitely succeed.
And...
With three soul cores.
That is the main peak of the Ming Dou Mountain Range.
Back when Ye Xishui fought Di Tian,
their battle shook heaven and earth.
The majestic main peak of the Ming Dou Mountain Range...
Was leveled flat by the mere shockwaves
of their fight.
Now this place has become
the location of the White Tiger Duke’s command tent.
I’m going to see that person again...
Yuhao, you seem a little nervous.
Do I?
Benefactor, you’ve arrived.
General Zhang, there’s no need for such formality.
The Marshal and the Title Douluos
have been waiting in the tent for quite some time.
Please, come in.
Yuhao...
Yuhao, you’re here.
You must be Tang Wutong.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Wutong has already advanced to Title Douluo.
Her title is Dragon Butterfly.
Her strength is actually above mine.
You’ve finally come to see your father.
That’s wonderful.
Du— Brother...
What is it?
In the army, we address people by their position.
It’s “Regiment Commander.”
Senior Dai, long time no see.
Welcome, Junior Brother Huo.
What formidable soul power.
I’ve already reached Soul Douluo level...
And I’m even more outstanding
than my father was at my age.
But compared to Huo Yuhao,
I still can’t compare.
And he’s a full seven years younger than me.
Brother...
Come, let me introduce everyone.
This is the outstanding genius
from Shrek Academy...
Huo Yuhao, the Eye of the Asura.
Don’t let his young age fool you.
He helped us tremendously back then.
Without him, Star Luo might never have
been able to reclaim the Ming Dou Mountain Range.
Truly a hero from a young age.
Senior Poison...
How come Senior Du’s cultivation has dropped
slightly compared to when he fought Di Tian?
It seems the losses suffered by the Body Sect
were even more severe than expected.
Half of the Title Douluos here
are Super Douluos.
This one’s cultivation is as high as level 97,
second only to Senior Poison.
Reclaiming the Ming Dou Mountain Range...
Naturally, the Duke deserves the greatest credit.
I wouldn’t dare take the credit.
Yuhao, come.
Let me introduce you.
This is the Heavenly Sun Douluo from the Dou Ling Empire.
Senior Heavenly Sun is over 150 years old.
He’s a senior figure in the soul master world.
A level 97 Super Douluo
with extremely formidable strength.
This operation will be led by
Senior Body Sect and Senior Heavenly Sun.
Greetings, Senior Heavenly Sun.
A promising young talent indeed.
Level 89 soul power...
The younger generation is truly formidable.
We old folks really are about to step off
the stage of history.
Since everyone is here,
let’s discuss the operation plan first.
Dai Hao, you explain.
For this operation,
our Star Luo Empire...
Along with the Heavenly Soul Empire and Dou Ling Empire,
will each contribute five Title Douluos.
We will head to the Sun Moon Empire together...
To carry out the assassination
of the Sun Moon Empire’s emperor, Xu Tianran.
The operation is codenamed:
Emperor Extinction.
[Tang Wutong — Titled Douluo]
[Sun Douluo - Debut Level: Level 97 - As the foremost offering priest of the Spirit Hall, he possesses top-tier strength among Super Douluo. His martial soul, Sun, is a fire-attribute martial soul of the highest grade. At over 150 years old, his combat experience is extremely rich. As the chief priest of the Spirit Hall, Sun Douluo’s overall strength surpasses all others.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™