(Adapted from Soul Land 2: The Peerless Tang Clan
written by Tangjia Sanshao)
(Underage viewers must seek
parental permission before watching.)
(All content is computer-generated.
Please do not imitate it in real life.)
(Previous Episode)
Beast God, Di Tian, it's you, huh?
How do you know
I can't arrive in true form?
The situation is terrible.
Many meridians are ruptured.
His vitality is extremely weak.
Wutong, thank you.
You... Don't be so reckless
in the future.
(In this vast world,)
(there is endless
elemental energy to absorb.)
Episode 126
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(What if I infuse spiritual power
into this solidified soul power?)
This soul power funnel seems to have
developed a strange magnetic field.
And it's already starting
to affect the surrounding space.
In terms of size,
it's almost as big as a small black hole
inside Di Tian's body.
But its purity is much lower.
With my current abilities,
I can't absorb this soul power funnel
into my body.
This highly compressed soul power
could explode at any moment.
For safety's sake, I must
find an open and deserted place.
(The elemental energy
of heaven and earth within thousands)
(of square meters around
is converging here.)
(It's amazing.)
(What kind of law is this exactly?)
(It's out of control!)
(I can't observe it closely anymore.)
What's going on? Is it an enemy attack?
I don't know. The communication team
hasn't reported yet.
(The explosive power is so strong...)
(And this is just
an unfinished product.)
Huo Yuhao!
Where have you been?
I... I went outside
to get some fresh air.
Getting fresh air takes so long?
I... The night is so beautiful tonight.
How did you know I wasn't in the tent?
I was passing by and thought
I'd drop in to check on you.
Since you're fine, let's go back
to the academy tomorrow.
Finally, we can return to Shrek City.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Members of Shrek!
The front line is in a tense situation.
Marshal and Princess Jiu
are both tied up.
But the rewards
Marshal requested from His Majesty,
especially the title
conferred upon Mr. Huo,
are on their way.
Please wait a few more days.
After the conferment,
Marshal will personally
host a banquet to bid you farewell.
I don't need any rewards.
I appreciate the kindness
of White Tiger Duke and His Majesty.
Farewell, everyone. Until we meet again.
Not even the title?
We've been flying for six hours.
Let's take a rest.
Huo Yuhao, I want grilled fish.
(Why does he look so preoccupied?)
The grilled fish is ready.
Everyone can eat now.
I'm not hungry.
I'll eat after cultivating.
Yuhao, you're working so hard.
How can we keep up?
It smells so good.
Nannan.
Do you think today's grilled fish
is different from last time?
It seems like something's missing.
I don't think there's any difference.
It's still as delicious as ever.
I see.
Indeed, something is missing.
But it's not ours.
It's your grilled fish.
(Shrek City)
Third Senior Brother, you guys
go back to the Tang Clan first.
I'm going to the Haishen Pavilion
to consult with Mr. Xuan.
Hello, Ms. Tang. Hello, Senior Huo.
It feels so good to be home.
I'm going to Mr. Xuan's place. Farewell.
(Tang Wutong, why do you
pay so much attention to him?)
(You can't keep doing this.)
Mr. Mu, I'm back.
On this trip,
I actually saw Senior Ye Xishui.
She's now the Death Master
of the Sun-Moon Empire.
Mr. Mu,
can you hear me?
Mr. Mu can't respond to you.
During the beast tide, he
released energy that damaged his soul.
Now he can only recuperate
inside the Golden Tree.
The situation on the continent
has suddenly become so dire.
I never expected
Sun-Moon Empire to be hiding so deeply.
Ye Xishui is indeed still alive...
It's just that she and Long Xiaoyao
have sided with the Sun-Moon Empire...
That's something I didn't anticipate.
Two level 99 Super Masters...
They're enough to shake
the entire continent's situation.
Didn't Senior Du Busi
also break through?
Maybe...
Du injured his essence during the surprise
attack by the Sun-Moon Empire.
Plus, the younger generation of
Physical Sect has been almost wiped out.
Their morale has plummeted.
It'll be hard for them to compete
with Long Xiaoyao and Ye Xishui again.
After this surprise attack,
the Heavenly Soul Empire
has been severely weakened.
I'm afraid they won't have
the strength to fight again.
Mr. Xuan,
can we gather some hidden sects to fight
against the Sun-Moon Empire together?
After all, if the three
original Douluo Continent empires
are invaded by the Sun-Moon Empire,
they won't fare well either.
It's already being done.
Many sects have responded positively.
But in the face of the Sun-Moon
Empire's most advanced weapons,
this resistance force is still too weak.
Mr. Xuan, there's something
I'd like to ask you for advice on.
Previously, when I faced Ye Xishui
in the Mingdou Mountains,
I activated the Reverse Scale
to summon Di Tian to possess me.
Di Tian injected his power into my body
through spatial force,
descending through my body.
At that time, I noticed
that Di Tian's soul power operates
entirely differently from mine.
As if it was a series
of interconnected black holes.
It contained an extremely
terrifying amount of spatial force.
The knowledge taught at the academy
only goes up to the Great Soul Master.
It doesn't cover the changes in soul power
after reaching the Grand Soul Master.
Is Di Tian's black hole soul power
unique to Super Master?
Although they're both Super Masters,
Di Tian is clearly
stronger than Ye Xishui.
If Ye Xishui doesn't
use her Tower of Reaper,
she's no match for Di Tian.
I didn't expect
you to reach this level so quickly.
Your judgment is correct.
After a soul master becomes
the Grand Soul Master,
their soul power will transform from its
original liquid state to a solid state.
After completing the solid transformation,
a cultivation bottleneck
will be encountered.
For the vast majority of soul masters,
this bottleneck
is very difficult to overcome.
Why?
It's simple.
Solidified soul power cannot flow.
Therefore, after many Grand Soul Masters
solidify their soul power,
their cultivation progress
becomes extremely slow.
However, solidifying soul power
is the foundation for breaking
through to the Grand Soul Master.
The solidified soul power
will settle in the dantian,
known as the soul core.
The soul core continuously rotates,
absorbing external soul power
for the soul master to use.
So the reason Di Tian is so powerful
is because his soul core can still flow.
Your reasoning is sound.
However, Di Tian's technique
is even more superb.
=The Peerless Tang Clan=
This is the principle
behind Di Tian's soul power situation.
Using his own soul power as a guide,
he causes spatial collapse,
forming a black hole that can
endlessly devour the elemental energy.
Such black hole soul power
requires spiritual power to control.
I can only maintain it temporarily,
while Di Tian can keep it
in a constant state.
This is the gap between me and Di Tian.
Keep it constant?
Wouldn't that mean Di Tian's spiritual
power consumption is extremely huge?
No, he has condensed a second soul core.
The two soul cores complement
each other, forming a stable balance.
The second soul core...
All Super Masters have
condensed a second soul core.
Mr. Mu, Ye Xishui, Long Xiaoyao,
and even Du Busi are all like this.
However, their second soul cores are
all much smaller than their first ones.
Only Di Tian's second soul core
is on par with his first in strength.
So,
he is far more powerful
than ordinary Super Masters.
His strength has already
approached that of a deity infinitely.
A deity?
Yuhao, you have twin martial souls.
It will be much easier for you
to become a Super Master than for us.
When you break through
to become a Grand Soul Master,
you must strive to achieve
twin soul cores simultaneously.
Your spiritual power far exceeds that
of soul masters of the same level.
It can even rival that
of a Grand Soul Master.
At that time, spiritual power
will be your second soul core.
Mr. Xuan,
what if I achieve a soul core
at my current stage?
Then your cultivation speed
will increase dramatically.
Because the absorption speed of a soul
core for the elemental energy
is several times
or even dozens of times faster
than that of meditation cultivation.
However, when you reach level 90,
the difficulty of breaking through
to become a Grand Soul Master
will be unprecedentedly high.
Because the first soul core will exert
a huge pulling force on the condensation
of the second soul core.
This is a problem
that even many level 98 Super Masters
face when attempting to break
through to level 99 Super Masters
and feel helpless about.
Mr. Xuan, I want to try.
Alright, I will personally guard you.
Good, keep going.
Let me see how far
you can go in the end.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(Compress... Compress again...)
(Rotate... Rotate again...)
(The solid soul power has exceeded half
of the total soul power in my body.)
(My soul power is draining rapidly.)
(Fifty percent. Sixty percent.
Seventy percent.)
What a strong soul power fluctuation!
Someone is attempting
to become a Super Master.
The core of the soul power fluctuation
is in Mr. Xuan's room.
Since Mr. Xuan is guarding,
there should be no need to worry.
Let's observe here for a while.
That's weird. Who could be attempting
to become a Super Master?
Could it be him?
Eighty percent of the soul power
has been devoured!
Yuhao, hold on.
Your solid soul power
has already been attributed.
If you can successfully
construct a soul core at this level,
you will be able to reach level 89
in a very short time.
Although breaking through to become
a Grand Soul Master will be difficult,
but this is also your opportunity.
Hold on!
Yuhao has reached his limit.
Out of necessity,
I'll use my soul power to confine
his solidified soul power,
and then send it high
into the sky to detonate.
There shouldn't be too much danger.
It's just that Yuhao
will need a few days to recover.
What is that?
Life Reflection Shield!
Skydream!
Keep going. I've got your back.
You're infusing your essence power
into Yuhao's body.
In that case,
if Yuhao fails to ascend to godhood,
when he dies of natural causes,
you'll die too.
When I chose Yuhao,
I had already decided
to share life and death with him.
(Yuhao's soul power and spiritual power
are both nearing their limits.)
(But I can't interrupt him
at this moment.)
(Otherwise,
he'll suffer severe backlash.)
Come on.
Collapse!
(It feels like my soul
is being sucked in.)
(There's endless darkness
in that black hole vortex.)
(Endless unknowns...)
(Yet it's intimately connected to me.)
(Is this my soul core?)
(Huo Yuhao's first soul core is of spiritual
attribute, taking the form of a black hole.)
(The first soul core provides
powerful assistance to Huo Yuhao.)
(Condensing a soul core
is a necessary step)
(for a soul master to ascend
to the Grand Soul Master.)
(Xuan Zi's soul core is
of earth element attribute.)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™