(Copyright Notice)
♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Audience under 18 are requested to watch
with the permission of their guardians.)
(The whole video is made by CG.
Please do not copy in real life.)
(The film is purely fictitious and does not
serve as a basis for scientific knowledge.)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
This is the "Star Map."
It can contain a massive number
of Sealing Stars.
Once you have gathered the complete Codex,
you will not be far from fully controlling
the Starry Tower.
I will work hard, Teacher.
I will lead the Earth lineage
to stand among the strongest of the universe.
(Feng, where are you?)
(I miss you so much.)
If there is still no resolution,
our Ross family will...
I didn't expect
the Ross family representative
to be you.
Episode 198
(Starry Tower)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Six thousand years ago,
I tried to warn King Quwu
to beware of King Tienson,
yet he still fell under the siege
of the demon clan.
All these years,
I used my true body under the alias
"King Samhoy"
to investigate everywhere.
I found that the incidents where King Tienson's
teammates were ambushed
happened more than once.
It's just that every time, King Tienson
cleaned things up flawlessly,
leaving almost no survivors,
so no one ever discovered his true face.
He actually uses these despicable tricks.
Since he has provoked me,
there is no chance he'll escape alive.
Starry Tower,
search all human immortals inside.
Find this person.
There are currently 359 human immortals
inside the tower,
none matching this person's physical features.
None?
Search previous records.
According to records,
the human matching that description
left 1,800 years ago.
Master, what should we do now?
King Tienson is still a member
of the Hone Alliance.
I'll ask Queen Starphantom later.
We'll naturally discover his whereabouts.
But before that,
to ensure nothing goes wrong when we face
King Tienson,
we must first expand our power.
Who are we going to find for help?
The immortals of all races inside the tower.
A large-scale hunt
is about to begin.
Go!
This kind of attack can't kill me.
What?
Lost 52% of my immortal body?
Run!
Trying to control me?
No! No!
I'd rather fall!
Explode!
(To prepare for battling King Tienson,
who excels in soul-attacks,)
(I set my sights on)
(soul-type masters at peak King level
and above)
(and began the trials.)
(And I explored the power of the Star Map.)
(After several failures,)
(I finally subdued the first expert.)
(With the addition of King Liamson,)
(King Cushoo)
(our hunting success rate greatly increased.)
(King Junsong)
(Over the next month,)
(King Forsway)
(my followers rapidly grew to nine.)
(King Tetchy)
(The news of me)
(King Churtsan)
(slaughtering)
(King Jehong)
(countless aliens)
(King Beimay)
(spread quickly.)
(But because of this,)
(it also attracted more ambitious predators.)
(Of the nine,)
(King Liamson has the strongest soul ability.)
(King Camarrow previously got)
(the Purple Bell. King Forsway,)
(based on his fighting styles,)
(he is best suited for the new treasure,
the Ice-Soul Net.)
(These three can become my main force.)
Young,
I've found King Tienson's coordinates.
(Seventh Battlefield)
He's in the Twin Vortex Domain
(The Twin Vortex Domain)
of the Seventh Battlefield.
(Twin Vortex Domain, Seventh Battlefield)
King Bladeriver.
I knew that if you didn't die,
you'd be trouble.
I didn't expect that in just
six thousand years,
you'd become this terrifying.
Teleport?
King Forsway,
King Liamson, King Samhoy,
all limit king level.
These three are not to be provoked.
We're leaving.
Trying to escape?
Go all out.
Kill them all!
It's King Forsway's ultimate technique,
Forsway Sea.
Being enveloped by it severely limits
our movement.
Force your way out!
Ice-Soul Net!
Scatter!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
- Swallowed Star -
- Starry Tower -
(Darn it!)
(I have to eliminate King Forsway first!)
The Purple Bell isn't just defense.
Let him taste its real power.
Demonic Flame Bell!
It's like snow meeting boiling water.
It can't resist at all.
Only 33% immortal body left!
I am attacked by an alien squad!
They have a heavy treasure!
Hurry, save me!
King Bladeriver!
I knew it was you.
King Tienson.
No! Never!
Master.
Where are the aliens?
The space has been sealed.
They couldn't have escaped
in such a short time.
Search.
(King Snowhorn)
Detected hidden signal.
So strong! Limit king level!
How dare you attack your own ally!?
It's King Bladeriver!
And King Tienson is also here!
I gave my all to rescue King Tienson.
Instead, I was attacked by my own people.
Misunderstanding!
We didn't know King Bladeriver arrived first!
Yes! We thought
an alien squad was hiding there!
Since King Tienson is unharmed,
we'll return to formation!
Remove the space seal now!
Wait.
Everyone, I just contacted the military system.
Guess what I found.
King Bladeriver is no longer in the system.
He's retired.
His tremendous wealth...
That means
we can...
King Bladeriver risked his life to save me,
and you dare plot against his treasures!?
King Tienson,
you'd better step aside.
rest for now.
Leave everything to me.
King Bladeriver may be retired,
but he's still a human elite.
I've heard he was only peak king level,
yet he managed to slaughter
that many powerhouses.
He must have heavy treasures.
Interesting.
Hone Alliance members won't abandon
their principles.
Hone Alliance won't do anything,
but we aren't from the Hone Alliance.
Do it!
Die!
Good.
(You dare covet the treasure
with such meager power?)
Such strong space fluctuations!
What!?
Go to hell!
Kill him!
Shining Moon Strike!
You want to kill me?
Keep dreaming.
Heaven-Rending Claw!
No!!
(Darn it!)
(Just a moment and 35% of my immortal body
is gone!)
Die!
King Bladeriver!
(So fast!)
(The Wings of Slayer Wu can't dodge it.)
(Whip Shadow!)
(King Sevenswords!)
What!?
King Sevenswords.
You managed to survive one of my thrown swords.
You have some skill.
King Sevenswords, a powerhouse like you,
I've long wanted to test myself against you.
Good.
Come on.
(Twin Vortex Domain: the smaller)
(is 3.9 light-years across.)
(The larger, 4.2. The deeper you go,)
(the stronger the pull. Until)
(it reverses into repulsion.)
(No Kings have reached the core.)
(King Snowhorn, cold and ruthless.)
(A human powerhouse lacking
sense of camaraderie.)
(King Snowhorn, cold and ruthless.)
(he sought to seize his treasures. Front Back)
(Q: What's the brightest known star like?)
(A: In July 2010, astronomers)
(found an astonishing star in the)
(Large Magellanic Cloud's Tarantula)
(Nebula, 165,000 light-years away.)
(It was named R136a1. Its mass is)
(estimated to be 230–345 times)
(that of the Sun, and its luminosity is
6.16 million times the Sun's,)
(making it the brightest known star.)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star"
available on Starting point Chinese net)
(Copyrights reserved)
(by Shanghai Tencent Penguin
Film Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Next Episode Preview)
There's an immigrant ship approaching.
This is Earth.
Identify yourselves, outsiders.
Who gave you permission?
This is the voice.
Luo Feng is getting way too arrogant.
King Sevenswords's sword force is unmatched,
completely overwhelming King Bladeriver.
King Sevenswords, your sword seems slower.
No matter how capable he is,
he can't shake our foundation.
Louder.
You think you can come after me?
How ridiculous.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™