(Copyright Notice)
♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Audience under 18 are requested to watch
with the permission of their guardians.)
(The whole video is made by CG.
Please do not copy in real life.)
(The film is purely fictitious and does not
serve as a basis for scientific knowledge.)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(What force is supporting him?)
(I miss you all so much.)
(I really do.)
Now, countless forces are watching us.
Master.
I made it.
I often sit on the mountain peak,
many beings in the universe call me
Zoranco.
Episode 197
[Starry Tower]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
I have prepared two supreme treasures for you.
The Starry Tower is one of them.
And the other is called
the Raid Armor.
Although you have not seen it,
you have already had some connection with it.
The Raid Armor is the personal battle armor
Teacher forged for you.
It possesses the ability to birth
offspring armor forms.
The Soldier Armor, General Armor, King Armor,
and even
the higher-level Emperor Armor
you've encountered
are all offspring born from the Raid Armor.
It is a treasure coveted even by Cosmic Lords.
(So I had already contacted offspring
of the Raid Armor.)
(Perhaps the reason I could obtain the Soldier,
General, and King Armors)
(was not pure coincidence.)
With such generosity from Teacher,
Luo Feng,
do you have anything to say?
Thank you for your guidance, Teacher.
But to activate it requires the power
of a hundred million–fold Realm Lord.
With your current strength, you still
cannot use it.
For now, I will store it with
the Flame God Race,
and your Second Senior Brother
will safeguard it temporarily.
Do not worry.
I have also prepared a treasure
that you can use right now.
The "Original Soul."
I gave it to your Second Senior Brother
earlier.
It is also capable of producing offspring.
These are
cosmic strings linking different dimensions?
What you are seeing
are the Soldier, General, King, and Emperor
Souls born from the Original Soul—
a supreme treasure for cultivating the soul.
It will greatly benefit the Earth lineage.
The Earth lineage?
The Flame God Race is born with
extraordinary talent.
They are natural-born warriors.
Your Second Senior Brother, Emperor Flame,
is among the best.
But in terms of soul power,
they are rather ordinary.
To make up for this flaw,
Teacher created the Earth lineage.
(So the Earth lineage)
(was created for this purpose.)
Emperor Flame already has the Original Soul's
main body.
Of the remaining million offspring souls,
you may take a portion.
The rest will be
supplied to the Earth lineage.
In the future,
when you become a supreme powerhouse,
under your protection and guidance,
they will naturally grow into a mighty race.
With this mission,
I'll put in all my effort.
Aside from these,
there is one final treasure.
Come with me.
Go.
(This speed clearly surpasses light-speed,)
(yet we haven't entered the Dark Universe.)
(Everything ahead remains perfectly visible.)
Surprised?
Teacher is one of the strongest beings
in the universe.
He can change rules with his words.
If he says that countless beings
whose lifespans have reached
their end shall fall,
then countless powerhouses will fall.
If he says a star shall vanish,
or a planet shall release endless radiance,
then it will be so.
If he says the limit is no longer light-speed,
but ten times the speed of light,
then within this region,
tenfold light-speed becomes reality.
Do you know why
the Nine Spiral Nebula exists in the distance?
I do not, Teacher.
It is the Starry Tower actively absorbing
cosmic energy
to sustain itself.
You cannot provide such overwhelming energy,
so you cannot fully drive it.
That is why the Starry Tower
must remain here.
As a substitute,
you may use this.
This is the "Star Map."
It can contain a massive number
of Sealing Stars.
I will place one hundred inside for now.
When your cultivation matures,
the remaining 16,135 idle Sealing Stars
inside the tower
may also be merged into the scroll.
The Sealing Stars that kings across all races
fight desperately for
now lie before me within a single scroll.
That's the structure of
the "Heaven-Rending Claw".
It seems the Star Map
can channel any secret technique
I can conceive.
This is truly the supreme treasure
of a spirit master.
Now that you have the Star Map
and a powerful soul,
you need one last item
to end everything.
(This is...)
(Three sets of coordinates appeared
in my mind.)
(Yinfa Secret Realm, Planet Jansen)
(The Nine Tribulations Codex fragments!)
The Codex consists of five pieces.
You need to find the remaining three,
each hidden in a dangerous location.
You must retrieve each at Realm Lord, Immortal,
and Cosmic Sage stages.
Once you have gathered the complete Codex,
you will not be far from fully controlling
the Starry Tower.
Understood.
=Swallowed Star=
=Starry Tower=
I have lived through countless eras.
The past drifts away like the wind.
But
I will remember this moment.
I will work hard, Teacher.
I will lead the Earth lineage
to stand among the strongest of the universe.
Since you have met our teacher,
my duty is finished.
You are leaving too?
From now on, the Starry Tower
is yours to manage.
I may finally travel the universe freely.
(Because I was under the pressure
of the trials,)
(I couldn't spare awareness to enter
the Virtual Universe.)
(Now that six thousand years have passed,)
(my family must be terribly worried.)
(Unread Mails)
(Mails)
Dad, several clan members recently...
- I've brought back treasures
- Great potential...
- from the Battlefield.
- Are you still there?
- Family gathering...
- Dad.
I met your friends from the VUC.
Brother, great news.
Return to Rainshine Mountain.
- We will gather.
- After meeting your family,
- come see me.
- Why aren't you challenging the Sky Bridge?
My family...
(Unread emails: King Derivative, 2; Mother, 73)
(Xu Xin, 35,029)
Feng, it has been three thousand years.
Where on earth have you gone?
(Belho Starfield, Unknown Starfield)
Feng,
I'm now on a remote planet
in the Belho Starfield.
The scenery is beautiful,
yet it feels far too lonely.
Feng, the Ross family has been restless lately,
but don't worry.
I will fight for the Luo family no matter what.
(We are only over ten thousand years old.)
(But the 6,000 years inside the Starry Tower)
(forced us apart for half our lifetime.)
(I could only catch glimpses)
(of her lonely years through emails.)
(I must spend)
(my entire life making up for it.)
Feng, where are you?
I miss you so much.
(West Lake Villa, Virtual Universe)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Luo Ping.
Dad.
Is the pressure too much?
Dad,
as long as you come back,
none of this matters.
The population scale of our Luo family
has expanded to the size of over
ten thousand life planets.
When you were here, we could still manage.
But Dad,
you've been gone too long.
Rumors of your fall are spreading.
All forces are stirring,
trying to get the Luo territory.
I shouldn't be gone for so long.
Where's your mother?
She's negotiating with representatives
of the Ross family.
Their family is backing down
on business matters,
relying on their King-level Immortal patriarch.
A year ago,
one of our Luo family juniors killed a member
of the Ross family to protect a servant.
They used this to escalate the conflict,
demanding compensation.
They're negotiating with Mom now
because of this incident.
(Ross Family; Patriarch: King Swordscrush;
Early King-level Immortal)
(Student of a Cosmic Sage)
A mere Early King-level Immortal,
and he dares to be so arrogant?
He's seeking death.
Mrs. Luo,
the negotiations have reached the seventh day.
This is the last day.
If there is still no resolution,
our Ross family will...
Boss!
I didn't expect
the Ross family representative
to be you.
Feng.
Leave it to me now.
Trying to play dirty while I'm away?
Are ou tired of living?
We...
We were only discussing possible solutions.
Please don't force our two families
into full hostility.
Still talking back?
Have her reconnect to the virtual universe.
Or next time,
the one who dies will be her real body.
Yes, yes!
Everything you've done is nothing
more than trying to force me to appear,
testing whether I truly fell.
With me here,
your strength is nowhere near enough
to stand equal to the Luo family.
This negotiation
is no longer necessary.
Tell your patriarch, King Swordscrush,
that if he doesn't give me a perfect answer
for everything the Ross family has done,
I don't mind
letting him perish
and erasing the entire Ross family.
That includes your BDM royal clan.
Brolyn.
Your response?
Yes.
Let's go.
(After accompanying Xu Xin,)
(I went to report my 6,00 years)
(of cultivation to the Chaos City Lord.)
(He said that once I
pass the Realm Lord level
Original Sky Mountain,)
(he'll arrange for me to join)
(the Hone Alliance again under the name
"Luo Feng.")
(This way,)
(I alone)
(can possess two Hone Alliance memberships.)
(Then I purchased over three million
Chaos Coins worth of wine)
(to bring to my teacher, King Derivative.)
(While we were drinking joyfully,)
(a message arrived from King Swordscrush.)
(He claimed he would come in person
to apologize.)
(He allowed his subordinates to trouble
the Luo family.)
(No matter how humble he acts now,)
(this matter cannot simply be brushed aside.)
(I demanded 99% of their assets
as compensation)
(and that all those involved be handed over
to the Luo family.)
(Only after everything was settled)
(could I finally sit down with my family)
(for a long-awaited reunion meal.)
Wonderful!
(Original Soul, a bead-like treasure.)
(It can give birth to Emperor, King, General
and Soldier souls.)
(When merged into the soul, it greatly
strengthens it.)
(Emperor, King, General, Soldier)
(Colorful Space,)
(a mysterious space that emits brilliant
five-colored light,)
(storing Original Soul and countless
sub-souls.)
(They scatter throughout the universe.)
(Q: A celestial body known as)
(a brown dwarf is often called)
(a "failed star." Why?)
(A: A brown dwarf has only 13 to 80 times
the mass of Jupiter.)
(It can't support hydrogen fusion)
(and can only fuse deuterium.)
(The heat and light produced
is extremely limited.)
(Thus it is called a brown dwarf.)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star"
available on Starting point Chinese net)
(Copyrights reserved)
(by Shanghai Tencent Penguin
Film Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Next Episode Preview)
A large-scale hunt
is about to begin.
Guess what I found.
Where are the aliens?
(King Cushoo)
(King Junsong)
(King Forsway)
(King Tetchy)
(King Churtsan)
(King Jehong)
(King Beimay)
Interesting.
I gave my all to rescue King Tienson.
No way.
Instead, I was attacked by my own people.
Die!
You dare covet the treasure
with such meager power?
(So fast! The Wings of Slayer Wu
can't dodge it.)
You managed to survive one of my thrown swords.
You have some skill.
King Sevenswords.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™