(Copyright Notice)
♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Audience under 18 are requested to watch
with the permission of their guardians.)
(The whole video is made by CG.
Please do not copy in real life.)
(The film is purely fictitious and does not
serve as a basis for scientific knowledge.)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(These three can become my main force.)
Young,
I've found King Tienson's coordinates.
King Bladeriver!
I knew it was you.
King Tienson.
Master.
King Bladeriver is no longer in the system.
King Bladeriver risked his life to save me,
and you dare plot against his treasures!?
Die!
Good.
(You dare covet the treasure
with such meager power?)
Shining Moon Strike!
King Bladeriver!
(King Sevenswords!)
Episode 199
[Starry Tower]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
King Sevenswords,
your sword seems slower.
King Sevenswords's sword force is unmatched,
completely overwhelming King Bladeriver.
But in terms of speed,
he isn't losing at all.
He attacks from long range,
even if King Sevenswords gets serious,
he can't do anything about him.
(Once we really go all out,)
(eight stars can only barely affect
his sword speed.)
(Seems I'm still not on his level.)
You truly are formidable.
Impressive.
I'll be taking my leave first.
You think you can come after me?
How ridiculous.
King Bladeriver,
I will come back for revenge.
Such astonishing speed,
and formidable strength.
He made me use five swords.
His power is enough
to be worthy of a heavy treasure.
He actually acknowledged his strength.
That's terrifying.
With that speed, who could compare?
We'd better not provoke him in the future.
("Better to meet Sevenswords and die,
than meet Bladeriver.")
(This saying spreads widely.)
Come on.
Is he really that strong?
When we see him, we all need to step aside.
Feels like he's even scarier
than King Sevenswords.
Be careful.
- Don't provoke him.
- This...
("Better to meet the Seven Swords and die,)
(than meet the Blade River."
The rumor spreads everywhere.)
(I knew you weren't simple.)
(King Bladeriver's deeds spread rapidly
across the outer battlefield.)
(But no matter how wildly it spreads,)
(I've already returned to my identity.)
(I'll continue cultivating quietly.)
(I'll first pass the Realm-lord-level
Original Sky Mountain.)
(Once I pass,)
(I can enter the Hone Alliance
under my own name.)
(Next,)
(I'll challenge Sky Bridge, level 20.)
(It's said that those who pass level 20,)
(their comprehension of laws can rival
an Invincible King.)
(So I want to see)
(what happens if I challenge it)
(as a realm lord.)
(Sky Bridge; King Derivative: Level 20)
(Luo Feng: Level 20)
(Bran: Level 18)
He just passed Sky Mountain,
and now he's already reached level 20
of Sky Bridge,
(King Derivative, Luo Feng)
(at the same level as his teacher.)
I thought entering the Original Space
would let me close the distance.
Didn't expect the gap grew even larger.
To surpass the past self
is to live up to the effort you once made.
Let's keep going together.
Chaos City Lord sent a mail saying
you can officially enter the Hone Alliance
as Luo Feng.
However,
he repeatedly warned:
you must not reveal that you're
King Bladeriver.
(The Hone Alliance won't let)
(anything about your secret leak.)
(Do NOT reveal that you're Bladeriver.)
My teacher is indeed thorough.
Once my identity is exposed,
the other races will likely see me as a threat
and spend enormous resources to assassinate me.
Teacher Zoranco provided me
(Enfa Realm, Goofan Realm. Uhoa Realm)
with three metal plate coordinates.
(Goofan Realm)
One of them can be accessed at my stage.
To avoid ending up passive against other races,
gathering the third metal plate
must now be put on the agenda.
(Xu Xin)
(The family banquet is arranged.)
But before that,
(I'm waiting for you.)
I need to return to Earth first.
There's an immigrant ship approaching.
This is Earth.
Identify yourselves, outsiders.
Master,
how could they not recognize you,
the lord of Earth?
Dad, look.
Those immigrants are completely out of control.
(Walk toward a new shore.)
Last time I returned,
they detained me for half a day under
the excuse of "identity verification."
Clearly just trying to put me in my place.
Stop. Don't add trouble for Dad.
Who gave you the right?
Listen,
Earth's defense control
has been taken over by
the Immigrant Headquarters.
(The agreement clearly stated that)
(Sovereignty Division Agreement)
(Earthlings would retain half the control.)
(I didn't expect that in the six thousand years
I was gone,)
(power would be eroded this much.)
Get lost!
Lord Luo Feng!
- Swallowed Star -
- Starry Tower -
What are you doing?
Why are you kicking us out?
You have no right to drive us away!
You're just bullying us!
This area is temporarily requisitioned.
(Fully open, building an immigrant homeland.)
Luo Feng.
I've been away too long,
that's why immigrants are doing this.
I know the Immigration Authority can see this.
Remember,
your jurisdiction
is limited to the oceans.
As for the continents of Earth,
don't even think about touching them.
Luo Feng is getting way too arrogant.
He doesn't take us seriously at all.
Master, don't be angry.
He is the disciple of the Chaos City Lord.
Before, when he was away,
we could still act freely.
But now,
we must restrain ourselves.
So what?
Most immigrants to Earth
are elites from the Five Major Human Factions,
including the descendants of Cosmic Lords.
No matter how capable he is,
he can't shake our foundation.
This aura...
Even I, as an Immortal King, can feel fear.
This is...
What is that?
An Immortal Star-Eater Vine.
Its power
is likely no weaker than a limit King.
From this moment on,
all immigrants and Earth's native residents
are forbidden from stepping into
each other's territories.
Those still lingering
in the other side's domain
must leave within twelve cosmic hours.
Anyone who violates this
will be killed on sight.
Great!
Luo Feng!
Don't let him escape!
(A restriction on both sides,)
(but in practice, aimed at immigrants.)
He's bluffing.
He has no authority over
the Immigration Authority.
He doesn't,
but the Chaos City Lord does.
(Effective immediately.)
This is a decree just issued
by the Chaos City Lord.
(All immigrants are forbidden
from entering continent regions.)
(Meanwhile, Earth's original residents)
(are strictly forbidden from
stepping into ocean regions.)
(Anyone violating this law)
(shall be executed.)
Chaos... Chaos...
And what can you do?
I don't believe he'd really take things
this far.
Be careful.
Don't cross the boundary,
or your end
will be just like these
who resisted enforcement.
Even if you two are senior officials,
you are no exception.
Luo Feng, you...
This is a threat to all immigrants! You...
Would you rather die to the Star-Eater Vine,
or die at my subordinate's hands?
If not,
then leave.
Lord Luo Feng,
King Interception spoke out of turn.
Please forgive him.
We will leave at once.
(Effective immediately.)
(Chaos City Lord)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(With the Star-Eater Vine present,)
(the immigrants no longer dare invade
Earth's territory.)
(I can now leave Earth with peace of mind.)
This biological spaceship confiscated
in the Starry Tower
is better for hiding my identity.
And it can reach up to eighty times
light-speed.
It'll get me to the metal plate's location
much faster.
Even the Almen ship
can be retired now.
I have never forgotten the legacy
Teacher Huyan Bo left me.
And now,
with the inheritance and treasures
I've obtained,
I'm much more confident
in avenging him.
I can postpone the metal plate search for now.
Tell me
who killed
Teacher Huyan Bo?
(Planet Magshow)
If I hadn't requested you from King Blooddemon,
you'd already be dead as test subjects.
(King Magshow) Give me a smile as repayment,
that's not too much to ask, right?
This is the sound.
Louder.
King Magshow,
tormenting your servants at will?
What a mighty king.
My lord,
we've never met before.
I don't know how I have offended you.
Please, enlighten me.
(King Sevenswords. Front, Back)
(Emerged from Giant Axe at a young age,)
(he became a disciple of a Cosmic Lord.)
(Soon, he was near invincible King level.)
(As a human genius, he's feared
by other races.)
(Floating City, a settlement built)
(above Earth's oceans.)
(They are massive and luxurious,)
(inhabited by alien talents.)
(In name, they are harmless.)
(Q: What is the "infant universe"?)
(A: It refers to the extremely early state
of the universe)
(right after the Big Bang, during
a short period.)
(It describes how the universe expanded
from a super-hot,)
(high-density state, cooled down,)
(and gradually formed the cosmos
we know today.)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™