[Previously]
Rumors all say Blade River King is Luo Feng.
Finally something to boast about.
This is the legendary Ancestral God Secret Region.
Five-Colored Aurora Lake...
up to ten light-years wide...
power boundless.
From this moment...
you two are inheritors of Purple Thorn Island.
Disrespecting you...
would be an insult to me.
This Ancestral God Cult virtual space...
is nothing compared to the Virtual Universe.
Episode 205
[Ancestral God Contract Arc]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
They all believe I'm Blade River King...
then Blade River it is.
Blade River King!
The legendary Blade River King!
That very Blade River King!
Glory World Rankings...
my spot is here.
Inheritors of different levels...
are ranked on separate lists.
Seventh highest...
Seven Sword King.
Ranked by wins and losses.
Victories earn Glory Points.
One hundred points exchange
for an extra inheritance chance.
Our earlier battle...
was truly exhilarating.
Let's spar more in the future.
Millions of inheritors in the plaza...
yet Hong Alliance side...
has only over a thousand.
Over here!
That's him!
Blade River King is riding high now.
Machine and Demon races
have open bounties.
Beat him senseless...
and fame will soar.
That Seven Sword King group...
is the Northern Border Alliance.
Just weak races banded together...
not as strong as our Hong Alliance.
But inheritance tokens are scattered
across the universe...
many races, vast territories...
so more come here.
Northern Border loves to gossip.
Ignore them.
Glory Points are precious...
everyone's cautious...
rarely issuing challenges.
Out of jealousy...
they provoke others
to reject human challenges.
So annoying.
What are you looking at?
I got tons of challenge letters.
Your fame is just too big...
plenty of unconvinced geniuses.
You'll get thousands, probably.
Over sixty thousand already.
What?!
Blade River King, a mere World Lord...
relying only on law comprehension
and secret arts...
can't possibly kill Peak Kings.
Yeah...
Must have treasures or rare encounters.
But...
in Glory World battles...
everyone uses equal divine bodies...
weapons and gear chosen only here.
His treasures are useless.
Challenge!
I'll thrash the legendary Blade River King!
Be careful...
no backing out once accepted.
They're peerless geniuses from all races...
most created peak secret arts...
some even ultimate arts.
Lose...
and wait an era for new Glory Points.
Ultimate arts?
My self-created peak arts...
already earned Chaos City Lord's praise.
Blade River King...
I...
Pa E Ka Fen Si King challenges you!
Dare you accept?
Such big fame...
just from lucky encounters, right?
Blade River King...
Got the guts? Bet three Glory Points!
Blade River King!
Hilarious!
That new human actually accepted...
over six hundred twenty thousand challenges!
Never happened on Purple Thorn Island before.
Such a powerful divine body—perfect!
Before becoming Immortal...
I can fight with a body
at 100,000 times World Lord power!
Blade River King!
What?!
You actually lost
to that Blade River King?
He's just a World Lord
without treasures!
Pathetic!
Let me take him on.
Warm-up complete.
Next battle...
Die!
Another Glory Point delivery.
Damn it...
I'll lose points to him too!
Without external aids...
a World Lord atop
third-level inheritors...
I'm convinced.
Never thought he'd reach this level.
The Ancestral God Cult
is forging a supreme powerhouse for humanity.
But...
assassinations against Luo Feng...
will only grow more frenzied.
Blade River King cannot live.
If he becomes a Universe Venerable...
he'll wield Universe Overlord strength.
A greater threat than
an unrevivable Overlord.
Our Demon vassal races...
who's receiving inheritance here?
Venerable Marsh Erosion...
currently fifth-level inheritor.
Our Prison Race is remote...
let's watch from the sidelines.
The four core pinnacle races...
will put on a fine show.
Add Blade River King
to humanity's priority kill list.
Pick the right moment...
As you command.
Father God...
Eliminate human Blade River King at once!
Yes.
Kong Wan and Jue Guang
pay respects to Insect Empress.
Across our Insect Alliance...
you're the best fit, Jue Guang.
Kong Wan excels at soul control.
Losses from Aurora Lake annihilation...
the Alliance will compensate
upon revival.
Best to soul-enslave Blade River King...
cutting off humanity's revival chance.
If not, kill him outright.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
It's over.
Your Glory Points exceed 610,000.
One hundred points
for one precious inheritance chance.
Quite a harvest.
Why hasn't he emerged?
That cowardly human!
While studying Beast God Path...
those 620,000 battles honed me.
Now...
my Beast God Path nears third stage perfection.
Space law comprehension rises too.
Earthling and Golden Horned Beast
can now teleport.
But space lockdown and strangulation...
need more study.
Time for the next Beast God inheritance.
Sacrificing a Universe Venerable...
just for one World Lord.
You should be proud.
So fast!
Demon camp's Venerable Marsh Erosion.
I'll observe first.
Enslave me?
Dream on!
What?!
His soul defense is this strong?!
Then...
die!
This...
Marsh Erosion and Luo Feng's auras!
Venerable Marsh Erosion attacked Blade River King...
and was slain.
Blade River King's body
is completely destroyed.
Those wings of Blade River King...
priceless supreme treasure!
Ancestral God Cult decree...
forbids looting among inheritors.
Blade River King is dead...
it's ownerless now.
The ban should lapse.
How?!
The treasure flew inside!
Impossible!
Blade River King lives!
Y-yes, Island Lord!
Venerable Marsh Erosion violated the ban...
Island Lord...
assassinating an inheritor
on sacred grounds...
even if revived through time reversal...
the Ancestral God Cult
will hunt him relentlessly...
until death.
Island Lord...
How is this possible?!
He looks completely unharmed...
Could he have the legendary
clone talent?
Blade River King lives!
Disperse, all of you.
Blade River King is an inheritor
of our Ancestral God Cult.
Assassinate him...
and face annihilation
from the Ancestral God Cult.
Never seen the Cult
value an inheritor this much.
Killing Luo Feng here...
will be near impossible.
[Glory World Plaza: The Ancestral God Sect’s virtual world sanctuary.
Although its scale and functions cannot compare to the Virtual Universe, it still offers valuable opportunities for inheritance and learning. Those who wish to gain additional teachings may come here. Most of the plaza is used as a venue for inheritance exchanges and communication.]
[Cosmic Creature: Its entire body is covered in thick, viscous alien tissue. Upon entering combat, its originally gentle twin eyes instantly erupt with terrifying killing intent. Its tongue possesses astonishing destructive power—comparable to layered spatial crushing. Even gods who confront it dare not underestimate the threat of its tongue.]
[Q: What is a cosmic bubble?]
[A: A cosmic bubble is a concept from multiverse theory. It describes boundary regions between different universes. Each bubble represents an independent universe with its own physical laws and initial conditions, forming and colliding within higher-dimensional space.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™