(Copyright Notice)
♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Audience under 18 are requested to watch
with the permission of their guardians.)
(The whole video is made by CG.
Please do not copy in real life.)
(The film is purely fictitious and does not
serve as a basis for scientific knowledge.)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
Such astonishing speed,
and formidable strength.
His power is enough
to be worthy of a heavy treasure.
(I didn't expect that in the six thousand years
I was gone,)
(power would be eroded this much.)
All immigrants and Earth's native residents
are forbidden from stepping into
each other's territories.
(Chaos City Lord)
Anyone who violates this
will be killed on sight.
I have never forgotten the legacy
Teacher Huyan Bo left me.
King Magshow!
Episode 200
[Ice Prison Planet]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
My lord,
(Planet Magshow)
we've never met before.
I don't know how I have offended you.
Please, enlighten me.
(Those servants who have seen me
in such a sorry state,)
(if I escape this ordeal,)
(I'll kill them all.)
Luo Feng! Kill him!
You know how to behave.
But sadly,
no matter how you struggle,
you will die.
I...
Demon Emperor!
Give me a reason.
Soaring Shuttle!
Luo Feng, let me out.
I want to watch him die.
And this artificial life...
You are on Huyan Bo's side.
(Evolution Heart)
(is a Mechanism race treasure.)
(It can grant a body to an artificial life.)
(Barbata will also have the chance
to cultivate and evolve.)
(But most importantly,)
(it gives Barbata the chance to take revenge
with her own hands.)
It's done.
Master,
did you see that?
King Magshow is dead.
He's dead.
Back then you entrusted me to keep your legacy.
I never dared tell Luo Feng who your enemy was.
I never imagined this day of vengeance
would come.
It's okay to cry.
Stay as long as you need
to sort out your feelings.
(Uhoa Realm)
(The Ice Prison Planet Belt)
(hosts a special lifeform that has existed)
(since the universe's birth)
(named the “Doko.”)
(They are beautiful in appearance,)
(innocent by nature,)
(but murderous.)
(According to VUC records,)
(three meters tall)
(they are loving and united internally,)
(beautiful)
(but extremely xenophobic.)
(Born under an innate icy aura,
they are naturally)
(a hundred times stronger than humans.)
(According to the directions,)
(the third black metal plate)
(is located in the Ice Prison Planet Belt
of the Uhoa Realm.)
(What I must do)
(is to find it among the many
ice prison planets)
(and take it away.)
- Tienson.
- Here.
I need to pick, from your servants,
someone agile and quick.
Master.
From now on,
you will obey my master's commands.
Yes, yes.
Master's master.
Coordinates have been sent to you.
Remember,
you must keep the micro-detector active
at all times,
hide your whereabouts,
and avoid being discovered.
So cold.
Master's master told me to find
some black metal plate,
but where exactly is it hidden?
Sister,
we haven't seen any new ice sculptures
in a long time.
I guess there'll be another unlucky soul soon.
They came out from inside.
Moro Monkey, go take a look.
(There's actually a palace)
(within the planet.)
Such overwhelming pressure...
There's a terrifying powerhouse inside.
Master's master,
what should I do?
Avoid the palace,
scan the entire planet.
(Ice Prison Planet)
Outside the palace,
the region is entirely made of ice.
It seems
the black metal plate
can only be inside the palace.
Enter the palace!
Yes.
Master's master,
I am in position.
This one?
No.
Not this.
That one?
No.
This one? Next.
Next one.
Which one?
No, no, no.
Alien!
(No Signal)
If I enter the inner hall,
I will be discovered.
If I don't enter,
I won't get the metal plate.
=Swallowed Star=
=Ice Prison Planet=
(Outside the Ice Prison Planet Palace)
Befa.
(Iawu)
You came to see that alien too?
Come on, let's go together.
(Inside the Ice Prison Planet Palace)
Teacher Terasa.
(Terasa)
Iawu, Befa, you're here.
Where is that alien?
These aliens
all want the Ice Prison Stone
and the Ice Prison Dew.
They overestimate themselves.
Look.
A moro monkey from the demon race,
roughly Marquis-level strength.
(So many of them.)
(Doko truly is ruthless.)
(Although she acts gentle towards
her own people.)
A moro monkey?
This is the first time I've seen one
in reality.
This thing is so ugly.
Befa, don't you agree?
Befa.
Befa?
(If she discovers who I really am...)
What's with you today?
You're totally out of it.
Is something bothering you?
What's wrong?
Not in a great mood.
I don't want to talk about it.
Alright, don't force him to speak.
Stay here and keep him company.
I need to go to the virtual universe.
Befa, let's go to the Mystic Hall.
I'll pass.
I want to walk alone.
Then I'm off.
(Lucky,)
(I found a chance to act alone so quickly.)
(Doko Clan, Virtual Universe)
That's
Befa?
Yeah.
What about it?
He was just in my hall earlier,
looking gloomy.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
I got it so easy.
As long as I fly out of Ice Prison Planet,
then accelerate to lightspeed,
I can escape without anyone knowing.
Alien!
(She found out!)
Die！
(He escaped?)
(His teleportation distance exceeded
my sensing range.)
Terasa.
Chief, he stole...
I know. Leave everything to me.
(Luckily my Mosas avatar is immune
to soul attacks.)
Little one, you run fast.
But you can't escape my grasp.
This will take some effort.
Right there.
Greetings, My Lord.
No.
You got played.
Got it.
Impressive.
You actually toyed with a Cosmic Sage.
(Ice Prison Entrance, Ice Prison Planet)
Let me see.
Look, look!
Chief, kill that alien!
He dared pretend to be me?!
He even held my hand.
The one pretending is already dead.
This is the mastermind.
Chiefs,
what should we do with this alien?
Naturally, he must be slowly tortured.
The Ice Prison is about to open again.
This alien is doomed.
It's a killing ground in there.
Once inside, it's worse than death.
(So that's the Ice Prison,)
(the most legendary place
in the entire Planet Belt.)
(Guarded by the Doko Sages,)
(it's suppressing countless powerful beings.)
Enjoy it, human.
(Azure Doko Sage & Violet Doko Sage)
(Formed from extreme ice-cold essence,)
(they are beautiful and eerie.)
(They are pure in nature, without gender.)
(Violet Doko's cold kills souls more easily,)
(Azure Doko's cold kills the body more easily.)
(Front, Face, Back)
(Ice Prison Entrance)
(Crystal-clear icicles hang from the tree.)
(The blue sky reflects off
the snow-covered ground.)
(And at the base of the tree trunk,)
(a bright blue glowing opening is the entrance)
(to the Ice Prison.)
(Q: At what distance would)
(a supernova threaten Earth?)
(A: For a Type 1a supernova,)
(at 50 light-years away,)
(Earth's surface would receive)
(about 35 million joules per square meter.)
(This is considered the safe threshold
for Earth.)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star"
available on Starting point Chinese net)
(Copyrights reserved)
(by Shanghai Tencent Penguin
Film Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Next Episode Preview)
I heard the newcomer is a human.
(The Ice Prison Icefield Map)
(Ice Lake, Ice Stele)
If you've got the guts, come out.
Arrogant.
(So this is Teacher Zoranco's)
(true intention in bringing me here.)
The Ten Kings and the Five Giants
are all looking for him.
I want to talk.
Why start fighting the moment we meet?
You actually recognize me.
(Such overwhelming suppression.)
(Space trembles at every moment.)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)