Child, welcome home.
Human, you truly thought you could hide from me?
Human Luo Feng pays respects
to the Starry Sky Ancestor.
Within a hundred Epochs,
if you succeed,
I shall bestow upon you
the ultimate treasure set of the Beast God lineage.
May I ask, what requirement
did Teacher Zuo Shan Ke leave?
Defeat me.
As long as you continue cultivating
the Nine Calamity Secret Codex,
allowing the Golden Horned Beast
to reach the Perfect Gene level,
I, for the Universe...
This is a Miniature Universe.
Previously, fearing immense consumption,
I never utilized this innate
talent secret method after acquiring it.
It is indeed astonishing.
How profound and wondrous.
I can absolutely control
this Miniature Universe,
suppressing enemies at will,
enhancing myself...
And with just a single thought, I can destroy this universe.
This secret method is far too heaven-defying.
Babata.
You aren't...
in the Beast God Realm?
Truly beautiful.
These secret pattern diagrams
are the operational laws
of the entire Miniature Universe.
Vast, complex, and precise.
This is...
The secret patterns from the
sixty-four Beast God statues.
So these seemingly random tangles
of billions of Law threads
are actually composed of
small secret patterns from those statues.
This is unbelievable.
Could it be that constructing
ultimate techniques
actually follows discernible laws?
The Great Annihilation Era is
an unfathomably distant time,
known by few.
Before the Great Annihilation,
there existed a cultivation method
using the sixty-four secret patterns
as basic elements.
What use is constantly
sketching secret patterns?
It has been over ten thousand years.
The most crucial and elusive part
of the Beast God Path
is the Heart of the Beast God.
One must comprehend the Heart
to truly incarnate as a Beast God.
He has strayed onto the wrong path.
The Eight Great Beast Gods
are embodiments of fused laws.
And the sixty-four secret patterns
are the perfect interpretation of the natural Eight Beast Gods.
The most pinnacle secret techniques
can all be decomposed into sixty-four secret patterns.
Luo Feng's Nine Nether Avatar
reached the Perfect Gene level
even before reaching Immortality.
He must have received the gift
of the strongest talent technique.
If Luo Feng notices the connection
between his talent technique and the sixty-four secret patterns,
he won't need to understand
the underlying principles;
he only needs to firmly memorize
the structure of each secret pattern,
then reference the structure
of the talent technique he received
to create...
Once successful,
he can create a simplified version
of the strongest talent technique.
It is not impossible.
Restoring all secret patterns
is too difficult for now.
For now, focus on studying
the eight secret patterns
of the Gold Beast God.
I am...
the Beast God.
I actually lost focus for a moment.
What a curious sensation.
Is this what Zhuangzi dreaming of butterflies feels like?
What?
The ultimate bottleneck
of the Beast God Path—
the most elusive and hardest-to-obtain
Heart of the Beast God—
he actually mastered it just like that?
But even so, it doesn't mean...
Wait, that is...
It actually succeeded.
A pinnacle ultimate technique
at the level of a Universe Master.
Starry Sky Ancestor.
I, Luo Feng, challenge you.
Challenging me?
With what weapon?
You use your hands.
Shall I also use these human hands?
Hands.
You comprehended the Heart of the Beast God,
yet you cannot use hands as weapons?
Make your move.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
He actually won.
Even if suppressed to the same
Divine Body level,
that is still the Ancestor!
This feels unreal.
Thank you, Starry Sky Ancestor.
From beginning to end,
you were purely defending.
That is why I was lucky enough to win.
No need for modesty.
I already deployed the highest defensive measures
of a Universe Master.
If I had attacked with full force from the start,
I might have defeated you.
But if you continued challenging me,
you would eventually triumph.
Since that is the case,
there is no need to waste time.
Well done, Luo Feng.
After one hundred eighty million years,
you have finally been completely
reborn and remolded.
In the past, you relied on
supreme treasures and secret codes to stand among the strong.
Now, you have accumulated
truly deep and substantial power.
In the coming cultivation,
you should be able to achieve a breakthrough in one breath.
Probably only crossing the threshold
of Universe Master will pose a slight obstruction.
Zuo Shan Ke, don't get cocky.
Those are your disciple's achievements,
not yours.
Furthermore, his success...
who can say it isn't because of
the Golden Horned Beast avatar?
Whose credit it is doesn't matter.
But don't forget the bet.
You are the Starry Sky Ancestor,
one of the nine superpowers of the universe.
You wouldn't be stingy, would you?
I'm still waiting for that
Treasure Set of yours.
If I lose, I lose. I naturally
keep my word.
Luo Feng, look.
This is the Treasure Set—Beast God Armor.
Composed of five hundred
and twenty-six Treasures.
Five hundred and twenty-six!
Even Chaos City Lord's
teacher's 'River of Ten Thousand Treasures'
was composed of only a thousand treasures.
Within the set, there are four
High-Level Treasures and one
Pinnacle Treasure.
The rest are ordinary Treasures.
Its fangs, horn, scales, and body
can be used separately.
Combined, they merge into one,
possessing world-shaking might.
It is absolutely the most suitable
equipment for powerhouses cultivating the Beast God Path.
It's too wonderful.
We have disturbed you for years;
it is time we left.
Luo Feng.
Don't be in such a rush.
There is one more thing.
It has nothing to do with you.
Many thanks, Ancestor,
for the gift.
Luo Feng, my Starry Sky Beast Alliance
possesses superior resources
and better prospects for growth.
Do you have any thoughts of leaving
the Human Race?
No.
As I thought.
You haven't cultivated for long;
your kin and friends are all here.
Your heart still holds attachments.
How about this:
Let your Golden Horned Beast avatar
join my Starry Sky Beast Alliance.
It won't affect your status
as a human.
And you gain another faction
as your backing.
What's not good about that?
But correspondingly, you bear
more responsibility.
The Alliance aids you, so naturally,
you must shoulder responsibilities.
No problem. I can bear the
responsibility.
Starry Sky Ancestor, seeing your
expression, the recruitment worked.
Is there any benefit for my disciple?
Doesn't the clan bestow Treasures
upon the rise of new talents?
Previously...
Don't tell me the Beast God Armor
counts—that was from a bet.
It wasn't gifted by the Alliance
to Luo Feng.
Fine, fine, fine.
You old fellow really know how
to bargain.
My disciple joining the Alliance
is a blessing for your Starry
Sky Beasts.
You, as a teacher, weren't even
this generous.
Rest assured, what I give will be
better than yours.
Then I shall bestow upon his human
true body a High-Level Treasure close-combat weapon.
You old rascal.
After obtaining the 'Zhan Ye Blade'
from Starry Sky Ancestor,
my teacher and I returned to
the Original Universe.
If you need to contact me,
just transmit a message via
consciousness entering this; I will receive it.
The recovery of universal
operating rules
allowed my Golden Horned Beast
to rapidly transform.
Leaping in a short time to become
a Perfect Divine Body.
Everything is ready. It is time
to return to the Original Stars.
Say whatever, he insists on going
to the Original Stars.
Two epochs have passed, and he
hasn't entered even once.
He just doesn't dare to go in,
right?
He has too many Treasures and
too much fame.
The moment he enters, he will
definitely be besieged by all factions.
He isn't stupid.
Entering the Original Stars
as a human
will surely lead to even
more brutal slaughter.
The outside world is spreading
rumors that I am afraid.
The outskirts of the
Original Stars...
However,
that is precisely what I desire.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™