(Previously on Swallowed Star)
Beneath the Nine-Tiger River,
you cannot escape.
This...
The starry sky has completely changed.
This is the most sacred ground of our Alliance.
It was reshaped by the greatest existence
in our alliance—the Stellar Ancestor.
So the perilous land is actually
the outer buffer zone.
Come.
The super existences in the alliance
are waiting for you.
Episode 218
[First Encounter with the Primordial Star]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Not good.)
(Will I be discovered?)
(What should I do?)
Look,
the powerhouses of your lineage have come
to welcome you.
(Whatever.)
(Having come this far,)
(I likely have no way back anyway.)
(What?)
(Over a dozen Cosmic Sages,)
(two Cosmic Lords.)
Move aside, move aside.
Brother, welcome home.
- Wandering the universe is not easy.
- Welcome.
I'm Swaren Sage.
I'm Sail Sage.
Since your Gold-horned Giant lineage is here,
we'll leave him to you.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Leave him to us.
We've got everything covered.
They say Stellar Beasts are cold
and bloodthirsty,
yet when they meet their own kind,
they treat them like brothers.
(Gold Horn Lord)
(Zionmall Lord)
Child, welcome home.
Greetings to Gold Horn Lord and Zionmall Lord.
I'm Jin Feng.
Child,
to have grown into a Cosmic Sage on your own
is truly remarkable.
Under the alliance's guidance,
you will surely become even more exceptional.
Child,
the Stellar Ancestor wishes to see you
in person.
The Stellar Ancestor?
Don't be afraid.
Most Cosmic Sages here have never
had the chance to meet the Stellar Ancestor.
To receive an audience right after your return
is a tremendous opportunity.
Greetings to the Stellar Ancestor.
(Stellar Ancestor)
To have killed Mevjon Sage
is no small feat.
(The entire starry sky here was reshaped
by him;)
(nothing that happens there escapes his eyes.)
You flatter me.
Human.
Did you truly think you could hide it from me?
(He extended his divine power to probe me.)
(There was no way to resist it.)
To dare fight powerful enemies
to the death in defense of Earth—
your courage is commendable.
Truly worthy of the human race's
rarest genius in hundreds of millions of eras.
Luo Feng of the human race pays respects
to the Stellar Ancestor.
I fell into this perilous land by accident.
Possessing the Gold-horned Giant
back then was a last resort.
Please forgive me.
The possession was a matter of your fortune;
I will not interfere.
However, your arrival here
was no accident.
It was arranged by your teacher, Zoranco.
I have an agreement with him.
I will open the most important grounds of
our Stellar Beast Alliance to you,
to aid you in cultivating the Beast God path.
Across this vast universe,
only the Stellar Beasts have truly grasped
the essence of the Beast God
because we are the descendants of
the Beast God.
(When the Gold-horned Giant could so easily
fuse so many Xueluo Crystals,)
(I already suspected there must be)
(a connection between the Gold-horned Giant
and the Beast God.)
(I never imagined he would be a descendant
of the Beast God.)
Come.
But if you cannot meet your teacher's
requirements,
you will be trapped here forever.
This is...
The Beast God Realm.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Stellar Ancestor.
Do you see those statues of the innate
Beast Gods?
Each one contains pinnacle secret techniques.
You may learn from them freely.
Moreover, the flow of time here
10,081 times faster than in
the original universe,
greatly accelerating your cultivation.
Impressive, isn't it?
(That is comparable to a supreme treasure
like a Time Palace.)
(Such cultivation artifacts typically
accelerate time tenfold;)
(a hundredfold is already astronomically
expensive.)
(Ten thousandfold acceleration)
(is truly unheard of.)
But even with this advantage,
I don't think you can meet your teacher's
requirements.
I even made a bet with him:
if you succeed within one hundred thousand
eras,
I will grant you a supreme treasure set
most suited to the Beast God lineage.
If you fail,
your teacher will lose me a pinnacle
supreme treasure.
May I ask what requirement Teacher Zoranco
left behind?
The requirement is simple.
Defeat me.
Defeat you?
A mere Immortal defeating a Universe Strongest?
How is that possible?
My avatar will maintain the same divine body
strength as yours.
And while you are still an Immortal,
I will only use pinnacle techniques
at the Cosmic Lord level.
If, as an Immortal, you can
create an ultimate technique at the
Cosmic Lord level,
or if you become a Universe Strongest
in this Beast God Realm,
then there is a glimmer of hope.
Otherwise,
you will be trapped here forever.
Use all your skills.
I await your challenge.
=Swallowed Star=
=First Encounter with the Primordial Star=
(Becoming a Universe Strongest)
(is too far out of reach for me.)
(Creating a Cosmic Lord's
ultimate technique...)
(My law comprehension has just reached
the threshold of a Cosmic Sage,)
(still lacking a solid foundation.)
(Can this gap be bridged)
(through the Beast God Realm?)
This is the Gold Beast God.
An embodiment of the fusion laws of space
and gold.
Exactly the lineage you cultivate.
(There are sixty-four statues in total.)
(Eight innate Beast Gods,)
(each with eight statues.)
(Each statue has a different posture)
(and different scale patterns.)
(Each set of patterns seems to manifest
its own fusion law.)
Look.
Everywhere are the engraved marks left
by generations
of Stellar Beast Cosmic Lords.
All of them are ultimate techniques.
I can sense their extraordinary subtlety,
yet I cannot comprehend them,
let alone create such techniques myself.
The Stellar Ancestor only asked you
to defeat his avatar.
He never said you couldn't use innate
secret techniques.
That's right.
A technique like I Am the Universe
is almost unheard of.
And when I was granted that innate
secret technique,
the power of that light point far exceeded
that of a Cosmic Lord.
It should be considered a Cosmic Lord's
ultimate technique.
As long as I continue cultivating
the Nine Tribulations Codex
and bring the Gold-horned Giant to
the perfect gene level,
I should be granted another innate
secret technique,
just like the Nethersea Avatar.
Even if not,
the Gold-horned Giant
should then be able to use I Am the Universe.
(Gold-horned Giant's gene level)
No need for a hundred thousand eras.
Perhaps in a hundred years, it will be done.
And in the original universe, only 100 days
would have passed.
(Gold-horned Giant's life gene level)
Success.
Why is there no reaction at all?
No dramatic change in the divine body,
no consciousness drawn again into
that mysterious place.
Given the current size of
the Gold-horned Giant's divine body,
even if I were to force I Am the Universe,
the technique would likely consume all my
divine power before it could even take shape.
Zoranco,
it seems your disciple is in trouble.
Patience.
Everyone who reaches the perfect gene level
receives a bestowal from
the original universe's source.
The body evolves to perfection,
and the consciousness receives the most
powerful innate secret technique.
If we were in the original universe,
I might
lose this bet.
Unfortunately,
this is my universe.
My universe is far from as powerful
as the original universe.
I cannot bestow techniques upon him,
nor strengthen his divine body.
All he can rely on is this Beast God Realm.
You can't win.
Quite confident.
Good wine.
Give me some later.
(This old man isn't worried at all.)
(Could it be...)
(Teacher Zoranco never makes a losing bet.)
(Since he placed his wager,)
(he must believe it's possible for me
to succeed.)
(Where exactly)
(is this possibility?)
(Teacher went to such lengths to have me
cultivate here.)
(The key factor must still lie within
the Beast God Realm.)
(I have observed for a long time)
(and successfully mastered two techniques.)
(Nine Peaks Lock, Gold Beast God)
(But they only increased my soul
and divine body amplitude a hundredfold.)
(It seems merely studying predecessors'
techniques is not the way.)
(Surely many have come to the Beast God Realm.)
(If any had succeeded,)
(the Stellar Ancestor wouldn't be so certain
of his bet.)
(That is to say,)
(the key lies not solely in the external
factors of the Beast God Realm,)
(but also in my own unique characteristics.)
(What connection is there between these two?)
(The most profound thing in
the Beast God Realm)
(is these sixty-four statues.)
(The patterns seem to represent
the ultimate laws of the universe,)
(and they can be integrated into one whole.)
He only recognized a few patterns.
The cultivation of the Beast God path
is not so simple.
Who said I was giving it to you?
You're going to lose your pinnacle
supreme treasure to me.
This little wine means nothing.
You...
(Then what do I have that is unique?)
(The patterns on the Starry Tower are even
more profound than those here,)
(and they seem to be of a different system.)
The Nine Tribulations Codex can only
be practiced step by step;
I cannot unravel its mysteries.
What remains is only
I Am the Universe.
(Within the Beast God Realm, time)
(flow differs from the outside.)
(One era in the Realm equals)
(1 year in the original universe.)
(The statues standing within)
(are of the eight innate Beast Gods.)
(Stellar Ancestor, the)
(greatest existence in the Alliance.)
(The place he controls is the sacred ground.)
(He is dedicated to cultivating the lineage.)
(True Form, Human Form.)
[Q: Why are observatories built on mountains?]
[A: Dust, smoke, and water vapor in the atmosphere interfere with astronomical observations.The higher the altitude, the thinner the air, and the less dust and water vapor, the less interference. That is why (most observatories are built on mountains.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™