Your people prepared for hundreds of years,
and this is the only secret tunnel you dug?
This is beneath the Cathedral of the Church of Light!
Just sneaking in here,
and figuring out how to haul the dirt out
without being detected
was already a miracle.
Careful!
Blood-sucking bats!
They've built a nest here.
This baby is here!
Make way, everyone!
This is the Barrier of Light I told you about.
We Necromancers
are restrained by this pure power.
There is no breaking through.
So that's why you sought me out.
It worked.
Or maybe not.
Could it be...
you didn't use enough blood?
How about...
My blood shares the same attribute
as the barrier.
Contacting it only causes fusion.
Even if I drained all the blood
from my body,
it probably wouldn't work.
Is there really no way at all?
If gentle doesn't work,
use force.
If we use opposing attributes,
it might be effective.
It worked!
With my current power, I can't break
it open.
Plus, this barrier self-repairs.
Brother Leon,
this favor is troubling me.
It went inside.
Little Dragon,
how did you get in?
I'm not quite sure myself.
It felt like the power of the Great
Priest of Light was helping me.
Because it absorbed the God Relic?
Little Dragon, try again.
Try again.
Maybe you can break the seal.
Alright.
Since Little Leon is asking me,
Excellent!
It really went in.
Sanders the Sage is saved!
Seems safe inside.
Let's go in too.
Brother Chen,
looking for books?
I'm investigating an ancient secret.
Books written in the common tongue
of the past millennium are useless.
First, gather all the ancient language
books.
This is the den of the Church of Light.
Looks like on this wanted list,
neither of us can escape.
What is there to fear?
Heavy debts make light of danger.
Alright, alright.
I have some knowledge of Western
ancient script.
Most books here are religious texts.
Take out the books from your ring,
I'll help filter them.
Works for me.
Chen Nan,
I found a glowing book.
It has a barrier on it.
That must be a treasure of the
Church of Light.
Little Dragon,
we're counting on you.
Alrighty!
This barrier feels suffocating.
Like walking through a swamp.
Everything feels sticky.
I'll reward you with a red wine bath
tonight.
Yay!
Then I'll swim a few more laps.
Brother Leon,
check these few first.
Yu Xin's handwriting.
She's been here.
The Du family is ungrateful.
They betrayed the Chen family.
Forcing Yu Xin into marriage.
"I will not marry."
"Rain sparse, wind sudden..."
After a life-and-death battle,
Yu Xin slew the Du family Martial God,
but was gravely injured herself.
Hesitating on whether to reincarnate.
She ultimately decided to travel
west,
seeking aid from the Goddess of Life.
Yu Xin became the Corpse Spirit King...
meaning she didn't find a way to
continue her life.
And finally perished.
Her death was actually caused by
the Du family.
These wicked slaves who benefited
from my Chen family...
Du family!
I will grow stronger.
And wipe out every single one of you.
Brother Chen,
Brother Chen, restrain yourself!
Don't lash out!
If this place breaks,
we're all finished.
Brother Chen, you...
I'm fine.
Chen Nan, give me a hand.
We made quite a commotion.
This isn't a good place to linger.
Wrap it up.
Let's go.
To save your necromancer sage.
The seal on this floor...
it's stronger.
What is this thing?
I confess my crime...
I have been imprisoned for a hundred
years.
I confess...
I am a sinner.
The entire second layer of hell
holds undead creatures.
Corpse demons,
wraiths,
bone devils.
The truly terrifying figures are
on the lower floors.
The Church of Light is truly formidable.
To suppress so many powerful beings
underground.
Lord Sanders,
where are you?
Lord Sanders!
Little Sanders, where are you?
Your Leon is here to find you!
Leon?
Is that Leon?
Is Leon here?
Lord Sanders!
Your Sanders is actually a ball of
fire.
Undead all look like this.
Leon...
I'm almost done for.
Quickly break the seal!
San—
It's very weak.
If I weren't holding it,
it would probably be torn apart
passing through the barrier.
Lord Sanders!
After thousands of years,
I just knew
that even the Pope of the Church
of Light couldn't destroy you.
I never had that kind of strength.
They merely spared my life.
This old undead holds no resentment
after escaping.
Nor does he threaten revenge.
Truly worthy of the name "Sage."
Someone's been rescued!
Let me out!
Save me too!
Save us!
Leave first.
The commotion might attract guards.
Go!
To casually break a barrier formed
by Divine Light...
that little dragon...
Your Holiness, disaster!
Someone invaded the second layer
of hell.
And rescued a necromancer.
I'll send people to stop them now!
No.
Let them go.
But Cardinal Malun must already know.
If you don't take action,
Enough.
No matter what actions Malun takes,
you are not to interfere.
Go to the first layer of hell.
Return the books from this spatial
ring
to their original places.
Remember,
you saw nothing.
Yes.
This den of the Great Priest of Light...
turns out you can just waltz in
and out.
Many thanks, Divine Dragon.
And thanks to this unknown young
man for his aid.
Congratulations on your freedom,
Great Sage.
Brother Chen,
I told Sanders about our agreement.
He promises to tell you the whereabouts
of the Great Dragon Blade.
In my long life,
I have indeed heard
of that number one divine weapon
in the world.
It is most likely lost
in the depths of the ancient elven
tribe's primeval forest.
That is all I know.
That Godfallen Land...
It feels like destiny,
some force is drawing me there.
Thank you for the information,
senior.
Our cooperation is complete.
Brother Chen,
we part ways here.
When did the ring disappear?
I didn't notice a thing.
To hide it from both of us...
that person likely used a lost art
of spatial magic.
Possessing such terrifying ability,
yet letting us leave with the rescue...
Looks like the Church of Light isn't
so clean either.
But regardless,
Du family...
Your Eminence,
your guess was correct.
The Dark Church has no intention
of sparing Chen Nan.
In the coming days,
they will make new moves.
Continue.
I also received news
that members of the Eastern Supreme
Royal Family, the Du clan,
will arrive in Baidan tomorrow.
Chen Nan has issued a challenge to
them.
Chen Nan has issued a challenge.
Oh?
Then I'll add a little something.
Take two men, disguise yourselves
as Dark Church members.
Before the duel date, go assassinate
him.
Yes.
Pope...
Although I don't know what you're
planning,
since you let him go,
I will make sure he dies.
[Eighteen Layers of Hell: A mysterious artifact containing eighteen worlds, each sealed with a powerful ancient being. The deeper you go, the stronger the enemy. Defeat them to advance— a prison, and a trial of strength.]
You Du family truly court death.
I didn't come looking for you,
yet you deliver yourselves to my door.
The desert scenery is nice.
Perfect place for your graves.
All things return to the flow.
Heaven-shaking, Earth-shattering!
I say,
you Du family...
don't you have anything of your own?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
This aura...
It's so strong.
Du family dogs!
Descendant of the Chen family!
You seek death!
You Du family truly court death.
I didn't come looking for you,
yet you deliver yourselves to my door.
But to think killing a side branch
of the Du family
would make you so arrogant.
Wake up!
The Chen family's era is long past.
In this world now,
my Du family calls the shots.
Leeching off my Chen family's Profound
Arts to survive for ten thousand
years,
and you dare claim to be masters?
Nothing but rats who can't be put
on the stage.
Impudent!
True enough.
The Chen family was once glorious.
But ten thousand years have passed,
it has long since turned to dust.
And your existence
should be erased from this world.
The desert scenery is nice.
Perfect place for your graves.
All things return to the flow.
Heaven-shaking, Earth-shattering!
Even after ten thousand years,
as long as I live,
you Du family
will forever be servants of my Chen
family!
Damn it!
The rumors are true.
Their Profound Arts stem from the
same root.
Same root...
I can already judge who is superior.
Chen Nan clearly has the upper hand.
Du Hong!
Finger of Imprisonment!
Hand of Annihilation!
I say,
you Du family...
don't you have anything of your own?
Ten thousand years have passed.
Countless noble families and experts
have founded sects,
creating their own lineages.
Yet your Du family
doesn't even have its own inherited
techniques.
How pathetic.
This is...
Demonic energy!
The intel was real.
He didn't cultivate the Lower Volume.
But rather...
reversed the Xuan Gong.
Impossible.
How could the Xuan Gong be reversed?
You lot could never achieve it.
Did that fool Du Yu not tell you?
This Chen Family Xuan Gong
can only be reversed by me.
These paths of Gods and Demons...
I alone may tread upon them.
Betraying the Chen family—
that is disloyalty.
Driving Yuxin to her death—
that is inhumanity.
Disloyal, inhumane, shameless wretches...
deserve to die.
What?
You...
You hid your true strength when killing Du Yu.
It seems your strength isn't lacking...
but your wits are dull.
You're only realizing that now?
Madman.
The Elder was right.
All you Chens are raving lunatics.
Mad?
Blood debts must be repaid in blood.
To kill...
one must accept the risk of being killed.
No...
I...
I am of the Du family.
I know.
The Elders said...
we Du descendants are born rulers of this world.
So why...
did I have to die by your hand?
When my father granted you the Xuan Gong,
that was the cause.
Today, I claim your lives...
that is the effect.
Only thus can we call it...
a settling of karma.
Jin Bai.
Who else wishes to step forward?
Chen Nan.
Watch out!
The Dark Church's Twin Saint Dragon Knights.
Talida...
and Andeni.
We are here for revenge for our old friend.
Where did these scoundrels crawl out from?
They actually have the gall to attack a junior.
Reaping the benefits...
the Dark Church truly is shameless.
I, Chen, am quite enjoying this slaughter.
You two...
care to test your mettle?
You Eastern whelp...
you know nothing of the world.
That is...
the Divine Dragon.
Return.
This isn't a fight for you.
Or you'll fall into slumber again.
Relax.
These two are nothing.
They can't touch me.
Mm.
With the Divine Dragon present,
our Saint Dragons won't stand a chance.
No.
The Divine Dragon seems uninterested in fighting.
Now is our chance.
Kill him!
Chen Nan.
His Dragon Tongue Magic is instant-cast.
It will hold you back.
This desert shall be your burial ground.
Just you two?
It is not enough.
An attack of this level...
cannot break a Saint Dragon's defense.
Young, yet so accomplished.
What a pity.
Seize this moment.
Chen Nan.
You are truly a peerless genius.
Perhaps in another ten years,
the entire Dark Church couldn't stop you.
It is a shame...
you have no time left.
Pray to your gods...
for a quick death.
Do you really think...
you have me cornered?
I have seen enough...
of your skills.
Now...
it is my turn.
A Saint Dragon's defense is impregnable.
How is this possible?
Talida!
Saint Dragon...
is merely a toy in my hands.
How...
could this be?
Such loyalty and devotion...
I shall send you all on your way together.
Consuming mountains and seas...
power shattering a thousand weights.
Truly terrifying.
His strength is exhausted.
The time has come.
Despicable!
They're resorting to a tag-team battle.
It's over...
How many enemies does this guy have?
Shameless cowards.
Damn it.
He deliberately lured us out.
Those who came to die today...
are truly numerous.
Rise up.
[God-Trapping Finger: An ancient sealing technique that binds even the strongest foes. It suppresses power and prevents escape— a single strike is enough to seal everything.]
[Next Episode Preview]
Tell me...
have peerless masters become so cheap?
Showing up one after another to die.
You've finally revealed a flaw.
The ultimate law...
transcends all laws of this world.
How does one transcend?
By reforging heaven and earth.
And creating a new realm.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™