I heard the Church of Light was robbed yesterday.
Three young men from the East stormed the temple
and caused chaos right under the noses
of a bunch of fifth-tier experts,
then escaped without a scratch.
We on the Western Continent
have grown far too reliant
on energy-storing artifacts and magic crystals.
By the way...
Why did those three and the Dark Church suddenly attack the temple?
Spread the word and muddy the waters.
Say the two major churches clashed.
Claim the three Easterners
took advantage of the chaos to injure our temple mages.
Remember this:
Do not mention the divine bone under any circumstances.
Yes, sir.
One hundred and fifty thousand.
Two hundred thousand.
Two hundred and fifty thousand.
Meng Ke'er,
you'd better know when to stop.
Why should I let you—
You...
That divine bone is mine. I must have it.
Don't... don't you dare—
The Huntian Dao is willing to offer three hundred and fifty thousand gold coins
to purchase this divine bone.
Meng Ke'er,
don't force my hand.
The Tantai Sect offers four hundred thousand,
and no matter how much he bids,
I'm willing to add another fifty thousand.
You—
You...
Too many monks, not enough porridge.
In that case,
why not go rob a few more temples?
After this incident,
which empire's temple
do you think will unseal their shrine anytime soon?
Allow me to speak frankly.
Even if you obtain this divine bone,
you won't be able to wield the power within it.
What do you mean?
Before the God of Light was shattered,
he had already prepared for his resurrection.
He sealed his own power inside the divine bone.
How could any of you possibly refine it?
Stop trying to scare us.
If it's useless,
then why are you fighting over it?
I intend to place it within an array
to reinforce the seal on the devil inside our sect's secret realm.
What?
That devil...
is about to break free from the seal?
That's right.
The power of the seal has weakened considerably.
It must be replenished with divine power.
Otherwise...
once the seal breaks,
even the Huntian Dao won't be spared.
Don't forget,
back then, when our founding ancestor sealed that devil,
your Huntian Dao played a part as well.
The "devil" she's talking about...
Could it be the one we saw in the Void Heaven Illusion Realm?
So that's why she risked her life to seize the divine bone.
It was for this reason.
Dragon Baby,
give her the divine bone.
We're leaving.
Spit it out right now!
Damn it!
Baby is angry...
and the consequences...
Enough talk!
Spit out the divine relic!
Stop it, all of you!
How do you feel?
Is your body acting strange?
I feel something...
rolling around in my stomach.
Rolling... and rolling...
Dragon Baby...
Is Baby about to awaken his Heavenly Eye?
Why won't this thing leave?
Damn it, damn it!
Dragon Baby...
The God of Light's power has vanished.
Damn it!
That stupid dragon actually got the benefit!
When interests align,
people come together.
Now we're going to have new troubles.
Farewell.
Hahaha!
Chen Nan,
you'd better watch yourselves.
Meng Ke'er,
Wait a second.
What’s there to say to that woman?
Your old friend asked me to pass on a message.
What message?
Let me think how it went...
A hundred times... a hundred times...
You...
That damn rascal dragon!
Sooner or later, I’ll skin you alive!
He’s really learned some bad habits.
Looks like when it comes to framing me,
they’re all in perfect agreement for once.
Chen Nan,
Baby is so sleepy...
Alright.
Mmm...
What’s going on?
Wait!
Dragon Baby, don’t fall asleep!
Wake up!
Dragon Baby!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
That Eastern woman posted a letter outside the temple.
Please take a look.
Respected Grand Mage,
When the three of us first arrived,
we accidentally stumbled into the clash between the two churches
and unintentionally injured your temple mages.
To express our apology,
we captured the Dark Church mage who stole your holy relic.
The relic and the thief will be delivered to the temple by Chen Nan
as our way of making amends.
Looks like they’ve turned on each other.
The holy relic has fallen
into the hands of that young man named Chen Nan.
Should we send people to hunt him down?
No.
Both the man and the relic are in that youngster’s hands.
The Dark Church is probably even more anxious than we are.
Spread the word.
Say that the Church of Light
is willing to let this misunderstanding go.
We will send someone to contact Chen Nan today.
Yes, sir.
Not bad. They’re quite clever.
They publicly posted this apology letter,
yet didn’t mention a single word about what the holy relic actually is.
At least they didn’t let the plan to resurrect the God of Light
become public knowledge.
My lord,
we’ve found the kidnapped experts.
The red-haired Easterner sent them back.
It says Chen Nan already killed the man.
The divine bone
is in Chen Nan’s hands.
You useless bunch!
Not only did you fail to steal the divine bone,
you’ve also brought shame upon the Dark Church!
For all your crimes combined,
receive your judgment!
Dragon Knight
Chen Nan.
Two fifth-tier experts behind him,
one in front,
and one hiding in the shadows.
I need to draw all these troublesome guys together
and finish them off at once.
Heaven Extinguishing Palm!
Young man,
I admire you for surviving
several days of pursuit by three fifth-tier experts.
Truly impressive.
Why not hand over the holy relic?
We can consider letting you leave.
What a joke.
You pinned that Dark Church mage’s death on me,
and these past few days I’ve made you lose even more men.
Let me go?
The Dark Church really has no face left to lose.
After him!
I wonder when Dragon Baby will wake up...
If I can’t get Xiang Tian’s Godfiend Wings later,
I’ll just have to try stealing Meng Ke’er’s Jade Lotus Platform instead.
They finally couldn’t hold back any longer.
Take him down!
You—
Get down!
Heaven and Earth Shaking!
I’ve been watching you for a while.
You’re quite good.
But your strength is running out,
and that little dragon has fallen into a coma.
You have no chance of escaping.
You’re wary of my Divine Spirit Dragon,
so you’ve been secretly observing
and hesitated to make a move.
But did you know...
I’ve been waiting for you to show yourself
for a very long time.
Every last one of you here
who wants to die—
come after me.
I’ve prepared a very special gift just for you.
How arrogant!
After him!
Chen Nan,
you have nowhere left to run.
Hand over that little creature and the divine bone.
At least then you can die with some dignity.
Attack!
Hand over the divine bone! Hand it over!
Everyone’s here.
The terrain is perfect too.
Next up...
I hope you’re ready for the grand gift
I’ve prepared for all of you.
Heavenly Demon
Hand!
No!
Quick!
Stop him!
Four fifth-tier experts attacking at once...
Not even an immortal could escape that.
Ten days...
Is there any point in searching anymore?
What a shame... my dear prince.
[Haoran Sect Seal: The Haoran Sect is a righteous force that once swept across all directions. It is said that the sect possesses divine-level seal techniques. The Haoran Sect Seal is one of its supreme techniques, capable of suppressing all things. When activated, it can gather the power of heaven and earth and seal everything within its domain. Once sealed, it is extremely difficult to break free.]
[Next Episode Preview]
The Church of Light has been loudly praising your deeds.
You’re completely famous now.
However...
let me remind you—
just because it’s called “Light”
doesn’t mean it’s actually bright.
This aura...
Why do you know my Chen family’s secret technique?
The Du family has inherited our legacy for ten thousand years.
We are the imperial sovereigns of the Eastern cultivation world.
Today,
I will eliminate you—the so-called number one of the younger generation!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™