Oh, it's you two.
So you really are alive.
Amitabha Buddha.
Donor Chen, you bear the aspect of a great demon.
Without the salvation of a Great Buddha,
you would surely become a scourge
for a thousand years.
Truth be told,
we came here to collect your corpse.
Seems like
we made a wasted trip.
You risked danger to come for me.
This debt of gratitude
I, Chen Nan, acknowledge.
My dear Prince never fails to disappoint.
Since Chen Nan is safe and sound,
you two...
wish to take your leave here?
Or...
What?
Need me to help you collect corpses too?
Rumor has it Meng Ke'er challenged
the Successors of Righteousness and Evil
to a duel in the West.
It seems she was using these people
to mask her true objective.
I, Chen Nan, survived this calamity.
Would you grant me this small courtesy
to cease hostilities for now?
The Prince's face is naturally to be given.
But next time...
who knows?
Brother Chen,
farewell.
Until we meet again.
Amitabha.
Where do you plan to go next?
Naturally, I shall return to the city
in glory
and deliver a grand gift
to the Church of Light.
Heard about it?
That Easterner retrieved the Sacred Artifact.
Who would've thought there'd be
such a devout believer in the East?
Hero!
Young Master Chen's meritorious deeds
are engraved in the heart
of our Church of Light.
I, Chen Nan, dislike taking what others love.
My actions this time
were simply my duty.
If the Dark Church seeks revenge later,
you may present this medal at our church
to seek aid.
Hero!
Then, I thank you in advance.
Hahaha!
The Church of Light is loudly
proclaiming your achievements.
You are thoroughly famous now.
However...
let me warn you,
those named "Light" are not necessarily bright.
I wonder if those charlatans
have noticed the
Divine Relic is missing?
But even if they haven't,
the Church of Light's actions
have completely enmified the
Dark Church against me.
Whether it's "raising bandits for leverage"
or maintaining
a balance of power,
they can all reap the benefits.
Brother Chen, do be careful.
The Dark Church has endured
for a thousand years...
It must have its strengths.
No matter.
Whether they "raise bandits for leverage"
or maintain parity,
chess players operating in the open
pose no real threat.
Seems I needn't remind him.
Object Location Spell—
that's the Church of Light's
specialty after all.
Brother Kelly,
I toast you.
Looks like you need a favor.
A small matter.
I plan to go to the Holy City of Baidan
to meet the highest hall
of the Church of Light.
Before I leave,
I'd like you to spread a message for me.
Chen'er...
You truly repay kindness
with kindness, and hate with hate.
What is this?
Hero and the Rose.
A love cursed by the gods.
Trio of Fate.
Knight.
The perilous game between the Mage
and the Female Assassin.
Chen Nan, you bastard!
You've disturbed my Dao Heart so much.
Damn it!
He actually managed to kill
four peerless experts.
Why is his progress so godlike?
I refuse to accept this!
I will close my seclusion right now
and break through.
If I don't reach the Fifth Rank,
I swear I won't leave seclusion!
Brother Chen,
lend you my Unicorn temporarily.
Once you reach your destination,
it will return on its own.
Then, I thank you.
Have a safe journey.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Father once said,
the path of the warrior
is not about closed-door training.
Cultivating martial arts
is tempering the heart.
A flash between life and death
is cultivation.
The mortal world of red dust
is also cultivation.
A warrior's Dao
first requires understanding
the human heart,
then learning martial skills.
Only then can the mental state
be perfect and round.
Whole and without flaw.
Following successive great battles,
breaking through feels as natural
as water flowing to its level.
Fifth Rank Peerless.
Break!
This is the border region
of the four empires.
Originally a land of a hundred wars,
but due to the intervention
of the Church of Light,
it has gradually become peaceful.
Chen Nan,
why did that big con artist's relic
turn into a horn sprouting
from my head?
It's hideous!
Is it?
I think it looks rather cute.
This baby wants to be dashing,
not cute!
Hahaha!
Some petty thieves.
After traveling for so many days,
the Dark Church finally couldn't
hold back.
Strange.
Why do I sense on this man...
a breath of the same origin as myself?
You...
are Chen Nan?
Come.
Let me see
just how much the so-called
Number One of the Younger Generation
really weighs.
This aura...
Sky Severing Hand.
I thought it was just
a coincidence of names,
but it seems the legend is true.
Chen Nan,
you are a descendant of Chen Zhan.
You...
are a man returned from the dead.
This secret,
besides myself and the Nameless Demon,
should be known by no one.
I don't understand.
You can quibble,
but techniques
cannot lie.
Baby Dragon,
stand guard.
This man is connected
to my Chen family.
I'll handle him myself.
Listen well.
Chen Nan,
the one who kills you
is Du Yu.
Du Yu.
Why do you know the secret arts
of my Chen family?
Before you die,
I will mercifully tell you.
Every technique you know,
I know as well.
And I am only Fifth Rank.
Fifth Rank?
Didn't you know that two months ago,
I killed four Fifth Rank experts
in a single day?
Ridiculous.
After the Profound Art permeates
the body,
even a Fourth Rank can suppress
a Fifth Rank.
If it were me,
I could have annihilated
those four without a scratch.
Unlike you, who was so battered.
Your Profound Art True Qi...
it's actually multicolored?
Pathetic.
Ridiculous.
My Du family has been inherited
for ten thousand years.
We are the emperors of the Eastern Lands'
cultivation world.
Today,
I shall rid you, the so-called
Number One of the Younger Generation.
I will show the world
what a true Royal Family is.
Your legwork lacks refinement,
your Qi circulation is sluggish.
You even cultivated the Golden
Profound Art into a motley version.
This technique in your hands
is a sheer waste of heavenly gifts.
This Profound Art
is only fit to be used by my Du family.
You...
are unworthy.
You say
I am unworthy?
Wha—!
Impossible!
The silver
and yellow True Qi of my clansmen
cannot even compare to mine.
Yet you possess this chaotic, mixed Qi?
My clansmen are all...
Very well.
You people are truly...
Damnable!
The Imperial Du Family?
What third-rate, backwater clan is that?
In the cultivation history
of the Eastern Continent,
there has never been a great clan
surnamed Du.
Damn it!
If not for the Bloodline Curse,
my Du family would have long
since emerged into the world.
I understand now.
What are you laughing at?
Back then,
it must have been my Chen family
who imparted techniques to yours.
And granted you a corresponding mission.
Otherwise,
why would we give our Profound Arts
to outsiders?
Your Du lineage has served my Chen family
for many years.
and has been quite diligent.
Now, I shall transmit to you
the Upper Volume of the Profound Art.
You must cultivate it with care.
Thank you, My Lord!
I require you to swear a
Bloodline Venomous Oath:
After I depart,
your lineage shall reside in seclusion
within the Mystic Realm.
You are forbidden to emerge.
When ten thousand years have passed
and my son returns,
you shall pledge allegiance to him.
At that time,
he will naturally transmit
the Lower Volume to you.
This lowly one has noted it well.
In other words,
your family
should have been servants
of my Chen family.
But with the master absent,
the tail wags the dog,
and you've grown arrogant.
Impudent!
You...
You are simply...
You are not even Fourth Rank!
Finally figured it out?
I only recently broke through.
I originally intended to give
the Dark Church a surprise,
but the first to arrive
is a master-biting, wild dog.
This...
What sort of technique is this?
A wicked slave biting its master—
I shall be the one to
cleanse the family of this disgrace.
[Dong Family — Located in the western Taiyin region, a land rich in divine sources, the Dong Family stands as a prominent ancient clan with immense heritage and strength; their lineage is deeply rooted, producing many powerful experts across generations, and their influence extends far and wide, making them one of the most formidable families in the region. Land of a Hundred Battles — A harsh and chaotic domain where conflicts never cease, filled with endless struggles and trials; only the strong can survive here, tempering themselves through constant battle to rise above others and carve out their own legend.]
[Next Episode Preview]
Regarding the matter of dealing
with Chen Nan,
once you find traces of him,
I will naturally make my move.
Who taught you your techniques?
And what are these so-called oaths
and curses?
Du Yu,
often times,
the dead
are more useful
than the living.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™