You've been staring at the screen for a long time.
Don't just watch.
Subscribe, coin, and like.
I demand your one-click triple combo.
I want it now.
Granny, Grandpa, and Ancestor...
have all gone to Carefree Village.
Old Master, half a year without seeing you—
so you went *there*.
Where is Carefree Village?
Mu'er.
Got any food?
I've been starving for days.
Deafy Grandpa.
You're back.
Food will be ready shortly.
Mu'er's culinary skills...
are indistinguishable from the head chefs in Yan Kang's capital taverns.
Old Master, where have you been these days?
Went to Yan Kang to find the Mute.
Travel funds ran out.
Had to sell paintings.
People lack the virtue of the ancients.
Couldn't sell a single one.
Was truly starving,
met Old Lady Si,
she gave me some coins,
and mocked me for a good while.
Don't tell the Medicine Master about this.
That guy always laughs that my paintings don't sell as fast as his medicines.
Times are troubled now,
so no one buys paintings to collect.
Next time you're short on cash,
just sell them to the National Preceptor's Manor.
The Yan Kang National Preceptor would surely pay a high price.
I wiped out tens of thousands of his troops last time.
Going to his house to sell paintings...
He'll definitely use *Orthodoxy* on me.
I can't beat him.
Come find me at the Academy.
However many paintings you bring, I'll buy them all.
Are there other paintings in the study?
All burned.
What about the others?
Terrible handwriting.
I'll go find them tomorrow.
What is this?
I am...
Ugly looking.
You!
Your elders have even less manners than you.
Demon King.
Deafy Grandpa can't hear.
He just heard what you said clearly.
Sometimes he can hear,
sometimes he can't.
I see.
One more thing.
Demon King, don't run around at night.
The darkness is very dangerous.
This brat dares not enter the darkness—
Perfect timing for my escape.
Once I enter the darkness,
I'll preside over the Grand Sacrifice,
and summon my true body
to descend upon this world.
Now is the perfect time to leave.
This darkness...
It's different from the one in the Capital Sky World.
Constant Mo Corpse Chicken Granny Emperor...
Bu Na He Chicken Granny Sac...
What are you doing?
Why are you speaking Demon Tongue?
If there is a next time,
I will certainly not spare you lightly.
This old timer's ears are sharp.
Wait.
Isn't he supposed to be deaf?
Mu'er.
I'm going out to find the Village Chief and the others.
You and Big Dog watch the village.
I am not a dog.
I am the Auspicious Beast, half-dragon, half-qilin.
Deafy Master.
Help keep an eye on my Master.
Did he hear me or not?
He probably heard.
Wonder how Big Guy is doing lately.
I organized some techniques from the Book Pavilion.
They should suit his cultivation well.
I told you not to run around.
Constant Mo Corpse Chicken Granny Emperor...
This brat knows too.
Strange.
Why are Big Guy and Dragon Elephant gone?
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Wearing iron shoes everywhere in vain,
found without effort.
Never expected to meet the Heavenly Demon Cult Leader here.
Step aside.
Demon Head, you are full of cunning schemes.
Releasing the Root Demon to scatter us,
causing the death of several comrades.
Your sins are heavy.
That Root Demon has already been suppressed by the Holy Church.
If not for you letting it go,
how would it have had the chance to harm again?
If not for you, Demon Head, making the Root Demon disguise itself to deceive us,
how could such a tragic event have occurred?
Zen Master, your Heart Demon is deep indeed.
Demon Head, let me send you on your way.
Perfect timing to test my skills on you.
Trying out my perfected Five-Yao Divinization form.
I am not one who enjoys killing.
I have long since refined my evil thoughts into Zen beads.
Now, employing thunderous means
to rid the world of a scourge.
Come, good.
Such intense Metal Qi.
Truly a demonic path technique.
Using evil thoughts to forcefully boost strength—
Is this your Zen heart?
Demon Head, I will not listen to your demonic words.
Void Meditation Seal! Go!
If there is a next life,
be reborn as a good person.
Vajra Invincible!
Spawn of evil, die!
It ends here.
A combat expert of the Six Harmonies Realm.
Not to be underestimated.
Young Master,
Young Master, you are injured!
The venomous insect from Sanqi Fortress—
It is that woman.
She is already at the Seven Stars Realm.
Stronger than Ban Chi.
That insect flew from the banks of the Yong River.
We can ambush her there.
Young Master.
What are you doing?
Fighting.
Fighting again?
The Fish Monsters of the Yong River are also Five-Yao Realm.
Yet before the venomous insect she raised, they were crushed instantly.
Heavenly Demon Cult Leader.
How should I address the lady from Sanqi Fortress?
The Cult Leader holds high authority,
supreme under heaven, yet you are so polite to your enemy?
Calling me 'Big Sister'.
Within the Great Ruins, I am not the Heavenly Demon Cult Leader.
I am just an ordinary child from the Crippled Old Village.
I also ask you to let go of grudges,
leave the Great Ruins,
go back for the New Year,
and live well.
The New Year...
Yes.
Everyone should go home for the New Year.
It is just that...
My home was already reduced to ashes.
Destroyed by you and the Yan Kang National Preceptor.
My home was in Sanqi Fortress.
My Ancestral Master was Lord Tian.
My beloved master was Princess Tian You.
In the Battle of Great Xiang City,
the Heavenly Demon Cult delivered the Yan Kang army to the city,
killing countless of my senior brothers and sisters.
My master shielded me,
and died at the hands of the Duke of Wei.
I sneaked back to Sanqi Fortress,
only to find my family labeled as rebels,
their heads displayed in public.
In this lifetime, I can never celebrate the New Year again.
I have no home left to return to.
Cult Leader, should I kill you or not?
I should.
But when you rebelled, you should have considered
what fate
would befall your family upon failure.
Justice always requires some to risk their lives to uphold it.
Otherwise, where would justice exist under heaven?
Cult Leader,
say no more.
This concubine is here to send you on your way.
Different paths lead to no cooperation.
Dragon-Horned Lad did not come.
Got lost?
Or got taken out on the way?
Or perhaps she is nearby...
Heavenly Demon Cult Leader.
Killing a beauty—
you must be in quite a good mood.
The Deaf One ran away too.
Untie me.
Hurry up, hurry up.
I can't move, it's uncomfortable.
Quick, quick.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Stop!
Don't hit!
Smelly brat!
How have I offended you this time?
[Taibai Star Lord — Divine Manifestation: The Metal deity of the Five Luminaries, ruler of all metal energy. In this form, one draws in metal power, turning vital energy into steel— making weapons sharper and stronger.]
[Jupiter Star Lord — Divine Manifestation: The Wood deity of the Five Luminaries, ruler of life and growth. In this form, vital energy becomes wood energy—capable of healing wounds and controlling plants in battle.]
[Water Star Lord — Divine Manifestation: The Water deity of the Five Luminaries, nourishing all things through water. In this form, vital energy becomes water energy— and all abilities take on the power of water.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™