(Adapted from Tales of Herding Gods on Qidian Chinese Network under China Literature, Author: Zhaizhu)
- Tales of Herding Gods Season 3 -
Hey, you.
Are you following the series?
Have you dropped a coin
and smashed that like button?
Please,
give us that triple support!
I'm begging you!
(The setting, worldview, and locations in this series
are entirely imaginary. All characters, organizations,)
(and events portrayed are purely fictional.
They have no connection to, nor do they intend to imply,)
(any real-world entities, organizations, or events.
We advocate a scientific and positive lifestyle)
(and reject all forms of superstition.)
Episode 58
(Mount Shenglin Chapter)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
They say the Three-Marvel Fort has three marvels:
First, insects, then medicine, and last, beautiful women.
Looks like it's true.
No wonder you produced a Noble Consort.
Fan Yunxiao, the Dao Sect's expelled disciple?
Didn't you run off to be a fire bandit?
When did you turn over a new leaf?
How did I turn over a new leaf?
Your Cloud-Chasing Pirate Ship is now
a Cloud-Chasing Passenger Ship.
Didn't that mean you turn over a new leaf?
In times of peace, I robbed people for money.
In times of chaos, running a passenger ship
makes money faster than robbery.
General, could you let us pass?
The imperial court has hunted me for years
and never caught me.
General, are you sure you want to try?
We're leaving.
Master,
a bunch of officials
disguised as merchants are hiding in that ship.
Are we really just letting them go?
We can't delay our trip to the Southern Border.
As for them,
the insects will handle it.
Mr. Qin,
he really is a bandit leader!
I've gone straight.
Really.
Don't worry.
I'll get all of you safely to the capital.
You're a guest on my ship.
It's my duty to protect you.
Now that you've been robbed,
I can't take your money.
Boss,
the furnace got gnawed by the insects and exploded!
I told you, stop calling me boss.
I've gone straight.
That wretched woman played dirty behind my back.
Come help!
We'll have to abandon the ship.
It can still be fixed.
Boss, bad news!
The darn insect swarms are back!
Go help him!
Qin,
my strength will only last one incense stick!
That's enough.
We're saved!
Boss,
this kid fixed the furnace,
and now it's running even hotter than before!
Qin,
who taught you blacksmithing?
At this speed, when I go back to robbing,
who could ever catch me?
I thought you'd already gone straight.
It's Fan Yunxiao, the fire bandit!
I've gone straight! I'm a law-abiding citizen now.
(Merchant Ship License)
Here, this is my license.
(Cloud-Chasing Passenger Ship)
This ship is called "Cloud-Chasing Passenger Ship".
Let's go.
Qin,
you're wasting your talent by not being a bandit.
Why not come with me and...?
Fan, you were expelled from the Dao Sect
for your crooked nature,
but I'm a well-regarded scholar at the Imperial Academy.
By the way,
I heard the Dao Sect had a classic numerology text,
the "Numerology Codex of Supreme Mystery".
Have you seen it?
I happened to steal a copy when I left the Dao Sect.
If you want to learn it,
(Numerology Codex of Supreme Mystery)
it's yours.
This book is used to enlighten their disciples.
Once they master it, they can study the Dao Sword Forms.
If they master all 14 chapters, they'll be unmatched
and godlike.
The Dao Sect uses this codex to identify geniuses
and then trains them in the Dao Sword Forms.
The Academy's reform of genius cultivation
can't wait any longer.
The capital really is the best.
(Yankang)
Once the world is at peace,
my men can go back to the old trade and be bandits again.
Qin, if you ever change your mind,
come find me anytime!
What are you staring at?
You're skin and bones.
Why don't you go find something to eat?
People bring me food and drinks every day.
Why would I leave?
I'm perfectly comfortable here.
Is eating and drinking all you aspire to?
How could a fox understand a qilin's ambition?
Mr. Qin,
squatting has made this Dragon Qilin stupid.
Let's ignore him!
My master resigned from office
and ran off with an old man.
He abandoned me.
I had nowhere to go,
so I stayed here to guard the gate.
Now a bull bullies me every day.
I'm barely hanging on!
(Imperial Academy)
You were the Grandmaster's mount?
We're from the same sect.
I'm the Sect Master of the Saint Sect.
Don't talk nonsense!
There's no Grandmaster or Sect Master
in the Imperial Academy.
You knocked me unconscious.
I haven't even settled that score with you!
That was because you tricked me into fighting that bull.
How about
I call the bull over
and let you beat him up?
Are you trying to knock me out again?
(Tales of Herding Gods Season 3)
Mr. Qin...
Why are you following me?
You knocked me out,
so you're responsible for feeding me.
Didn't you just say people brought you food every day?
After my master left,
no one cared about me.
I haven't eaten in over a month.
Everyone thinks I'm a stone statue.
And I can't bring myself to beg.
That bull has Chancellor Ba Shan backing him,
so he keeps bullying me,
saying I toyed with his feelings.
Alright, alright.
I'll feed you.
I have money.
What do you eat?
I only drink water from Jade Dragon Lake
and eat ten liters of Redfire Pills a day.
Mr. Qin,
he'll eat us out of everything we own!
I can starve if I have to.
Five liters is fine.
One liter works, too.
Just one liter.
That's as low as I go!
I can refine pills myself.
That'll save some money.
You won't go hungry.
But I can't feed you for nothing.
You knocked me out,
and we're from the same sect.
You're the Sect Master,
and I was your Grandmaster's mount.
It's your responsibility to feed me!
Then you must give me some miracle saliva every day.
Otherwise, I can't afford you.
Miracle saliva?
Your drool.
That's easy.
By the way,
didn't you say you could call that bull over
so I could beat him up?
Don't push your luck,
or I'll cut your daily ration to five liters a day.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
With a body that big,
no wonder he eats so much.
I'll call you Big Dragon from now on.
You'll be the bull's big brother.
Mr. Qin, Sister Ling'er,
I'm still a little hungry.
I'll take you to refine medicine.
From now on, if you are in trouble, Mr. Qin,
just say the word.
I'm great in a fight.
You didn't even dare fight a bull,
and you call that great?
A divine medicine indeed!
Let's run another experiment.
Stop!
Sirs,
how much is this bottle of miracle saliva
worth to you?
Money comes in much faster this way than by robbing others.
Move aside, all of you!
That giant lion is alive?
Mr. Qin,
these blind fools have cleared a path.
Please.
You're drawing too much attention.
Do not do that again.
Senior brothers and sisters,
pardon us.
Cowherd!
Ever since Her Highness returned from that trip,
she's become just like that devil
from the Scholars' Quarters.
She even said she'd beat everyone in the Royal Garden.
Cowherd,
where have you been these days?
I...
and Mr. Ba Shan were really worried about you.
You've grown
even stronger since we last met.
Be careful.
The new Grand Chancellor is Gu Li'nuan.
He even asked Daoist Ling Yun about you.
Erudite Qin, you'd better
return the Shaobao Sword to Gu Li'nuan.
He's notoriously petty.
I can arrange a meeting
so that the two of you
can reconcile.
Otherwise, he might make life difficult for you.
In the Great Wasteland,
anything earned by one's own skill
never needs to be returned.
Besides, Gu Li'nuan said
he was the Crown Prince's teacher.
You're the Second Prince.
Do you really think he'll respect you?
Aren't you worried he'll make things difficult for you?
I will soon petition my father
to let me lead troops at the border.
Yuxiu, the court is full of hidden dangers.
Why don't you come with me?
If I can't bear to stay here anymore,
I'll definitely go to you.
But for now, I want to continue training
under Chancellor Ba Shan.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I'm here with her.
That is exactly what worries me.
Greetings, Grand Chancellor Gu.
You stole my Shaobao Sword.
Did you really think you would never fall into my hands?
Hand it over now!
I was appointed by His Majesty
as an Erudite of the Imperial Academy,
and I saved the Empress Dowager's life.
If you lay a hand on me,
the Emperor will take your head.
A Divine Bridge master
is attacking a Wuyao cultivator?
Shameless.
No need to trouble the Emperor to kill you and your family.
I will do it first!
Chancellor Ba Shan, you want to stand up for this brat?
Gu,
it's been 200 years.
Your soul-summoning spell is outdated now.
Do you need me to teach you a few tricks?
Teach me? Bring me the Heavenly Blade,
and maybe we can talk.
Are you really going to oppose me
for an outcast from the Great Wasteland?
He is my junior brother.
Imperial Preceptor?
I never would've imagined
the Sect Master of the Heavenly Saint Sect
would be the first Erudite of the Imperial Academy.
What an amusing turn of events.
Imperial Preceptor,
you did not come just to say that, did you?
You don't seem
surprised to see me.
The Heavenly Saint Sect accepts all without distinction.
There are many factions within the sect.
It is only natural that you would have
people among the upper ranks.
Then why are you not afraid?
Aren't you worried I might be here to kill you?
If you mean to kill me,
fear is useless.
If you don't kill me,
the Saint Sect will not rebel.
If you kill me,
then it certainly will.
(Three-Marvel Fort)
(This sect is famed for its beautiful female disciples,
its mastery of gu-based healing,)
(and above all, its terrifying insect army)
(Numerology Codex of Supreme Mystery)
(One of the Dao Sect's classic numerology texts.
It uses yin and yang and the eight trigrams)
(to deduce the workings of all things
and calculate vast cosmic patterns)
(Concept art design of Qin Mu)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™