(Adapted from Tales of Herding Gods on Qidian Chinese Network under China Literature, Author: Zhaizhu)
- Tales of Herding Gods Season 3 -
Hey, you.
Are you following the series?
Have you dropped a coin
and smashed that like button?
Please,
give us that triple support!
I'm begging you!
(The setting, worldview, and locations in this series
are entirely imaginary. All characters, organizations,)
(and events portrayed are purely fictional.
They have no connection to, nor do they intend to imply,)
(any real-world entities, organizations, or events.
We advocate a scientific and positive lifestyle)
(and reject all forms of superstition.)
Episode 56
(Mount Shenglin Chapter)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
There are many disciples
of the Heavenly Saint Sect within Yongzhou.
Seeing the situation here,
what are your thoughts?
You assisted the Imperial Preceptor
in founding the academies,
yet our sect's disciples have nowhere to study.
You thought of the world,
but forgot about the Saint Sect.
You should establish primary, secondary,
and imperial academies within our sect,
so our disciples won't fall behind the times.
That is the duty of the Sect Master,
not the Grandmaster.
Why didn't the previous Sect Master do it?
He was infatuated
with his wife
and no longer cared for the people.
Why don't we
select outstanding disciples from our sect
and have them take part
in the Imperial Academy's examinations?
That way, the Academy can help nurture our disciples.
If only you had been born 40 years earlier.
Left and Right Guardians,
are all our people assembled?
The Sect Mistress and the Saintess have yet to arrive.
Of the Four Great Kings of our sect,
King Qian still hasn't returned yet.
We're gathering this openly?
Could it be
that the main altar of our sect is located here in Yongzhou?
All 360 halls, raise your banners!
Junior Sect Master,
this is the holy land of the Heavenly Saint Sect,
Mount Shenglin.
Are Mu and the Grandmaster here?
Youyou,
show some restraint.
Who told you to reveal your true form?
The child you raised is about to become the Sect Master.
Do you want to turn his enthronement into a farce?
That's more like it.
Let's go.
Grandma!
Greetings, Junior Sect Master.
I am Si Yunxiang, the Saintess.
Saintess?
Our current Saintess is much more well-behaved.
The last one was a real troublemaker.
- I'm still here! - Grandma...
What's your problem, old fool?
Mu,
Xiang is from our Si family.
After the Grandmaster met her,
he personally trained her for several years.
No wonder she always reminded me of Grandma Si.
King Qian still hasn't arrived?
Not yet.
Look into it.
See that King Qian's family is well cared for.
Imperial Preceptor,
there's unrest in Yongzhou.
The senior members of the Heavenly Demon Sect
have gathered there,
and the City Lord's Mansion vanished into thin air.
I see.
It's the top demonic sect.
We cannot take them lightly.
If you knew who their Grandmaster is,
you wouldn't be so alarmed.
Their Grandmaster?
He was the Grand Chancellor of the Imperial Academy.
So he has been hiding here all this time.
Could he be...?
You're overthinking it.
Years ago, I traveled the land
to learn from all the great sects,
but I found each one hoarding its knowledge
and guarding its teachings,
which stifled the wider progress
of cultivation arts and techniques.
So I began visiting them,
hoping to tear down those barriers.
The first person I met
was the Grandmaster of the Heavenly Demon Sect.
He was the first to cast aside sectarian pride
and teach me sincerely,
showing me a clear path forward.
He even personally recommended me to the Dao Master.
Because of his recommendation,
the Dao Master treated me with favor
and granted me access to "The Fourteen Dao Sword Forms".
He also helped me gain entry to the Great Thunderclap Sect
to receive the teachings of Rulai.
Though he never revealed his identity,
he couldn't hide it from me.
Nor did he try.
(Hall of the Imperial Academy)
I invited him to oversee the Imperial Academy
not because of his skills,
nor because of his identity as
the Grandmaster of the Heavenly Demon Sect,
but because of his broad-mindedness.
He was the first person I ever met
with such purity and magnanimity of heart.
(Hall of the Imperial Academy)
Only he was fit to lead the Imperial Academy.
He is both my teacher
and my companion on the Way.
If he is your companion,
why did he resign and leave?
Likely for the next Sect Master of the Heavenly Demon Sect.
I will go and meet this new Sect Master myself.
If our paths align, he will thrive.
If they diverge, he will perish.
A blessed day,
a fortunate hour.
As heaven and earth unite,
endless blessings descend!
Disciples of the Heavenly Saint Sect,
welcome the Junior Sect Master to the throne!
Welcome to the throne, Junior Sect Master.
Welcome to the throne, Junior Sect Master!
Grandmaster,
why do we call the Sect Master's inauguration
an enthronement?
Isn't "enthronement" for emperors?
In the golden age of our sect,
we ruled six nations.
Their emperors were all our subjects.
Calling the Sect Master's inauguration
an enthronement was, in truth,
an honor for the emperors.
(Hall of the Sage's Heart)
But times have changed.
Now, a nation is the greatest of all sects.
A sect can no longer make everyone its disciple,
but a nation
can make everyone within its borders
its people.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(Tales of Herding Gods Season 3)
The Heavenly Demon Sect is gathering in Yongzhou.
They're likely about to install a new Sect Master.
They've been in chaos for over 40 years.
The arrival of this new leader
is no blessing for the people.
He must be eliminated.
Understood.
The Imperial Preceptor of Yankang has adopted
the Heavenly Demon Sect's doctrine as his guiding principle.
Yankang Nation has effectively become
a vast extension of the Heavenly Demon Sect.
What should our Dao Sect do about that?
The Imperial Preceptor's ability cannot match his ambition.
History has seen geniuses greater than him
and empires grander than Yankang Nation,
yet they all turned to dust
and then to the Great Wasteland in the end.
This world is far more complicated than he imagines.
When he suffers a crushing defeat, he will learn the truth.
Although Mount Shenglin now lies beyond the heavens,
it was once part of the mortal world.
When our founding master Wei Suifeng first came here,
he saw a woodcutter
felling this very pine.
Each time the axe struck, the tree would regrow
the missing piece.
Realizing he had met a sage,
the founding master sought his teaching.
The woodcutter sat upon this rock and began to preach,
continuing for decades.
The founding master later compiled the sage's words
and wrote "The Ultimate Heavenly Demon Codex" for the world.
Qin Mu,
will you inherit the founding master's virtues, wisdom,
principles, and knowledge?
Yes, I will.
Then
the sect will be yours.
You must bear its weight.
I will.
This is the Sage Rock
and Sage Seat.
The woodcutter sage
and the founding master shared no bloodline
or personal gain.
He taught simply because one sought the Way.
The Saint Sect has endured for over 20,000 years.
Once you sit upon the Sage Rock,
you become the Sect Master and Saint Master,
charged with passing on our teachings, guarding our faith,
and carrying the Heavenly Saint Sect into the future.
We pay our respects to you, Sect Master!
(Great Thunderclap Sect)
Fresh reports say
the prefect of Yongzhou
is Elder Yulin of the Heavenly Demon Sect.
Yongzhou has become a fortress of the sect.
Si Yunxiang, who defeated the Chanzi,
has also appeared there.
She is likely one of their disciples.
This gathering may be related to their new Sect Master.
(Great Thunderclap Sect)
The Heavenly Demon Sect
has been without a leader for over 40 years.
It has been riven by internal strife,
leaving it no time to meddle in Yankang's reforms.
(Great Thunderclap Sect)
But just a while ago, the Imperial Academy
used one of the Heavenly Demon Sect's disciples
to defeat our Chanzi.
If this was their new Sect Master's doing,
we cannot let it pass.
Understood.
There is one more matter.
Junior Brother Ma came out from the Great Wasteland.
Fate moves as it must.
Go investigate the new Sect Master
of the Heavenly Demon Sect.
I will personally settle this karmic debt.
Li Tianxing,
the new Sect Master has ascended the throne.
Aren't you going to appear and pass on our sect's arts?
Do you mean to take them to the grave?
I obey the law of the sect.
So Grandma's inner demon was Master Li all along.
Traveler,
you have watched from there for a long time.
What have you seen?
Please enlighten me, Sage.
Traveler,
your kin are already bones in their graves.
You have stood here watching for 100 years.
Have you seen anything?
Humans, demons, ghosts, and spirits
all follow their courses.
All creatures follow their own natural patterns.
That is the great constant of existence.
So the Great Unity Technique
of "The Ultimate Heavenly Demon Codex"
was hidden in the Sage's discourse.
How much one grasps
depends on one's own fortune.
Grandmaster,
the transmission is complete.
I must now seek a way to break free.
Only by destroying her (him)
can I devote myself wholly to cultivation
and advance further.
It is not yet certain who will destroy whom.
Grandmaster,
when Mu wakes, tell him
to come home for the New Year.
I'm leaving.
(Heavenly Saint Sect)
([Doctrine]: "The Way of the Sage is no different
from the people's daily life.)
(Whatever departs from it is heresy.
To follow one's true will and live in full accord)
(with nature is the Way." This is the foundation
of the Heavenly Saint Sect's creed and the opening tenet)
(of "The Ultimate Heavenly Demon Codex.")
([Origin]
The 360 cultivation paths taught by the woodcutter sage)
(became the origin of the Heavenly Saint Sect's 360 halls.)
The founding master gained endless insight
yet was still not satisfied,
so he asked the woodcutter...
May I ask, Sage,
how can I become a sage?
You must establish virtue,
establish merit, and establish teachings.
Thus, you will die yet not perish and become a sage.
How can one become imperishable?
You must first achieve the Three Clarities:
Clarity in principle, clarity in knowledge,
and clarity in teaching.
Only then can you become
the Saint Master of thousands of people.
(Concept art design of Qin Mu)
(Scan the QR codes to follow the official
Tales of Herding Gods account and join the official fan group)
(for more exciting news and surprise benefits)
When I left the Great Wasteland,
the grandpas and Grandma Si of Canlao Village
walked a long way with me.
I kept turning back again and again,
and each time I did, they followed me a little farther.
How I wish I could stay by their side
in Canlao Village forever.
But I know
that only by traveling farther to cultivate
can I find the Way that belongs to me.
(They taught me everything)
Grandma Si,
aren't you the one who least wants Mu to leave the village?
(But they never learned how to say goodbye)
Every fledgling
must leave the nest someday.
I didn't leave the village because I missed Mu.
I have real business to take care of.
- I'm leaving to check on my leg.
- The grandpas and Grandma Si of Canlao Village...
- I'm out to avenge the loss of my eyes.
- gave me everything.
- As the former Saintess of the Saint Sect...
- On those nights in Yankang...
- It's only right that I go meet...
- I often thought of them.
- the new Sect Master. - I believe they think of me, too.
They just
don't say it out loud.
So we all have real business to attend to after all!
But beyond Yankang and the Great Wasteland,
in every village all over the world,
there are grandpas and grandmas like mine.
They keep watch over empty homes
and think about their children far away.
Let's be there for them.
We can start with small things, like sharing a meal.
Bilibili Charity Platform's Elderly Companion Program
supports rural elders suffering from malnutrition.
Each month, it delivers nutritious food
and celebrates festivals and birthdays with them.
(Elderly Companion Program: Share a meal with the elders)
This lasting care
has become a source of warmth
in their lives.
Their companionship
gave us the courage to face the world.
Join me in protecting their health and happiness
through one shared meal.
Your kindness
will be recognized with a special certificate
that marks this bond of warmth and care.
Join me in sharing a meal with them.
(To care for the world is to care for ourselves)
To care for the world is to care for ourselves.
Mu,
go and make your own way.
We're all
doing just fine.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™