(Adapted from Tales of Herding Gods on Qidian Chinese Network under China Literature, Author: Zhaizhu)
- Tales of Herding Gods Season 3 -
Hey, you.
Are you following the series?
Have you dropped a coin
and smashed that like button?
Please,
give us that triple support!
I'm begging you!
(The setting, worldview, and locations in this series
are entirely imaginary. All characters, organizations,)
(and events portrayed are purely fictional.
They have no connection to, nor do they intend to imply,)
(any real-world entities, organizations, or events.
We advocate a scientific and positive lifestyle)
(and reject all forms of superstition.)
Episode 57
(Mount Shenglin Chapter)
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(Hall of the Imperial Academy)
His Majesty's decree:
"Gu Li'nuan, upright in nature
and versed in the classics and histories,
is hereby appointed Grand Chancellor
of the Imperial Academy, overseeing all its affairs.
May you nurture worthy talent
and live up to my expectations."
I will give my life for the cause and serve until death!
I received news from the Imperial Academy.
The new Grand Chancellor is Gu Li'nuan.
His learning and virtue are far from sufficient,
but this is something
I cannot question.
My power has grown too great.
It is only natural that His Majesty harbors concern.
Otherwise, even I would feel uneasy.
Present the matter of the Heavenly Demon Sect's
new Sect Master to His Majesty.
As for the former Grand Chancellor's true identity,
leave that unspoken.
Now that you are the Sect Master,
what do you plan to do first?
Establish the 361st hall,
the Hall of Learning.
I know you like tearing things down.
I had no problem with you
dismantling the Scholars' Quarters,
but you must never
take anything apart on Mount Shenglin.
I don't tear things down that often.
Right, right.
You were at the Imperial Academy for less than eight days,
and you only took apart two or three buildings
before heading beyond the border for more damage.
Every hall and palace here is an ancient site
engraved with cultivation techniques
for all disciples to learn.
There is no need to hoard knowledge.
Mastering it is what truly matters.
Stop here, Sect Master.
This farewell will be forever.
No matter how far you walk with me,
we must part at some point.
Grandmaster,
these are the treasures I took from the Golden Palace.
Trade them for travel expenses.
I also prepared some tonics.
The bottles are categorized by solar terms.
Take the white ones on the Spring Equinox,
and the blue ones on Frost's Descent.
Here's a bucket of Nine-Dragon Carp I just caught.
They're still fresh.
These are the peace knots I made by myself,
along with some thick robes and shoes...
Thank you, Grandmaster,
for your century of teaching
and a lifetime of guidance!
We bid you farewell!
Village Chief,
have you been lying like this for the past two days?
Did you stay here even when the darkness fell?
Apothecary, something's been bothering you.
You used to send me home every evening,
but yesterday, you forgot.
Couldn't you walk or fly back by yourself?
How? Remember
that I have neither legs nor arms.
You possess immense power.
Even the darkness couldn't kill you.
And now you're playing the helpless old man with me?
I was simply too lazy to move.
My fault.
(Canlao Village)
It is always a pleasure to greet a friend from afar!
My friend,
you are now free of burdens.
(Hall of the Sage's Heart)
After receiving the teachings from the woodcutter sage,
the Sect Master should develop their own
Great Unity Technique
to harmonize all the techniques
in "The Ultimate Heavenly Demon Codex".
(Soul-Summoning Guide)
Mount Shenglin, far removed from the clamor of the world,
is the perfect place for such enlightenment.
(Talismanic Script of Ghost and Spirit Command)
The Sect Master, raised by all of you,
is exceptionally bright
and was born with the Domineering Body.
Yet my knowledge is limited.
I had never heard of such a physique,
so I came to seek guidance.
Looks like we even fooled
the Grandmaster of the Heavenly Demon Sect.
Pardon my rudeness.
Here's the truth
behind the so-called Domineering Body.
Developing the Great Unity Technique
cannot be achieved in a day or two.
The Grandmaster likely meant for the Sect Master
to master another supreme art of our sect
as soon as possible.
You mean the teleportation art?
It requires extremely high skill in numerology.
The Sect Master is still young. It may be difficult for him.
He's forged a teleportation artifact already?
Does his rapid progress have to do
with his Domineering Body?
(Phoenix Pavilion)
This is the Phoenix Pavilion of our sixth Sect Master!
Please, Sect Master, stop tearing things down!
Sect Master,
the teleportation art is dangerous
and consumes Vital Energy rapidly.
With your current stage,
you can teleport only three or four times at most,
each time no more than 200 zhang.
If you run out of Vital Energy halfway,
you can get stuck inside a wall or a tree!
- Look out!
- You should confirm the destination before teleporting.
If you end up in a forbidden zone,
you might die without even leaving a body behind!
I understand now.
I need to determine each destination first
and then link them together
to teleport accurately.
The Sect Master's Domineering Body is really something.
Such rapid mastery is probably something
that even the Grandmaster did not expect.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(Tales of Herding Gods Season 3)
So his so-called Domineering Body
is actually nothing extraordinary.
But he believes in it with unshakable confidence
and has beaten so many talents and geniuses,
making them flee in disgrace.
What about the Domineering Body Triple-Elixir Skill
he practices? There must be something unique about it.
The Triple-Elixir Skill
is simply the most basic Guiding Skill
to keep healthy in the old era.
If only ordinary people before the disaster
could practice this technique,
then how did the Sect Master awaken his Mortal Body?
Was he born before the disaster?
Where was Mu really born?
Carefree Township.
Where is this Carefree Township?
If you are interested, my friend,
we can
leave the village tonight
and search for it in the darkness
at the source of the Yong River.
Do not damage the sacred tree!
He's developed his own Great Unity Technique!
When did you all arrive?
"To follow one's true will
and live in full accord with nature
is the Way."
Sect Master, the way you immerse yourself in the Way
is truly remarkable.
King Lu, you flatter me.
Mr. Qin, you must be hungry.
Here.
These pheasants were raised by the former Saintess.
Grandma Si raised them?
Too bad someone ate half of the Nine-Leaf Lingzhi
in the Medicine King Hall.
Otherwise, we could use it to nourish you.
I just remembered.
As an Erudite of the Academy,
I've barely attended any classes there.
I plan to leave today.
In every sense, we should ask you to stay longer,
but your studies come first.
We won't keep you.
Your studies come first.
Do come back often...
I will.
This new Sect Master is really something.
The teleportation art relies on numerology,
and the Great Unity Technique depends on comprehension.
Yet he mastered both in just over ten days.
Such talent and insight are rarely seen in the world.
True.
But he still can't match the Imperial Preceptor,
a sage seen once in five centuries.
That's not necessarily true.
We only know what we've witnessed.
He may have grasped even more.
I can't wait to see him
lead our sect to new glory.
Our holy land is now above Guazhou?
Lately, the imperial relatives of Yankang
have rebelled there.
Sect Master!
My lord,
a kid popped out of nowhere.
No need to be alarmed.
I just want a ride to the capital.
From Guazhou to the capital?
That'll be 100 Dafeng coins.
That much?
Where else will you find such a fair price?
Times are hard. There's war every day. Danger is everywhere.
We risk our lives with every trip,
so of course we charge more.
These people don't look like proper boatmen.
They're clearly bandits!
Please, sir, take the honored seat!
Do you feel good?
Sir,
after my father visited the Imperial Preceptor that night,
the Three-Marvel Fort in Guazhou,
the Liqing Palace in Linzhou,
and the Beggar Sect in Pingzhou all rebelled.
I heard Emperor Yanfeng was so enraged
that he sent Consort Che, who came
from the Three-Marvel Fort, into a cold palace.
Send my words to all the sects.
Gather forces on the Southern Border.
The Imperial Preceptor has let this rebellion drag on.
When will he act?
It's the insect army of the Three-Marvel Fort!
Change course!
Increase firepower!
Full speed ahead!
What great swordsmanship!
I am Fan Yunxiao.
Are you from the Yuyuan clan?
I'm Qin Mu. I'm from the Imperial Academy.
(Concept art design of Qin Mu)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
(for more exciting news and surprise benefits)