You've been staring at the screen for ages.
Don't just sit there watching.
Go follow, like, and upvote.
I want that one-click triple combo from you.
Right now.
[Calamity Arc — FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™Episode 37]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Holy Sect Master,
You've made me suffer so much.
I will have my revenge.
I'll slaughter every last member of the Heavenly Saint Sect!
I'll kill you all!
Kill you all!
Could the Heavenly Demon Cult Leader have gone to the God-Severing Mountain Range?
Isn't he one of the abandoned people?
Isn't he afraid of being shot down by the Profound Gear Crossbows?
Perhaps there's a path to survival hidden there.
Send the bugs to scout ahead.
What a shame.
This female is actually quite beautiful.
The root demon made too much noise.
It's drawn the pursuers over.
Holy Cult Leader, I will kill you!
And wipe out the entire Heavenly Saint Sect!
Demon, what grudge do you hold against the Heavenly Demon Cult?
They sealed this little lady here for six hundred years.
My hatred for them runs as deep as the sea.
Master, if you can topple this stone stele and rescue me...
I will repay you with my body.
You need not follow me in cultivating Zen.
Just help me kill the Heavenly Demon Cult Leader.
And I shall release you.
Such petty fox tricks are enough to bewitch your heart?
The Heavenly Demon Cult follows the demonic path.
Any demon they suppress must be a righteous one.
We'll need a guide on our journey to the Great Ruins.
Everyone, help me push down these demon-suppressing steles.
And free this fellow cultivator.
Thank you, Master.
I can finally eat people again.
I can finally eat people again!
This is bad.
That demon was deliberately sealed here by the Heavenly Demon Cult Leader to trap us!
Little Red, lure it toward the Profound Gear Crossbows.
We've successfully drawn the demon away.
It didn't harm the people of Yan Kang.
That's a blessing in itself.
Even a divine artifact couldn't subdue it.
How is that possible?
Up ahead...
lies the Great Ruins.
This heavenly disaster is a warning from the gods.
It seems to target only Yan Kang.
Come to think of it, ever since I started following Master,
it's been many years since I last returned to the Great Ruins.
Ruins...
Could there still be gods and demons here?
Some died in battle.
Others were sealed away.
But when darkness falls,
they will rise once more.
There's a saying everyone in the Great Ruins knows:
Don't go out after dark.
What does darkness matter?
My Heaven World has already been destroyed and plunged into total darkness.
In the dark, I thrive like a fish in water.
You don't believe me?
Come nightfall, I'll take a stroll and show you.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
The root demon has been released.
Who could be this stupid?
Who did this?
This demon really is courting death,
rampaging wildly through the Great Ruins.
The Great Ruins hold far too many mysterious powers.
Even Grandpa Village Chief
wouldn't act so recklessly.
It's fine. The Great Ruins are always like this.
Some ruins hide gods and monsters within.
Just remember to burn incense and pray, and you'll be safe.
That root demon probably accidentally disturbed one of the ruins
and provoked the deity inside.
The Great Ruins have no king or laws.
So no matter who you meet,
you must always show proper respect.
Otherwise, if you offend the wrong person,
you could easily get killed.
This is too dangerous. I want to go back to Heaven World.
What kind of mortal realm is this broken world of yours?
It's full of demons, monsters, gods, and spirits everywhere!
Fine, I won't invade, okay?
Just let me go.
I want to go home.
Once you learn the rules of the Great Ruins,
you'll find it's actually much safer than Yan Kang Kingdom.
If you don't believe me, ask Ling'er.
Young Master came out this time
precisely to gain experience in Yan Kang Kingdom.
Training in the Great Ruins doesn't even count.
That just shows how dangerous Yan Kang truly is.
Don't worry.
The Great Ruins are very safe.
You'll be fine as long as you stay with Young Master.
I was only looking for a low-level world
where my people could settle down.
The Heaven World is already finished.
If I keep fighting you with blood and lives,
we'll truly go extinct.
We'll truly go extinct.
Young Master seems quite pitiful, actually.
He's only a strand of consciousness.
His true body is still in the Heaven World.
If he really wanted to keep searching for other worlds,
why would he insist on sending this consciousness back?
Not a single word from that guy can be trusted.
I can't fly anymore...
Dragon Fatty told you ages ago to lose some weight.
Young Master!
Young Master is back!
How does Yan Kang Kingdom compare to our Great Ruins?
Yan Kang is far more chaotic than the Great Ruins.
Rebellions and wars every day—it's total chaos.
Definitely not a good place.
Indeed.
Not long ago, many refugees fled into the Great Ruins.
They said they escaped because of the snow disaster.
It's good that Young Master is back.
After all, home is still the safest.
Young Master! Young Master is back!
Granny.
Has the City Lord returned?
The City Lord came by a while ago and then left.
Will Young Master be staying?
I'll prepare the rooms right away.
No need.
The New Year is approaching.
I'll head back to the village first.
You've eaten and lazed around enough. Ready to move?
Let's get going.
Xian Qing'er.
The cowherd boy has returned in glory!
Was it fun outside?
It was okay... except everyone kept trying to kill me wherever I went.
By the way, has Little Lai come looking for you?
Good fortune and great profit!
He never made it here.
What bad thing did you do to get chased like that?
Probably because I'm just too outstanding and people are jealous.
I'll come visit your village for New Year's when I have time.
Just don't let your folks kill me.
Okay.
Granny, Grandpa, I'm back!
I went through so much hardship to rush back.
Why is no one paying attention to me?
Trying to prank me again?
Mute Grandpa.
Medicine Grandpa, I see you!
Horse Grandpa.
Village Chief Grandpa.
Deaf Grandpa.
Butcher Grandpa.
Tumor Grandpa.
Blind Grandpa.
Granny...
Strange... where did everyone go?
The Medicine Master and I will take the Heavenly Demon Cult's Patriarch and Law Enforcement Elder
into the darkness for a trip.
We'll scout out Carefree Village.
If anyone returns, help the Medicine Master feed the bugs.
The Village Chief and the others still haven't come back.
The Blind One and I will go look for them.
Those old fellows might have run into danger.
The Horse Master and I will also head to Carefree Village.
Mu'er.
I'll go bring those old things back for the New Year.
Don't wander around.
If you see the Deaf One, make him something to eat.
He's about to starve to death.
Granny, the grandpas, and the Patriarch
have all gone to search for Carefree Village.
[Root Demon: Its true form is a mass of roots. By absorbing divine blood and demonic blood, it evolves into a great demon, gaining immense power. Extremely dangerous, it disguises itself as a woman during hunts, using this form to lure prey into its trap.]
[Great Ruins Rules: The Great Ruins are desolate and strange, filled with sinister anomalies; there are no nations or laws, and to survive one must follow its unique rules. Here, strength is everything—the strong prey on the weak, and only the fittest survive, with all one seizes becoming their own. At the same time, in this land overrun with gods and monsters, one must observe proper rites: by day, offer incense and pray when encountering temples to remain safe; by night, never go out, and never act recklessly within the dark ruins. These rules are not written laws, but the boundaries of survival discovered through the lives of those who came before.]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™