(Adapted from Tale of Herding God
on Qidian Chinese Network
under China Literature, Author: Zhaizhu)
(Tales of Herding Gods)
You've been staring
at the screen for ages.
Don't just watch.
Follow the series, drop coins,
and hit like.
I want your triple support.
I want it right now.
(The story depicted in this animation is entirely fictional)
(Episode 79)
(The Calamity Arc: Heavenly King of Zhenhai)
Grandpa Deaf has been gone six days
without a word.
There are only three days left
till New Year.
They've been gone too long.
Do you think something happened
on the way?
Let's go to the source of the Yong River
and find them.
Even someone as strong as Master
didn't come back.
What good would it do if we went?
Hu Ling'er, go to Xianglong City
and report this.
Get the Sacred Sect's experts moving.
Have them gather news
and track down clues.
Big Dragon and I will head up
along the Yong River
and go find the entrance
to the Dark Realm.
Something's changing again
in the distance.
Looks like we have quite a few guests.
We'd better prepare more thoroughly.
So no one says people from
the Great Wasteland lack manners.
Demon King.
You're from
the Heavenly Demon Race too, right?
You want to use my power?
No!
If you treat me a little better,
I might agree to it.
But you hit me for no reason,
and that really annoyed me.
If you help me find the elders
in the village,
I'll set you free.
How does that sound?
Deal.
Young Master,
I'm off to deliver the message.
Let's go!
Everyone who searched this area is dead.
Something's off.
This village is huge,
but there's not a soul in sight.
This whole village is full of treasures.
Go!
We can't go into this village.
Hong, move!
It's getting dark.
There are ruins up ahead.
Let's head there!
Senior Brother Chiyun.
After spending some time training
in the Great Wasteland,
I'm still shaken
by all its strange wonders.
Even these ruins have
such a grand Heavenly King statue.
Junior Sister,
my disciple Shao Yuan
was just discussing this with me.
Many people from the Great Wasteland come to
offer incense for the Heavenly King statue.
This statue clearly has
an extraordinary origin.
There's something off
about these Daoists.
I know.
One of the female Daoists
is Long Jiaonan.
(Tales of Herding Gods)
Should we make the first move?
The Great Wasteland has its rules.
When darkness falls,
no one fights inside the ruins.
There is an aura
of the True God in the dark.
That's a huge disturbance.
Why is tonight different from usual?
When the darkness fell just now,
the giant beast bones in the ruins
came back to life,
turning into the Beast God,
and walked out of the ruins.
It is fighting demonic monsters
in the dark.
It's already past midnight.
Clear the way.
(Silence)
(Clear the way)
Silence!
Heavenly King of Zhenhai,
Ao Zhen, the East Sea Dragon King, has used
the heavenly calamity to stir chaos.
His Majesty has sent an order
from Worry-Free Land.
We were ordered to come here
to help you take him down!
Worry-Free Land.
It's been in chaos
for over twenty thousand years.
And this guy still dares to rise up.
Bring me my blade!
Where is my mount?
Kylin steed,
why won't you move forward?
Carry out the order now.
Ride out with me!
Go back to Worry-Free Land
and report to His Majesty.
I have fulfilled my mission.
The rebel leader
has already been taken down!
Aye!
Big Dragon, what's wrong?
I dreamed I was carrying
a God King on my back.
We charged
into a fierce, chaotic battlefield.
Countless dragons came at me.
But the God King on my back
cut them down with his blade.
That God King cut off
a Dragon King's head!
That dream felt so real.
This Heavenly King statue really did
strike down an East Sea Dragon King.
The blood on the blade
is the East Sea Dragon King's blood.
Where exactly is Worry-Free Land?
Let's go.
(Zhenhai Guandi Temple)
(Scan the QR code to follow the official Tale
of Herding God animation account
for more exciting news and surprise benefits)
(Adapted from Tale of Herding God on Qidian Chinese Network
under China Literature, Author: Zhaizhu)
(The exclusive global Information Network Communication Rights of this work
belong to Shanghai Kuanyu Digital Technology Co., Ltd.)
(The complete Copyright of this work and all elements contained within it
are jointly owned by Shanghai Kuanyu Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
and Hangzhou Sparkly Key Technology Co., Ltd.)