[Previously]
Creation God... Creation God...
Even after all these years
since your death...
you made such elaborate preparations.
In that case...
let me see...
if the ending you hoped for...
can come true.
Long Haochen...
Go... become a god.
Only a god...
can slay a god.
Mother Goddess...
Lord Electrolux left you
a final gift.
My dear disciple...
this is the path to godhood
I prepared for you.
In legends of the Holy Demon Continent...
death...
is an endless, boundless river.
Every drop...
is a departed soul.
No matter how fierce the emotions...
no matter how unrelenting the regrets...
all fade in the River of the Dead...
dissolve away.
Like...
water vanishing into water.
Here...
is the final destination
of all living beings...
the end of every cycle.
The realm ruled solely...
by the God of Death.
Sheng Cai'er...
you are my most cherished chosen.
Today...
you shall command the Ferry of the Far Shore...
become the new God of Death.
Ruler over billions of souls...
in this vast River of the Dead...
their new sovereign.
The God of Death I remember...
was never this generous.
I know...
compared to other gods' blessings...
mine is... different.
Some might even call it...
cruel.
But this river holds...
countless regrets and obsessions.
The greatest power...
yet the heaviest burden.
Without enduring the agony
of losing all six senses...
how could one bear
this entire river?
Since you've come...
you must be prepared.
So this time...
what do you want from me?
The River of the Dead...
bears souls of the entire world.
They must cleanse all obsessions...
within the river...
to reach the far shore of life.
The God of Death's duty...
is to ferry souls here.
But over countless ages...
five sinful souls escaped the river.
You want me to ferry them back?
Yes.
Bring them back...
let their obsessions return
to the river.
This...
is your trial.
This River of the Dead Pact...
will help you...
locate them.
But remember...
before the pact fully depletes...
complete the trial.
Or else...
godhood will forever elude you.
Go...
Sheng Cai'er.
When the river fills with souls...
a new god shall be born.
Curse Crow Flower...
In the endless past...
even gods...
made mistakes.
Those mistakes...
became sins.
Divine Sin...
brings endless slaughter and death.
It grows by devouring
blood and carnage...
Heart...
It hunts every living being
that discovers it.
Like...
a born seed of evil.
You seem...
different from those fools.
Its body...
Do you think...
I'm guilty?
brims with sin and resentment.
For every life you took...
I'll repay you...
a hundredfold in agony.
You're no different from them.
None of you understand...
the joy of death.
His strength...
rivals the top fifteen Demon Gods.
Tear flesh...
shatter bone...
scorch the soul...
burn the soul!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
When life fades, it rings out...
a melody the dull River of the Dead...
has never known.
I killed them...
as they slaughter cattle...
as they slaughter sheep.
Survival of the fittest...
the law of nature.
Even a god...
cannot purify me.
You...
don't deserve purification.
So vile and filthy...
you deserve only death.
What did you say?!
The River of the Dead...
No!
You can't kill me!
Ferry to Oblivion!
Go confess to those you slew.
Whose sin do you think I am?
I am the sin of Death itself!
Think becoming Death is easy?
Those words planted doubt
in Sheng Cai'er...
but she pressed on...
delving deeper...
into this so-called trial.
Unstoppable...
she finally reached...
the last sinful soul's domain.
One moment, please.
The previous four sins...
brimmed...
with evil and hatred.
Yet this final one...
feels so serene.
You've come for me.
I'm sorry...
I can't leave yet.
Don't come closer!
Why?
I sense...
no killing intent in you.
Then why stay?
I...
don't remember.
I only know...
this is my blood.
And...
there's something vital...
I can't leave yet.
But I can't recall it...
something crucial...
I must never forget.
I've lost precious memories too.
Will you...
trust me?
I remember now!
My daughter is waiting!
Divine envoy...
thank you for restoring my memory.
Can you take me to her?
Just to see her...
know she's well.
Then...
I'll go with you to the river.
You're a good mother.
But I'm sorry...
I can't.
Why?
In that brutal war...
your homeland...
was massacred.
Your daughter included.
All souls...
ferried to the river...
reborn anew.
You're the last.
So...
you can't...
see your daughter again.
But I can feel...
she hasn't vanished.
She hasn't vanished!
If she had...
that flower would be gone too.
But the flower remains.
I can sense it...
so my daughter lives!
She can't have vanished!
I don't know why...
you still sense...
your daughter's presence.
But...
I too have one...
who'd do anything for me.
I'll try with you.
Thank you...
Thank you!
To see my daughter...
I'll do anything.
Picture your deepest bond...
with your daughter.
I'll take you to her.
Found her.
Divine envoy...
my daughter's below!
Riverbed of the dead...
You sure?
No doubt.
I feel my daughter's aura.
Fine.
Let's see.
Where...
Where's my daughter?
Riverbed of the dead...
holds only forgotten...
dissolved obsessions.
Your daughter can't be here.
No!
She's here for sure!
My daughter...
waits for me!
Looks like...
her longing's too deep...
causing illusions.
Over there!
Someone there!
What?!
All souls...
should've been reborn by now...
They must cleanse obsessions here...
to reach life's far shore.
Death's duty...
is ferrying souls here.
Child...
My child!
She...
wasn't reborn!
Mama...
Mama!
You said as long as the flower blooms...
you'd return.
So I've waited here.
Sorry...
Mama failed you...
couldn't find you sooner.
But everyone...
was devoured by the river!
The river...
doesn't ferry souls to rebirth...
it imprisons them!
Why?!
Sheng Cai'er...
You've found the final sin.
Kill her...
and the trial ends.
She bears no sin!
The sinner...
is you!
Whose sin do you think I am?
I am Death's own sin!
Think becoming Death is simple?
As Death...
you should ferry souls...
yet you imprisoned them...
in endless torment!
That's your sin!
What sin have I?
By trapping souls in the river...
I absorb their power forever!
Eternal Death's might...
not fading like other gods!
Sheng Cai'er...
I'm teaching you how to be a god!
Then I'll teach you to be human!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™