(Copyright Notice)
(Minors, please watch only with
guardian permission.)
(All content in this film is
computer-generated.)
(Do not imitate in real life.)
-THRONE OF THE DIVINE SEAL - ♪I stand for a long, long time♪
♪Before fate turns against me♪
♪On the open plain♪
♪Is what’s right still clear to me?♪
♪Silent mountains surround me
day and night♪
♪Even this land of tears
is stirred by storms♪
♪I answer with a shining light♪
♪For endless moments of tomorrow♪
♪We share the last feast together♪
♪Swallowing pairs of tearful eyes♪
♪We need not be remembered♪
♪Creation is destruction♪
♪Change is the only constant♪
♪Shouting aloud♪
♪We stand in the center
of the universe♪
♪Everywhere is forward♪
♪Why not move ahead?♪
- THRONE OF THE DIVINE SEAL -
- ASTRAL CHART OF FATE -
(Previously) The Abyss is divided into the outer layer,
the inner layer, and the core.
The deeper you go,
the more dangerous it gets.
At the deepest point,
even light cannot escape.
Senior Ye,
I’ve learned many lessons,
but none of them say
to just watch a hero die.
Drag everyone
Dragon Haochen cares about
into this mess.
I’ll push this death match
to its peak.
I want Dragon Haochen to fall into utter despair.
EPISODE 185
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
You’ve revived the glory
of God Juling Shen.
You’ve made the bloodline of Juling Shen boil once again.
But in history,
descendants of Juling Shen
like you
all die suddenly
one night.
They just drop dead.
This is
the curse of the gods.
(Burning through hell)
Where is this?
What’s going on?
So many demons
showed up suddenly.
The weakest are
seventh rank.
We’re only
fourth or fifth rank.
There are many civilians
with no fighting power.
We must protect them.
What are these darn demons
trying to do?
Dragging so many civilians
into the chaos.
Darn it.
They’re clearly
toying with us.
Brothers, devour them!
Win this for
His Highness the Prince!
Warriors, protect the civilians!
Little Cake!
It’s Hall Master Wang
from the Warrior Temple!
We’re saved!
Take her out first!
Darn humans!
You’ll all die sooner or later.
You talk too much.
Demons—
are all dead!
We won!
Humans are victorious!
That’s great!
Wait, no—
There’s still one left.
Hall Master Wang!
Be careful!
It’s the Demon God!
Crush these despicable humans!
(So strong…)
Hall Master!
What a terrifying aura…
Which Demon God is that?
That…
That must be the Fifth Pillar
Hell Demon God—
Marbas.
Hell Demon God.
How come I’ve never seen him?
According to the Alliance records,
the last time he appeared was thousands of years ago.
He’s been hidden
for so long.
His power
is probably unfathomable.
At first, Marbas was just an ordinary demon.
He looked completely average, nothing special at all.
But with one move, he killed the Seventy-Second Pillar Demon God.
He rose to the rank of Demon God.
Then,
he became a hellish asura,
slaughtering his way from
the Seventy-Second Pillar
all the way to the Fifth Pillar.
He pierced the heart of the
Fifth Pillar Demon God.
He shattered the Demon God Crown
of the Fifth Pillar.
From then on,
he became the new Hell Demon God.
Though competition among Demon Gods
is always fierce,
his rise still shook the demon race.
To calm the demons,
His Majesty ordered me
to imprison him.
Until now.
He must be enjoying
this long-lost freedom.
(Fifth Pillar Hell Demon God: Marbas)
That was a heavy blow.
Next.
Dad…
You’d better last a bit longer.
Who said you could touch them?
You’re really annoying me.
You actually survived one of my attacks.
Interesting.
It's been so long since I last killed.
You'd better make this fun for me.
What is this?
Welcome to
Slaughter Hell.
(Domain: Slaughter Hell)
I'll give you the highest level of hospitality.
What does he want with Yuanyuan?
He's suppressing his own rank.
Sealing part of his power.
The demon god wants to torture his prey.
Let's play a little longer.
Don't waste my kindness.
He actually lowered his rank to match my ninth rank, second level.
If you can hurt me, you win.
Come.
Blood Saw Frenzy!
How is this possible?
At the same rank,
his power is still many times mine.
Come on,
little warrior.
Not bad.
You've got strength.
My turn now.
Run faster!
Got you!
Little warrior.
(So strong.)
(Until now,)
(he hasn't even used a skill.)
Blood Domain!
Activate!
Yuanyuan's Blood Domain has been broken.
And with just one move.
Is that all you've got?
Aegis of Juling Shen!
Could it be you're a descendant of Ju Ling Shen?
This is getting interesting.
No wonder you survived my attack.
Ju Ling Divine Weapon!
Sever the Void!
It worked!
Such a nostalgic move.
Ju Ling Divine Weapon!
Sever the Void!
What?
Why does he
know that move?
Three thousand years ago,
the first to awaken Ju Ling Shen's bloodline was burned alive.
The second awakened
froze to death in a blizzard.
The third, every bone in his body was shattered.
He couldn't even crawl.
Just like
this punch.
On his body,
why is there Ju Ling Shen's power?
Aegis of Juling Shen!
It's broken.
Three thousand years ago, I first tasted Ju Ling Shen's power.
So sweet.
So powerful.
With that power, I became the Fifth Pillar Demon God.
To devour all Ju Ling Shen's power,
I waited patiently.
Cursing in hell every awakened Ju Ling Shen descendant.
So the one killing Ju Ling Shen's bloodline
is you.
(Ju Ling Shen)
Now,
you're the last one.
(Hell Ju Ling Shen)
Once I kill you,
I'll have all Ju Ling Shen's power.
With this power, I'll remake myself completely.
Become greater than a demon god.
Surpass the Demon God Emperor Feng Xiu.
What's happening?
Our Furious Battle Force—
The Furious Battle Force from Lord Wang—
He's using Yuanyuan
to extract all Ju Ling Shen's power.
Finally,
the last of Ju Ling Shen's power
is mine too.
I've finally become
the complete Ju Ling Shen.
Yuanyuan...
The demons
are about to win again.
Our bloody goddess of war
is she going to lose?
Ju Ling Shen...
Yuanyuan...
We of the Warrior Temple are all ordinary people without talent.
Except for hard work and blood, the only thing we rely on
is our faith in Ju Ling Shen.
You carry his bloodline.
You're our most vital spark.
You must restore Ju Ling Shen's glory.
Restore the glory of warriors.
This bloodline made me lonely,
but also proud.
But now,
I grieve for this bloodline.
And rage.
The so-called divine curse—
the truth is laughable.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Just a greedy thief.
You
are not worthy of Ju Ling Shen.
Let me tell you—Ju Ling Shen
is not my greatest power.
It's not about bloodline, not about anything else.
It's just a heart that fights
to the very end.
What?
Ju Ling...
Ten Thousand Bloods to Ashes!
(Ten Thousand Bloods to Ashes)
Why is this fire burning me?
With the descendant's final forbidden art,
I ignite Ju Ling Shen's bloodline within me.
The flames from this bloodline
will ignite all Ju Ling Shen's power in the world.
You will be burned by the Ju Ling Shen power
inside you until nothing remains.
Darn it.
But a mere mortal like you can only burn for a few moments.
I am
the mighty Fifth Pillar Demon God.
Hell Demon God.
He unleashed all his power.
Returned to his original rank: ninth tier, level seven.
Yuanyuan.
Until you burn to ashes, I will still stand here.
You are nothing but a tiny kindling.
How could you ignite the whole night?
How long can you endure this pain?
It truly hurts.
I am just kindling too.
But our captain once told me,
Yuanyuan,
you have never fought alone.
Behind you,
countless warriors stand.
The faith you have always held
is also their faith.
They all believe in you deeply.
Believe in us.
Believe in all humanity.
We will surely achieve victory.
So,
even if I am just kindling,
the passion that belongs
to humanity,
our faith and will,
warriors, as long as our belief endures,
Temple Master Wang will not fall.
Humanity will not fall.
Yuanyuan will not fall.
This willpower
lets me burn
and grow at the same time.
H-how is this possible?
You're insane!
This is the world's most agonizing punishment.
You will, for all eternity, every single moment, suffer the pain of burning flames.
It cannot be reversed.
There is no escape.
Then let these flames burn through hell,
and consume everything.
From now on,
my God Juling Shen bloodline
will be ruled by me alone.
Like this,
it's not so bad.
(When the God Juling Shen bloodline)
(fades from the scrolls of history,)
(Wang Yuanyuan's scorched spine)
(becomes the path of new fire.)
(She burns away the divine blood,)
(with an unquenchable will,)
(becoming the Warrior Temple's)
(new faith.)
(From now on,)
(this fire will never die,)
(this clan will endure forever.)
Loser.
You even dreamed of surpassing Father Emperor, but your own greed burned you to nothing.
Seems it's not this fate star.
So who will die
next?
I failed to kill you last time.
This time,
I will rip out your bones and dig out your heart.
With your flesh and blood,
I will reforge my son's Crown of Inheritance.
(To be continued)
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Add to favorites and follow.
Never get lost following the series.
Everyone is watching so intently,
surely you've mastered the scan process.
♪Will tomorrow be better?♪
♪The world gives no answer.♪
♪On its own,♪
♪spreading flowers everywhere.♪
♪Do you still believe in me?♪
♪Then let us bloom.♪
♪What am I holding in my hand?♪
♪It doesn't matter anymore.♪
♪You say pain is like a song.♪
♪Our loneliness at this moment♪
♪shines just the same.♪
♪We don't need forever.♪
♪I want the world to see me.♪
♪You will pour down,♪
♪becoming the morning sun.♪
♪You will soar high,♪
♪leaping over sorrow.♪
♪I will call out behind you again and again,♪
♪without end.♪
♪Don't look back, don't look back.♪
♪You will run wildly ahead,♪
♪no matter how long it takes.♪
♪You will leave your mark,♪
♪across the open fields.♪
♪I will call out behind you again and again,♪
♪without end.♪
♪Don't look back, don't look back.♪
♪I will call out behind you again and again,♪
♪without end.♪
♪Don't look back, don't look back.♪
=THRONE OF THE DIVINE SEAL= (This work is fully copyrighted by Changsha Angel Culture Co., Ltd.)
(Exclusively shared with Shanghai Tencent Penguin Pictures Co., Ltd.)
(Next episode preview)
Here.
Why are there so many fallen demigods?
With me here, don't even think of hurting them.
You look so pathetic—it's amusing.
Since you seek death, I'll grant your wish.
Ling'er.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™