[PREVIOUSLY]
Three gods join forces.
Quite the spectacle.
Ceaseless rabid barking.
Such noise.
I shall use my Divinity
and my Divine Power
to forge your Sword of God.
I will uphold the will to protect,
carry your will,
the will of two worlds,
to defeat the God of Retribution.
You are worthy of seeing this sword.
Before the universe was born,
amidst the endless void,
there were only two deities:
Creation and Retribution.
But unlike Creation, who opened the world
and birthed all living beings,
Retribution
was born hating the light,
hating all life in existence.
Its very birth
represented the antithesis of Creation:
the destruction of the cosmos.
Just as Creation bestowed infinite possibilities,
Retribution would bring upon the world
its inevitable end.
Unable to bear witness to the world's demise,
Creation, at the moment of dissipation,
personally sealed Retribution away.
But eroded by endless time,
even a seal cast by Creation
inevitably developed a hairline
fracture.
In that instant,
Retribution did not hesitate to unleash
all of its power—
even sacrificing the majority of its essence—
successfully sending a wisp of its power
outside the seal.
Thus, the prelude to destruction began.
The first world this wisp descended upon
was the
Ancient Land.
The Ancient Land.
Retribution transformed into a new life form,
utilizing the growth properties of living beings
to gradually dissolve the seal
and reclaim its power.
This life possessed a brand-new, nascent soul.
But for Retribution,
it was merely a vessel, a tool.
Retribution lurked deep within its soul.
As it evolved,
it would seize control of the body
and destroy the Ancient Land.
But it underestimated
it underestimated
the will of living beings.
All the powerhouses of the Ancient Land
offered their own blood as sacrifice,
forming the Ten-Earths Nine-Heavens
God-Slaying Array
to trap Retribution.
Ultimately,
Retribution detonated all its power,
perishing alongside
the Ancient Land.
After Retribution's death,
the destructive energy that dissipated
was partially absorbed by the
God-Slaying Array,
but the remainder reincarnated once more.
It became the Nine-Headed Chimera.
It possessed nine chances at rebirth.
It intended to grow again,
but it hadn't anticipated
that in this dimension of darkness and fire,
vengeful spirits
were awaiting its return.
That nascent life
experienced repeated, ignorant rebirths,
only to be slain by the spirits.
It did not know what crimes it had committed,
nor even its own name.
Until,
during its final reincarnation,
the battered creature
was summoned by a ray of hope
to another world.
There, it encountered a small human.
For the first time,
it was given a name of its own.
No...
And Retribution,
and Retribution
remained hidden deep within its soul,
lurking silently in the depths.
Using this human,
it grew step by step,
until it reclaimed enough power.
broke through the seal,
and once again became
the God of Retribution.
Do you understand now, Brother?
It is merely a vessel.
Its body,
its power,
even its soul,
all originate from me.
Without me,
it is nothing.
How dare you bare your fangs at me?
Silence!
You have no right to speak of Haoyue.
You have no right to utter his name.
Because of you,
Haoyue was killed again and again,
bearing the sins of destruction,
shouldering endless hatred in your stead.
Yet you,
could only hide within Haoyue's soul,
a despicable, cowardly...
coward!
Power of Destruction...
Brother,
let's defeat him together.
Together.
Don't get it wrong.
Even if, by using this vessel,
you possess a trace of destructive power,
it is merely a fraction I discarded—
a power that is one in a billion,
a mere billionth of my strength.
Is that so?
The Power of Retribution
is supreme.
Even Creation could not erase it.
But now,
Long Haochen has gathered the dual divinity
bestowed by the Demon God Emperor,
and with Haoyue's assistance,
mastered a sliver of the origin of destruction.
All elemental attributes,
stripped away!
How dare you...
use my own power against me!
It's not over yet.
Haoyue,
Brother,
we are here.
Shatter it!
Long Haochen swings his sword
at Retribution.
Becoming an unprecedented threat
to the Supreme God.
What?
Even if it's just a fraction of my power,
it is still the Power of Destruction.
It can wound me.
How does it feel to be injured
by your own power?
Damn it.
You actually possess
power capable of hurting me.
But do you truly understand destruction?
Watch closely.
This is true destruction!
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Lowly vessel,
I grant you one chance.
Kneel, return my power,
and merge with the great Retribution.
Become one with the great Retribution.
Or I kill you
and take it myself.
We will never merge with you.
That's right!
Not even in death!
We will stay with Brother forever.
Haoyue does not belong to you.
He is...
My younger brother.
My own brother.
Long Haochen,
I underestimated you.
Since the birth of the universe,
you are the only existence
capable of threatening me.
Therefore,
I must kill you.
Now, the moment of Finality has arrived.
Constellations fall silent,
mountain ranges crumble,
all things cease to be.
All destinies
return to...
The Sword of World Annihilation!
Power of Creation!
The Power of Creation...
That bastard Creation
actually left this power for you.
Just to reach this step...
We have already sacrificed too much.
Grandfather,
Caier,
Haoyue,
and everyone else.
Everyone in this world.
And I...
to protect humanity,
to protect my kin,
I will never let them down.
At this moment,
the conviction Long Haochen possesses,
his power,
and the hopes of this world for him,
all converge here.
All gather at this point.
Allowing him to unleash the most
pinnacle power he has ever known.
And thus, he activates
the ultimate form of the
Throne of Eternity and Creation.
Divine Throne,
God Seat.
Only in this way
can he truly harness that ultimate trump card
left for him by the God of Creation.
Long Haochen,
this most pure Power of Creation...
You can use it
to seal Retribution once more
for thousands of years.
You, your loved ones,
and your entire world,
can live out a happy and peaceful life.
In a thousand years,
perhaps someone else
will take up this duty,
inherit this responsibility,
and tread the same path as you.
This is the best solution.
Seal it?
You mean, in a thousand years,
it will awaken again?
No.
I will not leave the catastrophe
of Retribution
for future generations.
I will bring this
to an end myself.
I have a method.
It's far too risky.
Do you know what you'll be facing?
I do.
But it's the only way.
Are you truly prepared to take this step?
Long Haochen,
what you are about to pay...
is an unimaginable,
a price heavier than death itself.
To answer your resolve,
the Throne will spare no expense,
granting you
its absolute, unreserved aid.
May this burning heart of yours
become the undying sun.
This sword is the Sword of World Creation.
With my twin eyes as sun and moon,
my spine as the mountains,
my breath transforming into wind and cloud,
my blood surging into rivers and seas.
All living beings
run wild and thrive.
All destinies
begin with the King,
the Sword of Creation!
You think this can stop me?
Destruction
will inevitably descend.
You have no chance.
What are you doing?
Where is this?
This is...
the world I created.
Long Haochen, have you gone mad?
I thought you would exhaust
your power of creation
to seal me.
Yet you actually created a world?
Have you forgotten
that I was born to destroy worlds?
I will make you understand
what it means for creation
to be synonymous with destruction.
An instant is eternity.
Retribution!
I will, today,
put an end to you forever!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™