This is the 6198th year since the Demon Race descended
upon the Holy Demon Continent.
The 6198th year
since the Demon Race descended
upon the Holy Demon Continent.
After endless struggle,
and countless sacrifices,
at this very moment,
finally...
the Holy Demon Continent
has welcomed its own dawn.
The war between humans and demons
ends here.
Humanity
has claimed victory.
No wonder you managed to defeat
that old fool, the Demon God Emperor.
Becoming a god has made my dear brother much stronger indeed.
But if you think
that’s enough to beat me,
you’re still far from it.
By the laws of divinity,
this radiance ends here.
Not good enough, brother.
Your sword
is nothing but a child’s toy.
Once I destroy the Holy Demon Continent,
and obliterate the entire world,
only you and I will remain.
Because I dislike
anything superfluous.
Superfluous.
You actually managed to wound me.
Not bad at all, that strike.
Brother.
I’ve seen enough of ants building their nests.
Sorry about that,
brother.
I accidentally used a bit too much force.
I didn’t expect
that the so-called savior
of the Holy Demon Continent
would amount to so little.
If this is all you’re capable of,
then this needless affection of yours
is something you won’t be able to bear.
You had to test us first
before letting us come out.
You foolish child.
The old relic and the woman are here too.
Brother,
did you really think
adding them to your side
would change anything?
Why don’t we find out?
Let’s go!
The complete God of Heavenly Retribution
is an existence that stands
above all other gods.
However, his power of Heavenly Retribution
is still sealed.
He is not in his complete form yet.
My divine power
can still harm him.
The three of us gods combined
are more than enough to face him.
Feng Xiu,
you pathetic stray dog.
How do you have the face
to stand before me?
Your manners have only gotten worse.
Austin Griffin,
after wandering for a thousand years,
you truly resemble a stray dog
of the void.
Woman,
what right do you have
to appear here?
Barking nonstop...
How noisy.
Brother,
relying on these old fossils
and a woman
is the only way you’ve lasted this long.
Aren’t you ashamed?
Are you jealous?
Then I’ll grant your wish.
Die together.
Did you think
I would come unprepared?
Did you think I would come unprepared?
Throne Law Seal
was set during our previous battle.
In three seconds,
everything will be destroyed.
Divine Seal Throne.
Origin Vortex.
Myriad Phenomena Crucible.
What?
My technique...
has been deconstructed by you?
The Myriad Phenomena Crucible
can deconstruct all energy
and reshape it.
As long as I wish it,
your skills
will be unable to harm us.
Destruction
ends today.
Divine Realm.
Silent Light Shore.
In the name of the gods,
Dawn’s first light,
the twilight of the gods
descends upon this land.
Three gods working together...
Not bad at all.
Looks like I was played by you after all.
Brother.
Enough talk.
Now hand over your life!
Alright then.
I’ve had my fun.
Cai’er...
This aura...
It’s the true
God of Heavenly Retribution.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Next,
let the world
pay homage
to the descent of the God of Heavenly Retribution.
You broke the seal.
My dear brother.
You all want to kill me.
If I don’t think of something,
should I just obediently wait for death?
That guy Chuangshi has been dead for ten thousand years.
The seal he left behind
has grown weaker and weaker.
And all this time,
as you grew stronger,
I made several moves
and reclaimed quite a bit of power.
I broke the seal long ago
and took back that portion of Heavenly Retribution power.
I have become the true
God of Destruction.
Then I pretended nothing had happened
and watched you all
fight desperately like clowns,
thinking you were close to victory,
only to fall straight into the abyss once more.
It was truly hilarious.
Also...
The moment I became the God of Heavenly Retribution,
the moment I became the God of Heavenly Retribution,
I cast away that lowly demonic beast of yours.
The blood pact between you and it
can no longer affect me.
And you even went through the trouble
of hiding it away,
planning to use it against me.
Brother.
Haochen...
You didn’t really think
this would be enough to stop me, did you?
Everything in this world
shall return to destruction
before the God of Heavenly Retribution.
Killing you three inferior gods
is no different to me
than crushing an ant.
Does this look familiar,
Feng Xiu?
This is
the very strike that once destroyed the Primordial Lands.
The scene from six thousand years ago
shall repeat itself.
When I return,
the entire world will fall into ruin.
Destruction
has arrived.
The defenses of Yulong Pass have been breached.
The Holy Demon Continent is in danger.
Haochen,
focus on dealing with the God of Heavenly Retribution.
Leave the rest to me.
I will protect the Holy Demon Continent for you
and safeguard everyone.
Cai’er,
protect yourself.
You too.
Don’t forget our promise.
One of them slipped away.
No matter.
In the end, they all have to die.
Feng Xiu,
you pathetic stray dog,
you actually dare face me directly?
You spent a thousand years
plotting your revenge,
thinking you could destroy the Holy Demon Continent
and thereby destroy me.
Who would’ve thought
you’d lose so miserably to Long Haochen?
A total defeat.
Even those two brothers of yours,
who didn’t leave a single bone behind,
died for your sake.
You’re still just as much of a failure as you were six thousand years ago.
No one can be protected.
They can only be killed by me.
You are the true culprit behind all of this.
You...
are not worthy of speaking any victim’s name.
Lingxuan...
This child
really does take after you.
Haochen,
in your current state,
you cannot defeat the God of Heavenly Retribution.
You must fully merge the power of both gods.
Grandpa...
What are you going to do?
Farewell,
my child.
No...
Grandpa!
I am the greatest Demon God Emperor
in the history of the Demon Race.
The supreme powerhouse unmatched in all of heaven and earth.
For six thousand years,
this towering hatred
has bathed my body day and night.
I must have my revenge,
then lead my people home.
Compared to this long journey,
a single year is as fleeting as morning dew.
Yet I have remembered it for so long...
so very long.
Perhaps because only during that one year
did I not have to be the Demon God Emperor.
I didn’t have to live solely for hatred.
I was simply Feng Ling.
Lingxuan...
After you left,
I began to learn your gentleness,
your compassion.
As if in doing so,
a part of you could continue living on within me.
Later,
everyone I cared about—
my flesh and blood,
my brothers—
all met the same fate as you.
I couldn’t protect a single one of them.
But in the end,
even if it costs me everything,
I will protect
our Haochen.
I will use my godhood,
my divine power,
to forge them into your Sword of Divinity.
Only then
will you be able to wield the full power of both gods.
Grandpa...
I already killed you once.
I shattered your heart.
Now...
I’m giving it back to you, Grandpa.
[I’m sorry, Haochen… you were right. Everything the living beings of the Primordial Land suffered should never be repeated on the Sacred Demon Continent. Now, I entrust my will—along with the will of the former Primordial Land—to you.”]
- Fall of the Gods -
I will carry out the will to protect,
bearing your will
and the will of two worlds,
to defeat the God of Heavenly Retribution.
That old man really was good to you, huh?
He actually used a sacrifice like this
to grant you the power of two gods.
Austin Griffin...
The power of light and god-slaying,
the ultimate force of salvation in this world
and the ultimate force of slaughter.
When the two become one,
even a god who can destroy everything
should tremble before it.
The power of two gods...
Not bad at all.
This is the first time
since the birth of the universe
that anyone has managed to wound the God of Heavenly Retribution.
You are qualified to see this sword.
This sword
is called Destruction.
All methods of the world,
all phenomena across the realms,
beneath its blade
shall receive their final
destruction.
Do you see now,
brother?
Now that they’re all gone,
who else is left to help you?
Brother.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™