[Previously]
Haoyue.
Brother.
We are...
Shatter him!
You think this can stop me?
Destruction...
will surely descend.
Long Haochen,
what you will pay...
is an unimaginable...
a price heavier than death itself.
I will not let the disaster of the Heavenly Scourge...
I will not let the Heavenly Scourge's disaster...
be left for future generations.
I want it all...
to end with me.
Produced by: Shenman Culture | Undertaken by: Jiuzhou Ranman
Since the birth of the universe,
Long Haochen is the only one...
to possess both Creation and Destruction.
He alone can accomplish one thing.
Long Haochen uses the power of Genesis to forge this world,
solely to imprison the Heavenly Scourge within.
Then erase all connections between this world and the outside.
No matter the cost,
I will, today,
completely end the Heavenly Scourge.
He wants to be in this world,
a world with only him and the Scourge,
to fight the Heavenly Scourge endlessly,
until it is terminated.
Long Haochen,
you are truly mad.
By imprisoning me,
you imprison yourself.
You've done so much,
yet in the end, no one will remember you.
You strive to protect a world where you do not exist.
Yes.
I said,
today, I will end you.
I want to protect...
a world without me.
And to completely sever this connection,
every spacetime...
every "self"...
must willingly...
make the same choice.
Have I become a true Knight?
You always were.
Haoyue,
You've grown so big.
Alright, alright.
Don't fight.
Come, eat dried fish.
You guys eat.
Brother, there's plenty here.
Don't grab.
Fu...
We haven't played like this in a long time.
Haoyue,
are you happy?
I am happy too.
Time to say goodbye.
Haoyue,
though I am reluctant,
we must part.
Haoyue, be good.
Be obedient.
You must live well.
Don't be picky with food.
Don't just eat dried fish.
Eat more vegetables too.
And...
I'm sorry.
I was the one who brought you into this world.
And I am the one abandoning you now.
Sorry.
Haoyue...
Fu...
It shouldn't be like this.
I should have had...
a very, very good child...
a disciple I was proud of.
I should have had...
the gentlest, kindest younger brother.
someone who would entrust me with his life,
a friend who honors promises above gold.
There should have been a person...
who would change my entire life.
Behind me...
it seems there should always be that person.
As long as that person is there,
I can forever only march forward.
That person...
seems like they would never fall.
Why...
It seems we have all forgotten...
that person.
I can't beat them.
I'm sorry.
There is one person...
I absolutely will not forget.
He is more important than my own life.
He is more important than my life.
More important than everything in this world.
From the moment we met,
my soul engraved this promise.
Do not...
forget.
I...
Liar!
We clearly made a pact...
that you would return.
No matter how beautiful the world,
without you, I don't want it.
You are my sun.
My everything.
How could you abandon me again?
Long Haochen!
Have you forgotten...
that I am the God of Death?
I swear upon my Divinity...
that even in death,
nothing can separate us.
My Caier...
It seems there is someone you cannot bear to part with.
I will, out of mercy,
help you two star-crossed lovers.
Help you two star-crossed lovers.
And shatter this cage you created.
Caier...
I'm sorry.
Long Haochen!
You dare?!
Caier,
from now on,
you can live a life unbound by any identity.
You can go feel the world...
its most ordinary,
yet most precious things.
To truly and freely...
live for yourself, just once.
Forget me.
Caier...
Long Haochen!
Haoyue.
Attack!
We absolutely won't let Brother down.
Haoyue.
I will guard your final divine sense.
Until you return.
This is...
Nine-Headed Chimera.
Haoyue and the Scourge have merged.
What does he intend to do?
Haoyue...
wants to perish together with the Scourge.
No!
You lowly beast!
Even if you bite me to death,
you all must die too!
Even if we die, we won't let you bully Brother!
We were born into this world as tools for you,
tools for you.
Scourge Intent... Everyone wants to kill us.
Grand Dao Intent... Only Brother...
Only Brother fights desperately to protect us.
Time and time again.
This time...
we must protect Brother too!
Damn it!
Don't forget who the master is!
I will thoroughly obliterate your consciousness!
What do you count as?
Just a vessel of mine,
and you dare resist me?
Protect...
Brother!
Just die!
Haoyue...
Come back!
Bro...
Brother is here.
Don't be afraid.
Brother...
What a touching drama of brotherly love.
But why...
could you be so ruthless towards me?
Brother...
Is this how you...
created the world? Like this?
Why?
I want to take you...
along with this entire world...
this entire universe...
Everything you care about...
Everything you cherish...
utterly destroy.
Brother...
I was useless.
I was incompetent.
I failed to kill him.
It’s alright.
From now on,
let us face it together.
Let us face it together.
Just like we always have.
Good.
With blood...
With soul...
I forge my brother's blade.
This body, this life...
Hearts aligned, thoughts united...
The sword slashes at the End.
At this moment,
the bond between Long Haochen and Haoyue,
surpassing everything,
actually interwove into a power...
unknown even to Genesis and the Scourge—
Long Haochen.
Your destruction is ordained.
Just like this world.
If destruction is ordained,
then why...
can I feel your trembling?
Why...
do you fear my sword strike?
From six thousand years ago until now,
the living beings of this world
have constantly resisted you.
Throughout this endless time,
we failed again and again,
yet reignited from the ashes again and again.
Do you see?
The power you fear...
Spanning ten thousand years...
It has never extinguished.
Never extinguished.
And it is named...
Hope.
Even if destruction is long ordained,
we...
will never abandon hope.
Never abandon hope.
Si...
Brother...
We succeeded!
That’s right!
All thanks to Haoyue.
Then Brother...
Are we going to be separated?
Little Thunder...
Little Gold...
Little Yellow...
Little Purple...
Little Blue...
Little Green...
Little Fire...
Little Light...
Meeting Brother was truly wonderful.
Meeting Haoyue made me very happy too.
Really?
Of course.
When has Brother ever lied to you?
Last time you lied to me,
saying the BBQ-flavored dried fish wasn't spicy.
But you can't eat that much either.
I really don't want to...
be separated from Brother.
Haoyue...
I will definitely find you.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™