Gentlemen.
If you don't mind,
let me offer you some advice.
Master Guan, the chief of Guanzhong Disciplinary Hall,
please come to our hall in Xuzhou
for a cup of tea.
We're not even sure if we can leave the Guixiang Pavilion now.
We'll try our best to clear your names
and reveal the truth behind the Luo family massacre.
Take this sword and blade back.
But remember,
you owe me a favor.
You must be Xuanyuan Guang.
Today,
let's see which one of us is better.
We don't need to compete.
How could I be a match for the legendary thief?
Before this feather touches the ground,
if I can't pluck a single hair from your head,
I'll admit defeat.
The feather has landed!
Ming Hong truly lives up to his reputation.
You're too kind.
Young Master Xuanyuan,
you should depart soon.
Gentlemen,
until we meet again.
Wait a moment.
Although I haven't joined your gang,
we're in the same boat.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Please go ahead.
Earlier at Guixiang Pavilion,
a young lady mentioned that
your gang knows something about my master.
You're referring to the cause of your master's death, right?
Please share what you know.
Your master's wounds were very unusual.
The only techniques that could cause such wounds,
apart from the Hainan Wild Wind Sword Technique
and the Tianshan 72 Sword Arts,
there's another little-known martial art.
What martial art?
Kunlun Divine Art.
The Demonic Cult?
Exactly.
I don't know much about it either.
After you join the Heroes' Gang,
you can ask the leader personally.
May I ask who your gang's leader is?
You'll meet him in due time.
Let's go.
Xuanyuan Guang is finally gone.
The moment I saw him,
I clutched my money pouch tightly
and kept at least five feet away from him the whole time.
Otherwise...
Senior brother.
It's full of stones.
Check yours quickly!
Gentlemen,
your breakfast is ready.
that'll be 100 copper coins.
Young man,
my brother and I are a bit short on money these days.
Would it be possible to pay later?
Please help us out.
We'll have money in a month
and will repay double.
Junior brother.
Brother, it's time I taught you
some survival skills for the jianghu.
Today,
we'll use the martial arts our master taught us
to earn ourselves a meal
and broaden your horizons.
Step one of jianghu survival:
choose the right location.
For a wandering performer to make a living with their skills,
they must choose remote villages and towns.
The locals here haven't seen much
of the traveling performers and their tricks.
Even a simple forward roll will get you applause.
Senior brother,
what are you doing?
Step two of survival in the jianghu:
follow the scent.
Walk through the streets at mealtime
and smell the food aromas wafting through the air.
You can roughly determine how wealthy the residents are
and find a street with rich households to set up shop.
That's brilliant, senior brother!
This place is good.
I can smell wine.
These people are rolling in money!
Senior brother,
what's step three?
Step right up, ladies and gentlemen!
My brother and I have just arrived in your fine town
and know no one here.
Today we'll demonstrate authentic
Southern Five-Form Transformation Boxing
for your entertainment.
Those with money can show appreciation with coins,
those without can show appreciation with applause!
I, Zheng Da, am here
and thank you all in advance!
Junior brother,
after I finish the routine,
you go around collecting money.
Senior brother,
what routine are you performing?
Just the Five Animal Exercises.
Even my father knows that one.
Here's something for you.
Thank you.
Senior brother,
we've made our first money!
Look at this!
People really aren't as generous as they used to be.
Ten years ago when I first started performing,
one routine would earn me thirty or forty copper coins.
People's tastes have become so refined nowadays.
Thank you all for your generosity
in providing my brother and me with enough for a meal.
I wonder if you all
would like to see some other tricks
and perhaps reward us with enough for a pot of wine?
Breaking stones on the chest!
Eighty copper coins!
Good!
Yes!
Let's see that!
Do that one!
Let's have that!
Senior brother,
can you do that?
As long as your body is strong enough,
anyone can do it.
Since everyone wants to see this feat of iron body qigong,
this ultimate skill,
how could I refuse?
Please be patient,
while my brother and I make some preparations.
I'll keep the crowd entertained here.
Take the money
and quickly buy a rectangular stone and an iron hammer.
Senior brother,
where do I buy those things?
Step four of survival in the jianghu:
adapt to circumstances.
What can I help you with, sir?
Greetings, good sir.
My brother and I are passing through your town
hoping to earn a meal by performing.
Now we want to perform
the stone-breaking feat on the chest.
I wonder
if I could borrow that rectangular stone from your residence?
Sir, you must be joking.
This Taihu Diamond Stone
has already been sealed by imperial order.
They say it's to be used in the imperial gardens in Chang'an.
Even if I had the greatest courage,
I wouldn't dare lend it to you.
I see.
This stone truly brings misfortune.
The imperial messenger deliberately sealed this stone
forcing my family to spend money day and night to maintain it.
All because he coveted my 'Turtle and Crane Longevity' painting.
Sir,
may I take a look at that painting?
It's been so long and still nothing.
Pay me back!
I'm leaving.
How long has it been?
Are you trying to cheat a child out of money?
Everyone,
if you're feeling bored,
allow me, Zheng Da, to tell you a story.
Ladies and gentlemen,
there was once a great warrior from the south
who traveled a long distance with his apprentice.
They were heading to Lingnan to establish a martial arts school
but encountered a great disaster.
He was severely wounded
and no doctor dared to treat him.
Just when he and his apprentice were in trouble,
they met a stunningly beautiful woman.
A forgery.
That's impossible.
In the authentic Zu-style 'Turtle and Crane Longevity',
the crane is always soaring freely beyond the sky.
Therefore, the painting only shows the turtle
and never the crane.
I see now.
No wonder General Cao of the Left Guard
also said this painting was a convincing fake.
I've made a terrible mistake.
Sir, you are truly talented.
I am a merchant from Xuzhou,
Bo Tinggui.
May I ask your esteemed name?
I am
Zu Beiqiu from Yizhou.
Master Zu!
It must be you!
This discerning eye,
this eloquence,
this calm and composed demeanor.
You must be the one as famous as Lord Cao, known as
'Zu of the Southern Turtle.'
I never thought that today
I would actually meet you in person.
You flatter me.
Master,
would you honor me with two of your ink treasures?
First, to solve my urgent problem,
and second, to fulfill my lifelong wish.
If I could witness your painting skills with my own eyes,
not only would I offer this diamond stone,
but I would also present you with a thousand taels of gold.
The warrior was startled by these words
and replied,
'She doesn't know any healing techniques.
The one who treated my wounds
was her husband.'
Senior brother!
I'm back!
Just for a few copper coins,
you hired so many people.
As expected from someone whose family owns a bank.
Senior brother,
lie down here.
This bench is more comfortable than the ground.
Advanced.
Junior,
you know how to care for others now.
Senior, please wait a moment.
Something good is coming.
Junior,
what kind of stone is this?
Benefactor.
Big hammer.
Benefactor,
smash this cursed thing
and be done with it.
Old man,
just watch.
80.
Dongting.
In life,
you will face many challenges.
This wooden knife is old.
You can have it.
To strengthen yourself through hardship,
you must have a strong heart.
Ten years later.
You will be powerful enough to conquer the world.
I beg you.
I swear I will never use the martial arts of the Seven Sects and Eight Schools,
just let me keep my Swallow Flying Cloud technique.
If I break my oath,
the heroes of the martial world
shall put me to death.
Junior,
did you find anything?
I checked all the hiding places we agreed on,
but found nothing.
Same here.
I noticed these hiding spots
have already been searched
very thoroughly.
So,
someone already has the evidence.
That's right.
But this person
didn't give it to Master Guan.
Could they have figured it out?
If they had,
they would have exposed it already.
They want to conceal the killer's identity.
Why?
If those people killed the entire Luo family,
he would eventually have to confront them for justice,
but he doesn't have the courage.
He wants fame
but also values his life.
What a greedy person.
Now
we can only create new evidence
to save them.
If we do that,
it will certainly make that person suspicious
and everything will be exposed.
We can't worry about that now.
Let's clear Brother Zheng and Brother Zu's names first.
Senior,
you're awake.
Our performance was quite successful.
We earned a whole string of coins.
Brother.
Where did you get this stone from?
It's quite extraordinary.
Of course it is.
This stone
is worth a fortune.
Brother.
When the stone broke,
everyone cheered.
Many were so moved they cried.
I met a wealthy merchant who wanted paintings.
I traded two longevity paintings for it.
He even offered me a thousand gold taels.
He was already in desperate need.
How could I
take more money from him?
You idiot!
What are we performing for?
To learn
and survive in this world.
I've learned plenty.
Brother.
Seeing you so happy,
I have more good news.
We've become famous.
Many boatmen told me
they'll spread our names everywhere.
You didn't tell them your real name, did you?
Of course I mentioned your name first.
Mine came after yours.
Brother.
There's a fifth step to surviving in this world.
While I'm still alive,
let me teach you everything.
Brother,
tell me.
In everything you do,
you must think ahead.
Now think carefully.
After we've become famous in this town,
what will happen next?
I can't figure it out.
Can't think and can't hear either?
'Capture Zu Beiqiu alive!
Seize Zheng Dongting!'
'Arrest the two villains of the Central Plains!'
Brother.
You should run.
I plan to kill the prisoners with my Lion's Roar
and escape from this prison.
What do you think?
Since Master Duan is in the mood,
I'll play along.
'Heavenly fragrance stains clothes at night.'
'National beauty intoxicates the morning wine.'
'Only the peony has true national beauty.'
'Peach blossoms are indeed bewitching,
making my heart itch with desire.'
Now about chrysanthemums...
Who goes there?
Haven't we met somewhere before?
'One night of stars and rivers.'
'Falling from the western sky.'
Elder Wang.
Something's happened.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™