FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
We can only fabricate another piece of evidence
to save them.
Before this feather touches the ground,
if I don't pluck a hair from your head,
I'll admit defeat.
Today we'll use the martial arts our master taught us
to earn a living.
Breaking stones on the chest!
80 copper coins!
May I have two pieces of your calligraphy?
Not only this diamond,
I'm also willing to offer a thousand taels of gold.
[Eighty]
I have more good news for you.
We brothers have become famous.
Capture Zu Beiqiu alive!
Seize Zheng Dongting!
Brother,
you should escape on your own.
Guild Master Guan,
forgive my sudden visit.
I apologize for any offense.
I've found important clues about the Luo family massacre
and had to rush here urgently.
We've all misunderstood Zheng Dongting and Zu Beiqiu.
The Luo family massacre wasn't their doing,
but the work of the Taihangshanzhài gang.
Here's a letter written in blood as proof.
Who goes there?
Guild Master Guan,
help me capture this villain!
look out!
We've arrived.
What's all this noise?
Have you no dignity as members of a respectable sect?
Zheng Dongting,
Zu Beiqiu,
are merely suspects in the Luo family massacre
and haven't been formally convicted yet.
We're not like the Taihangshanzhài gang.
We need evidence.
I am Elder Wang of the Guanzhong Sword School,
Wang Guchang,
and also the chief of the Martial Alliance's Execution Hall.
I'm responsible for interrogating major criminals in the martial world.
You're suspected of massacring the entire Luo family.
Now,
will you confess to your crimes?
Elder Wang,
my brother and I are innocent.
How dare you, Zheng Dongting!
At the end of your rope,
yet still trying to deny it?
Where is the executioner?
Bring out the punishment rods!
Beat them until they confess!
Didn't you just say respectable sects need evidence?
Hold your hand!
Fellow martial artists,
you must stay away from vice and corruption,
and uphold the virtuous ways of our great Tang dynasty.
Elder Wang speaks wisely.
Guards!
Put Zheng Dongting in cell Tian-A.
And put Zu Beiqiu
in cell Tian-B.
You're putting them with those two prisoners?
Isn't that a bit...
These days, thieves are everywhere
and our cells are overcrowded.
If anything happens to Zu Beiqiu
or Zheng Dongting,
blame it on these troubled times.
Hahaha!
You're awake?
Where am I?
Cell Tian Yi.
For high-profile criminals.
Brother Zu, you deserve this cell.
May I ask,
did you kill everyone in the Luo family?
No, no.
Zheng Dongting killed half of them.
Anyway,
what you did was deeply satisfying to many.
Haha!
Pleased to meet you.
I haven't asked your name
and why you're imprisoned?
My humble name isn't worth mentioning.
As for me,
I'm here for deflowering women.
In our world,
is there anything wrong with picking flowers?
Brother Zu,
could you be a fellow practitioner?
You're Zheng Dongting who wiped out the Luo family.
I didn't.
I'm not.
What a coward.
At this point,
if you killed them, just admit it.
Why hide it?
You're...
you're the Lion King Duan Teng.
That's right,
it's me.
Legend has it
you killed all Tianshan disciples who could use the Night Falling Stars sword.
I did kill quite a few.
The Night Falling Stars sword technique is what I hate most in my life.
I watched hundreds of my brothers die under that sword.
You look familiar.
Have we met somewhere before?
Impossible.
We've never met.
You're scum of the martial world,
a disciple of Mu Tianhou.
You dare call my master scum?
I merely killed innocents.
Your master was a thief and a fraud,
deceiving everyone.
Absolutely disgraceful.
Years ago, your master used sweet talk
to steal the Night Falling Stars sword technique
from Tianshan heroine Ye Ting.
I suppose your master must have taught
you that sword technique.
I swear
I will never use the Night Falling Stars sword.
Let's have a friendly match,
not a real fight.
Not even a friendly match.
If you won't take the easy way,
you'll take the hard way.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Fine then.
Tonight I was planning to escape from this prison,
but because you came in,
I decided to stay and have a match with you.
Master Duan wants to escape?
Don't let me delay you.
How do you plan to escape?
I plan to kill the inmates with my Lion's Roar,
and escape while they're collecting the bodies.
What do you think?
A friendly match isn't really fighting.
Since Master Duan is in the mood,
I'll oblige.
Elder Wang handled this matter beautifully.
Just thinking about Zheng Dongting and Zu Beiqiu
meeting those two demons in prison,
I almost feel sorry for them.
Yes.
We've saved face
and pacified Ouyang Fei and the injured members of the Jixiong Alliance.
I hope Elder Wang will continue to guide us in the future.
Such is the world we live in.
What can we do about it?
Let's drink to this damned world.
Cheers!
Good.
Speaking of famous flowers,
one cannot avoid mentioning it.
Heavenly fragrance stains clothes at night,
national beauty intoxicates in morning wine.
Only the peony is truly the nation's beauty,
when it blooms, the capital stirs.
The peony,
it's full-bodied.
Good.
Well said.
Your verses, brother,
make me dream of Luoyang.
What about peach blossoms?
Mirrors before and after reflect the flowers,
flower faces shine upon each other.
Purple paths and red dust brush against the face,
everyone comes to see the flowers bloom.
Peach blossoms,
they're enchanting.
Good.
Peach blossoms are indeed bewitching,
so bewitching that I can't resist their charm.
How about apricot blossoms?
Delicate beauty transforms thrice,
a tree full of spring breeze.
Let you pick them and look with care,
they say spring breeze reaches the flower stems.
Apricot blossoms,
they're tender.
If one obtains apricot blossoms,
it's like passing the imperial exam.
Truly the most romantic thing in the world.
What about lotus flowers?
Lotus emerges from clear water,
naturally unadorned.
Meeting her lover, she wants to speak but lowers her head and smiles,
jade hairpin falls into the water as she touches her hair.
Lotus flowers,
they're fresh and pure.
Brother, you're so talented.
I can picture it all.
Now about chrysanthemums.
I'm going to use the Eighteen Beast Blade technique.
First form:
White Dragon Emerges from the Sea.
Blade stands upright attacking the middle,
blade tip points at the brow.
Hold this hand position,
look carefully.
A line of stars breaks through the sky,
long sword strikes from above.
Pointing diagonally to the sky,
sword sweeps across the heavens.
Strike here,
here.
Tiger Tucks Tail.
Crafty Rabbit's Three Burrows,
retreat three steps.
Dodge to the left,
blade twists behind.
Side roll.
Damn you!
You dare to counter-attack me?
This blade of mine could split a mountain in half.
Why didn't you dodge?
You first used White Dragon Emerges from the Sea,
your next move would surely be a horizontal slash.
If I had retreated,
I would have given you the advantage.
How could I dodge?
Aren't you afraid of dying together with me?
I'll strike first.
Your strike looks fierce,
but it's just a feint.
Your energy is weak,
no match for the speed of my sword.
Your swordsmanship,
why is it different from other swordsmen?
They don't use their swords correctly.
Not correctly.
Green Monkey Offering Fruit,
Rolling Body Through Clever Clouds.
Three Advancing Strikes.
Watch this.
This.
How will you counter?
Starry Rain Washing Autumn Pond.
What the...
What?
You're stealing my glory again.
My Green Monkey Offering Fruit is a swift strike.
Your blade weighs 38 jin,
your arms are 4 chi long,
and you're over 8 chi tall.
By the time your blade reaches my vital points,
my sword would have already turned you into a sieve.
Lazy Donkey
Rolling.
Eighteen Tumbles,
body lying sideways.
Enough.
You don't need to describe how a lazy donkey rolls.
I can imagine it.
Green Blade Crossing Sky, Seven Stars Falling.
Is it my turn to make a move?
You're rolling on the ground.
How can you attack?
My move is an aerial strike,
delivering seven consecutive sword thrusts.
Keep rolling.
Carp Leaping Dragon Gate,
Stars Illuminating Three Thousand Paths,
Black Bear Hugging Tree,
Flying Star Flirting with Queen Mother of the West.
Dilu Horse Crossing Stream,
Star Light Fading on Western Window Tree.
I'll fight you with my Rabbit Kicking Eagle move!
One Night of Stars,
Falling in Western Sky.
Brilliant blossoms still flourish.
No news from the beauty.
Lonely eastern fence wet with dew.
Golden dimples still reflect in mud and sand.
Autumn threads surround the house like Tao's home.
Encircling the fence as day turns to sunset.
Rustling west wind fills the courtyard,
cold stamens and chilled fragrance keep butterflies away.
When autumn comes on the eighth of September,
my flowers bloom while others wither.
Brother,
I still have two flowers.
They're at the Earth God Temple on South Mountain.
Help me.
I remember now.
It's you.
So it was you.
Brother Ouyang, why are you so late?
The wine is cold now.
Elder Wang.
Something's happened.
Brother Ouyang.
Something happened to those two villains, right?
These two truly live up to their reputation.
In that case,
their bodies still need to be properly collected.
I've already asked people to bring them out.
Elder Wang,
would you like to examine them?
- Let's go.
- Let's all take a look.
Evil truly gets its just deserts.
The time has come.
This way no one will blame us.
Guards!
Bring out Zheng Dongting and Zu Beiqiu.
I will execute these two as a sacrifice.
Bao Yexing is dead.
It's Zu Beiqiu.
We've been wronged, sir!
We didn't kill anyone.
Sir, please investigate thoroughly.
Did Lian Qingyan help you escape?
Master Lian,
how did you get injured?
Master Guan is dead.
The Luo family wasn't actually killed.
They're all alive.
Young Master Gong,
how did you know the iron box with the blood letter was evidence?
If the Luo family had truly been massacred,
how could I have met the young master of the Luo family?
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™