♪Alert♪
♪I open my eyes to a huge explosion♪
♪The fight between
imagination and reality is tied♪
♪I will defeat you♪
♪Scattered in Guixu.
May all souls go home♪
♪The war is beginning again♪
♪The dragon is thousands
of meters in the air♪
♪Returning will only crowd this place♪
♪No one cares about your history♪
♪It's full of failures♪
♪Dragon slaying. Anti Chu♪
♪God Slayer. What are they♪
♪They bring only grudges to the table♪
♪How ridiculous are their excuses♪
♪Walking the line between good and bad,
visible or invisible♪
♪See through clouded mysteries♪
♪Let the light shine on my back♪
♪All the absurdities are revealed♪
♪I shall win my fame♪
♪I shall rewrite the story.
I shall create a new realm♪
♪Remove barriers to the truth♪
♪Sharpened edges clash under the sky♪
♪I read your mind in an instant♪
♪Stop flashing around
and aim at my chest♪
♪Do your worst and make my heart burn♪
♪Let's fight♪
♪I measure the world with my feet♪
♪I clear the ground along
with the morning light♪
♪My strength is unstoppable♪
♪Truth is in my hands♪
♪Sharpened edges clash under the sky♪
♪Stop flashing around
and aim at my chest♪
♪Let's fight♪
♪I measure the world with my feet♪
♪I clear the ground along
with the morning light♪
♪My strength is unstoppable♪
♪Truth is in my hands♪
- Wealth and Wonder -
Episode 24 - Shennong Messenger Ziyue
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Parental guidance is required for minors.]
[Previously]
I'm going to put your soul
into my test subject No. 516.
What I've been through
is like the castles in the air, a dream and illusion.
If I die here, I will be
an embarrassment to Chu Tiange.
If you give up on the Legendary Mission
of Reviving State of Sui,
I will think about it.
Your voice makes me sick!
Wake up, Ziyue.
[Dragon City Central Plaza]
Chu Tiange, you're not as righteous
as you pretend to be.
You'd abandon
saving the world for a girl!
What a pity.
All this struggling is pointless.
What would you know
about bonds between friends?
You're the one who should be struggling!
Tides rise and fall,
heed my command.
The deep sea roars,
burning the past away!
[Abyssal Volcanic Domain]
Ocean Dragon Stranglehold!
Useless.
Power of the stars, heed my command.
Meteor shower,
shatter earth and stars!
Your gameplay is indeed solid.
Too bad
the Fallen Enchanter King class
is unbeatable!
It's the ultimate class in the game.
I created it for myself
before the game even launched!
No skill required.
One word decides your fate!
Heaven and earth shall be remade.
You know what this skill
would be called in the real world?
It's called power.
Power?
Some level up by grinding.
Like Roamer.
Some are blessed with luck.
Like Emperor of Luck.
Some are at the top of their skill.
Like Rui Wen.
And some grow stronger
by spending money.
Like me.
But all of us advance
within the rules the game allows.
What you call power
seeks to overturn the entire game.
Cut the crap.
Sand and stone, heed my command.
Gather the sand into a spirit,
crushing the void with my fist!
I'm just passing through.
You guys carry on.
Let's make a deal.
Even if you have the money, you won't be able to pull it off!
[Mysterious Shop, Empty Version]
How did you get in here too?
I can't even take advantage
of a deal handed to me.
Look.
My shop's been cleaned out
by some thief.
They even stole thte Shennong Plant
I dug up from an 80-level map!
[Flashback]
Might not be a petty thief.
[Kid! How dare you insult an elder!]
More like a master criminal.
I'm not here to buy.
I'm giving you a whole treasure vault.
And I'll even pay you for it.
Is there such a good deal?
The Merman Emperor is dead.
The vault won't open.
You figure it out.
Prodigal, you've come to the right man.
This is the Dragon Princess statue I dug up after countless trials and ancient hunts.
So, what do you think?
Leave the work to the professionals.
[You just stole it.
Don't act like some curator.]
Where's Linglong?
Brother,
[Huh?]
I've been following you in secret.
Linglong, take him to the Dragon's Vault.
I just need the item to upgrade
my level 40 skill.
You can have the rest.
[Luoyang Shovel]
No time to lose.
Horned girl, lead the way.
Brother, be careful.
What?
Finally ready to surrender?
You locked down the logouts
for your own selfish goals.
You turned this game, meant for adventure, into a nightmare where we wait to die!
You're beyond saving.
Disintegrate!
You made me lose
the most precious companionship.
You deserve to die!
Ocean Dragon Form!
[Ocean Dragon Form]
My character
is the strongest in the game.
It's overpowered.
What do you have that can beat me?
Is that so?
But how else
do we restore the game
if we don't kill you?
Dragon Drains the Ocean!
Eternal Frost!
[Eternal Frost]
Enchanter King, huh?
Speak it, and it's law, huh?
Let's see how you talk with your mouth sealed shut!
Beat him!
Roamer, beat him to a pulp.
Don't throw trash everywhere.
This is humiliating.
Absolutely humiliating!
What a bunch of losers.
None of you could stop them!
It's over.
Isn't your class
the Primordial Dragon Emperor?
Then I'll bury you in a dragon's gut.
It'll be a proper ending.
[Eroding Wave
of the Cursed Sea Dragon Soul]
Eroding Wave
of the Cursed Sea Dragon Soul.
Go!
Hurry!
Give me the Dragon Stones!
Where are the rest?
Catch them!
Detecting
all four Dragon Stones assembled.
Altar integrity restored.
Tiange, hurry!
Purify the dragon souls at the altar
and complete the mission.
There's still hope!
Too late.
The dragon souls are gone.
They're inside me now.
What?
What happened to you?
So you're saying
our plan to save
all the players has failed?
Then what was the point
of all our struggle?
I believe Master will find a way.
Forget that for now.
At this rate, we'll die before the other players do.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Don't attack.
They're not game code.
They're the dragon spirits
who once protected our world.
These are the last fragments
of their souls.
Chu Yi is right.
I can feel their pain and struggle.
It's like they're whispering to me.
But
I can't understand them.
This is so frustrating.
Enough talk.
Figure something out!
This isn't working.
Maybe only a mythic item can counter this.
But where would we get a mythic item?
The Weaving Dreams Shuttle Meow left me
is almost broken.
I can't use it again.
We'll have one soon!
Team up with me, and your luck will spike.
We'll get what we need.
Just as I thought.
Only a mythic item can counter another.
Numbers culminate at nine,
heed my command.
Nine dragons merge,
boiling seas and scorching skies!
[Nine Dragons Merge,
Sea Boiler & Sky Scorcher]
This isn't a complete mythic item.
The mythic power is too limited.
You think that's all?
Dragon souls descend, formless and unseen.
Heed my command, devour their hearts and souls!
This bleeding status isn't even showing.
None of my skills can remove it.
Where is the Mysterious Merchant??
If we could upgrade our skills, we might still have a chance.
Mysterious Merchant?
[Flashback]
You really think you can counter
my power that easily?
This is the resentment forged when I refined generations of Ocean Dragon King souls in the furnace.
Enjoy the suffering!
Ziyue!
I can hear the Ocean Dragon Kings' wail.
They yearn for release.
They want to help us.
But that villain controls them
against their will.
But their will and pride
survived the refinement.
Ziyue,
use the Shennong Plant.
Ziyue!
It hurts.
I'm feeling what they're feeling.
I can help them.
Shennong Plant.
My instincts were right.
Only Ziyue can unlock its true power.
I don't know what's happening, but Ziyue,
you're our top healer.
I told you we'd get this.
[Prompt: Successfully resonated
with the Flame Emperor's soul]
[to undergo a second awakening
and advance to Shennong Messenger.]
[Accept?
No / Yes]
Chu Yi, wait for me.
I will save everyone.
This is...?
Someone's awakening a hidden class.
Flame Emperor's Sanctuary!
[Flame Emperor's Sanctuary]
It actually purifies souls?
What skill is this?
[Ziyue, Shennong Messenger]
All the immortal dragon souls here,
in the name of Shennong Messenger,
you are free now!
Ziyue, thank you
for giving us hope again.
Thank you for trusting me all along.
Don't think I don't know.
You never needed a healer
in the first place.
Your set bonus
already gives you two lives.
But I need you.
You're more important to me
than you imagine.
Besides, the team needs you too.
Master needs me too.
I want a hug from Master as well.
Everyone,
this is our last stand.
As long as I'm here,
no one will get hurt!
I won't let you succeed!
They wouldn't betray us
after we helped them, would they?
We pay homage to the Dragon Emperor
and the Princess!
Nine generations of Ocean Dragon Kings, leading all of Dragon City in submission to the Dragon Emperor.
[Nine Generations of Dragon Souls]
So these are
the powerful beings that existed
in some era of Earth's history?
Impossible.
Even if these dragon souls were purified, they wouldn't regain their sanity and swear loyalty to you?
I...
I refined them all myself!
The Dragon Kings sensed the obsession
burning in Master's heart.
Only by resonating with him could they break through Dark Sky's barriers and manifest here.
This is something
only Master could achieve!
The dragon race perished long ago
in the world you once knew.
Civilization has collapsed.
But if you wish to restore
the dragons' glory within The Era,
then lend me your strength.
Let the silent Dragon City rise
from the desolate Ocean's Lost Pearl
and reclaim its place in the world.
I, Chu Tiange, the Tenth Dragon Emperor,
will not fail you!
I will restore the dragon race!
No one can stop my plan!
[Eternal Night's Frost, Undying Flames] Eternal night's frost, undying flames,
heed my command.
Shatter this world!
In the name of Dragon Emperor,
Nine Heaven Holding Dragons!
Kill them all!
Let the spiritual energy of The Era
flood into reality,
achieving immortality!
I think I just gained control
of Dragon City.
[Dragon City, Floating Isle]
Dragon City Ascends!
[Advertisement]
[Ocean Dragon King Souls: Remnant souls
of generations of Dragon Kings ]
[who fell in the war
of the Primordial Era.]
[After the Ocean's Lost Pearl was opened,
they were refined by Dark Sky,]
[losing their consciousness
and becoming vengeful spirits.]
[After awakening her Shennong class,
Ziyue used the Shennong Plant]
[to purify the Ocean Dragon King Souls.]
[The nine generations of dragon souls
broke free,]
[regained their freedom, and submitted
to Dragon Emperor Chu Tiange.]
[Shennong Messenger: A server-wide
unique hidden class awakened by Ziyue]
[after resonating
with the Shennong Plant.]
[Next Episode]
I'm using a completely new power.
The power of cash.
Have you restored your power
to its peak?
Notify all players to log out!
Cheng?
Chu Yi, I'm out.
By devouring these spiritual entities, I can harness the power of the upgraded Psyforge to break the space barrier!
You trash.
You need to sacrifice
all the players to level up?
Chu Yi!
It feels like I've forgotten something.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪I see the light of homes♪
♪The thin fog floats♪
♪I've learned to review my lessons♪
♪The moment I create a miracle♪
♪No adventure with you is formidable♪
♪Unlocking threads of mysteries♪
♪We are born with heated blood♪
♪We start from light years away♪
♪When I have friends♪
♪I have the whole world♪
♪Can time stop at this moment♪
♪We encourage each other
and fight for tomorrow♪
♪In the future♪
♪I will still be feeling it like now♪
♪I hope time stops at this moment♪
♪No matter how harsh fate is to us♪
♪We will not let go of each other♪
♪Can time stop at this moment♪
♪We encourage each other
and fight for tomorrow♪
♪In the future♪
♪I will still be feeling it like now♪
♪I hope time stops at this moment♪
♪No matter how harsh fate is to us♪
♪We will not let go of each other♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™