♪Alert♪
♪I open my eyes to a huge explosion♪
♪The fight between
imagination and reality is tied♪
♪I will defeat you♪
♪Scattered in Guixu.
May all souls go home♪
♪The war is beginning again♪
♪The dragon is thousands
of meters in the air♪
♪Returning will only crowd this place♪
♪No one cares about your history♪
♪It's full of failures♪
♪Dragon slaying. Anti Chu♪
♪God Slayer. What are they♪
♪They bring only grudges to the table♪
♪How ridiculous are their excuses♪
♪Walking the line between good and bad,
visible or invisible♪
♪See through clouded mysteries♪
♪Let the light shine on my back♪
♪All the absurdities are revealed♪
♪I shall win my fame♪
♪I shall rewrite the story.
I shall create a new realm♪
♪Remove barriers to the truth♪
♪Sharpened edges clash under the sky♪
♪I read your mind in an instant♪
♪Stop flashing around
and aim at my chest♪
♪Do your worst and make my heart burn♪
♪Let's fight♪
♪I measure the world with my feet♪
♪I clear the ground along
with the morning light♪
♪My strength is unstoppable♪
♪Truth is in my hands♪
♪Sharpened edges clash under the sky♪
♪Stop flashing around
and aim at my chest♪
♪Let's fight♪
♪I measure the world with my feet♪
♪I clear the ground along
with the morning light♪
♪My strength is unstoppable♪
♪Truth is in my hands♪
- Wealth and Wonder -
Episode 25
[Dragon's Lament]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
[Parental guidance
is required for minors.]
[Previously]
Chu Tiange, you're not as righteous
as you pretend to be.
What would you know
about bonds between friends?
This is the resentment forged
when I refined
generations of Ocean Dragon King souls
in the furnace.
Enjoy the suffering!
Chu Yi, wait for me.
I will save everyone.
Thank you for trusting me all along.
I, Chu Tiange, the Tenth Dragon Emperor,
will not fail you!
I will restore the dragon race!
[Endless Ocean]
Want to stop us?
Not a chance!
Dragon City
ascends today!
[Exhausted]
Brother,
I'm back.
Mm.
Where's the Mysterious Merchant?
That chubby man
[Linglong's Crystal]
refused to leave
the Dragon's Vault.
So I came back.
They're trying to shatter
the core of Dragon City
and make it crash.
Back in the Primordial Era,
Dragon City's defenses
would never be this weak.
The Primordial Era?
What was it like back then?
In the Primordial Era,
you would channel your power
into the Heart of Dragon City,
creating impenetrable barriers
to protect it.
[Confirm Purchase? Yes]
Anyone approaching Dragon City
would trigger defensive arrays
to snipe all invaders.
Even at one-tenth
of its former power,
those defenses could keep
all these villains out.
If your power wasn't still recovering,
they'd never dare bully us like this.
Is that so?
Brother.
When I opened my eyes,
it felt like I'd returned
to the Primordial Era.
How did you do it?
Have you
restored your power to its peak?
I'm using a completely new power.
[I'm rich]
The power of cash.
[Confused]
Don't overstay in the battle.
Shatter the Statue
of the Dragon Emperor now!
Is it okay
to let them keep attacking?
Your defeat is fated.
The holy Dragon City
tolerate any intruders.
Begone!
[Floating Isle]
Congratulations to Player Chu Tiange
on completing Act III
of the Reviving the Sui Dynasty mission
and obtaining the reward
[State of Sui's Jade Seal]
of the Sui Dynasty's Jade Seal.
Finally,
the final step.
Notify all players
to log out!
Attention, all players.
The data corruption in The Era
has been resolved.
Logout channels are now open again.
You may save your progress
and log out at any time.
Repeat.
Attention, all players.
We can finally log out!
We can leave
this hellhole!
[Bai, wait for me offline!]
I'm never gaming again!
[I want to hang out with you!]
Everyone,
[Little Elk]
we're really leaving this time!
Finally, we can log out.
[Bankrupt]
This stupid game!
I'll sue you into bankruptcy!
So happy!
[Smack]
Going home!
[Thud]
Did he succeed?
I won't lose.
I won't!
By devouring these spiritual entities,
I can harness the power
of the upgraded Psyforge
to break the space barrier!
[Enchantment, Divine Union]
Enchantment,
Divine Union.
[Dark Sky, Merged Form]
Run!
The game's gonna crash!
Get through that door!
Run!
I don't want to die!
[Little Elk]
Dark Sky!
We have to kill this monster.
Or countless players will die.
Then Master's efforts
will all be in vain.
I'll find the Empress!
Divine Herb Radiance, Gift of Revival!
[Divine Herb Radiance, Gift of Revival]
[Shuttle Ring Space]
Mom, Dad,
I did it.
I reopened the logout channels.
Mom, Dad!
Mom and Dad always leave messages
when they appear.
Is The Singularity messing with me?
Xiaocheng?
Weren't you in the mental hospital?
Chu Yi,
I'm out.
Was it my parents...?
Patience.
I'll tell you everything now.
[Summit Cathedral]
Where's the Shuttle Ring?
Why don't they have it?
I detected energy fluctuations earlier.
Three spiritual entities performed
dimensional travel.
Hello?
Darn it!
[Internal Game Data Center]
Warning.
Unauthorized intrusion detected.
Commencing elimination
of uploaded human consciousnesses.
Xiaocheng,
use your mythic item, the Phoenix's Eye,
to send us into the Core of The Era.
The moment we enter,
we'll be assimilated by the colossal
amount of data in the Core.
Like water merging with the sea.
An individual's consciousness
is too insignificant.
[Chu Tiange's Room]
Because I overused the Phoenix's Eye
and fried my brain,
I could only guide you into the game
to obtain the Shuttle Ring
and to stop Luo Fan and the others
from joining forces
with these sealed alien creatures
and invading the real world.
Your parents
never wanted you involved
in this crisis,
but I...
No.
You're different from us players.
Like the ancient ancestors,
you entered this world physically.
You can't complete in-game missions.
This is a task
only I can accomplish.
Saving the world, you know.
Who else is gonna do it but me?
Chu Yi,
you successfully reopened
the logout channels
and obtained the Shuttle Ring.
But it's
not completely over yet.
Dark Sky has been using the Psyforge
to slowly harvest players' spirits
since the server launched.
And now he's gone completely mad.
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
Chu Yi!
- Master!
- Tiange!
Chu Tiange!
[Dragon's Gaze Unleashes the Lance]
Dragon's gaze unleashes the lance,
shattering the world in its wake!
No!
I refuse to fall here!
So close.
I was so close!
So close?
In your dreams!
As long as I'm here,
you will never succeed!
And
do you think only we in the present
are stopping you?
Even the accumulated spiritual essence
of countless ancient sages within The Era
will stand against you!
The mythic item,
Phoenix's Eye?
Wake up,
accumulated spiritual essence
of State of Tang!
Answer my call,
ignite your spiritual forms,
and defend the homeland
of future generations!
[Li Jing]
I pacified Xiaoxian,
and annihilated the Turks,
How dare you, a later-generation brat,
cause such chaos!
[Cheng Yaojin]
My three axe strokes
are enough to cleave your heads!
With exuberant inspiration, my brush
shakes the Five Peaks.
[Li Bai]
Upon finishing the poem,
I laugh and soar above the vast seas.
Come on,
Gao Shi!
Let my sword's light
illuminate Yumen Pass,
while your iron spear stirs the sands
of the Western deserts!
How about pairing
your silver saddle and white steed
[Gao Shi]
with my thunderous drums
that shake the earth?
[Chen Zi'ang]
I see the ancients before me,
and those to come after.
The universe is vas.
How profoundly fortunate!
They're just a bunch of
failed, lonely ghosts!
They should have died long ago!
I'm shattering this world
to give them release!
Your goal
was to trigger a spiritual awakening
in the real world?
This formation
trapped a powerful enemy,
but it also drained
the real world's spiritual energy.
Blame your parents
for blocking my cultivation,
hindering my path to immortality!
Is this your mythic item?
You trash.
You need to sacrifice all the players
to level up?
No. Impossible!
You just got the Shuttle Ring.
How can you withstand
its psychic backlash?
Aunt said
as long as...
As long as your uncle and I
retain a shred of clear consciousness,
we would have infinite opportunities
to tear open the curtain of the new Era.
Added Legendary Mission,
Reviving State of Sui.
[Legendary Mission: Reviving State of Sui]
Added preset commands
for Plan A and Plan B.
Shatter the blockade of The Singularity.
Blast apart all enemies
threatening to invade the real world!
I've killed you once,
twice,
and I'll kill you a third time
in the real world!
Others get to log out.
You?
You get a funeral!
No!
Let's go.
Time to return to the real world.
It feels like I've forgotten something.
Stop!
Stop now!
We want to log out too!
Whose dog is this?
Come get it!
Prodigal Chu Tiange!
[Streets of the Real World]
Too bad we never found Meow in the end.
And Chu Yi isn't answering my calls.
I need to hurry over there.
Vinebound Radiance,
Blossom Flash!
[Vinebound Radiance]
[Your every purchase
reshapes the apocalypse.]
The barriers of the real world
will finally be shattered.
Now
the new Era has arrived!
Xiaocheng, stop playing around.
[You have created the character:
Primordial Dragon Emperor.]
[Load now? Yes]
Or I'll have to spank you.
[Advertisement]
[Nan Xiaocheng: Chu Tiange's cousin,]
[treated as mentally ill since childhood
due to overusing the Phoenix's Eye.]
[She has an eccentric
and hyperactive personality.]
[After Chu Tiange's parents
were framed by Dark Sky,]
[Nan Xiaocheng helped them]
[enter the Core of The Era
as spiritual entities,]
[guiding Chu Tiange to complete
the mission of saving all players.]
[Phoenix's Eye: Can detect
hidden mythic items within The Era]
[(e.g., the Psyforge
created by Dark Sky)]
[It can also assist the Chus
in entering The Era,]
[records events
witnessed by the holder in the past,]
[and even deploy the Silvery Divine Realm
to pull enemies into a psychic domain.]
[Risk Warning: Overuse may cause
mental instability in the holder.]
[Core: The core code
storing all data of The Era.]
[After the Chus
were framed by Dark Sky,]
[they were sent into the Core
as spiritual entities.]
[Next Episode]
Jiangnan City
has a major problem.
The new Era has arrived after all.
006!
All grown up? Time for a new experiment!
I'm Master's maid,
not anyone's lab rat!
Mr. Ling, your spear isn't rusty, is it?
Spear stands firm, blade remains sharp.
Xiaocheng!
The Director is catching up to us!
What do you mean?
- Wealth and Wonder -
(Watch the Latest Donghua Episodes: www.h-donghua.xyz)
♪I see the light of homes♪
♪The thin fog floats♪
♪I've learned to review my lessons♪
♪The moment I create a miracle♪
♪No adventure with you is formidable♪
♪Unlocking threads of mysteries♪
♪We are born with heated blood♪
♪We start from light years away♪
♪When I have friends♪
♪I have the whole world♪
♪Can time stop at this moment♪
♪We encourage each other
and fight for tomorrow♪
♪In the future♪
♪I will still be feeling it like now♪
♪I hope time stops at this moment♪
♪No matter how harsh fate is to us♪
♪We will not let go of each other♪
♪Can time stop at this moment♪
♪We encourage each other
and fight for tomorrow♪
♪In the future♪
♪I will still be feeling it like now♪
♪I hope time stops at this moment♪
♪No matter how harsh fate is to us♪
♪We will not let go of each other♪
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™