- Renegade Immortal -
(Copyright Statement)
(Minors Should Watch Only
with the Consent of Their Guardians)
(This Film is Entirely Fictional)
(Including cultivation systems
and all mystical powers)
(Please Do Not Imitate in Real Life)
(Adapted from Er Gen's
"Renegade Immortal" on Qidian)
(Previously on...)
(In just ten years,)
(my soul is fully restored.)
(This body)
(holds lightning power.)
(It proves)
(the Dao has not doomed me.)
(The Fatebreaker Pearl
was already full of mysteries.)
(Now that it's complete,
it's even harder to grasp.)
(To break my Dao intent
with a mere gate?)
(Dream on!)
(Let me see
what truly lies within this gate.)
Do you know
what is Dao?
(At the end of seeking the Dao,)
(one seeks oneself.)
(That figure...)
(Who is it?)
Episode 146
[Commanding Thunder]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
(The Thunder Immortal Realm
is about to open.)
(This time,)
(inside the Thunder Pool,)
(I must refine as much
of my origin power as I can.)
(This...)
(is pressure.)
(Did something happen
to the Thunder Pool?)
(A Silver-Horned Thunder Beast)
(and a Yin Void Puppet?)
(Wait...)
(Is he a Lightning Immortal Envoy too?)
(He's only an Ascension cultivator.)
(How is he staying there
like the Thunder Pool is nothing?)
(With just one glance,)
(Shengong Hu, Lightning Immortal Envoy)
(he wounded my mind,)
(Yin Void, fallen from Yang Real)
(shook my Dao heart,)
(and sent my cultivation plummeting
to Yin Void.)
(So the Fatebreaker Pearl)
(actually holds a monstrous chance
to reach the third step?)
(I only glimpsed a crack today,)
(and already gained this much.)
(If that gate ever fully opens,)
(I dare not even imagine it.)
(The gaze that nearly shattered my mind)
(must have been
the legendary Dao nightmare.)
(If I can follow him,)
(it would be the fortune of a lifetime.)
Greetings, Senior.
What do you want?
Senior,
my name is Shengong Hu.
I'm from the Shen Gong Clan
of Southern Domain
and a second-rank
Lightning Immortal Envoy.
I was once at the Yang Real stage.
I beg you, please let me serve you.
Serve me?
I know...
- (Is he saying this)
- my cultivation is weak.
- (because of my insight)
- I'm not worthy to serve you.
- (scared him into submission?)
- But
many cultivation clans answer to me.
(But I may never be able)
- (to use that insight again.)
- Whatever you need,
- (Shengong Hu used to be Yang Real.)
- I can be useful to you.
- (If he ever sees through me,)
- My loyalty is sincere.
I swear to heaven.
(I'll be in serious danger.)
All I ask
is for a few words of guidance
when I break through.
No.
Senior,
I'll offer you my Dao soul.
I swear it on my Dao heart.
Please let me serve you
for a thousand years.
He's even offering his Dao soul?
(Once I have his Dao soul,)
(I won't have to fear betrayal.)
(He's quite decisive.)
You will not regret this?
Never.
Why are you here?
The Thunder Immortal Realm
will open soon.
I came here to cultivate
and absorb origin power.
I'm not from Luotian.
How long
before the Thunder Immortal Realm opens?
Thirty years.
When the time comes,
a Thunder Cauldron can take you inside.
(Thirty years?)
(The Rain Immortal Realm back then)
(laid the foundation for my battles
across the stars.)
(Now, this Thunder Immortal Realm)
(is somewhere I must go,
no matter what.)
Does the Thunder Immortal Realm
have any cultivation restrictions?
Senior,
anyone at peak late-stage Ascendant
or below
can enter.
With the Lightning Immortal Temple's
secret art,
even the second step cultivators
can go inside.
But once inside,
no one can use divine techniques
beyond early Nirvana Glimpse.
Otherwise,
the realm will collapse.
(Then...)
(Seventy steps?)
(Eighty steps?)
(Ninety-five steps?)
(One hundred steps?)
(One hundred steps in,)
(and the thunder means nothing to him.)
(Senior really is a hidden master.)
(I, Shengong Hu,)
(made the right bet.)
(Ten steps...)
(Right now,)
(ten steps is my limit?)
(If I were at full strength,)
(fifty steps would not be a problem.)
(In my battle with Lei Daozi,)
(I overused the Net-Severing Sword Art.)
(It nearly drained my origin power dry.)
(At the first step,)
(recovering origin power
is painfully difficult.)
(Fortunately,
I have the lightning soul.)
(With the Lightning Essence Art,
I can turn it into origin power.)
(I need to recover as fast as possible.)
(At one hundred steps,)
(he's pulling that much thunder
into his body?)
(If I tried that,)
(my soul would be crippled.)
(Senior's cultivation)
(is beyond anything I can read.)
(Two Years Later)
(The thunder near the edge)
(is still too weak and impure.)
(Only deeper inside)
(can I refine truly pure origin power.)
(If I want to recover faster,)
(I have to go deeper.)
(He moved.)
(Senior is finally moving again.)
(I waited two years)
(just for this exact moment.)
(If I can catch even a trace
of his divine technique,)
(it will be a blessing from heaven.)
(The thunder pressure here)
(is terrifying.)
(Ten steps?)
(Senior finally moved again,)
(but only ten steps?)
(That terrifying aura before...)
(Was it just luck?)
(Then my pledge)
(would be a complete joke.)
(Brute force will not get me through.)
(My soul and thunder
share the same source.)
(There has to be a way in.)
(Even the same source was rejected?)
(Could it be)
(not about power,)
(but Dao?)
(All things in heaven and earth)
(begin within the self.)
(It's not about using power.)
(It's about becoming one with the Dao.)
(Only when the Dao aligns
can the source be absorbed.)
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.com)
He...
He's walking on thunder!
The lightning itself becomes his path.
Heaven and earth welcome him.
This is the true peak
of the Lightning Dao.
I waited two years
just to witness
a divine power like this.
(That fleeting insight
into the third step)
(and the understanding of Dao)
(may not be confrontational,)
(but it's more valuable)
(than countless divine techniques.)
Well...
this place is lively.
Zhan Konglie?
(Zhan Konglie, Lightning Immortal Envoy,
Yang Real)
(Late-stage Ascension,)
(yet he can sit in the inner ring?)
(He must have a treasure
blocking the thunder.)
You don't belong here.
Get lost!
Well, well.
Shengong Hu.
Forgive my poor eyes.
I almost did not recognize you.
Your cultivation
has fallen quite a bit.
None of your business!
This young man looks unfamiliar.
To sit safely in the inner ring,
you must have quite the treasure on you.
Why not show it to me?
Let me broaden my horizons.
Master!
This is bad!
We're in real trouble.
He came looking for a fight.
If he sees through us,
we're finished.
(A Yang Real cultivator...)
(He thinks I have a powerful treasure.)
(He'll not let this go.)
(To prove his loyalty,)
(Shengong Hu will defend me
at all costs.)
(Before, we were evenly matched,)
(so I had to play along.)
(But with my Lord here today,)
(why should I fear him?)
You have three breaths.
Leave
or die!
(Fight me to the death)
(over some Ascension junior
with a treasure?)
(Shengong Hu,)
(what are you really planning?)
Zhan Konglie!
Die!
Gladly.
Let me see
what you are really hiding.
They're fighting!
Shengong Hu's cultivation has dropped.
He cannot last long!
(If Shengong Hu loses,)
(I'll fall into Zhan Konglie's hands.)
(If I back down now,)
(Shengong Hu will grow suspicious.)
(Either way, I'm in danger.)
Shengong Hu,
I'll not help you in this fight.
Consider this your trial.
If you lose,
I'll return your Dao soul.
Don't worry, my Lord.
I'll not disappoint you.
My Lord?
To keep the treasure for yourself,
you two are putting
on this pathetic act?
You think that will scare me away?
What a joke.
(His thunder-summoning art is strong.)
(He uses origin power
to draw on heaven and earth.)
(It nearly rivals forming a cauldron
from origin power.)
(But as the power moves,)
(something is missing.)
(There's a flaw hidden in its rhythm.)
(There it is...)
(the way out.)
Go!
I have never liked you.
But after today,
I admit you have some skill.
Shengong Hu,
your divine technique
may carry thunder's might,
but it lacks its true essence.
Your Dao heart is not one with thunder.
How can you command
true lightning power?
My Lord, you're right.
That is exactly where I'm stuck.
Please guide me, my Lord.
Merge one's Dao intent with thunder?
Everyone knows that.
But the path forward is unclear.
No one knows how to do it.
Anyone can talk in riddles.
Still pretending?
Let see how you get out of this.
Do you understand now?
(Strip away the surface.)
(Go straight to the source.)
(Only this can break the deadlock,)
(win without fighting,)
(and force Zhan Konglie to retreat.)
(He actually grasped
the source of the Dao?)
(No wonder Shengong Hu's Dao heart)
(advanced in an instant.)
(This man is no Ascension.)
(His true cultivation
is beyond measure.)
My Lord, your guidance
has given me a second life.
I...
understand.
Zhan Konglie!
Again!
I, Zhan Konglie, failed to recognize you.
I disturbed your cultivation, Senior.
Please forgive my offense.
Congratulations, Shengong Hu.
You have found a worthy master.
This is truly
a heaven-sent fortune.
I'm truly convinced.
I have received a summons
from the Lightning Immortal Temple.
In the future,
we may serve there together as envoys.
Until then.
My Lord, sorry for disturbing you.
What summons?
My Lord, it's an order
from the Lightning Immortal Temple.
Anyone chosen as a candidate
will receive one.
Three months before its opening,
candidates compete to fill
any remaining envoy seats
that are vacant.
With Zhan Konglie's cultivation,
he's likely to secure a seat
unless something unforeseen happens.
(If Shengong Hu stays here,)
(he may attract more trouble.)
I'll enter seclusion for a while
to comprehend
an important divine technique.
You should leave for now.
This is a message jade slip.
Whenever you call,
I'll come immediately.
This jade slip also contains
a detailed star map
of the Southern Domain.
It may help you find your way, My Lord.
Go.
(Eight Years Later)
(After ten years of refining,)
(my soul is complete.)
(I cannot absorb any more origin power.)
(I have reached a bottleneck.)
(If I want to go further,)
(I must break through the second step.)
(The Five Elements are now complete.)
(But Yin and Yang remain split apart.)
(What does that mean?)
(Fatebreaker Pearl,)
(what do you need)
(for the next step?)
(Thankfully,)
(Muwan and the others' divine souls
are unharmed.)
(They even seem more stable
than before.)
(The Thunder Immortal Realm opens
in twenty years.)
(Right now,)
(breaking through comes first.)
(Southern Domain)
(has many abandoned planets.)
(Mortals live there.)
(They are perfect for hiding)
(and cultivating in peace.)
(I need to find a safe base soon.)
(It's time)
(to claim a cultivation planet
of my own.)
(Renegade Immortal: Thunder Immortal Realm Rising)
Immortal arts are mysterious.
They can command the wind and rain
and turn beans into soldiers.
No matter how precious the immortal art,
you must claim it
with your own strength.
Do not let your master's techniques
fade away in your hands.
Ask
(Qi Condensation)
(Foundation Establishment)
(Core Formation)
(Nascent Soul)
(Soul Formation)
(Soul Transformation)
And turn the tide of the stars
(Ascension)
Constantly refreshing the rules
Rehearsing every possible outcome
Once resolve is born,
right and wrong no longer matter
Cutting free from every shackle
without hesitation
A soul that breaks away
from mediocrity
Forged by loneliness and resilience
One more step
and it's the edge of the abyss
Don't fall
Look toward the summit
Chase it
Tempered and forged into perfection
Through countless trials,
never retreating
Daring to defy the will of heaven
Shattering every barrier
on the path ahead
Igniting the seas with blood
Blooming through relentless refinement
No matter how sharp these thorns
Let everything turn to ash
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™