[Adapted from Ergen's novel, Beyond Time's Gaze]
- Beyond Time's Gaze -
[Year-long animation]
[Copyright Notice]
[This story is purely fictional.]
[Underage viewer discretion is advised.]
[Please do not imitate in real life.]
[Previously]
The lucky hour is here.
[Grand Opening of Port No. 176]
Port No. 176 is now open.
I
used to be all alone.
Somehow, so many people are now around me.
Mr. Zhang San.
Congratulations on your grand opening.
Announce to all disciples,
the war
is upon us.
Episode 27
[Life Flame Mystic Splendor]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Look!
What's up?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Bells ring on all seven peaks.
Hurry up!
Run fast!
What's that?
Lift your hand, please.
Okay.
You can go.
Bells keep ringing.
Still ringing.
Could it be…?
The war has begun.
You heard the bells too?
You came as well.
Such a huge scene.
The war is really coming.
Mr. Xu.
Look!
That's the Grandmaster!
No mistake about it!
The Grandmaster's shown up!
All Qixuetong disciples, listen up.
I'm Xuelianzi.
I've got news for you.
Our sect
is officially at war
with the Haishi Tribe.
Greetings, Grandmaster!
All seven peaks,
line up for battle!
They're approaching.
Old sect scrolls say
every peak follows a unique cultivation way.
The First Peak
cultivates Sword-ship.
Its master watches over the north of Forbidden Phoenix Ground all year,
commanding crimson-robed warriors
to shield the southwest domain of our sect.
Yes, Grandmaster!
- Yes, Grandmaster! - Yes, Grandmaster!
The Second Peak
walks the Tao of alchemy
and masters healing balms and antidotes,
standing as our sect's firmest backing.
Yes, Grandmaster!
- Yes, Grandmaster! - Yes, Grandmaster!
The Third Peak
is well-versed in forbidden incantations and uncanny arts.
It's the most cryptic and outlandish lineage of the sect.
Yes, Grandmaster!
- Yes, Grandmaster! - Yes, Grandmaster!
The Fourth Peak,
with beast mastery as its core discipline,
domesticates spirit beasts and savage monsters
and commands beast hordes for battle.
Yes, Grandmaster!
- Yes, Grandmaster! - Yes, Grandmaster!
The Fifth Peak governs formations,
and the Sixth Peak forges treasures.
The two peaks have marched to the front.
The Seventh Peak…
Yes, Grandmaster!
- Yes, Grandmaster! - Yes, Grandmaster!
Hahaha.
Kaiyi,
you've quietly gained
profound Tao insights,
and a breakthrough is near.
Well done.
You flatter me.
For this war,
peak masters and elders have sworn to answer the call.
But Foundation Building and Qi Condensation disciples bear no such duty.
I know full well
your cultivation
comes from your own blood,
sweat and toil,
with scant aid from the sect.
Yet the Haishi Tribe holds wealth worth over a hundred billion.
I resolve
to split half of all plunder
as rewards for you all.
Once you join the fight,
you may not withdraw at will.
Who among you
is willing to march to war?
I volunteer to fight!
Golden Core souls of the Haishi Tribe
greatly boost the Soul-devouring Fire Scripture.
I've felt its power myself.
If I wish to ignite the life flame swiftly,
this great war is a perfect chance.
Disciples of the Qixuetong, heed my command!
March forth to war
with me!
All Haishi Tribe troops, listen up!
Recapture the Four Mermaid Islands
at all costs!
For the Qixuetong,
fight till our last breath!
[Frontlines of the Four Mermaid Islands]
For the Qixuetong,
fight till our last breath!
You Mermaid Tribe switch sides
time and again.
Have you no backbone at all?
Mere insects!
[Shiwei, Haishi Tribe's war colossus]
Reinforcements!
Help has arrived!
It's the Haishi Tribe's war colossus!
Send an urgent plea to the Qixuetong!
Slay the four Mermaid Islands!
Your doom
- is here! - is here!
Nascent Soul! Nascent Soul cultivators!
And a pressure far beyond the Nascent Soul realm!
Xue... Xuelianzi is here!
All disciples, heed my order!
Slay every member of the Haishi Tribe!
Spare none!
- Charge! - Charge!
Is this
the true battlefield?
The Qixuetong
has gathered all the elites from the seven peaks.
Pass the order.
Hold this ground
until our mighty ones arrive.
[Third Elder of the Seventh Peak,
Late Golden Core Realm of the Six Palaces]
All Foundation Building disciples, listen!
New mission of destroying Haishi Tribe's hidden teleport arrays.
Ten thousand spirit stones
for each array destroyed.
[Qixuetong's battle puppets]
And...
let's slaughter our fill today.
The two armies' clash
is brutal!
Such overwhelming pressure.
Oh no!
That was close.
One hit would turn me
to dust instantly.
Over there!
Grandmaster,
all preparations complete.
This battle is beyond my strength.
Staying here will get me caught in the crossfire.
I'll take the Third Elder's mission first
and hunt down the Haishi Tribe's teleport arrays.
Where the Haishi Tribe lurks, the alien taint runs thick.
The Shadow senses the alien taint sharply.
It can help me search.
You,
find the teleport arrays for me.
Any questions?
Your probation period
can be shortened by ten days.
Go easy on him.
Do not be upset, Master.
Little Shadow may not fully understand you,
yet I know you are worn out.
We ought to take burdens off your shoulders.
Share your worries
and sorrows.
Do you get it?
Oh!
I hate your killing aura.
Lead the way.
The teleport array is hidden right here.
[The Haishi Tribe's Hidden Teleport Array]
Haishi Tribe's scent.
Someone's teleporting over.
Their cultivation is weak.
They're here!
Ambush!
What is this thing?
Refine.
Well.
Ugh.
Little Shadow cultivates by devouring alien taint,
yet I rely on artifact spirit essence.
My path
is far harder.
The souls of the same-rank Haishi tribemen
are twice as potent as sea beasts.
Master,
let us ruin this teleport array
and seek the next.
Hold fast.
More Haishi tribesmen shall arrive via teleportation.
Lying in ambush here
will hasten my opening of apertures.
At last, I'm out.
[Aperture 21, opened]
[Aperture 23, opened]
[Aperture 24]
The Shadow acts abnormally.
The Mystic Splendor State.
A cultivator with the life flame.
I can't let him through.
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.com)
Mortal human!
I see you clearly.
I will slay you the moment I arrive.
Seek another teleport array.
Let us reap countless foes this day.
Wage unbridled slaughter.
Fight fiercely,
and we shall count our kills.
[Aperture 25, opened]
That pressure…
It's him again.
Human,
it's you once more!
I won't let you escape.
[Aperture 26]
[Aperture 28]
With one more aperture opened,
[Aperture 29]
I can condense life flame.
The Haishi Tribe has sensed trouble.
No more reinforcements will be teleported over.
I have to hunt for another teleport array.
Once the life flame forms
and my Life Lamp is lit,
my strength will match that of dual-fire cultivators.
I wonder
if I'll be strong enough to beat the captain.
Master,
there's a huge commotion inside.
You,
go scout it out.
Two
Haishi tribemen.
One human
- at Foundation Building.
- You can speak now?
Master,
it says inside are two Haishi tribemen at the Foundation Building
and one human at the Foundation Building.
None has awakened the life flame.
Little Shadow,
did you check thoroughly?
You must prioritize Master's safety
above all, just like I do.
Never be careless.
Only one aperture left before I ignite the life flame.
Slaying those two Haishi tribemen
will surely trigger my Mystic Splendor State.
Fellow disciple of the Seventh Peak.
Disciple of the Third Peak!
Friend,
aid me now.
Afterward,
[Disciple of the Third Peak, 13 apertures]
I'll reward you handsomely afterward.
Die!
One hundred thousand spirit stones.
Deal.
[Muchi, Haishi Tribe, 18 apertures]
He has a reinforcement.
[Seal]
Moshu.
[Moshu, Haishi Tribe, 29 apertures]
Stand back.
I'll fight him.
His strength matches mine.
He's only a hair away
from igniting the life flame.
I can't kill him quickly.
Take down the weaker ones first.
Feint east, strike west.
He's only after me.
That aura…
It's Lord Yunchen.
We're doomed.
You're the human who kept cutting off my teleportation!
[Yunchen]
Moshu,
[Single-Flame Foundation Building]
guard the teleport array.
After three breaths,
I'll slice him into pieces.
Those in Mystic Splendor State out-speed those in normal Foundation Building.
Once he teleports over,
I'll have no way to flee.
My only chance is…
No!
He's going to kill Muchi
to activate the Mystic Splendor State.
If you don't want to die,
go hold him back.
I have no choice but to trust him.
Use secret arts.
Take the gamble.
Bind!
Moshu,
save me!
Taicang!
Get out of my way!
This is terrible!
I can't let him trigger the Mystic Splendor State.
So slow.
The whole world drags on.
I see every move
and every breath
he takes clearly.
This power…
It feels as if I blend with heaven and earth.
At last,
I've reached this stage.
Pair of iron fists
Heaven and earth blaze Mystic Splendor,
Life flame burns bright.
Lone fearless heart
Mystic Splendor State,
activate!
Eight hundred li of life-or-death frontier
[Xu Qing in Mystic Splendor State]
The Mystic Splendor State!
A fleeting phantom shadow
Cast clone secret art
to slip away.
Fight with all resolve
Forge a new heaven
You
can't run away.
Outer Firmament
Mounds of corpses cannot build a sky-reaching path
No!
Living souls shall not cross the Yellow Spring River
Endless dark sundials weigh down our spines
Whoever strikes first shall reign supreme
Human,
I'm out.
Got your last words ready?
Next one.
This world lacks sunlight
It's your turn now.
[Mystic Splendor State]
Scan this QR code.
Drink with me on the spirit ship someday.
You're the only one missing.
[Next Episode]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™