(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Audience under 18 are requested to watch
with the permission of their guardians.)
(The whole video is made by CG.
Please do not copy in real life.)
(The film is purely fictitious and does not
serve as a basis for scientific knowledge.)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
Slayer Wu,
absorb as much light as you want.
No, stop!
Stop!
You thief! Thief!
This is
a Thread Map?
The Universe Sea is perilous.
Please take great care.
Now with a Supreme Treasure guarding us,
we humans in the Original Universe
will no longer be easily bullied
by foreign races.
Episode 229
[The Universe Sea Arc]
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Please keep the news of me obtaining
a Supreme Treasure secret for now.
It will be announced
when the right time comes.
Furthermore,
I have summoned you all here
not just for a celebration.
There is an important item
to deliver to you all.
This map of the Cosmic Vessel
is integrated from both my
and Luo Feng's map data.
Good lad.
It is no surprise to me
that Giant Axe has map data.
But you not only have a map too.
It even records some core areas
of the Cosmic Vessel.
Hmm.
Where did this kid get a map?
It's quite detailed.
(Although it still cannot cover
the entire Cosmic Vessel,)
(the more detailed the data is,)
(the more assured the treasure hunt
into the Cosmic Vessel is.)
Luo Feng.
You have made great contributions
by donating the map for free.
But our treasure vault
has limited items.
And I cannot give you
an equivalent return either.
I can only give you
5,000 Treasure Points.
But Senior Giant Axe,
you provided the map for free,
so should I....
You need to grow stronger,
so don't refuse.
Senior, rest assured.
I will also contribute
to support our race.
Cheers!
Finally here.
(Cosmic Vessel, Universe Sea)
The Cosmic Vessel.
It spans hundreds
of millions of light-years
and continuously absorbs
endless chaotic energy,
making the Cosmic Vessel's
periphery full of dangers
and harsh conditions.
The Cosmic Vessel's interior
is even more perilous.
No one knows the Cosmic Vessel's origin.
Even before the birth
of the two Holy Land Universes,
it already existed.
It often attracts
and devours small universes.
Because of that,
it is publicly known
as the Cosmic Vessel.
The Cosmic Vessel
truly lives up to its name
as a Dangerous Land.
Luo Feng.
It's Senior and Void-Gold Lord.
(As the teacher of Hong,
he is indeed extraordinary.)
(I heard that guided by Void-Gold Lord,)
(Hong kept breaking through
and has become a King.)
As expected,
since the Cosmic Vessel map was shared,
everyone wants
to venture into this place.
Your big brother Hong
is already a rare genius.
I didn't expect you
to be far superior to him.
Now you've even started
exploring a Dangerous Land.
However, in the perilous inner domain
of the Cosmic Vessel,
even we might accidentally perish.
And Icepeak and I
both plan to act alone.
You are alone.
So be extra careful.
Understood.
(Ice Crystal Zone
Cosmic Vessel, Universe Sea)
In the action route you drafted,
there are a total of
892 dangerous places.
This zone, where ice blades rage,
is only ordinary.
Flame Sand Cup!
What truly qualifies as top-level danger
(Godsbane Stream, Cosmic Vessel, Universe Sea)
is the Godsbane Stream ahead.
Let's venture in to find out
how dangerous it is.
(Yin Tuo)
A human?
Daring to overreach
and enter Godsbane Stream alone?
There is a terrifying being
called the Lava Demon God here.
(It can almost)
(kill anyone
below the Universe Strongest.)
Suppress!
The rumors are true.
The Silver Wings Treasure
is truly domineering to the utmost.
Heh heh, it seems these Silver Wings
are destined to become mine.
He comes with ill intent.
He's the First Reincarnation Era's
Ancestor God Sect's member,
Yin Tuo.
(As early as his era,)
(Yin Tuo was notorious
for being tricky.)
(Compared to Amyoung Lord,
he is even harder to deal with.)
Human, hand over the Silver Wings,
and I will spare you.
How is it?
Impossible.
- Swallowed Star -
- The Universe Sea Arc -
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.com)
Petty trick.
(So he is like me,)
(following the path
of the Golden Beast God.)
(His use of secret techniques
is even sharper than mine.)
You have angered me, human.
(Such a domineering gust!)
(Almost every 0.01 seconds,
it delivers the equivalent of)
(a Cosmic Lord's
full-power punch's impact.)
A magma whirlpool.
This is also one of Godsbane Stream's
deadliest threats.
Second only to the Lava Demon God!
For hundreds of eras here,
I've survived
countless magma whirlpools.
I've long been able to handle them.
With my absolute environmental edge,
you have no chance of winning!
The Silver Wings are mine!
Wishful thinking!
Get lost!
Give me the Silver Wings!
Human, don't run!
(It's better not to display
the Golden Kingdom's ultimate power.)
(If the power of the Wings of Slayer Wu
is further spread,)
(it will make more
powerful beings covet it.)
Is that all you've got?
I won't waste my time.
Trying to stop me?
(Once he is in
the magma whirlpool's center,)
(I'll use a secret technique to trigger
the Annihilation Whirlwind at the core.)
(My Divine Body is strong,
and my talent is special.)
(So I can survive it.)
(And once most Cosmic Lords
fall into it,)
(they will be instantly killed.)
Now is the time!
Yin Tuo, do you think
I don't know the danger
at the magma whirlpool's center,
the Annihilation Whirlwind?
How can this be?
You Original Universe beings'
exploration of the Three Dangerous Lands
is very limited.
Even my Ancestor God Sect
has only just learned this secret
in this Reincarnation Era.
Heh heh.
Jie Fanzi's records about
magma whirlpools are very detailed.
Trash!
(This aura)
(is from billions of kilometers away,
yet so swift and fierce.)
(And two Divine Eye Clan members too?)
(I'm speechless.)
(When it rains, it really pours.)
Show time!
(In such a vast Cosmic Vessel,)
(I actually encountered
three Cosmic Lords at once.)
(What a hassle!)
(Ultimate Arrow is one thing.)
(But Five Chaos is here too.)
(Five Chaos Lord)
(Ultimate Arrow Lord)
(Cosmic Vessel: One of the Universe Sea's
Three Dangerous Lands.)
(As an immensely huge wrecked spaceship)
(spanning countless light-years,
it has existed here since endless eras ago.)
(No one knows its origin.)
(The environment is perilous,
but it also hides endless treasures.)
(Yin Tuo: Cosmic Lord.)
(The First Reincarnation Era's
Ancestor God Sect's powerful member.)
(Looking like a child, he's actually
a super-powerful special life form.)
(He cultivates the Path
of the Golden Beast God)
(and can turn into a one-horned lizard
about 100,000 kilometers long.)
(Q: Is the North Star
always in the north?)
(A: Currently, yes, but not forever.)
(Due to the slow wobble
of the Earth's rotation axis,)
(which is called 'precession,'
with a period of about 25,800 years,)
(the 'North Star'
it points to will change.)
(In about 12,000 years, Vega will
take over as the new 'North Star.')
♪When the city is shadowed in gray♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star"
available on Starting point Chinese net)
(Copyrights reserved)
(by Shanghai Tencent Penguin
Film Culture Communication Co., Ltd.)
(Next Episode Preview)
Hand over your wings now!
I heard your Wing Treasure
is quite good.
I was the one
who first discovered these wings.
Then let's have some fun.
None of you will get away unscathed!
Silver Wings Lord, are you crazy?
We gave you a chance.
None of you can escape.
If we all die together,
we can call it a life-and-death bond.
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™