A hundred years ago,
Luo Hou, Demon Sovereign of Qiumina,
obtained the Turbidity Lock.
He led his clan from the Netherworld
to invade our lands.
The Turbidity Lock cast a spell
to drain our essence blood
to fuel his power.
All Five Clans of Mulingor live
under Luo Hou's oppression.
But
I have always believed a legend:
Deep within the Mulingor Oasis
lies a divine sword that can sever
the Turbidity Lock.
To claim it,
one needs the Dragon and Phoenix Beasts
to open the Zone.
Once I hold that divine sword,
I can slay Luo Hou
and change everyone's fate.
Xihe,
you're secretly
practicing swordplay again.
Still chasing that divine sword tale?
The legend must be true.
The two beasts have proven it.
They were born with the divine sword.
Those chick and worm?
You truly think they are divine beasts?
Ever since you found them,
all they do is eat and sleep.
Have they grown fatter again?
I have seen their true forms.
Do not trust this disguise.
They are divine beasts, after all.
If they do not eat more,
how will they ever grow
and slay Luo Hou?
Xihe,
stop teasing me.
Luo Hou is the Demon Sovereign.
And we are only refugees.
I do not want you to die.
It can't get worse than this.
Once we find the divine sword,
we
won't be bullied
by the Demon Clan again.
The demons are here.
Hide here.
Do not let them find you.
Luo Hou comes for blood to cultivate.
We tried to resist.
But the Demon Clan is too powerful.
They have the Nine Vile Phases.
We once had the Seven Phases,
including Refining,
Foundation, Immortality,
Celestial, Formless, and Purity.
But the Turbidity Lock's spell
sealed the ethereal spirit within us.
Under Luo Hou are the Four Demon Lords.
Chen Yuan delights in taking lives.
Yet Luo Hou made him our warden.
No matter the phase,
once you fight with Qi,
the spell will be activated,
and you'll die a violent death.
We are fodder,
trapped in this refugee camp,
for the Demon Clan's cultivation.
His Grace nears the Vile IX Phase,
about to break through.
He needs more fresh blood.
All of you
are honored to offer your blood.
The divine sword
is our hope to overthrow all this.
But until we find it,
we can only endure in silence.
Endure.
And endure.
Are you okay?
Careful!
Give me a hand.
Senior.
It is no use.
They have been drained too often.
They will soon become Blood Mist
and feed Luo Hou.
Even so, I hope
they may die with dignity.
All of this
will come to an end.
Come with me.
If Luo Hou reaches the Vile IX Phase,
he will rival a Purity Greatmaster.
By then,
what awaits us
is utter ruin.
Stay calm.
Trust Chiyang's plan.
Raise your heads.
As chief of the Luminara Clan,
this mission
will be under my command.
Before Luo Hou breaks through,
he will become weak first.
When the Blood Moon rises,
Luo Hou will begin his seclusion,
the Demon Lords will guard him,
and defenses will be at their weakest.
This
is our only chance to escape.
We'll move in two groups.
The elders and I
have chosen the Array Team.
They will set the array in the square.
Once the Blood Moon hangs high,
they'll trigger it
and blast the lock stake
to break the Zone.
Yes.
The rest will form the Escort Team
and wait at the border.
Once the Zone loosens,
take the clan and leave at once.
Yes.
You are the elite of our clan.
This time,
we must win.
Dismissed.
Senior.
I want to join the Array Team.
Why?
The Array Team needs better odds.
You think breaking the array
outweighs escorting?
Only by breaking the array
is there hope of escape.
I train daily with the sword.
I can handle it.
The plan is set.
Save your strength
for those we are escorting.
You took the remnant copy
of Luminara Swordsmanship
in my room, didn't you?
So, you knew.
I thought becoming stronger
would let me do greater things.
This is the Clan Sword.
It's called Scorch.
With this sword,
let me see how much you've grasped.
Please guide me.
Heavy.
Hasty.
Chaotic.
Is this the fruit of your practice?
I've practiced the swordsmanship
day and night.
What is
your practice for?
To break the spell,
kill Luo Hou,
and end the demonic turmoil.
But you can't do it alone.
Without our people,
everything the Array Team has done
would mean nothing.
To end the demonic turmoil,
you can't rely on yourself alone.
Why do you train
with the sword?
To protect our people.
I'll join everyone
to end the demonic turmoil.
Remember this state of mind.
Try that strike
again.
Please leave
the escort to me.
Even
with the whole clan,
we may still lose.
But we will prevail one day.
One person's flame may die,
but the flames of countless souls
can never be burned out.
The spark endures.
One day, it will ignite the world.
This
is our clan's legacy.
I will remember that.
The swordsmanship you've learned
can draw upon the ethereal energy
exceptionally.
Alas, it's just a remnant copy.
You must grasp and perfect
the moves within yourself.
Senior, could you
name the first move
I learned today?
Let's call it
Nightbane.
The darkness has lasted too long.
It's time for the light to return.
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.com)
Everyone,
the Blood Moon is coming.
Insert the sigil stones.
Activate the array!
It's Luo Hou.
The sigil stones!
No!
Who dares disturb me?
I'll kill them at once.
There's movement in the square.
Should we make our move?
Something's wrong.
The Zone hasn't weakened.
Trouble!
Everyone, stay calm.
Escort Team, hold position.
Protect our people.
Once the Zone is breached,
evacuate at once.
This...
This is...
It's Luo Hou.
The sigil stones were destroyed.
Is this the power
of the Vile VIII Phase?
The sigil stones are gone.
Let's use our flesh and blood
as the final sigil stones.
We must detonate the sigil array
at all costs!
To your positions!
Activate the array!
You old fools.
You still rebel at death's door.
You like to play, huh?
Fine, let's play.
These old geezers are mine.
The rest who want to die
are yours.
With my blood as the guide,
ignite my clan's soul.
Even if we die today,
we
will surely shake the Turbidity Lock!
Go to hell!
Senior Chiyang!
Has the mission failed?
No.
It's almost done.
You'll sacrifice yourself
to blow up the lock stake!
The clan needs you.
The clan never needed just one.
Today, we have come this far
because we trust in the clan's tomorrow.
Anyone can fall.
But the clan will march on.
Xihe,
hear my final command.
Today,
in the name of the chief,
I pass the clan sword to you.
From this day forth,
you shall carry the will of Luminara,
protect the clan in peril,
pass the torch to future generations,
and fulfill your mission
by killing Luo Hou
and liberating
the Luminara Clan.
In Luo Hou's eyes,
we fear death,
destined to bow
beneath the lock forever.
She is wrong.
At the end of humiliation,
we no longer fear death.
We vow to fight to the bitter end
with indomitable will.
I'm Fengyi Xihe.
I thus accept the sword.
This is...
The Zone is open! Go!
Run!
Keep up!
Keep up back there!
Run!
Keep up!
Move faster!
Run!
Quick, keep up!
Hurry, keep up!
We're almost out!