The Zone is broken.
The refugees have all fled.
None of them will escape.
Go find Lord Chen Yuan.
Kill them all.
Yes.
Don't even think
about harming my people.
I'll finish
her unfinished business.
The lock stake has fallen.
The spell has weakened.
I'll channel ethereal spirit
with my swordsmanship.
It'll be enough
to break the spell.
Look!
Impossible!
Kill her!
Forcibly breaking the spell
has shattered my heart meridians.
But before the last clansman leaves,
I must not stop.
All of you
must fall.
Interesting.
Xihe,
we're closer to the divine sword.
Once the spell is lifted,
using this swordsmanship again
is utterly unhindered.
But
how long
can your heart meridians last?
From here on,
just stay hidden.
Xihe, come up.
Let's
fly out together.
Darn it.
They got away.
Let me.
Report to the lord at once.
Who are you?
The girl who often contacts Xihe.
Hello.
I'm Bai Zhao,
a friend of Xihe.
Thank you for coming, Bai Zhao.
I promised to search
for the sword with you
at a spur of the moment.
I never imagined
your clan truly broke the Zone.
If it were me,
I definitely couldn't do it.
Don't be afraid.
When it comes
to piloting Flying Vessels,
no one can match your clan.
They're coming.
Follow my lead.
Trying to run?
You need my permission first.
I regret not killing you.
Yet you came seeking doom.
Oh?
You broke the spell.
What a pleasant surprise.
Not good.
The spell bound me for too long.
My body can't bear
so much ethereal energy.
You can stand against me?
A mere ant like you
has entered above the Celestial Phase.
But you were useless for years.
You'll only amuse me
by struggling longer.
Shut up.
I must stir my heart meridians
and summon the ethereal energy.
Those foolish old fools
broke the lock by self-blast.
I told you to shut up!
Faster.
Faster!
As long as the Turbidity Lock remains,
the lock stake will soon be mended.
You will
be trampled underfoot
forever.
I can't fall here.
Die!
Because
my mission is not yet done.
Kill Luo Hou.
Liberate
the Luminara Clan.
Is this all you have?
How can this be?
I won't let you leave here.
Rest easy.
Before you die,
I won't leave.
You bound us with the spell
for a century.
You've probably long forgotten
that Luminara is a fire clan.
Fire governs attack.
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.com)
This first move
is called
Nightbane.
Let me end the century of oppression
on my clan.
Xihe,
wake up.
Hold on.
From now on,
the Luminara Clan
depends on you.
Xihe.
Without the lock stake,
our bond with the divine sword returns.
Xihe,
your pets
are truly divine beasts.
You're injured?
With the spell in place,
I can't use my ethereal spirit to fight.
The demonic spirit has corrupted
the Flying Vessel.
Time is running out for us.
Please guide our way.
Where is the divine sword?
Head to the East Sea.
Xihe,
how did you convince her
to join this quest?
That was not easy.
Just like how you found me back then,
I found someone
who doesn't believe in fate.
With your remaining heart meridians,
you likely have only days left.
Are you
truly certain?
I am.
Even if there's
only one day left for me,
I will find that sword,
slay Luo Hou,
banish the Qiumina,
and take back the sky
that belongs to us.
Xihe,
what are your pets' names?
We don't have a name yet.
In that case,
you
shall be called Jadewash.
How lovely!
What about me?
You...
How about Little Chicken?
I refuse.
Just teasing.
You shall be called Lightbear.
Lightbear.
What does it mean?
You're so clueless.
You know nothing.
One person may be weak,
but gathered candle flames
will eventually light up the long night.
Senior,
I have fully grasped
the mindset you taught me.
This swordsmanship shall be called
Candlelight Swordsmanship.
Useless.
The East Sea is just over there.
We must cross this demonic spirit.
What's going on?
The Flying Vessel
can't hold much longer!
We'll have to risk it and push through!
We made it!
Bai Zhao.
Bai Zhao!
I am all right.
Xihe, get the divine sword!
Can you sense the sword?
It seems to be that way.
We will lead the way.
What's with the noise?
The Dragon and Phoenix Beasts.
Is the legend true?
These beasts can bring someone
the divine sword.