[Adapted from the Chen Dong novel "Shrouding the Heavens,"]
[PREVIOUSLY]
If I sink into depravity here...
my future path to enlightenment is doomed.
How about we cooperate?
Even if our divine senses intertwine in mutual bliss,
beneath my Dao,
All is void.
To prove the Dao here,
and be buried here...
This is...
the promised good fortune I bestow upon you.
Can even the Eight Forbidden...
not break this predicament?
If I can link these nine ancient characters,
perhaps I can shatter these shackles.
Today,
is the time to break the forbidden!
Episdoe 167
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™
Field!
Break!
Divine Forbidden Domain!
Back then,
during my battle with Yi Qingwu,
I briefly experienced the legendary Eternal Divine Forbidden.
As the ancients say,
so long as one is human,
one can never step into the Divine Forbidden Domain.
[Divine Forbidden Domain]
Only those who stand in the Eight Forbidden Domain
can have that fleeting, brilliant experience.
Capable of crossing nine small realms.
It seems the good fortune bestowed by the Sun Saint Emperor
cannot be borne without heaven-defying talent.
So,
is this "heaven-defying talent" referring to me?
The heavens aid my Golden Crow!
The Sun Ancient Scripture has appeared!
So it's actually connected
to this frail descendant of the Sun Saint Emperor's bloodline.
Saint Emperor's bloodline!
How dare you defile it!
Since you won't hand it over,
this old man will simply take it himself!
Indeed!
The Sun True Scripture is truly on him!
Whoever comes,
hand over the Ancient Scripture!
Hand over your sister!
Four years no see,
has this face of mine
become unrecognizable?
You're...
You're Ye Fan!
Uncle Jiang! Uncle Jiang!
The Sun Saint Emperor protected all beings his entire life,
yet you seek to exterminate his last drop of blood!
This is an outrage against heaven and earth!
You can only die!
Do you truly believe
you alone can stop my entire clan?
The answer to that...
That answer...
you won't live to find out.
Just...
in one move?
Ye Fan!
Your opponent is me!
Taiyin Shenzi (Son of the Moon)
You're still alive?
You wield the Sun,
I am of the Taiyin (Moon).
All things in existence have their natural counters.
The Sun True Scripture within you
will belong to me!
Taiyin Power...
With that tiny bit of Taiyin Power,
how dare you show off before an expert?
You... You...
actually studied the Taiyin Ancient Scripture too?
How can anyone cultivate both Taiyin and Sun?
A Saint's skull cannot be taken head-on.
Within this skull
lies immortal divinity,
and from its seven orifices,
the aura of a Saint gushes forth.
I need a way to isolate it.
Ah, right.
That Eternal Exile used by that bastard Wang Teng—
isn't that the solution?
This divine weapon of mine
was refined from the skull of a descendant of the Taiyin Empress.
You may now enjoy it properly!
Then watch closely,
for this move
was used by my son Wang Teng, who bore the posture of a Great Emperor!
Eternal Exile!
Suppress!
Kill!
My skull!
No!
This is mine!
Uncle Jiang!
I don't want you to die!
Uncle Jiang...
I won't get to see you grow up.
This old servant is incompetent.
Ashamed before the Saint Emperor!
Since I have received the grace of the Sun Saint Emperor,
as long as I live,
I absolutely will not let him come to harm.
Thank you...
You must...
protect him.
Uncle Jiang!
Don't go!
I have no family left.
Uncle Jiang...
Dad, Mom...
Brothers and sisters...
None of you are here anymore.
Little Squirrel...
Do you miss your family?
Tongtong...
Uncle Jiang and your family...
all wish for you to be happy.
Is crying shameful?
When you feel like crying...
you can cry.
Do you miss your family too?
I do.
Of course, I do.
It's been a very, very long time...
since I last saw them.
I understand now.
I won't cry anymore.
Please accept me as your disciple!
I want to become as amazing as you!
As amazing as me?
I'm not that amazing either.
You are the descendant of the Sun Saint Emperor.
There will surely be a sect that sincerely protects you.
Following me might just get you killed faster.
Master, above!
Please accept this bow from your disciple!
Master...
I'm a Master now?
It is actually the Sun Sacred Body!
Those with the Sun Sacred Body rarely survive past childhood.
Apart from the Sun Saint Emperor,
not a single one survived.
That this child has survived until now...
is solely due to the Divine Sun within him sustaining his life.
These nine ancient characters...
were bestowed by the Divine Will of the Sun Saint Emperor.
Perhaps...
they can be of benefit to him.
This is...
Master...
Every night when I sleep,
there are little golden figures teaching me how to cultivate.
No wonder this child cultivates with divine speed.
Within his body...
he should possess the complete Sun True Scripture.
The inheritance of the Human Race's Saint Emperor has not been severed.
Tongtong...
Master...
Now...
you have gained some small foundation.
I must continue searching for my way home.
Let's go.
Young Master...
The Purple Copper Warship was obstructed at the Ziwei Star.
Hindered by the suddenly appearing Human Saint, the Son of Tianxuan.
However, he was no match for the Thousand-Hand Great Saint.
He should have died in battle by now.
But the Sacred Body nearby triggered the phantom and aura of the Human Demon.
The clan is quite panicked.
We await the Young Master's decision.
Good that the old madman is dead.
Otherwise, he truly would have been somewhat troublesome.
As for that old demon Dongfang Taiyi...
he himself is problematic.
No need to pay him any mind.
However, this Ye Fan is truly strange.
The Sacred Body incident in the Ji Family was a variable.
I don't like it.
Understood.
We...
will cut down all things related to this variable.
Human Race...
The Divine Son is about to be born.
The Ancestor Kings are about to return.
By then, we will command the Big Dipper together.
The Heavenly Emperor's bloodline...
is on the verge of awakening.
Spanning the galaxy...
making all races...
submit beneath our feet.
Sweep across the Eight Desolations!
Blood-wash the Human Race!
Dream on!
I won't die, you bastard!
(Watch the Latest Donoghue Episodes: www.h-donghua.com)
Ye Fan...
Ziyue...
Master...
You actually have nightmares?
I dreamed of the Big Dipper...
overwhelmed by the army of the Ancient Race.
My friends struggling while bathed in blood.
I want to go back!
Master...
A powerhouse of your level...
rarely produces dreams like this.
Could it be a prophetic dream, a sign?
Master...
Perhaps...
it's just a heart filled with anxiety and alarm.
Where the heart is...
there lies the homeland.
I see you often gazing at the Big Dipper, heart uneasy.
Then that Big Dipper...
is your hometown, right?
Hometown...
Did I say something wrong?
Tongtong...
You are correct.
My hometown...
is on Earth.
There are my parents there.
The Big Dipper is my cultivation ground.
There are my friends who share life and death with me.
I must go back!
Before, I had...
Father...
Sisters...
and Uncle Jiang.
But now...
I only have you, Master.
Wherever Master is, I will be there.
Master says he wants to go back...
wherever it is...
take me with you.
Let's go meet two people first.
I never expected, Brother Ye...
that you could actually escape from the Eye of the North Sea.
Now it seems...
that place likely had other mysteries.
Congratulations, Brother Ye!
That bastard surnamed Ye...
Oh, pardon—
Brother Ye!
Benefactor Ye!
I truly yearn for the Big Dipper!
Such longing!
What?
Are you two also leaving Ziwei?
What ghostly trickery are these two perverts up to now?
The battle at the North Sea...
The Divine Maiden Furnace emerged.
For four years,
I've carried the infamy of being a "pervert,"
like a rat scurrying across the street—
everyone shouting "Hit him!"
I could endure that for myself...
But even my Senior Brother,
that beast in human clothing,
now finds fewer girls to swindle.
That's why we must leave!
I still have some admirers, you know.
It's just that...
you know...
Know what?
"A belly full of poetry makes one naturally elegant."
While you two uncles...
are destined to be perverts.
Where'd this brat come from?
Children just speak the truth.
Is this...
the bloodline left by the Sun Saint Emperor?
A fine sapling.
Let me instruct him for a few years,
and he will surely—
Shake the world with his brilliance!
What do you mean by that?
Looking like you stepped in dog shit.
What are you doing?
Sorry, Pervert Uncles...
I didn't mean to.
Face thicker than that Ye fellow's!
Back to business.
Let's talk serious matters.
Since we are crossing the star field,
do you two know...
where another Five-Colored Altar is?
I heard...
The Eight Sceneries Palace has a teleportation array.
Once activated,
it can reach other Five-Colored Altars.
However...
Yin Tiande
placed restrictions on it.
Outsiders...
cannot access it.
Exactly.
But that guy just vanished,
no news whatsoever.
But he has two attendants.
One of them...
was killed by you along with his brother.
The other handles herb procurement for alchemy.
Should be easy to find.
In that case...
this Herb-Gathering Attendant
is worth a visit.
[Ye Fan has reached the 8th Stage of the Immortal Platform Third Heaven.]
[Next Realms: Saint → Saint King → Great Sage→ Quasi-Emperor → Great Emperor]
[Ye Tong!]
[Ye Tong: The Solar Saint is known only through his bloodline descendants. Like the Solar Saint himself, he was born with a Solar Body. His body shines like a golden sun, radiating divine brilliance and surging vitality. Within Ye Tong's Immortal Platform lies the Solar Scripture, allowing him to cultivate even in his dreams. His cultivation advances at an astonishing speed, making him Ye Fan's first disciple. If the Solar Body merges with the Taiyin Body, it can give birth to the legendary supreme physique—The Innate Primordial Chaos Body.]
[Liao Tian "Slaying the Crows Arc" airs Wednesdays at 10:00 AM, exclusively streaming.]
The Golden Crow clan wants to fight you to the death!
Xiao Dao'er!
FANSUB: H-DONGHUA™